<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arms on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arms/</link><description>Recent content in arms on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 23:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia warns United States against sending more arms to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62672b54112483cc02e57c49/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 23:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62672b54112483cc02e57c49/</guid><description>Russia told the United States to stop sending more arms to Ukraine, warning that large Western deliveries of weapons were inflaming the conflict and would lead to more losses, Moscow&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to Washington said.
Highlights Russia tells U.S. to stop sending more arms to Ukraine, warning that large Western deliveries of weapons are inflaming the conflict and would lead to more losses, Moscow&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to Washington said. Russia&amp;rsquo;s Feb. 24 invasion of Ukraine has killed thousands of people, displaced millions more and raised fears of a wider confrontation between Russia and the United States.</description></item><item><title>Germany continues blocking arms exports to Ukraine due to new foreign ‘peace’ policy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e762b377d0755de7d787b7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 01:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e762b377d0755de7d787b7/</guid><description>Germany reiterated its refusal to send defensive weapons to Ukraine that according to Kyiv would help the country fend off a potential Russian invasion. This comes as part of a new German peace policy that aims at restricting arms exports and fostering peace via diplomacy.
Summary Germany reiterated its refusal to send defensive weapons to Ukraine that according to Kyiv would help the country fend off a potential Russian invasion. This comes as part of a new German peace policy that aims at restricting arms exports and fostering peace via diplomacy.</description></item><item><title>Mum has arms ripped off, dies stopping pit bull from attacking 4-year-old son</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</guid><description>Description A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says.
Summary A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says. She said, ‘I have no arms, and I’m dying,’” Ms Pingel’s sister, Shannon Pingel, told the Wausau Daily Herald.</description></item></channel></rss>