<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>missiles on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missiles/</link><description>Recent content in missiles on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 04:04:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missiles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia denies Moskva has sunk after apparent Ukrainian missile strike | Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258ee966e6ecd4e5e80e47b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 04:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258ee966e6ecd4e5e80e47b/</guid><description>US defence officials say it is unclear what caused blast which Ukraine claims to be result of missile strikes
Highlights Russia’s flagship cruiser Moskva is on fire but still afloat and moving across the Black Sea, the Pentagon confirms. The Ukrainian southern military command claims to have struck the cruiser with Neptune anti-ship missiles, causing it to start sinking and forcing the crew to abandon ship. Russia&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said it was investigating what had happened, but denied reports that it had sunk and claimed the fires had been extinguished.</description></item><item><title>China makes semi-secret delivery of missiles to Serbia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62531eadfc76d8c7af9149c4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 18:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62531eadfc76d8c7af9149c4/</guid><description>BELGRADE, Serbia (AP) — Russian ally Serbia took the delivery of a sophisticated Chinese anti-aircraft system in a veiled operation this weekend, amid Western concerns that an arms buildup in the Balkans at the time of the war in Ukraine could threaten the fragile peace in the region.
Highlights Six Chinese Air Force Y-20 transport planes landed at Belgrade’s commercial airport early Saturday, reportedly carrying HQ-22 surface-to-air missile systems for the Serbian military.</description></item></channel></rss>