<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sanctions on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sanctions/</link><description>Recent content in sanctions on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 03:16:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sanctions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oil prices fall, continuing downward trend from last week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622eb37ed3f9c222cc8cb606/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622eb37ed3f9c222cc8cb606/</guid><description>The fall came as a U.S. official said Russia was showing signs it might be willing to have substantive negotiations over Ukraine.
Highlights Oil prices fell on Sunday at the start of the session, extending last week&amp;rsquo;s decline. Prices fell last week as traders assessed potential improvements to the supply outlook that has been disrupted by the Ukraine crisis. Russia is showing signs it might be willing to have substantive negotiations over Ukraine, U.</description></item><item><title>UK announces first wave of sanctions against Belarus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</guid><description>Senior military figures targeted for role in joining and facilitating Russian invasion of Ukraine
Highlights Belarusian chief of the general staff, Maj Gen Victor Gulevich, and three other deputy defence ministers will all face sanctions, along with two military enterprises. Belarus has been used as a base for Russian soldiers to pour into Ukraine. US Treasury this week designated two large state-owned banks in Belarus, Belinvestbank and Dabrabyt, as subject to sanctions.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine conflict: Russian rouble plunges after new sanctions announced</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d1e2e928b36458f0a6c6d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 19:11:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d1e2e928b36458f0a6c6d/</guid><description>The Russian currency sinks to a record low against the dollar after Western countries impose new sanctions.
Highlights The Russian currency sinks to a record low against the dollar after Western countries impose new sanctions. &amp;ldquo;People are a lot more fearful. There is already talk about some companies having to go on reduced working hours, or even suspend production because they&amp;rsquo;re not able to access maybe key parts from the West due to sanctions or due to trade limitations, so there&amp;rsquo;s a great deal of concern on the street,&amp;rdquo; says Alex Politkovkovsky, a former Russian minister of state TV personality.</description></item><item><title>Japanese billionaire Hiroshi Mikitani donates ¥1 billion to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b16f622e5e49f65b97c69/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 06:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b16f622e5e49f65b97c69/</guid><description>The founder of Rakuten said in a letter addressed to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president that the donation will go toward &amp;quot;humanitarian activities to help people in Ukraine who are victims of the violence.&amp;quot;
Highlights Japan&amp;rsquo;s Rakuten founder will donate $8.7 million to Ukraine to help victims of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Japan has also imposed sanctions against Russia and imposed a host of other countries. The sanctions include freezing assets and banning key exports to Russia&amp;rsquo;s military.</description></item><item><title>Anti-war sentiment grows in Russia despite govt crackdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</guid><description>As Russian troops were closing in on the Ukrainian capital, more and more Russians at home were speaking out against the invasion even as the government&amp;rsquo;s official rhetoric grew increasingly harsher
Highlights At least 460 people in 34 cities were detained over anti-war protests on Saturday, including over 200 in Moscow. An online petition to stop the attack on Ukraine garnered over 780,000 signatures by Saturday evening. A prominent contemporary art museum in Moscow called Garage announced Saturday it was halting its work on exhibitions and postponing them “until the human and political tragedy that is unfolding in Ukraine has ceased&amp;quot; Dmitry Medvedev said Moscow may respond to Western sanctions by opting out of the last nuclear arms deal with the U.</description></item><item><title>S&amp;amp;P cuts Russia's rating to junk, Moody's issues junk warning</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a975947b839aaaac52f97/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 21:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a975947b839aaaac52f97/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine triggered a flurry of credit rating moves on Friday, with S&amp;amp;P lowering Russia&amp;rsquo;s rating to &amp;lsquo;junk&amp;rsquo; status, Moody&amp;rsquo;s putting it on review for a downgrade to junk, and S&amp;amp;P and Fitch swiftly cutting Ukraine on default worries.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine triggered flurry of credit rating moves on Friday. S&amp;amp;P lowered Russia&amp;rsquo;s long-term foreign currency credit rating to &amp;lsquo;BB+&amp;rsquo; from &amp;lsquo;BBB-&amp;rsquo; and warned it could lower ratings further.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine moves to impose state of emergency as U.S., allies pressure Russia with sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</guid><description>Russia had all of the necessary military capabilities Wednesday to launch a full-scale invasion into neighboring Ukraine, a senior U.S. defense official said.
Highlights At least five Ukrainian websites were hit by cyberattacks ahead of state of emergency vote. Russia evacuates its embassy in Kyiv, state news agency reports. U.S., Europe and other allies impose first salvo of sanctions on Moscow. Secretary of State Antony Blinken cancels a meeting with Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister.</description></item></channel></rss>