<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>investigators on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/investigators/</link><description>Recent content in investigators on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 09:14:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/investigators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Body of Florida woman, 93, found in freezer in her garage, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270f24bc7c64dce5d706e47/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 09:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270f24bc7c64dce5d706e47/</guid><description>Police in Florida are investigating what happened to Marie Hoskins, 93, whose body was found in a freezer in her garage.
Highlights Marie Hoskins was discovered inside the freezer in her home’s garage Thursday. A neighbor called police that day to conduct a welfare check on Hoskins, police say. A 64-year-old resident inside the home told police she hadn’t seen her mother in some time. Detectives are working with the medical examiner and the state attorney in the case, police said in a statement posted Saturday.</description></item><item><title>N.Y. Supreme Court judge whose home was raided by investigators found dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e81b08ccaa2fef14c8a82/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 06:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e81b08ccaa2fef14c8a82/</guid><description>John Michalski, an acting justice on the Erie County Supreme Court, died of an apparent suicide, according to attorney Terry Connors. Michalski was 61.
Highlights John Michalski, an acting justice on the Erie County Supreme Court, died of an apparent suicide. His property was raided by federal agents two weeks ago, his lawyer says. He had returned to his duties in January after going on medical leave in the wake of his apparent suicide attempt in February 2021.</description></item><item><title>Missing Utah college student Madelyn Allen found alive, 'covered in coal' in suspect's basement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 02:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</guid><description>Description Utah college student Madelyn &amp;ldquo;Maddie&amp;rdquo; Allen vanished last week and was found alive, covered in coal, in the basement of 39-year-old suspect Brent Brown.
Summary A Utah college student who vanished last week was found alive and covered in coal in the basement of a 39-year-old suspect&amp;rsquo;s home, according to authorities. The student, Madelyn Allen, 19, was reported missing after she was seen leaving her dorm at Snow College in Ephraim around 9:22 p.</description></item></channel></rss>