<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>employer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employer/</link><description>Recent content in employer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 15:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man told employer not to celebrate his birthday. He was awarded $450,000 after unwanted party.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d8042d8e005b421df1328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d8042d8e005b421df1328/</guid><description>A Kentucky man with an anxiety disorder asked his employer not to celebrate his birthday because it would trigger a panic attack.
Highlights Kevin Berling asked his employer not to celebrate his birthday because it would trigger a panic attack. When the company, Gravity Diagnostics, ignored his request and had a surprise lunchtime celebration for him on Aug. 7, 2019, he got upset. A jury awarded him $450,000 on March 31, a jury found that Berling suffered an &amp;ldquo;adverse employment action&amp;rdquo; because of his anxiety disability.</description></item><item><title>Human Rights Campaign strips Fox News of preferred LGBTQ employer status: 'Enough is enough'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247ea1f30c3f97d905c8f20/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 06:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247ea1f30c3f97d905c8f20/</guid><description>A version of this article first appeared in the &amp;quot;Reliable Sources&amp;quot; newsletter. You can sign up for free right here.
Highlights The largest network in the U.S. has been criticized for its anti-gay policies. The network is trying to incorporate the LGBTQ community into its films and other projects. The right-wing network has portrayed the media as a threat to the community&amp;rsquo;s right to sexualize children in the way they want to do so.</description></item></channel></rss>