<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dec on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/dec/</link><description>Recent content in dec on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/dec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope unfurls massive sunshield in major deployment milestone</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d088aef43b8174ee0f7aa8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d088aef43b8174ee0f7aa8/</guid><description>The $10 billion James Webb Space Telescope unfolded its huge sunshield on Friday (Dec. 31), pulling the five-layer structure out by sequentially deploying two booms.
Summary The sunshield of NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope is seen here fully unfurled during prelaunch testing on Earth. One of the James Webb Space Telescope&amp;rsquo;s most nail-biting deployment steps is safely in the books. Live updates: NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope missionRelated: How the James Webb Space Telescope works in picturesShine bright like a diamond 💎With the successful deployment of our right sunshield mid-boom, or “arm,” Webb’s sunshield has now taken on its diamond shape in space.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope reaches launch pad for Christmas liftoff</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c697609f40105eaecf0164/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c697609f40105eaecf0164/</guid><description>After more than two decades of development, NASA&amp;rsquo;s next-generation James Webb Space Telescope atop its Ariane 5 rocket is on the launch pad.
Summary An Ariane 5 rocket carrying the James Webb Space Telescope rolled out to the launch pad at Kourou, French Guiana, on Dec. 23, 2021. Related: How the James Webb Space Telescope works in picturesMore: NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope launch: Live updatesImage 1 of 6 An Ariane 5 rocket carrying the James Webb Space Telescope rolled out to the launch pad at Kourou, French Guiana, on Dec.</description></item></channel></rss>