<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>face on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/face/</link><description>Recent content in face on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/face/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unvaccinated People Ordered to Stay Home or Face Jail in City of 14 Million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbf5b69b3a228e67f4ade3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbf5b69b3a228e67f4ade3/</guid><description>After weeks of its lowest caseloads in the pandemic, the Philippines’ capital region is seeing a frightening rise in coronavirus infections.
Summary Under the order, unvaccinated people must stay at home except to buy essential goods or for medical purposes. Some officials criticized the council’s stay-at-home order for unvaccinated people, noting that even vaccinated people can contract and transmit the virus. “The recent exponential COVID-19 surge in Metro Manila happened even when 102 percent of the target population is already vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Intel tells unvaccinated employees they face unpaid leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</guid><description>Description Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April
Summary Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in AprilPORTLAND, Ore. &amp;ndash; Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don&amp;rsquo;t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April.</description></item></channel></rss>