<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>face on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/face/</link><description>Recent content in face on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:43:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/face/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Southern Baptists face push for public list of sex abusers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c29f47a1d2081514be8c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c29f47a1d2081514be8c1/</guid><description>A blistering report on the Southern Baptist Convention’s mishandling of sex abuse allegations is raising the prospect that the denomination, for the first time, will create a publicly accessible database of pastors and other church personnel known to be abusers.
Highlights A blistering report on the Southern Baptist Convention’s mishandling of sex abuse allegations, released on Sunday, May 23, 2022, is raising the prospect that the denomination, for the first time, will create a publicly accessible database of pastors and other church personnel known to be abusers.</description></item><item><title>Doctors who ‘mislead’ on social media could soon face regulatory action</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268baefcb6e06e303b77a80/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 03:39:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268baefcb6e06e303b77a80/</guid><description>Planned new guidelines say online posts could be scrutinised by the General Medical Council
Highlights General Medical Council is to update its Good Medical Practice guide for the first time in almost a decade. Posts made on Twitter, Instagram and TikTok could be scrutinised if a doctor is reported. Doctors must ‘be honest and trustworthy, make clear the limits of their knowledge’ and make reasonable checks to make sure any information given is not misleading’ The document will also make it a doctor’s duty to act if they become aware of workplace bullying, as well as discrimination and sexual harassment.</description></item><item><title>Carjacker beats up 72-year-old, takes car, only to die in crash, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dd486f90be4fb13dc0aba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 21:14:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dd486f90be4fb13dc0aba/</guid><description>A San Antonio great-grandmother is recovering after a brutal carjacking this week.
Highlights Shirlene Hernandez, 72, was on her way to a Shell gas station Tuesday morning to get a Diet Coke. On her way inside, a man grabbed her, hitting her several times in the face in a tussle to take her keys. Despite three men trying to tackle the attacker, he still got away with her car. Not long after, police found her car on the interstate, totaled – and with the suspected carjacker dead inside.</description></item><item><title>Retired officer says he had no choice in theater killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621900d6ecbfefebea7c7fa9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621900d6ecbfefebea7c7fa9/</guid><description>A retired police SWAT commander testified Thursday that he fatally shot a man in a movie theater eight years ago during an argument sparked by cellphone usage and escalated by a thrown popcorn bag because he feared he was about to be attacked by an “out-of-control” person who “looked like a monster.”
Highlights Curtis Reeves, 79, said he shot 43-year-old Chad Oulson on Jan. 13, 2014, because the younger, fitter man was cursing at him and about to attack him.</description></item><item><title>LA schools to require students to wear non-cloth face masks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread. Starting Monday, students must wear “well-fitted, non-cloth masks with a nose wire” at all times, including outdoors, the district announced.
Summary LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew to face civil sex assault case after US ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df5d94f5a3e4d1fa85e35d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df5d94f5a3e4d1fa85e35d/</guid><description>Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s claims against the Duke of York can continue to be heard, a US court says.
Summary While all this is going on, Ms Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s team will be pressing for the prince&amp;rsquo;s lawyers to disclose evidence. Their current demands - detailed in court papers - include information about the medical condition 20 years ago that prevented him sweating and, secondly, evidence to support his statement that he was at Pizza Express in Woking on the day Ms Giuffre says he abused her.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated People Ordered to Stay Home or Face Jail in City of 14 Million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbf5b69b3a228e67f4ade3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbf5b69b3a228e67f4ade3/</guid><description>After weeks of its lowest caseloads in the pandemic, the Philippines’ capital region is seeing a frightening rise in coronavirus infections.
Summary Under the order, unvaccinated people must stay at home except to buy essential goods or for medical purposes. Some officials criticized the council’s stay-at-home order for unvaccinated people, noting that even vaccinated people can contract and transmit the virus. “The recent exponential COVID-19 surge in Metro Manila happened even when 102 percent of the target population is already vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Intel tells unvaccinated employees they face unpaid leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</guid><description>Description Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April
Summary Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in AprilPORTLAND, Ore. &amp;ndash; Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don&amp;rsquo;t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April.</description></item></channel></rss>