<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>steal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/steal/</link><description>Recent content in steal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 19:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/steal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-deputy accused of posing as wedding guest to steal gifts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276c49631d14c24b7fecf5d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 19:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276c49631d14c24b7fecf5d/</guid><description>Authorities say a retired sheriff’s deputy posed as a guest at two Phoenix-area weddings to steal boxes of cards containing thousands of dollars, and is under investigation in a series of similar crimes
Highlights Landon Earl Rankin, 54, was arrested Wednesday in the thefts at private venues in April. Rankin was a deputy with the Pinal County Sheriff’s Office, joining the agency in 1994. Police learned of at least seven similar crimes in other Phoenix-area jurisdictions, a spokesman says.</description></item><item><title>Thieves Steal Gallery Owner’s Multimillion-Dollar NFT Collection: 'All my apes gone'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7ad676d0d55e9b2c21d31/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 03:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7ad676d0d55e9b2c21d31/</guid><description>Dealer Ross Kramer said thieves had stolen his $2.2 million NFT collection.
Summary This just sold please help me,” wrote gallery owner Todd Kramer, of New York’s Ross + Kramer Gallery, in a since-deleted tweet posted on December 30. A phishing scam had drained his Ethereum wallet of 15 NFTs valued at a total of $2.2 million, including four apes from the “Bored Ape Yacht Club” collection. With the help of the buyers and the NFT platform OpenSea, Kramer was able to get back several of his NFTs.</description></item></channel></rss>