<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>minnesota on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/minnesota/</link><description>Recent content in minnesota on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 08:19:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/minnesota/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minnesota woman accused of abandoning newborns charged with murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b716a9022554e2dc0969c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 08:19:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b716a9022554e2dc0969c/</guid><description>Jennifer Lynn Matter abandoned her two infants in 1999 and 2003.
Highlights Jennifer Lynn Matter, 50, is charged with two counts of second degree murder in connection with the death of her newborn son. Another infant, found years earlier under similar circumstances, has also been linked by police to the woman. Matter told investigators she was in a bad mental state that year saying she was &amp;ldquo;in and out of jail, drinking too much, doing a lot of stupid things,&amp;rdquo; the complaint says.</description></item><item><title>Minnesota authorities can't arrest or threaten journalists after judge approves settlement arising from George Floyd protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62042df6656512be663614e2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62042df6656512be663614e2/</guid><description>A federal judge has approved a settlement prohibiting Minnesota authorities from arresting, threatening to arrest, or using force against journalists.
Highlights A federal judge approves a settlement barring Minnesota authorities from arresting, threatening to arrest, or using force against journalists. The settlement stemmed from police tactics used against journalists during protests over the deaths of George Floyd and Daunte Wright. The American Civil Liberties Union called the action groundbreaking and said it requires state law enforcement to be held accountable to the First Amendment.</description></item></channel></rss>