<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>expected on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/expected/</link><description>Recent content in expected on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:18:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/expected/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Slovenia's populist PM loses election to environmentalist party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62681b35dfef9f4587492756/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62681b35dfef9f4587492756/</guid><description>Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist Prime Minister, Janez Janša, lost a national election on Sunday as the environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities.
Highlights Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist Prime Minister, Janez Janša, lost a national election on Sunday. The environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities. The election had been expected to be tight but the official preliminary figures showed the Freedom Movement, a newcomer in the election, leading with 34.</description></item><item><title>Slovenia's populist PM loses election to environmentalist party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266d845fc191c9b64f0130e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266d845fc191c9b64f0130e/</guid><description>Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist Prime Minister, Janez Janša, lost a national election on Sunday. The environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities. Preliminary figures showed the
Highlights Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist PM, Janez Janša, loses a national election on Sunday. The environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities. The election had been expected to be tight but preliminary figures showed the Freedom Movement, a newcomer in the election, leading with 34.</description></item><item><title>US Secretary of State Antony Blinken will visit Kyiv on Sunday - Zelensky</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626540912723ebe1cce58c71/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 12:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626540912723ebe1cce58c71/</guid><description>The US secretary of state, and the defence secretary, are expected in Ukraine later, President Zelensky says.
Highlights Two residential blocks were hit, killing at least eight people, including a three-month-old, her mother and grandmother. The Ukrainian government has said the killing of baby Kira and the seven other victims is an act of terror, designed to break people’s will to fight. The Russians claim they hit legitimate military facilities. But, there could be another rationale for the strikes, one that is as effective as it is cynical.</description></item><item><title>Consumer prices rose 8.5% in March, slightly hotter than expected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625588ec6bc4da7578a98836/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 14:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625588ec6bc4da7578a98836/</guid><description>The consumer price index for March was expected to increase 8.4% from a year ago, according to Dow Jones estimates.
Highlights Consumer price index jumped 8.5% from a year ago on an unadjusted basis. Core inflation was the hottest since August 1982. The data reflected price rises not seen in the U.S. since the stagflation days of the late 1970s and early &amp;rsquo;80s. However, core inflation appeared to be ebbing, rising 0.</description></item><item><title>A convoy of truckers protesting Covid-19 measures is expected to arrive in the DC area this weekend. Here's what we know</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222c5b17bcaa8c6dd971923/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 02:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222c5b17bcaa8c6dd971923/</guid><description>Convoy groups led by American truckers are making their way toward the nation&amp;rsquo;s capital to demand an end to all Covid-19 mandates and restrictions.
Highlights In late January, Canadian protesters spent three weeks demonstrating against Covid-19 mandates, crippling three US border crossings and downtown Ottawa. Police arrested more than 100 people when the so-called “Freedom Convoy,” turned violent after truckers blocked roads and irritated residents with honking horns. The protestors are expected to arrive in Washington, DC throughout the upcoming weekend.</description></item></channel></rss>