<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russia on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russia/</link><description>Recent content in russia on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia sees 'no grounds' for more security talks with US, NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</guid><description>Russia says it sees &amp;quot;no grounds&amp;quot; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine.
Summary Russia says it sees &amp;ldquo;no grounds&amp;rdquo; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine. “There is, to a certain extent, a dead end or a difference in approaches,” Ryabkov said, according to the Post.</description></item><item><title>US tells Putin to choose confrontation or dialogue over Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</guid><description>Secretary of state Antony Blinken says week of talks is moment of truth for Vladimir Putin
Summary Formal talks are under way between US and Russian officials in Geneva over the fate of Ukraine, amid low expectations and high tensions driven by fears that the Kremlin will order an invasion. The other path is confrontation and massive consequences for Russia if it renews its aggression on Ukraine. “We’re about to test the proposition of which path President Putin wants to take this week,” Blinken, told the ABC News programme This Week.</description></item><item><title>​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1317578f19497e1e890c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1317578f19497e1e890c9/</guid><description>​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions - EU Today
Summary ​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensionsMoscow has warned Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions between Russia and the western military alliance. Maria Zakharova, the Russian foreign ministry spokeswoman, accused the alliance of trying to pull the two countries into its orbit, the Times reports. “It is quite obvious that the ascension of Finland and Sweden to Nato would have serious military and political consequences that would require an adequate response from Russia,” she said, not specifying what response Russia might take.</description></item><item><title>Russia on Thursday declared Nadezhda Tolokonnikova, a founding member of the Pussy Riot band, and prominent satirist Viktor Shenderovich "foreign agents" as authorities press ahead with a crackdown on dissent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce48243202096fba3b89b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce48243202096fba3b89b8/</guid><description>Russia on Thursday declared Nadezhda Tolokonnikova, a founding member of the Pussy Riot band, and prominent satirist Viktor Shenderovich &amp;quot;foreign agents&amp;quot; as authorities press ahead with a crackdown o…
Summary Tolokonnikova, 32, is one of three members of Pussy Riot who were sentenced to two years in prisonMoscow (AFP) – Russia on Thursday declared Nadezhda Tolokonnikova, a founding member of the Pussy Riot band, and prominent satirist Viktor Shenderovich &amp;ldquo;foreign agents&amp;rdquo; as authorities press ahead with a crackdown on dissent.</description></item><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item></channel></rss>