<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russia on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russia/</link><description>Recent content in russia on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DOJ moves to seize 2 planes worth more than $400 million from Russian oligarch Roman Abramovich</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eec052b1b9045d31665cb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eec052b1b9045d31665cb/</guid><description>The planned seizure of jets belonging to Russian oligarch Roman Abramovich is the latest U.S. government response to the invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights The Boeing 787-8 Dreamliner and a Gulfstream G650ER are valued at more than $400 million. The Commerce Department&amp;rsquo;s Bureau of Industry is seeking penalties of up to twice the value of the aircraft. The move is the latest in a series of sanctions and economic attacks by the U.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops fought street by street with Kyiv's forces in battle for key Ukrainian city</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296301289ec1178364093fc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296301289ec1178364093fc/</guid><description>Russian troops pushed deeper into a key eastern Ukrainian city Monday, fighting street by street with Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s forces in a battle that has left Sievierodonetsk in ruins.
Highlights Russian troops advance into Sievierodonetsk, fighting street by street with Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s forces. Russian forces also shelled parts of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northeast, and struggle continues for control of southern region. EU agrees to a partial oil embargo to pressure Moscow to end the war. Six civilians, including a French journalist, killed in fighting in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second-largest city, also reported in Kharkarkarkiv.</description></item><item><title>Companies leaving Russia cost 45% of national GDP - Investment Monitor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b41c19834196bf1dd8472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b41c19834196bf1dd8472/</guid><description>Research from Yale shows that companies exiting Russia are taking with them revenues equal to almost half of Russia&amp;rsquo;s GDP.
Highlights Yale research shows that companies withdrawing from Russia are taking with them revenues equal to 45% of Russia&amp;rsquo;s GDP. Foreign direct investment (FDI) only accounted for 0.63% of the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP in 2020. Russian exports of oil and oil products are equivalent to only approximately 12% of GDP. Imports into Russia, on balance, are a net exporter, even as it is forced to sell oil and gas at highly discounted prices.</description></item><item><title>McDonald’s says it will sell its Russia business after previously pausing operations due to Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283675b4bfb41f007c69f11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 09:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283675b4bfb41f007c69f11/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said it will sell its business in Russia, a little more than two months after it paused operations in the country due to its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s has more than 800 restaurants and 62,000 employees in Russia. Franchisees operate only 15% of its Russian locations, while the company owns the rest. &amp;ldquo;If you can&amp;rsquo;t go to America, come to McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in Moscow,&amp;rdquo; was a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s ad slogan at the time in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Russia ‘using weapons smuggled by Iran from Iraq against Ukraine’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625678370494b1c1aa61cb39/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625678370494b1c1aa61cb39/</guid><description>Iraqi militias and others say undercover networks being used to supply materiel such as RPGs and anti-tank missiles
Highlights RPGs and anti-tank missiles have been dispatched to Russia from Iraq as Moscow’s campaign in Ukraine has faltered in the last month. Iranian-made Bavar 373 missile system, similar to the Russian S-300, has also been donated to Moscow by Tehran. Moscow is forced to lean on Iran, its military ally in Syria, following new sanctions triggered by the invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia threatens legal action if forced into sovereign debt default</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253c806eebc388546f07c2b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 06:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253c806eebc388546f07c2b/</guid><description>Finance Minister Anton Siluanov&amp;rsquo;s remarks to the pro-Kremlin Izvestia newspaper on Monday sharpened Moscow&amp;rsquo;s tone in its financial wrestling with the West.
Highlights Russia will take legal action if the West tries to force it to default on its sovereign debt, Finance Minister Anton Siluanov told the pro-Kremlin Izvestia newspaper. Russia faces its first sovereign external default in more than a century after it made arrangements to make an international bond repayment in roubles earlier this week, even though the payment was due in U.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin admits 'significant losses' of troops; Russia expected to shift defeated forces to east Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62507bf027eeb9ab56cf4fae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62507bf027eeb9ab56cf4fae/</guid><description>Ukrainian leaders have warned that the fighting in the Donbas is expected to be brutal and resemble the battles of World War II.
Highlights Rocket attack kills at least 50 people and injures more than 80, local authorities say. Thousands of civilians waiting at train stations in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s east to evacuate as Russian strikes intensify. Moscow denies targeting civilians despite well-documented evidence to the contrary. NATO says it would warmly welcome Finland to the alliance if it were to join the U.</description></item><item><title>Russia accuses Ukraine of attacking oil depot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249652957e00ef849a7f057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 09:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249652957e00ef849a7f057/</guid><description>Russia claims a Ukrainian helicopter raid set fuel tanks ablaze in Belgorod, a Russian city.
Highlights Russia claims a Ukrainian helicopter raid set fuel tanks ablaze in Belgorod, a Russian city. &amp;ldquo;I will neither confirm nor deny this information,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;It does not mean that Ukraine has to bear responsibility for all those catastrophes and all those events that happen on the territory of the Russian Federation. This is not the first time we have seen such accusations,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description></item><item><title>Russia bombards areas where it pledged to scale back</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62459d1489baa3486838579d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 12:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62459d1489baa3486838579d/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces bombarded areas around Kyiv and another city just hours after pledging to scale back operations in those zones to promote trust between the two sides, Ukrainian authorities said Wednesday.
Highlights Russian forces bombarded areas around Kyiv and another city just hours after pledging to scale back operations in those zones to promote trust between the two sides. Talks between Ukraine and Russia were set to resume Friday by video.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian forces retake town south of Sumy from Russia, U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62429587e4bf0e791dc3932d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 05:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62429587e4bf0e791dc3932d/</guid><description>The United States assesses that Ukrainian forces have retaken the town of Trostyanets, south of Sumy, from Russian forces, a senior U.S. defense official said on Monday.
Highlights The United States assesses that Ukrainian forces have retaken the town of Trostyanets, south of Sumy, from Russian forces. &amp;ldquo;The Ukrainians are continuing to try to take back ground,&amp;rdquo; a senior U.S. defense official says. The official, speaking on condition of anonymity, said the town was taken by Russian forces on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Russia seizes Audemars Piguet watches in apparent retaliation for Swiss sanctions | Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241981752d946f2cb236505/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241981752d946f2cb236505/</guid><description>Timepieces worth millions of dollars were taken by FSB agents in Moscow, according to a Swiss paper
Highlights Russian agents seize millions of dollars worth of Audemars Piguet watches in Moscow. Swiss paper says move was &amp;rsquo;likely an arbitrary repressive measure in response to sanctions&amp;rsquo; Swiss foreign affairs department officials said the move was ‘most likely an arbitrary measure’ Russia was the 17th-biggest export market for Swiss watches in 2021, accounting for 260m Swiss francs of shipments.</description></item><item><title>Russia reasserts right to use nuclear weapons in Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f2d8fcba1345c55860f54/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f2d8fcba1345c55860f54/</guid><description>Senior politician Dmitry Medvedev says Moscow’s nuclear doctrine does not require enemy state to use such weapons first
Highlights Russia threatens to use nuclear weapons against Ukraine, says Russian President Vladimir Putin. Russia has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest number of nuclear weapons, says Putin. Putin says Russia is prepared to use any nuclear weapons without the help of the U.S. military. Russia’s defence minister says he is ‘prepared to defend the sovereignty’ of the country and its allies in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says 400,000 citizens have been forcibly taken to Russia | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f04bd01220c9f7da9856f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 12:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f04bd01220c9f7da9856f/</guid><description>Ukraine accused Moscow on Thursday of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians from shattered Ukrainian cities to Russia, while the Kremlin has said the people relocated from Ukraine wanted to go to Russia.
Highlights Ukraine accuses Moscow of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians to Russia. The Kremlin gave nearly identical numbers for those who have been relocated, but it said they wanted to go to Russia. Some have reported shortages of food and water there.</description></item><item><title>US, G7 freeze Russian gold amid Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ee73c4f1b6a870e80572e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 10:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ee73c4f1b6a870e80572e/</guid><description>The restrictions aim to limit the country’s ability to use its international reserves and circumvent sanctions.
Highlights Restrictions aimed at limiting the country’s ability to use its international reserves. Restrictions are designed to limit Russia&amp;rsquo;s ability to circumvent punishing Western sanctions. The government of President Vladimir Putin has spent years building its reserves and currently has the fifth largest stockpile of gold in the world. Previously, sanctions against Russian elites and Putin had not affected Russia&amp;rsquo;s gold stockpile.</description></item><item><title>Spotify says it will suspend service in Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e7863fec466ed1fa751f4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 02:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e7863fec466ed1fa751f4/</guid><description>Spotify Technology SA said on Friday it will suspend its streaming service in Russia in response to the country&amp;rsquo;s new media law.
Highlights Spotify Technology SA said on Friday it will suspend its streaming service in Russia in response to the country&amp;rsquo;s new media law. The audio streaming platform closed its office in Russia indefinitely earlier this month, citing what it described as Moscow&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;unprovoked attack on Ukraine&amp;rdquo; Russia&amp;rsquo;s new legislation makes it illegal to report any event that could discredit the Russian military.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin says "nothing terrible will happen" if Russia is expelled from G20</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e3036bddc611cab4d4066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 21:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e3036bddc611cab4d4066/</guid><description>The Kremlin said on Friday that nothing terrible will happen if the United States and its allies succeed in expelling Russia from the Group of Twenty (G20) major economies because many of the G20&amp;rsquo;s members are at economic war with Moscow anyway.
Highlights Russia and its allies are at a state of war with each other, says U.S. President Vladimir Putin. Putin says some countries are taking a more sober approach towards Russia and not trying to isolate it.</description></item><item><title>‘We’re going back to a USSR’: long queues return for Russian shoppers as sanctions bite</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b1f225868462c96c110c3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 13:23:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b1f225868462c96c110c3/</guid><description>After an hour and a half queuing for sugar, or worse still fighting for it in a market, Russians are feeling the effect of shortages caused by an unprecedented cutoff from the world
Highlights Bags of sugar and buckwheat began disappearing from local markets a week after Russia launched its invasion of Ukraine. The shortages revived fears that the Kremlin’s invasion in Ukraine will lead to a virtual slide back to the shortages or endless queues of the Soviet Union.</description></item><item><title>Mariupol: Ukraine rejects Russian offer to surrender port city</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62384fe326d1d01c8c0ac3e6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 10:14:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62384fe326d1d01c8c0ac3e6/</guid><description>Russia issued an ultimatum offering to open humanitarian corridors in exchange for the surrender of the city.
Highlights Russia issued an ultimatum offering to open humanitarian corridors in exchange for surrender of the city. Russia says it will not let humanitarian convoys into the city if it does not surrender, and the city won&amp;rsquo;t let people out. Russia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;goal of the Russians is to start to [create] hunger [in the city] to enforce their position in the diplomatic process,&amp;rdquo; says Dzhokir.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s Zelenskyy appeals to Russians; officials say Mariupol art school bombed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238257e4fb46e41e479ace0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 07:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238257e4fb46e41e479ace0/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been more than three weeks since Russia launched its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights More than 90% of Ukrainians believe their country will win the war with Russia. 74% support direct talks with Russian leader Vladimir Putin. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy says 14,000 Russian soldiers have been killed since the invasion began. The United Nations says 10 million Ukrainians have fled their homes, including those who have left the country and others who remain within the border.</description></item><item><title>Russian mercenaries in Ukraine linked to far-right extremists</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62376f2abc630ac53fd2951d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62376f2abc630ac53fd2951d/</guid><description>Wagner Group connected to white supremacists, Tech against Terrorism investigation finds
Highlights The study was carried out in conjunction with the Russian Defence Ministry and the U.S. Department of Defence. The study has been carried out under the guise of the ‘denazification’ of the country’s military, the “deny military” of the nation, “theatre” and “vigorous” forces, such as the government, are “almost certainly” aimed at the ’deny” national security forces, the military, and the government.</description></item><item><title>Russian claims of bat bioweapon labs in Ukraine dismissed by US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236d3eb164a30f62ee6e9a5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 07:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236d3eb164a30f62ee6e9a5/</guid><description>Six countries with seats on the UN Security Council say Russia is spreading propaganda. They made the allegation at a meeting called at Russia&amp;rsquo;s request. Russia repeated its allegations that Ukraine has biological weapons program. The U.S. reiterated that Ukraine
Highlights Russia is using a UN Security Council meeting to spread its propaganda about its invasion of Ukraine, six Western members states say. The meeting was held at Russia&amp;rsquo;s request to discuss its allegations that Ukraine is developing biological weapons.</description></item><item><title>U.S. soldiers alive, despite Russia 'fake news' report, U.S. military says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 10:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</guid><description>Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well, the Tennessee National Guard said on Thursday.
Highlights Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well. President Joe Biden ordered the withdrawal of U.</description></item><item><title>Biden to ban Russian oil imports over Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227aa473d8ef599a6bc2ef8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 19:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227aa473d8ef599a6bc2ef8/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden announced Tuesday the U.S. will ban all Russian oil imports , toughening the toll on Russia’s economy in retaliation for its invasion of Ukraine, but he acknowledged it will bring costs to Americans, particularly at the gas pump .
Highlights President Joe Biden announces a ban on Russian oil imports, toughening the toll on Russia’s economy in retaliation for its invasion of Ukraine. Biden acknowledged it will bring costs to Americans, particularly at the gas pump.</description></item><item><title>Besieged Ukrainian city cancels evacuations, accuses Russia of breaking cease-fire</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245174e0f923e3e185f8ca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 06:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245174e0f923e3e185f8ca/</guid><description>Russia said Saturday it was declaring a temporary cease-fire in the key Ukrainian port city Mariupol, which it has besieged for days, to allow the creation of humanitarian corridors to evacuate civilians.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin says western sanctions are “the equivalent of war’s” Putin warns that any move to create a no-fly zone above Ukraine would be viewed as “participation” in the conflict. Israel&amp;rsquo;s prime minister meets with Putin in Moscow to discuss security, financial support for Ukraine and the continuation of sanctions.</description></item><item><title>Zara and Paypal suspend business in Russia over Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62239a0dc3a04433ebcea83d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 17:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62239a0dc3a04433ebcea83d/</guid><description>Inditex, which owns Zara and several other major brands, will close all of its 502 stores in Russia.
Highlights Inditex, which owns Zara and several other major brands, will close all of its 502 stores in Russia. &amp;ldquo;We believe that such actions will motivate the youth and active population of Russia to proactively stop the disgraceful military aggression,&amp;rdquo; Mr Fedorov said in a letter posted on his Twitter account on Friday.</description></item><item><title>NATO rejects Ukraine no-fly zone, says 'not part of this' war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622355028f384398240255d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 12:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622355028f384398240255d6/</guid><description>NATO on Friday rejected Ukrainian calls to help it protect its skies from Russian missiles and warplanes, wary of being dragged into Moscow&amp;rsquo;s war on its neighbour, but Europe promised more sanctions to punish Russian President Vladimir Putin.
Highlights NATO rejects Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s request to set up no-fly zone over Ukraine. G7 countries say they will hold accountable those responsible for war crimes and refuse to recognise any Russian territorial gains. NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg: &amp;ldquo;We are not part of this conflict&amp;rdquo; U.</description></item><item><title>U.S. delays ICBM test-launch in bid to de-escalate Russia nuclear tensions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62206a50b1c2aaaa37956c32/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 07:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62206a50b1c2aaaa37956c32/</guid><description>The U.S. military said on Wednesday it will postpone a scheduled test launch of a Minuteman III intercontinental ballistic missile, in a bid to lower soaring tensions after Russia announced it was putting its nuclear forces on high alert.
Highlights The U.S. military said on Wednesday it will postpone a scheduled test launch of a Minuteman III intercontinental ballistic missile. The move comes after Russia announced it was putting its nuclear forces on high alert.</description></item><item><title>$1 million bounty on Putin offered by Russian businessman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fa5e271132ab2a2f4f4d4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fa5e271132ab2a2f4f4d4/</guid><description>The Russian entrepreneur said the Russian president came to power by &amp;quot;blowing up apartment buildings in Russia.&amp;quot;
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin was offered to military officers by Russian entrepreneur Alex Konanykhin in a post he published on social media this week. &amp;ldquo;Putin is not the Russian president as he came to power as the result of a special operation of a. special operation in Russia, then violated the Constitution by.</description></item><item><title>Five people killed in Russian hit on Kyiv TV tower – video | World news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f7b32a27f2a44bc06a5d9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f7b32a27f2a44bc06a5d9/</guid><description>Five people have been killed and several wounded in a Russian attack on a TV tower in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s capital, Kyiv, according to reports
Highlights Two explosions heard in Borshchahivka and Dorohozhychi areas, reports say. Several channels were knocked off air, knocking several channels off air. The incident was first reported on social media by the Ukrainian interior ministry adviser, Anton Herashchenko, moments after Russia warned Kyiv residents to evacuate military and intelligence infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Russia calls in Canadian envoy, complains over protests outside its embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</guid><description>Russia threatened Canada on Monday with retaliation if it failed to ensure the safety of its diplomats and complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates.
Highlights Russia says it has called in Canada&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to Moscow to lodge a formal protest. Russia has complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates. Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry says it had called in the ambassador to Russia&amp;rsquo;s embassy in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>UPS and FedEx halting shipments to Russia and Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d11141a4753b50838d0ce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 18:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d11141a4753b50838d0ce/</guid><description>U.S.-based United Parcel Service Inc and FedEx Corp , two of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest logistics companies, have said they are halting delivery service to Russia and Ukraine in light of the Russian invasion of its neighbor.
Highlights U.S.-based United Parcel Service Inc and FedEx Corp halt delivery service to Russia and Ukraine. Both inbound and outbound services have been suspended to Ukraine, as well as deliveries to destinations in Russia, UPS and FedEx said in online statements.</description></item><item><title>Potent protest: Bars drop Russian vodka, promote Ukraine’s</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c75e9878706c929ffd3de/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 07:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c75e9878706c929ffd3de/</guid><description>By PAUL WISEMAN AP Business Writer Some bars and liquor stores think they&amp;rsquo;ve found a potent way to punish Russia for invading Ukraine: They&amp;rsquo;re pulling Russ
Highlights Some bars and liquor stores think they&amp;rsquo;ve found a potent way to punish Russia for invading Ukraine. Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine directed the state’s Commerce Department to cease the purchase and sale of Russian Standard, the only Russian vodka sold in Ohio (under the brand names Green Mark and Russian Standard) New Hampshire Gov.</description></item><item><title>Twitch and OnlyFans block all users from Russia due to sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b94fc3eaadef89329f81b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 15:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b94fc3eaadef89329f81b/</guid><description>The Brother HL-L2375DW “4-star” printer at €129.99 (-16%) Aliexpress is already crushing the price of the Redmi Note 11. The Philips 3000 series XD3110
Highlights The Brother HL-L2375DW “4-star” printer at €129.99 (-16%) Aliexpress is already crushing the price of the Redmi Note 11. Windows 11 on incompatible PCs, Macs in anticipation and better photos at Samsung. The Philips 3000 series XD3110/09/09 vacuum cleaner with bag with bag is €84.99 - a good deal – The Philips 3/5/9/10 vacuum cleaner is €85.</description></item><item><title>Intel and AMD suspended product deliveries to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b245ffc189aecd980ec06/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b245ffc189aecd980ec06/</guid><description>AMD and Intel have suspended deliveries of their products to Russia. This can lead to a shortage of computers, servers and other products, which will lead to higher prices. The Chinese office of Intel notified partners about introduction of a ban on the
Highlights AMD and Intel have suspended deliveries of their products to Russia. This is reported by RBC citing own sources. This can lead to a shortage of computers, servers and other products, which will lead to higher prices.</description></item><item><title>Biden says U.S. will sanction Russian financial firms, sovereign debt and individuals after Ukraine incursion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215a65fd2425c0d1f3fe962/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215a65fd2425c0d1f3fe962/</guid><description>President Joe Biden said Tuesday that Russia has begun &amp;quot;an invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine, and he announced sweeping sanctions on the Russian bank VEB.
Highlights President Joe Biden says Russia has begun &amp;ldquo;an invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine. Biden also announced sweeping sanctions on the major Russian bank VEB and its military bank, as well as on the country&amp;rsquo;s sovereign debt. Biden: &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t need blood unless you plan on starting a war&amp;rdquo; The prospect of a war involving Russia, the largest supplier of gas and oil to Europe, has rattled markets and fueled fears of higher oil prices.</description></item><item><title>US accuses financial website Zero Hedge of spreading Russian propaganda</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c488b56e1c92fe7378875/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c488b56e1c92fe7378875/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. intelligence officials on Tuesday accused a conservative financial news website with a significant American readership of amplifying Kremlin propaganda and alleged five media outlets targeting Ukrainians have taken direction from Russian spies.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Ministry announced Tuesday that some units participating in military exercises would begin returning to their bases. In a response posted online Tuesday morning, the website said it “has never worked, collaborated or cooperated with Russia, nor are there any links to spy agencies” Zero Hedge has been sharply critical of Biden and posted stories about allegations of wrongdoing by his son Hunter.</description></item><item><title>Russia told the US and West to stop supplying arms to Ukraine, saying it's threatening Russia..</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</guid><description>Russia is amassing troops on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border. The US and Ukraine warn of an imminent Russian invasion.
Summary The US and Ukraine have repeatedly warned that Russia appeared to be preparing to invade. The US has also given Ukraine military assistance, including arms and training. The US, Ukraine, and other allies have repeatedly warned that Russia appears to be preparing to invade Ukraine. And Ukraine warned that Russia was almost done gathering enough troops along its border for a possible offensive.</description></item><item><title>Erdogan Warns Russia Against Invading Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s supply of combat drones to Ukraine has drawn the wrath of Russia.
Summary Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Tuesday warned Russia against invading Ukraine, calling the former Soviet republic a &amp;ldquo;powerful&amp;rdquo; country with international friends. Speaking to Turkish reporters in Albania, Erdogan said he intended to discuss the rising tensions with Russian President Vladimir Putin. &amp;ldquo;You cannot handle these things by saying &amp;lsquo;I will invade something, I will take it&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; Turkish media quoted Erdogan as saying.</description></item><item><title>US intelligence indicates Russia preparing operation to justify invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</guid><description>The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.
Summary Washington (CNN) The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Russia sees 'no grounds' for more security talks with US, NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</guid><description>Russia says it sees &amp;quot;no grounds&amp;quot; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine.
Summary Russia says it sees &amp;ldquo;no grounds&amp;rdquo; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine. “There is, to a certain extent, a dead end or a difference in approaches,” Ryabkov said, according to the Post.</description></item><item><title>US tells Putin to choose confrontation or dialogue over Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</guid><description>Secretary of state Antony Blinken says week of talks is moment of truth for Vladimir Putin
Summary Formal talks are under way between US and Russian officials in Geneva over the fate of Ukraine, amid low expectations and high tensions driven by fears that the Kremlin will order an invasion. The other path is confrontation and massive consequences for Russia if it renews its aggression on Ukraine. “We’re about to test the proposition of which path President Putin wants to take this week,” Blinken, told the ABC News programme This Week.</description></item><item><title>​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1317578f19497e1e890c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1317578f19497e1e890c9/</guid><description>​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions - EU Today
Summary ​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensionsMoscow has warned Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions between Russia and the western military alliance. Maria Zakharova, the Russian foreign ministry spokeswoman, accused the alliance of trying to pull the two countries into its orbit, the Times reports. “It is quite obvious that the ascension of Finland and Sweden to Nato would have serious military and political consequences that would require an adequate response from Russia,” she said, not specifying what response Russia might take.</description></item><item><title>Russia on Thursday declared Nadezhda Tolokonnikova, a founding member of the Pussy Riot band, and prominent satirist Viktor Shenderovich "foreign agents" as authorities press ahead with a crackdown on dissent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce48243202096fba3b89b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce48243202096fba3b89b8/</guid><description>Russia on Thursday declared Nadezhda Tolokonnikova, a founding member of the Pussy Riot band, and prominent satirist Viktor Shenderovich &amp;quot;foreign agents&amp;quot; as authorities press ahead with a crackdown o…
Summary Tolokonnikova, 32, is one of three members of Pussy Riot who were sentenced to two years in prisonMoscow (AFP) – Russia on Thursday declared Nadezhda Tolokonnikova, a founding member of the Pussy Riot band, and prominent satirist Viktor Shenderovich &amp;ldquo;foreign agents&amp;rdquo; as authorities press ahead with a crackdown on dissent.</description></item><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item></channel></rss>