<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>defence on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/defence/</link><description>Recent content in defence on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 12:15:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/defence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Turkey has decided to give free Bayraktar TB2 to Ukraine by supporting the donation campaign initiated by Lithuania for Ukraine. With the money collected by Lithuania, ammunition will be purchased.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299fb38d493d6e475d70787/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 12:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299fb38d493d6e475d70787/</guid><description>Turkey has gifted a Bayraktar combat drone to Lithuania to be handed over to Ukraine, journalist and public figure Andri&amp;hellip;
Highlights Turkey and Baykar manufacturer have gifted a state-of-the-art Bayraktar TB2 combat drone to Lithuania. Last week, ordinary Lithuanians donated over 5 million euros in a fundraising campaign to purchase the drone for Ukraine. The drone will be ready within three weeks, and the Lithuanian Air Force will fly to pick it up and hand it over to Ukraine as soon as possible, Andrius Tapinas said.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan jets scramble as China air force enters air defence zone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295ce265a3a6982c24b4f82/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 08:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295ce265a3a6982c24b4f82/</guid><description>Taiwan on Monday reported the largest incursion since January by China&amp;rsquo;s air force in its air defence zone, with the island&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry saying Taiwanese fighters scrambled to warn away 30 aircraft in the latest uptick in tensions.
Highlights Taiwan has complained for the past two years of repeated missions by China&amp;rsquo;s air force near the democratically governed island. The latest mission included 22 fighters, as well as electronic warfare, early warning and antisubmarine aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Hiding in plain sight, a Soviet-era air defence system arrives</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d66dfe140607821d80969/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 13:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d66dfe140607821d80969/</guid><description>The US offered Slovakia US-made Patriot missiles if it would ‘donate’ its aging S-300 air-defence system to Ukraine
Highlights The US offered Slovakia US-made Patriot missiles if it would ‘donate’ its aging S-300 air-defence system to Ukraine. Slovakia also offered to &amp;lsquo;donate&amp;rsquo; its aging air defence system to the Ukraine. The U.S. also offered Slovakia Patriot missiles to Ukraine in exchange for its air defence. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Slovakia says it has given S-300 air defence system to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251943fe7a27e8d2bb113ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 14:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251943fe7a27e8d2bb113ba/</guid><description>Prime Minister Eduard Heger says donation does not mean the NATO member joined the war.
Highlights Slovakia has donated S-300 air defence system to Ukraine to help it defend against Russian attacks. The donation does not mean the country has joined the conflict, says the Prime Minister. The US has agreed to send weapons to Ukraine in response to Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. The United States has also pledged to send more weapons to the region, including the US Patriot missile system, to help with the Russian invasion of Crimea.</description></item><item><title>Over 66,200 Ukrainian men have returned from abroad to fight, says defence minister</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223626f69d933810172928a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223626f69d933810172928a/</guid><description>Ukrainian Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Saturday that 66,224 Ukrainian men had returned from abroad to join the fight against Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion.
Highlights Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Saturday that 66,224 Ukrainian men had returned from abroad to join the fight against Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion. Reznikov: &amp;ldquo;These are 12 more combat and motivated brigades! Ukrainians, we are invincible,&amp;rdquo; he said in an online post. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Minister said in a post: &amp;ldquo;Ukrainians are invincible.</description></item><item><title>Cyberattack on NATO could trigger collective defence clause - official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dff6be9fbb6a79c99423d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dff6be9fbb6a79c99423d/</guid><description>A cyberattack on a NATO member state could trigger Article 5, its collective defence clause, a NATO official said on Monday, amid concerns that chaos in cyberspace around Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine could spill over into other territories.
Highlights A cyberattack on a NATO member state could trigger Article 5, its collective defence clause. The military alliance has for years made clear that a serious cyberattack could trigger the clause, but such a scenario has so far been largely hypothetical.</description></item><item><title>U.S. and NATO say Russia is building up troops near Ukraine, not withdrawing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d769e093fc1e733d0e5ed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 22:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d769e093fc1e733d0e5ed/</guid><description>The United States and NATO said Russia was still building up troops around Ukraine on Wednesday despite Moscow&amp;rsquo;s insistence it was pulling back, questioning President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s stated desire to negotiate a solution to the crisis.
Highlights Russia says video shows tanks, infantry fighting vehicles, and self-propelled artillery units leaving Crimea. U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said key Russian units were moving towards the border, not away. Russia&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said its forces were pulling back after exercises in southern and western military districts near Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>British transport aircraft are now in their third day of delivering “thousands” of anti-tank weapons to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e85fca633a60cf9f75804c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e85fca633a60cf9f75804c/</guid><description>Summary British transport aircraft are now in their third day of delivering “thousands” of anti-tank weapons to Ukraine in the face of a massive build-up of Russian troops. Minister James Heappey told Times Radio that the Ministry of Defence has given “thousands” of anti-armour weapons to Ukraine. We have taken the decision to supply Ukraine with light, anti-armour, defensive weapon systems. This is a screenshot of flight tracking software showing two British C-17s in flight at various part of their journeys to and from Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell trial: Defence calls for retrial after juror says he was a 'victim of sexual abuse'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7124f479a9bd8b64eff43/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7124f479a9bd8b64eff43/</guid><description>The socialite&amp;rsquo;s lawyers say the juror &amp;quot;told reporters that he disclosed to the other members of the jury during deliberations that he was a victim of sexual abuse and further described his memory of those events&amp;quot;.
Summary Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s defence has called for a retrial after one of the jurors who convicted her told media outlets he was a victim of sexual abuse. &amp;ldquo;According to the juror, his disclosure influenced the deliberations and convinced other members of the jury to convict Ms Maxwell.</description></item></channel></rss>