<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>obama on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/obama/</link><description>Recent content in obama on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 07:10:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/obama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>School assignment shows Obama next to primates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889026cb459cedada18ccd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 07:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889026cb459cedada18ccd/</guid><description>The Oakland County, Michigan, school&amp;rsquo;s director of diversity described her reaction and response to the assignment that included the former president&amp;rsquo;s photo.
Highlights The Roeper School in Michigan is on leave after the assignment included the former president&amp;rsquo;s photo. The assignment asked, “Which of the following are primates?” Many parents and students were offended by the assignment. The school did not hold classes Thursday; police were stationed outside due to threats made online.</description></item><item><title>Former pres. Barack Obama tests positive for coronavirus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e6c3ce07306e9d29c3bba/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e6c3ce07306e9d29c3bba/</guid><description>Former US president Barack Obama tested positive for the novel coronavirus on Sunday. &amp;quot;I just tested positiv
Highlights Former US president Barack Obama tested positive for the novel coronavirus on Sunday. &amp;ldquo;I’ve had a scratchy throat for a couple days, but am feeling fine otherwise,&amp;rdquo; tweeted Obama. &amp;ldquo;It’s a reminder to get vaccinated if you haven’t already, even as cases go down,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;Michelle and I are grateful to be vaccinated and boosted, and she has tested negative,&amp;rdquo; said Obama.</description></item></channel></rss>