<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>11 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/11/</link><description>Recent content in 11 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:09:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>World Health Organization confirms 80 cases of monkeypox with outbreaks in 11 countries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ba4920f9d673880d6257/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:09:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ba4920f9d673880d6257/</guid><description>The WHO said the recent monkeypox outbreaks are unusual because they are occurring in countries where the virus is not endemic.
Highlights About 80 cases of monkeypox have been reported in 11 countries, the WHO says. The U.S. has confirmed at least one case, and Canada has confirmed two. Monkeypox is a disease caused by a virus in the same family as smallpox but is not as severe. The disease is usually found in Central and West African rainforests where animals that carry the virus live.</description></item><item><title>FDA authorizes Pfizer Covid booster dose for kids ages 5 to 11 years old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284ab81bdb402c784425edc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284ab81bdb402c784425edc/</guid><description>The FDA determined that a third shot can help boost protection for children in this age group and the benefits outweigh the risks.
Highlights Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Covid vaccine for children ages 5 to 11 at least five months after their two-dose primary series. CDC has final say on whether health-care providers should start administering the boosters. The FDA determined that a third shot can help boost protection for children in this age group and the benefits outweigh the risks, the FDA says.</description></item><item><title>7.3-magnitude earthquake strikes near Japan coast, triggering tsunami advisory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623245071d91ba8ef84a4d31/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 20:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623245071d91ba8ef84a4d31/</guid><description>A massive 7.3-magnitude earthquake struck near Namie, Japan, triggering a one-meter-high tsunami advisory in the region 11 years after it was devastated by a deadly quake.
Highlights The earthquake near Namie, Japan, was reported just before 11 a.m. ET on Wednesday. The Japan Meteorological Agency said the quake struck about 36 miles below the sea. Two aftershocks in Japan left seven people injured including six from falling objects. The northern Japan region was devastated by a deadly 9.</description></item></channel></rss>