<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>siderio on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/siderio/</link><description>Recent content in siderio on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 06:17:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/siderio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-officer charged with murder in shooting of 12-year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270c8d4671d67dea435713a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 06:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270c8d4671d67dea435713a/</guid><description>A fired Philadelphia police officer has been charged with murder in the shooting of a fleeing 12-year-old boy
Highlights Thomas &amp;ldquo;T.J.&amp;rdquo; Siderio, 12, was shot in the back of the neck after he fired at an unmarked police car, prosecutors say. A grand jury presentment unsealed Monday shows video contradicts the officer&amp;rsquo;s version of events. The boy&amp;rsquo;s great-grandmother: &amp;ldquo;I’m so heartbroken, none of us can’t sleep’s horrible” The officer is also charged with voluntary manslaughter and other charges.</description></item><item><title>Philadelphia police commissioner moves to fire officer who shot and killed 12-year-old who was allegedly armed | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62286211cfe29f252587a08e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62286211cfe29f252587a08e/</guid><description>The Philadelphia Police Commissioner announced Tuesday she plans to fire the officer who shot and killed 12-year-old Thomas Siderio because the shooting violates the department&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;use of force directive.&amp;quot;
Highlights Philadelphia Police Commissioner Danielle M. Outlaw said the officer will be suspended for 30 days and fired. She did not go into details about what action the officer took that violated the department policy. The officer who is being terminated is one of four officers riding in an unmarked police car when the rear window was struck by a bullet, police said.</description></item></channel></rss>