<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>massachusetts on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/massachusetts/</link><description>Recent content in massachusetts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 18:11:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/massachusetts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Massachusetts agrees to settlement for thousands of people who were wrongfully convicted of drug charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a4e9cc568ef8e30441cda/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 18:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a4e9cc568ef8e30441cda/</guid><description>The Commonwealth of Massachusetts has agreed to a settlement that would pay back fees associated with legal cases, probation and fines for tens of thousands of people who were wrongfully convicted of drug charges, according to court documents.
Highlights $14 million is estimated to go to about 31,000 people whose criminal convictions were vacated. The settlement still needs to be approved by a judge. The amounts are meant to refund fees incurred, including: victim-witness fees, probation fees, GPS monitoring, court costs, fines, drug analysis criminal assessment fees, parole fees, and driver license reinstatement fees.</description></item><item><title>Massachusetts state trooper fired over Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID vaccine mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 09:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</guid><description>Summary A Massachusetts state trooper was fired this week for not complying with Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate, which required more than 40,000 Executive Department employees to be fully immunized by mid-October. The development comes a week after MassLive reported the state had fired at least 60 Department of Correction workers for noncompliance. A volunteer at the Edith Nourse Rogers Memorial Veterans Hospital and the Special Olympics, the fired trooper “was never disciplined in any way shape or form” by the Massachusetts State Police prior to Baker’s vaccine mandate, SPAM said.</description></item></channel></rss>