<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>royal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/royal/</link><description>Recent content in royal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/royal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passengers scream as world’s longest cruise ship crashes into Jamaican pier</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295bf58be8e95faa111cf69/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295bf58be8e95faa111cf69/</guid><description>Investigation launched into alleged accident
Highlights The Harmony of the Seas crashed into a pier in Falmouth, Jamaica, on Thursday morning. The 227,000 tonne vessel was trying to dock at the busy port on the country&amp;rsquo;s northern shore. Video of the crash has attracted more than 500,000 views on social media. No injuries were reported - although the vessel sustained &amp;lsquo;cosmetic&amp;rsquo; damage. Port Authority of Jamaica has launched an investigation into the incident.</description></item><item><title>Queen hands over to Charles for State Opening of Parliament</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a73f843c824684d7cf732/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 14:18:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a73f843c824684d7cf732/</guid><description>It will be the first time she has missed the event since 1963, with Prince Charles delivering her speech.
Highlights It will be the first time she has missed the event since 1963. Prince Charles will deliver her speech at the end of the day. There are four counsellors of state - the other two are Prince Andrew, who has stepped down from royal duties, and Prince Harry, who is also no longer carrying out royal duties and lives in the U.</description></item></channel></rss>