<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>primary on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/primary/</link><description>Recent content in primary on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 04:27:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/primary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trump-backed Rep. Madison Cawthorn concedes North Carolina Republican primary race</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284758e7935840dc16e5104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 04:27:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284758e7935840dc16e5104/</guid><description>Controversial Republican Rep. Madison Cawthorn was endorsed by former President Donald Trump.
Highlights Rep. Madison Cawthorn called State Sen. Chuck Edwards to concede the race, a spokesman says. NBC News has yet to project a winner in the Republican congressional district of the district. CNN projects Ted Budd will win the Republican Senate primary in the race to fill the seat of retiring GOP Sen. Richard Burr, NBC projects. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Texas flagged 27,000 mail ballots for rejection in primary</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622acd31dab74943f519844d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 04:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622acd31dab74943f519844d/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — More than 27,000 mail ballots in Texas were flagged for rejection in the first test of new voting restrictions enacted across the U.S., jeopardizing votes cast by Democrats and Republicans alike and in counties big and small, according to an analysis by The Associated Press.
Highlights More than 27,000 mail ballots in Texas were flagged for rejection in first test of new voting restrictions. Rejection rate among mail voters in Texas primary was roughly 17% across 120 counties.</description></item></channel></rss>