<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mobile on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/mobile/</link><description>Recent content in mobile on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 02:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Crisis response teams achieve 70% reduction in people taken into custody under Mental Health Act</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ca6fc8533fdca598f86bba/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ca6fc8533fdca598f86bba/</guid><description>A program pairing a police officer with a mental health worker in Hamilton has reduced the apprehension rate under the Mental Health Act from 75 per cent of calls police respond to for people in crisis to 17 per cent.
Summary The program pairs a police officer with a mental health worker to answer 911 calls involving people in mental health crises. In the eight years since the program launched in Hamilton, there has been a marked reduction in taking people in mental health crisis into custody.</description></item><item><title>Covid: Travel misery for tens of thousands with at least 7,000 flights cancelled</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c8adc0d82aeae22ae227f5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c8adc0d82aeae22ae227f5/</guid><description>Chinese and US airlines are hardest hit amid a surge in Covid cases in many countries.
Summary If you are reading this page and can&amp;rsquo;t see the form you will need to visit the mobile version of the BBC website to submit your question or comment or you can email us at HaveYourSay@bbc.co.uk. Please include your name, age and location with any submission. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>