<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>inside on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inside/</link><description>Recent content in inside on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 20:15:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inside/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DC Police Find 5 Fetuses in Home of Anti-Abortion Activist Lauren Handy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62460ba3855af7e2b2408676/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 20:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62460ba3855af7e2b2408676/</guid><description>Police in Washington, D.C. discovered five fetuses inside the Capitol Hill home of anti-abortion activist Lauren Handy.
Highlights Police in Washington, D.C., discovered five fetuses inside the Capitol Hill home where anti-abortion activist Lauren Handy lives. The medical examiner&amp;rsquo;s office collected the fetuses, and police are investigating, the department told News4. Handy, and Jonathan Darnel, 40, of Virginia; Jay Smith, 32, and John Hinshaw, 67, and William Goodman, 52, of New York; Joan Bell, 73, of.</description></item><item><title>New York's Museum of Modern Art evacuated after two people were stabbed inside, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e34cf13be44e4888bd493/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 18:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e34cf13be44e4888bd493/</guid><description>Patrons at New York City&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art were evacuated Saturday afternoon after two employees were stabbed inside the iconic establishment by a man who was involved in two incidents of disorderly conduct at the museum in recent days, police said.
Highlights Patrons at New York City&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art were evacuated Saturday afternoon. Two employees were stabbed in the back, collar bone and back of the neck. The NYPD is still searching for the suspect, who was identified in a news release early Sunday as 60-year-old Gary Cabana.</description></item><item><title>Missing disabled woman found after 9 days inside a towed vehicle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216f7ac1c93362a36f6c196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 03:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216f7ac1c93362a36f6c196/</guid><description>Mother abandoned vehicle which was then towed to Burien with adult daughter inside
Highlights Mother abandoned vehicle which was then towed to Burien with adult daughter inside. Woman, 45, had not been seen since Feb. 5 when her mother parked her vehicle at a gas station and walked off, police say. Police contacted the tow company, who then located the woman inside the vehicle. She had been inside the car for nine days alone during near freezing temperatures.</description></item></channel></rss>