<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>saudi on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/saudi/</link><description>Recent content in saudi on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 05:17:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/saudi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disney is refusing to cut LGBTQ scene in Doctor Strange 2, Saudi Arabia says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267803f84481d7044faa168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 05:17:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267803f84481d7044faa168/</guid><description>Official denies Marvel film is banned but says kingdom ‘still trying’ to get Disney to cut 12 seconds referring to lesbian character with two mothers
Highlights Official denies film has been banned but says kingdom&amp;rsquo;still trying&amp;rsquo; to get Disney to cut &amp;lsquo;LGBTQ references&amp;rsquo; The cuts amount to &amp;lsquo;barely 12 seconds&amp;rsquo; in which a lesbian character, America Chavez, refers to her ‘two moms’ Saudi Arabia’s general supervisor of cinema classification said the film will not be banned.</description></item><item><title>Saudi-led coalition air strikes pummel Yemen despite Huthi truce</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62418a841128b89b3bb2b8f9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 10:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62418a841128b89b3bb2b8f9/</guid><description>The Saudi-led coalition launched air strikes Sunday on Yemen hours after Huthi rebels announced a three-day truce, with the UN chief condemning a surge in violence as the war enters its eighth year.
Highlights The Saudi-led coalition launched air strikes Sunday on Yemen hours after Huthi rebels announced a three-day truce. The raids targeted Sanaa, the rebel-held capital, according to Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Al Ekhbariya TV. The attacks began shortly after the Iran-backed Huthis announced a truce and offered peace talks on condition that the Saudis stop their air strikes and blockade of Yemen and remove &amp;ldquo;foreign forces&amp;rdquo; UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres condemns the sudden rise in hostilities.</description></item><item><title>CNN Exclusive: US intel and satellite images show Saudi Arabia is now building its own ballistic missiles with help of China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4f18423cdd004762cb169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4f18423cdd004762cb169/</guid><description>US intelligence agencies have assessed that Saudi Arabia is now actively manufacturing its own ballistic missiles with the help of China, CNN has learned, a development that could have significant ripple effects across the Middle East and complicate the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s efforts to restrain the nuclear ambitions of Iran, the Saudis&amp;rsquo; top regional rival.
Summary Iran and Saudi Arabia are bitter enemies and it is unlikely Tehran will agree to stop making ballistic missiles if Saudi Arabia has begun manufacturing its own.</description></item></channel></rss>