<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>family on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/family/</link><description>Recent content in family on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 17:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boston Hospital refuses heart transplant for man after he refuses to be vaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f02cc4f855ea5e54011307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f02cc4f855ea5e54011307/</guid><description>Brigham and Women&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Boston says its policy won&amp;rsquo;t allow DJ Ferguson to have the surgery since not being vaccinated seriously hurts its chances for success and his long-term outlook.
Summary A Boston hospital says it won&amp;rsquo;t consider performing a heart transplant on a patient who refuses to get vaccinated against COVID-19, CBS Boston reports. DJ Ferguson, 31, is fighting for his life at Brigham and Women&amp;rsquo;s Hospital and in desperate need of a heart transplant.</description></item><item><title>Teen suspect accused of shooting 16-year-old 22 times free on bond, court records say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</guid><description>The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records.
Summary HOUSTON – The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records. Frank Deleon Jr., 17, was taken into custody Monday and charged with murder for the Jan.</description></item><item><title>13-Year-Old Student Dies of Fentanyl-Related Overdose at Hartford School: PD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</guid><description>A 13-year-old student at The Sport and Medical Sciences Academy in Hartford who was in grave condition because of an overdose has now died, according to police&amp;hellip;.
Summary The Hartford Public Schools superintendent has released a statement. &amp;ldquo;I extend my heart and offer my deepest condolences to the student’s family, friends, and loved ones for their loss. I ask that everyone keep the family, friends, and the entire school community at SMSA in their thoughts and prayers,&amp;rdquo; she said in part.</description></item><item><title>Man Kidnapped as a Child in China Reunited with Family After Drawing a Map of Home Village from Memory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d38e258cb2b3cd11043d0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d38e258cb2b3cd11043d0d/</guid><description>Li Jingwei&amp;rsquo;s image was matched by police to a small village 1,000 miles away from where he had been taken, and a woman whose son had disappeared, leading to an emotional reunion after more than 30 years.
Summary Li Jingwei, from the Chinese province of Yunnan, said online that he had endured &amp;ldquo;countless nights of yearning&amp;rdquo; and been &amp;ldquo;homesick since I was little&amp;rdquo;. The link was made despite Mr Li remembering neither the name of his birthplace nor his road.</description></item></channel></rss>