<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>family on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/family/</link><description>Recent content in family on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 17:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rising US traffic deaths put focus on one Philadelphia road</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62964ebaec01a9c912db65d7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 17:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62964ebaec01a9c912db65d7/</guid><description>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Just one more step and the stroller would have been on the curb. The thought haunts Latanya Byrd years after a driver racing down Roosevelt Boulevard in Philadelphia struck and killed her 27-year-old niece, Samara Banks, and three of Banks’ young sons as they crossed the 12-lane road.
Highlights Roosevelt Boulevard is an almost 14-mile maze of chaotic traffic patterns that passes through some of the city&amp;rsquo;s most diverse neighborhoods and Census tracts with the highest poverty rates.</description></item><item><title>GoFundMe effort in honor of Uvalde couple raises more than $2.6 million in four days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294c821b0c124704150254f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 13:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294c821b0c124704150254f/</guid><description>A GoFundMe campaign started in honor of Irma Garcia, one of the two teachers killed in the Texas school shooting, and her husband, Joe, who died Thursday, has
Highlights A GoFundMe campaign started in honor of Irma Garcia, one of the two teachers killed in the Texas school shooting, and her husband, Joe, who died Thursday, has raised more than $2.6 million in just four days. Irma Garcia was a fourth grade teacher who had been teaching at Robb Elementary in Uvalde for 23 years.</description></item><item><title>US brothers freed after 25 years in prison for murder they did not commit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b70c86b5152a731ff761b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 19:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b70c86b5152a731ff761b/</guid><description>Judge issues apology to George and Melvin DeJesus, wrongfully convicted of 1995 murder of Margaret Midkiff in Michigan
Highlights George and Melvin DeJesus were convicted in the 1995 killing of Margaret Midkiff. A judge set aside their convictions early Tuesday. The brothers later embraced family members – and met some for the first time – at a restaurant in Lansing. Brandon Gohagen was convicted of second-degree murder and first-degree criminal sexual conduct in the case in 1997.</description></item><item><title>Some Russians are breaking through Putin’s digital iron curtain — leading to fights with friends and family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62369bde183a44924df36dbd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62369bde183a44924df36dbd/</guid><description>Putin&amp;rsquo;s digital iron curtain has fallen heavily on Russia, but many tech-savvy citizens can access outside news and social media easily. It&amp;rsquo;s leading to conflict over what&amp;rsquo;s true and what&amp;rsquo;s not between friends and family.
Highlights Some Russians are trying to pierce Russian President Vladimir Putin’s propaganda bubble, at times leaving them at odds with their own families, friends and co-workers. The war in Ukraine is only deepening the divide between young, tech-savvy people and an older generation who gets their news mostly from TV.</description></item><item><title>Bullied Black teen was falsely accused of threatening school, wrongly detained for 11 days, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210fa919075c79148f5fa3a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 14:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210fa919075c79148f5fa3a/</guid><description>A Black Florida teenager who says she was bullied for months by classmates was falsely accused of threatening her school and then wrongly detained at a
Highlights A Black Florida teen says she was falsely accused of threatening her school and wrongly detained at a juvenile detention facility for 11 days. The teen&amp;rsquo;s mother, Lezlie-Ann Davis, is suing Renaissance Charter School at Pines over the November incident. The lawsuit alleges that the girl was being bullied at the school in Pembroke Pines, about 20 miles north of Miami.</description></item><item><title>Nearly 58 years later, police solve cold case murder of 9-year-old Pennsylvania girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091fdfd884808f1c852be3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 15:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091fdfd884808f1c852be3/</guid><description>Marise Chiverella was murdered and left in a hole in Hazleton, Pennsylvania, in 1964. Thanks to DNA and genealogy tracking, authorities announced Thursday, they have solved her case.
Highlights Marise Chiverella was murdered and her body left in a hole in Hazleton, Pennsylvania, in 1964. State police worked tirelessly over the years but were unable to identify her killer until now. James Paul Forte, who died in 1980, was identified as the suspect in her murder.</description></item><item><title>Boston Hospital refuses heart transplant for man after he refuses to be vaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f02cc4f855ea5e54011307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f02cc4f855ea5e54011307/</guid><description>Brigham and Women&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Boston says its policy won&amp;rsquo;t allow DJ Ferguson to have the surgery since not being vaccinated seriously hurts its chances for success and his long-term outlook.
Summary A Boston hospital says it won&amp;rsquo;t consider performing a heart transplant on a patient who refuses to get vaccinated against COVID-19, CBS Boston reports. DJ Ferguson, 31, is fighting for his life at Brigham and Women&amp;rsquo;s Hospital and in desperate need of a heart transplant.</description></item><item><title>Teen suspect accused of shooting 16-year-old 22 times free on bond, court records say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</guid><description>The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records.
Summary HOUSTON – The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records. Frank Deleon Jr., 17, was taken into custody Monday and charged with murder for the Jan.</description></item><item><title>13-Year-Old Student Dies of Fentanyl-Related Overdose at Hartford School: PD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</guid><description>A 13-year-old student at The Sport and Medical Sciences Academy in Hartford who was in grave condition because of an overdose has now died, according to police&amp;hellip;.
Summary The Hartford Public Schools superintendent has released a statement. &amp;ldquo;I extend my heart and offer my deepest condolences to the student’s family, friends, and loved ones for their loss. I ask that everyone keep the family, friends, and the entire school community at SMSA in their thoughts and prayers,&amp;rdquo; she said in part.</description></item><item><title>Man Kidnapped as a Child in China Reunited with Family After Drawing a Map of Home Village from Memory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d38e258cb2b3cd11043d0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d38e258cb2b3cd11043d0d/</guid><description>Li Jingwei&amp;rsquo;s image was matched by police to a small village 1,000 miles away from where he had been taken, and a woman whose son had disappeared, leading to an emotional reunion after more than 30 years.
Summary Li Jingwei, from the Chinese province of Yunnan, said online that he had endured &amp;ldquo;countless nights of yearning&amp;rdquo; and been &amp;ldquo;homesick since I was little&amp;rdquo;. The link was made despite Mr Li remembering neither the name of his birthplace nor his road.</description></item></channel></rss>