<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>convoy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/convoy/</link><description>Recent content in convoy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 02:07:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/convoy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A convoy of truckers protesting Covid-19 measures is expected to arrive in the DC area this weekend. Here's what we know</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222c5b17bcaa8c6dd971923/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 02:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222c5b17bcaa8c6dd971923/</guid><description>Convoy groups led by American truckers are making their way toward the nation&amp;rsquo;s capital to demand an end to all Covid-19 mandates and restrictions.
Highlights In late January, Canadian protesters spent three weeks demonstrating against Covid-19 mandates, crippling three US border crossings and downtown Ottawa. Police arrested more than 100 people when the so-called “Freedom Convoy,” turned violent after truckers blocked roads and irritated residents with honking horns. The protestors are expected to arrive in Washington, DC throughout the upcoming weekend.</description></item><item><title>Trucker convoy protest in Washington DC flops as no-one shows up</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f9862dd030b92f5dad1ce/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 16:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f9862dd030b92f5dad1ce/</guid><description>Organisers had expected thousands of people to attend Freedom Convoy event
Highlights National Parks Service had given permission for the demonstration at the Sylvan Theater. Organisers expected several thousand people to rally against Covid-19 mandates. Organiser Kyle Sefcik is an MMA fighter and independent candidate for governor in Maryland. Several trucker convoys are still on their way to DC to oppose Covid mandates. Meanwhile, a security fence has been put in place around the US Capitol grounds as Joe Biden gives his first State of the Union address on Tuesday evening, with Joe Biden giving his first S.</description></item><item><title>Russia's 40-mile convoy has stalled on its way to Kyiv, a U.S. official says : NPR</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ee111d2f020d9d3bb14da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ee111d2f020d9d3bb14da/</guid><description>The convoy is apparently being hampered by fuel and food shortages, the official says. The news comes as Russia continues to concentrate attacks on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s largest cities: Kyiv and Kharkiv.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s 40-mile convoy has stalled on its way to Kyiv, a U.S. official says. The convoy is apparently being hampered by fuel and food shortages. Some elements within the military column are &amp;ldquo;literally out of gas&amp;rdquo; and having difficulty feeding their troops.</description></item><item><title>Pa. truck convoy protest fizzles out to a few vehicles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217a09e1c6b020c83a94d50/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217a09e1c6b020c83a94d50/</guid><description>The Pennsylvania truck protest convoy largely fizzled out on Wednesday in spite of its organizer promising a spectacular run along the highways to Washington, D.C. Organizer Bob Bolus had hoped to replicate what was seen out of the Canadian
Highlights The convoy organized by Scranton-area trucker organizer fizzled out early Wednesday morning. It was the first in a series of planned trucker protests modeled after recent Canadian border protests. The Pentagon has approved deployment of 700 unarmed National Guard troops to prepare for the protests.</description></item><item><title>Pentagon approves requests for National Guard as trucker convoy eyes D.C.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621686b063bf86a7320aeb06/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621686b063bf86a7320aeb06/</guid><description>The trucker convoy is expected to arrive in the D.C. area as soon as Wednesday.
Highlights National Guard will help during truck convoy protests headed to D.C. area. Truck drivers protesting vaccine requirements are expected to arrive late Wednesday or Thursday. About 700 National Guard personnel will be deployed to help control traffic at designated traffic posts and points leading to the Capitol. Trucker convoy is expected to depart Pennsylvania on Wednesday morning and drive to the area, arriving late Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Group of protesting truckers begin trip to DC area this week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621454d17ce5f7bf69e6e87a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621454d17ce5f7bf69e6e87a/</guid><description>Inspired by the trucker convoy in Canada, a group from California says they will now head to Washington D.C. to protest COVID-19 restrictions.
Highlights Inspired by the trucker convoy in Canada, a group from California says they will now head to Washington D.C. to protest COVID-19 restrictions. Convoy will start Wednesday at Adelanto Stadium in Southern California. Convoys will make about 10 stops on the way to the Beltway area, including in Arizona, Ohio and Hagerstown, Maryland.</description></item><item><title>Freedom Convoy leader Pat King arrested live on social media.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210a6e8a8acd94012b9718d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 08:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210a6e8a8acd94012b9718d/</guid><description>“I am being arrested. We will talk to you guys soon.”
Highlights Pat King, one of the most vocal members of the “Freedom Convoy’s movement, went on social media Friday to livestream his arrest. King was approached in his vehicle by a police officer who said: “You are under arrest, sir.” “I am being arrested by this officer right now,” he told viewers to his live Facebook feed. ‘I have the right to a lawyer?</description></item><item><title>Convoy protest organizer Chris Barber arrested in Ottawa</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f46e3a65c9ad45a03e1fd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 07:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f46e3a65c9ad45a03e1fd/</guid><description>Tamara Lich and Chris Barber, key organizers of the so-called Freedom Convoy that has occupied Ottawa streets for three weeks, have been arrested in Ottawa, CBC News has learned.
Highlights Two key organizers of the so-called Freedom Convoy have been arrested in Ottawa. The two remain in police custody and are expected to be charged criminally, according to sources. They are two of the three protest organizers named in a proposed class-action lawsuit filed with the Ontario Superior Court of Justice.</description></item><item><title>Police fire tear gas as anti-Covid restrictions ‘Freedom Convoy’ enters Paris</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208d973ec5ce6a5c0210702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208d973ec5ce6a5c0210702/</guid><description>Police fired tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs-Élysées avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a &amp;quot;Freedom Convoy&amp;quot; protesting against Covid-19 restrictions made it into the French capital.
Highlights Police fire tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs-Élysées avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a &amp;ldquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rdquo; protesting against Covid-19 restrictions made it into the French capital. Police have mobilised thousands of officers, set up checkpoints and deployed armoured personnel carriers and water cannon trucks in preparation for the protests.</description></item><item><title>Trucker convoy: Ottawa ‘under siege’ amid ‘nation-wide insurrection,’ officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffe51e5b54cf0e447e764a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 15:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffe51e5b54cf0e447e764a/</guid><description>Tensions are high as thousands of additional convoy supporters are expected to arrive this weekend, leading to a potentially ‘volatile’ mix says Ottawa’s former police chief.
Highlights More than 100 people gathered outside City Hall on Saturday afternoon to demand convoy supporters go home. Police Chief Peter Sloly said that the legal rules in place for police conduct “were never intended to deal with a city under siege,” he said. The trucker convoy has dug in over the past nine days amid what the chair of the police services board called a “nation-wide insurrection” Sloly, himself, and the Ontario premier have called an “occupation.</description></item></channel></rss>