<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>families on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/families/</link><description>Recent content in families on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 05:17:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/families/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandy Hook families drop 3 Alex Jones companies from lawsuit and ask judge to return their case to trial court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270bae4eac07e9fb6d032f2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 05:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270bae4eac07e9fb6d032f2/</guid><description>An FBI agent and eight Sandy Hook families that won a defamation lawsuit against Alex&amp;hellip;
Highlights The families of two boys slain in the Sandy Hook massacre have dropped three defamation cases against Alex Jones. The families hope the cases will be returned to state court in Connecticut. Jones&amp;rsquo; Free Speech Systems did not file for bankruptcy, but his cases have been removed from state courts while a federal bankruptcy judge in Texas weighs the three cases.</description></item><item><title>Over Sandy Hook families’ objections, federal judge gives Alex Jones time to defend bankruptcy plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d523564eac54187309fcf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 15:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d523564eac54187309fcf/</guid><description>A federal judge gave Sandy Hook families awaiting defamation damages trials in&amp;hellip;
Highlights A federal judge agreed to hear motions to dismiss Alex Jones’ bankruptcies as “bad faith’s” filings. The judge also gave Jones attorneys enough breathing room to prepare an unhurried defense of their plan to pay the Sandy Hook families defamation damages Jones owes without putting Infowars out of business. Jones has suffered financially since he called the worst crime in Connecticut history “staged” and “manufactured” “a giant hoax,” his representatives said in court.</description></item><item><title>‘They don’t believe it’s real’: how war has split Ukrainian-Russian families</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234b08b5aa9ec49b5dff267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234b08b5aa9ec49b5dff267/</guid><description>Ukrainians describe anger and frustration as they try to communicate invasion’s reality to relatives across the border
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s war in Ukraine is testing myriad familial cross-border ties that have endured for decades. While people in Ukraine can see with their own eyes what is happening to their country, people in Russia do so only through the house of mirrors that is state television. Russian television is pervasive and persuasive that even some people in eastern Ukraine who watch it were taken in by its version of events.</description></item><item><title>This Texas mom says she's moving her family to California to protect her transgender daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bcc9d691bb37a9156666c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 19:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bcc9d691bb37a9156666c/</guid><description>A Texas mom is doing whatever it takes to keep her transgender child safe &amp;ndash; even if that requires picking up their lives, leaving family and friends behind and moving hundreds of miles west.
Highlights Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton declared that gender-affirming surgical procedures in children and prescribing drugs that affect puberty are to be considered &amp;ldquo;child abuse&amp;rdquo; Five Texas District Attorneys issued a joint statement on Thursday calling the directives from the governor and attorney general cruel, life-threatening and un-American.</description></item></channel></rss>