<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bill on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bill/</link><description>Recent content in bill on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 02:16:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Woman Shocked After Being Charged $40 "For Crying" During Doctor's Visit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62884b487bd9a49f5329298a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62884b487bd9a49f5329298a/</guid><description>A US woman recently shared that her sister was charged $40 (early Rs 3,100) &amp;quot;for crying&amp;quot; at a doctor&amp;rsquo;s appointment. The photo of the medical bill has gone viral with more than 486,000 likes and thousands of comments.
Highlights Camille Johnson shared a picture of her sister&amp;rsquo;s medical bill on Twitter. She highlighted a segment of the bill that docked her sibling for a “brief emotional/behavioural assessment” The photo has gone viral with more than 486,000 likes and thousands of comments.</description></item><item><title>Ban on protests in front of homes signed by Gov. DeSantis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282f3f312e8507aa5dab823/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 01:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282f3f312e8507aa5dab823/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Anyone who protests in front of a private residence in Florida can face jail time and fines under a bill Republican Gov. Ron DeSantis signed Monday. The legislation makes it a second-degree misdemeanor to protest in a manner that is aimed at intentionally harassing or disturbing someone in their home.
Highlights Ban on protests in front of homes signed by Gov. DeSantis. Florida governor said the new law will prevent protests in Florida like those waged by abortion rights protesters.</description></item><item><title>Bill Gates says he has COVID, experiencing mild symptoms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b99edd8c8ddc2eb74d233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 11:12:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b99edd8c8ddc2eb74d233/</guid><description>Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates says he has tested positive for COVID-19 and is experiencing mild symptoms
Highlights Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates says he has tested positive for COVID-19 and is experiencing mild symptoms. Gates has been a vocal proponent for pandemic mitigation measures, specifically access to vaccines and medication. Gates Foundation in October said it will spend $120 million to boost access to generic versions of drugmaker Merck’s antiviral pill for lower-income countries.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis signs bill creating new Florida election police force</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267444b833797860a701fbe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267444b833797860a701fbe/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the latest controversial law signed by the Florida Republican in recent days.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signs a new election police force. Florida is one of the first states in the country with a unit focused on election fraud. The new law marks the second major overhaul of Florida&amp;rsquo;s election laws since the 2020 election. It&amp;rsquo;s the latest controversial law signed by the Florida GOP governor in recent days, including two bills that target Disney and legislation that imposes restrictions on how schools and businesses can talk about race and gender.</description></item><item><title>Disney heir comes out publicly as transgender, condemns anti-LGBTQ bills</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256390f88773962a92c94bf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256390f88773962a92c94bf/</guid><description>Charlee Corra, a member of the Disney family, came out publicly as transgender and condemned anti-LGBTQ bills in a recent interview.
Highlights Charlee Corra, a member of the Disney family, came out publicly as transgender and condemned anti-LGBTQ bills in a recent interview. They announced that their family would match up to $250,000 in donations to the Human Rights Campaign, the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest LGBTQ advocacy group, during the organization&amp;rsquo;s annual gala in Los Angeles last month.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky governor vetoes bill incorporating 'anti-critical race theory,' calling it a step backward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250386506c7ee4c76d2b351/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 13:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250386506c7ee4c76d2b351/</guid><description>Democratic Gov. Andy Beshear has vetoed a bill that contains elements of an &amp;quot;anti-critical race theory&amp;quot; bill that he says &amp;quot;tries to police classroom discussions on topics such as race.&amp;quot;
Highlights Democratic Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear has vetoed a bill that contains elements of an &amp;ldquo;anti-critical race theory&amp;rdquo; bill. SB1 states in part that public schools shall provide instructions that align with certain concepts including: &amp;ldquo;An individual, by virtue of the individual&amp;rsquo;s race or sex, does not bear responsibility for actions committed by other members of the same race&amp;rdquo; The bill received final passage from the state Senate last month, according to the Kentucky General Assembly page on SB 1.</description></item><item><title>‘Don’t Say Gay’ bill signed by Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624217413a25172f5258a9ff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624217413a25172f5258a9ff/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed a bill on Monday that forbids instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade, a policy that has drawn intense national scrutiny from critics who argue it marginalizes LGBTQ people.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signs a bill that forbids instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade. Critics say the bill marginalizes LGBTQ people, marginalizes them.</description></item><item><title>Washington state plans to ban most non-electric vehicles by 2030</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240b6a5c0e8628efc2f035e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 19:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240b6a5c0e8628efc2f035e/</guid><description>Washington state plans to ban most non-electric vehicles by 2030, according to a newly signed bill by Gov. Jay Inslee.
Highlights Washington state plans to ban most non-electric vehicles by 2030. Gov. Jay Inslee signed a bill that covers a lot of transportation issues in the state. The bill is part of a larger $16.9 billion transportation package called “Move Ahead Washington&amp;quot; The bill includes funding for four new hybrid-electric ferries, thousands of electric vehicle charging stations, 25 transit electrification projects across the state, as well as free fares for riders 18 and younger on public transportation systems, Inslee wrote on Friday in a Medium post.</description></item><item><title>Ohio Gov. DeWine signs bill into law allowing people to carry concealed weapons without a permit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62302f1771a53a63925f7dcf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 06:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62302f1771a53a63925f7dcf/</guid><description>Ohio Governor Dewine signed Senate Bill 215 that allows eligible Ohioans 21 or older to carry a concealed weapon without a permit Monday.
Highlights Ohio Gov. DeWine signs bill into law allowing people to carry concealed weapons without a permit. Ohio House members voted 57-35 in favor of the bill on March 2. The bill would also reduce penalties if a gun owner does not properly notify law enforcement they have a firearm in their possession; it will go into effect in 90-days.</description></item><item><title>Florida lawmakers approve bill to restrict rooftop solar incentives</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62290a60047c33a7f9ded5b3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62290a60047c33a7f9ded5b3/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. &amp;ndash; Major changes could be coming to rooftop solar energy in the state of Florida. House Bill 741 was passed by both the Florida House and Senate this past week, and will now be sent to Governor DeSantis to sign. Caption: WEAR. The legislation would effect a process called net metering. Net metering is the process in which additional energy goes into what is called a grid and homeowners are then given dollar for dollar credit by power companies, such as Florida Power &amp;amp; Light.</description></item><item><title>Congress passes bill to shore up Postal Service, delivery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62281b7810efd61309c59e84/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62281b7810efd61309c59e84/</guid><description>The long-fought postal overhaul has been years in the making and comes amid widespread complaints about mail service slowdowns. Many Americans became dependent on the Postal Service during the COVID-19 crisis, but officials have repeatedly warned that without congressional action it would run out of cash by 2024.
Highlights The long-fought postal overhaul has been years in the making and comes amid widespread complaints about mail service slowdowns. The bill would end a requirement that the Postal Service finance workers’ health care benefits ahead of time for the next 75 years.</description></item><item><title>New Mexico's governor just signed a bill to make college tuition-free</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227b900ba42a6509c3b5bf5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 20:19:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227b900ba42a6509c3b5bf5/</guid><description>For most New Mexico residents, college will now be officially tuition-free after Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham signed Senate Bill 140. Many states across the country have moved to provide some sort of tuition-free college education.
Highlights Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham signed on Friday Senate Bill 140, otherwise known as the New Mexico Opportunity Scholarship Act. The plan will waive tuition for students attending any in-state public school or tribal college, including community colleges.</description></item><item><title>South Dakota governor signs 2022’s first trans athlete ban into law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc99629cc95d31550cff2a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 03:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc99629cc95d31550cff2a/</guid><description>South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem signed a bill Thursday that bans transgender girls and women from playing on female sports teams.
Highlights South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem signed a bill that bans transgender girls and women from playing on female sports teams. The state is the first this year — and the 10th nationwide — to enact such a bill into law. The bill applies to all state-accredited schools, generally includes both public and private schools.</description></item></channel></rss>