<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>legal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/legal/</link><description>Recent content in legal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:32:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/legal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandy Hook families defamed by Alex Jones want him to pay their legal fees fighting his ‘sham’ bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1f640b048304815a9edad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1f640b048304815a9edad/</guid><description>Families of victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting say they want to be reimbursed for fighting Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; &amp;quot;sham&amp;quot; bankruptcy.
Highlights Sandy Hook families won three defamation cases against Alex Jones in Connecticut, Texas. They say Jones&amp;rsquo; bankruptcy filing was a &amp;ldquo;calculated stunt&amp;rdquo; to avoid jury trials. The families want state judges to make Jones pay their legal costs for the 45 days they had to fight his &amp;ldquo;sham&amp;rdquo; filing in federal court.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court takes up clash between religion and LGBT rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217139e487cdb5d686aa9e0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217139e487cdb5d686aa9e0/</guid><description>The top court agreed to hear an evangelical Christian web designer&amp;rsquo;s free speech claim that she cannot be forced under a Colorado anti-discrimination law to produce websites for same-sex marriages.
Highlights The U.S. Supreme Court takes up a major new legal fight pitting religious beliefs against LGBT rights. Christian web designer Lorie Smith says she cannot be forced under a Colorado anti-discrimination law to produce websites for same-sex marriages. Colorado law bars anyone from refusing &amp;ldquo;goods, services, facilities, privileges, advantages or accommodations&amp;rdquo; based on sexual orientation, age, race, gender and religion.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi fire chief dies hours after legal win allowing use of Ivermectin to treat COVID</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62053a81c1761200de2c8037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62053a81c1761200de2c8037/</guid><description>Wayne Doyle died Tuesday afternoon at North Mississippi Medical Center in Tupelo.
Highlights Wayne Doyle died Tuesday afternoon at North Mississippi Medical Center in Tupelo. He was given Ivermectin, which is not approved to treat the virus. Doyle died after he was moved out of the hospital to receive the drug. The drug has been at the center of attention during the pandemic of the virus in the U.S. Some used it for treatment, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not approved by the federal government and some use it to treat parasites in humans and animals.</description></item><item><title>Saudi princess released from jail: Princess Basmah Bint Saud has been a vocal critic of the kingdom's treatment of women. She was arrested three years ago when she was about to travel overseas for medical treatment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db06d02db723e1b9749fea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db06d02db723e1b9749fea/</guid><description>Princess Basmah Bint Saud has been a vocal critic of the kingdom&amp;rsquo;s treatment of women. She was arrested three years ago when she was about to travel overseas for medical treatment.
Summary Saudi authorities have released a princess and her daughter who had been detained without charge for nearly three years, her legal adviser said on Saturday. Princess Basmah Bint Saud bin Abdulaziz al Saud, 57, is a businesswoman, rights activist and member of the Saudi royal family.</description></item></channel></rss>