<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>left on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/left/</link><description>Recent content in left on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 17:12:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/left/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde teacher who officials mistakenly said left door open is traumatized and heartbroken, attorney says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a40e402048bbc42543666/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a40e402048bbc42543666/</guid><description>A Robb Elementary teacher has been traumatized and heartbroken since officials incorrectly said she left a door open prior to the shooting, her lawyer tells ABC News.
Highlights Lawyer Don Flanary: &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s heartbroken&amp;rdquo; after Texas officials incorrectly said she left a door open prior to the shooting. Officials have determined that she did close the door, but it failed to lock. Flanary says she saw the gunman crash a gray Ford pickup truck and head her way, toward the school, armed with a gun.</description></item><item><title>Two critically endangered Amur leopard cubs were born at the Saint Louis Zoo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ede15efe6ef750cc53ed/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 03:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ede15efe6ef750cc53ed/</guid><description>The Saint Louis Zoo has welcomed two adorable &amp;ndash; and incredibly rare &amp;ndash; bundles of joy: Anya and Irina, critically endangered Amur leopard cubs.
Highlights The female cubs were born on April 21 to lucky parents Dot and Samson. Amur leopards are thought to be the world&amp;rsquo;s rarest big cat, with around 120 left in the wild in Russia and China. The Saint Louis Zoo announced the exciting birth on May 19 via Twitter.</description></item><item><title>There are only 10 of the world's smallest marine mammal left in the world</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627907e2c58c99ef614806fb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627907e2c58c99ef614806fb/</guid><description>The world&amp;rsquo;s smallest marine mammal is so critically endangered that there are only about 10 left in its sole habitat of Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Gulf of California. But that may not yet spell doom for the vaquita porpoise, according to new research.
Highlights The world&amp;rsquo;s smallest marine mammal is so critically endangered that there are only about 10 remaining in its habitat in Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Gulf of California. The vaquitas have been pushed to the brink of going extinct due to illegal gillnetting, which is used to capture shrimp and totoaba fish that share the same habitat as the porpoises.</description></item><item><title>Teacher left classroom in stretcher after 5-year-old student’s attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62230d6259dee7105c8b07fc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 07:13:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62230d6259dee7105c8b07fc/</guid><description>A teacher was hospitalized after a 5-year-old Pines Lakes Elementary student attacked her.
Highlights A Broward County teacher was hospitalized on Wednesday after a 5-year-old student attacked her, police said. The student used fists and feet to hit his teacher shortly after 10 a.m., on Wednesday in the “Cool Down’s room. She was feeling “faint,” “weak, and dazed” before she started coughing and dry heaving. Firefighters used a stretcher to take the teacher out of the classroom and took her to Memorial Regional Hospital in Hollywood.</description></item><item><title>China places outright ban on tattoos, issuing fresh calls for footballers to have existing ink removed completely</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce3a0d6dfed9f3d0689d9e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce3a0d6dfed9f3d0689d9e/</guid><description>China’s General Administration of Sport have placed an outright ban on tattoos, and instructed national team players who have been inked to have them removed.
Summary The ban will affect a number of Chinese players, including Guangzhou FC defender Zhang Linpeng (left). READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>