<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>production on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/production/</link><description>Recent content in production on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/production/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alec Baldwin TV Show Canceled Amid 'Rust' Scandal, Loss of Mother</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62931c288e9d1ee098540f9c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62931c288e9d1ee098540f9c/</guid><description>Alec Baldwin is still working on coming to grips with the tragedies his life, especially following the tragic shooting on the set of Rust. That incident injured director Joel Souza and killed cinematographer Halyna Hutchins, with the moment Baldwin discovered the horrible truth captured on police [&amp;hellip;]
Highlights Alec Baldwin&amp;rsquo;s version of Match Game was canceled by ABC last month. The actor is still reeling from the tragedy of the shooting on the set of Rust.</description></item><item><title>FDA comes to agreement with baby formula factory to resume production</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62838336f45acb4232acb38b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62838336f45acb4232acb38b/</guid><description>Abbott Nutrition said it would still take months to get the product back on store shelves.
Highlights Abbott Nutrition agrees to fix safety issues at a Michigan factory that has been shuttered for more than three months. The agreement represents a first step toward resolving a problem that has sent parents scrambling from store to store to find sustenance for their infants. The company has previously said that once the FDA has signed off on the fixes, it will take six to eight weeks to get the product back on shelves.</description></item><item><title>Nestlé remains silent on child deaths from contaminated pizzas in France</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eaa4e06616a1d9c21603e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eaa4e06616a1d9c21603e/</guid><description>The food giant is citing the ongoing preliminary investigation into its Buitoni pizzas to avoid making any statement.
Highlights An 8-year-old boy died in Paris after suffering from severe hemolytic uremic syndrome (HUS) A newborn baby died eight hours after birth. The children ate Buitoni&amp;rsquo;s Fraîch&amp;rsquo;Up pizzas produced in the same Nestlé factory in Caudry (northern France) Analyses have revealed that the pizzas were contaminated by Escherichia coli (E. coli) bacteria.</description></item><item><title>Thailand Becomes First Country in Asia to Decriminalize Marijuana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f27c96bd7d2a935b235346/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f27c96bd7d2a935b235346/</guid><description>Thailand on Tuesday became the first country in Asia to approve the de facto decriminalization of marijuana, though authorities have left a grey area around its recreational use.
Highlights (BANGKOK) — Thailand on Tuesday became the first country in Asia to approve the de facto decriminalization of marijuana, though authorities have left a grey area around its recreational use. A tangle of related laws means that production and possession of marijuana remains regulated for the time being, leaving the legal status of recreational marijuana use in a grey area.</description></item></channel></rss>