<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>appoints on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/appoints/</link><description>Recent content in appoints on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 17:14:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/appoints/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More than 4.5 million have fled war in Ukraine: UN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253106dea533b02023fdc6c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 17:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253106dea533b02023fdc6c/</guid><description>Russia turns to Alexander Dvornikov, who has a record of brutality against civilians in Syria, say US officials.
Highlights The death toll from Friday’s railway station bombing in Kramatorsk has risen to 52. Russia denies responsibility, saying missiles responsible for the attack were used by the attack only. Russia turns to Alexander Dvornikov, who has a record of brutality against civilians in Syria, officials in Kyiv said. The U.N. has updated the number of refugees fleeing Ukraine since the war started, bringing the total to some 4.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has appointed Major General Eduard Moskaliov commander of the Joint Forces Operation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231c5cf7d6059bf0d6476c6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 11:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231c5cf7d6059bf0d6476c6/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has appointed Major General Eduard Moskaliov commander of the Joint Forces Operation. — Ukrinform.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin has announced the beginning of the invasion of Ukraine. Russia has been accused of war crimes in Ukraine. The International Criminal Court has begun documenting and investigating Russia&amp;rsquo;s war crimes. The United States, the European Union and other countries have imposed sanctions on Russia as an aggressor state whose international isolation is growing every day.</description></item></channel></rss>