<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>iowa on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/iowa/</link><description>Recent content in iowa on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:15:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/iowa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US egg factory roasts alive 5.3 million chickens in avian flu cull – then fires almost every worker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c00f96f49038aee8d76f8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c00f96f49038aee8d76f8/</guid><description>Laborers worked for a month disposing of birds killed in a gruesomely inhumane manner. Then they found they too were disposable
Highlights The largest culling at any factory farm in the country has been repeated at chicken and turkey farms across Iowa and 28 other states from Maine to Utah. About 250 people were summarily thrown out of work with just a few dozen skeleton staff remaining. The killing over, about 250 people spent nearly a month pulling the dead poultry from the cages and dumping them in carts before they were piled high in nearby fields and buried in huge pits.</description></item><item><title>Police: Iowa teens used baseball bat to kill Spanish teacher</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b63f0385cabfafc801101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 18:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b63f0385cabfafc801101/</guid><description>Police say two southeast Iowa teenagers used a baseball bat last fall to kill their high school Spanish teacher, and one of them then described in social media posts how they followed the woman, carried out the attack and hid her body
Highlights Jeremy Goodale and Willard Miller, both 16, are charged with murder in the death of Fairfield High School Spanish teacher Nohema Graber, 66. Her body was found Nov.</description></item><item><title>Worker discovers wooly mammoth tooth at Iowa construction site</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237295b360a09ff9f80d28a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 13:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237295b360a09ff9f80d28a/</guid><description>Justin Blauwet noticed something unusual while working at a construction site in Iowa. At first glance, it appeared to be a block of stone, just under a foot long, covered in ridges.
Highlights The tooth was found on March 4 on a construction site in Iowa. It is believed to be a pre-historic tooth that dates back to thousands of years. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a &amp;rsquo;nerd&amp;rsquo; like that,&amp;rdquo; says Justin Blauwet, who recognized the tooth.</description></item></channel></rss>