<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>slowdown on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/slowdown/</link><description>Recent content in slowdown on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 22:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/slowdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OnlyFans says it's not seeing a Netflix-like slowdown in subscribers despite rising inflation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fcc673a92a953020b1a10/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 22:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fcc673a92a953020b1a10/</guid><description>OnlyFans executives say the platform is not experiencing a slowdown in subscriber numbers despite climbing prices.
Highlights OnlyFans is not experiencing a slowdown in subscribers despite rising prices, executives say. In April, Netflix said subscriber numbers dropped by 200,000 in the first quarter. Inflation also poses a key risk to the business, as people are having to balance budgets to deal with rising costs. OnlyFans has a &amp;ldquo;completely different business model&amp;rdquo; to Netflix, said Lee Taylor, the firm&amp;rsquo;s chief financial officer.</description></item><item><title>Home prices jumped nearly 20% in February</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268d3e6df9012faa2d861fa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 05:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268d3e6df9012faa2d861fa/</guid><description>Home prices continued to surge higher in February, but rising mortgage rates may make that kind of growth unsustainable in the months ahead.
Highlights Home prices increased 19.8% in February year over year, according to S&amp;amp;P CoreLogic Case-Shiller index. Sun Belt cities continued to see the highest gains, with Phoenix, Tampa, Florida, and Miami seeing highest gains. Minneapolis, New York and Washington, D.C., saw the smallest price gains, although they were still in the double digits.</description></item></channel></rss>