<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>strikes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/strikes/</link><description>Recent content in strikes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 15:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/strikes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>At least 1 dead, 44 injured after tornado strikes northern Michigan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628900b8b595cce4d3262109/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 15:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628900b8b595cce4d3262109/</guid><description>One person died and multiple people were injured after a destructive tornado tore through northern Michigan Friday afternoon, authorities said.
Highlights A Munson Healthcare spokesman confirmed that there had been one death and 44 injuries. Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer signed a declaration of emergency for Otsego County on Friday night. The injured are being treated at four separate hospitals. Residents in Gaylord are asked to shelter in place through 8 a.</description></item><item><title>CIA Director: US “sees no practical evidence” that Russia is planning nuclear strikes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627744c8e19655f5e9112b8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 04:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627744c8e19655f5e9112b8b/</guid><description>The CIA director said the United States does not see Russia preparing for a nuclear strike
Highlights CIA director William Burns said the U.S. does not see Russia preparing for a nuclear strike. The preparations for such a strike are monitored from satellites, Burns said. Burns said Putin is in such a mindset that he cannot allow himself to be defeated. The second phase of the Russian invasion of Ukraine may be &amp;ldquo;even riskier&amp;rdquo; than the first phase, Burns noted.</description></item><item><title>Judge strikes down 4 Arkansas voting laws as unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62355908597240a054c4b714/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 04:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62355908597240a054c4b714/</guid><description>Four Arkansas voting laws passed last year were struck down Friday after a Pulaski County circuit judge ruled that all four violated the Arkansas Constitution by placing undue burdens on voters.
Highlights Four laws passed by the General Assembly last year affecting voters in Arkansas were struck down Friday. Pulaski County Circuit Judge Wendell Griffen ruled that all four of the laws violated the Arkansas Constitution by placing undue burdens on voters.</description></item></channel></rss>