<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>organization on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/organization/</link><description>Recent content in organization on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:09:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>World Health Organization confirms 80 cases of monkeypox with outbreaks in 11 countries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ba4920f9d673880d6257/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:09:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ba4920f9d673880d6257/</guid><description>The WHO said the recent monkeypox outbreaks are unusual because they are occurring in countries where the virus is not endemic.
Highlights About 80 cases of monkeypox have been reported in 11 countries, the WHO says. The U.S. has confirmed at least one case, and Canada has confirmed two. Monkeypox is a disease caused by a virus in the same family as smallpox but is not as severe. The disease is usually found in Central and West African rainforests where animals that carry the virus live.</description></item><item><title>San Diego Bank Lends Trump $100 Million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b12ad33d8419f68285bf8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b12ad33d8419f68285bf8/</guid><description>A bank&amp;rsquo;s decision to loan Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s company $100 million is the latest evidence the former president might survive fraud investigations and a&amp;hellip;
Highlights San Diego-based Axos Bank finalized the loan with the Trump Organization on Feb. The loan is being used to pay back an old loan backed by commercial space at Trump Tower that was coming due in September. A year ago, it looked possible that Trump might become a pariah after his supporters stormed the U.</description></item><item><title>'Significant evidence' of alleged fraud in Trump business investigation, NY AG says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e851b6b3c49085a16e134f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e851b6b3c49085a16e134f/</guid><description>Summary New York Attorney General Letitia James said that her office has uncovered &amp;ldquo;significant evidence&amp;rdquo; of fraud in her civil investigation of former President Donald Trump and the Trump Organization. The unusual statement amid an ongoing investigation came as James&amp;rsquo; office argued in court papers that Donald J. Trump, Donald Trump, Jr., and Ivanka Trump have not sufficiently responded to subpoenas issued as part of the investigation. &amp;ldquo;Thus far in our investigation, we have uncovered significant evidence that suggests Donald J.</description></item></channel></rss>