<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>local on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/local/</link><description>Recent content in local on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/local/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Local officials call on Idaho sheriff to resign after he allegedly made disparaging comments about Native Americans</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</guid><description>Members of a southeastern Idaho youth church group were being driven around by their chaperone last month,delivering Thanksgiving cards in the neighborhood to those they were thankful for when they decided last-minute to stop at the home of the county sheriff&amp;rsquo;s house, according to a probable cause affidavit later in court.
Summary What happened next outside the home of Bingham County Sheriff Craig Rowland has put the small Idaho community in the national spotlight.</description></item><item><title>Cleveland-area hospitals battling latest Covid-19 surge put ad in local paper that reads: 'Help'</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 15:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</guid><description>&amp;quot;Help&amp;quot; said the ad Sunday in the Cleveland Plain-Dealer, a response to the latest Covid-19 health crisis exploding in Northern Ohio, nearly two years into a pandemic that has killed more than 810,000 Americans and battered many of the nation&amp;rsquo;s hospitals.
Summary (CNN) &amp;ldquo;Help.&amp;rdquo; That word, in big black letters and surrounded by white space, called out from Ohio&amp;rsquo;s largest newspaper &amp;ndash; a desperate plea from six Cleveland-area medical systems facing a crush of Covid-19 cases.</description></item></channel></rss>