<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>local on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/local/</link><description>Recent content in local on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:57:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/local/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Austin becomes the first Texas city to experiment with “guaranteed income”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275c3d604227f85a71da940/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:57:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275c3d604227f85a71da940/</guid><description>Austin joins at least 28 U.S. cities, like Los Angeles, Chicago and Pittsburgh, that have tried out some form of “guaranteed income” — financial assistance targeted at needy households.
Highlights The Austin City Council voted Thursday to establish a pilot program to give low-income families $1,000 per month for a year. The city will send checks to 85 families at risk of losing their homes. The program will be a yearlong, $1 million pilot program that clears a key vote Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Pro-Russian protesters in Germany outnumbered by Ukraine supporters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62532bb32c167a11cb067d87/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 19:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62532bb32c167a11cb067d87/</guid><description>Pro-Russians on Sunday staged demonstrations in the German cities of of Frankfurt and Hanover, where they were far outnumbered by supporters of Ukraine, local police said.
Highlights Pro-Russians staged demonstrations in German cities of of Frankfurt and Hanover, where they were far outnumbered by supporters of Ukraine. Around 3,500 Ukraine supporters gathered in Hanover in the city centre, police said. Around 235,000 Russian citizens live in Germany, according to government statistics from late 2020.</description></item><item><title>Indoor masking no longer necessary for most of the U.S, CDC says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 16:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</guid><description>Indoor mask mandates are not necessary to be safe now across most of the United States, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Friday.
Highlights Most Americans are safe going without a mask in indoor settings, including in schools, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says. The new guidance puts more than half of the nation&amp;rsquo;s counties at low or medium risk for Covid, meaning masks are no longer necessary.</description></item><item><title>Police break up 50-person New Year's Eve sex orgy in Spain for breaking Covid rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1b0160f0cb3cd7a9e8a77/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1b0160f0cb3cd7a9e8a77/</guid><description>Officers (stock image) discovered more than 50 people had breached local Covid restrictions by turning up at the property in LIica d&amp;rsquo;Amunt near Barcelona for the sex party.
Summary Officers discovered more than 50 people had breached local Covid restrictions by turning up at the property in LIica d&amp;rsquo;Amunt near Barcelona for the sex party. Spanish daily El Mundo said a local raised the alarm after two people tried to enter his house wrongly thinking it was the orgy venue.</description></item><item><title>Local officials call on Idaho sheriff to resign after he allegedly made disparaging comments about Native Americans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</guid><description>Members of a southeastern Idaho youth church group were being driven around by their chaperone last month,delivering Thanksgiving cards in the neighborhood to those they were thankful for when they decided last-minute to stop at the home of the county sheriff&amp;rsquo;s house, according to a probable cause affidavit later in court.
Summary What happened next outside the home of Bingham County Sheriff Craig Rowland has put the small Idaho community in the national spotlight.</description></item><item><title>Cleveland-area hospitals battling latest Covid-19 surge put ad in local paper that reads: 'Help'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 15:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</guid><description>&amp;quot;Help&amp;quot; said the ad Sunday in the Cleveland Plain-Dealer, a response to the latest Covid-19 health crisis exploding in Northern Ohio, nearly two years into a pandemic that has killed more than 810,000 Americans and battered many of the nation&amp;rsquo;s hospitals.
Summary (CNN) &amp;ldquo;Help.&amp;rdquo; That word, in big black letters and surrounded by white space, called out from Ohio&amp;rsquo;s largest newspaper &amp;ndash; a desperate plea from six Cleveland-area medical systems facing a crush of Covid-19 cases.</description></item></channel></rss>