<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>spokesperson on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spokesperson/</link><description>Recent content in spokesperson on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:57:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spokesperson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Aggressive Fox’ Reported Near US Capitol, bites congressman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ce54073720655e10e1ba6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ce54073720655e10e1ba6/</guid><description>U.S. Capitol Police have received “several reports of aggressive fox encounters on or near the grounds of the U.S. Capitol,” the department said Tuesday.
Highlights A fox bit a member of Congress and a woman near the U.S. Capitol. Authorities captured one of the animals and warned the public about &amp;ldquo;aggressive fox encounters&amp;rdquo; Rep. Ami Bera (D-Calif.) described the moment the fox &amp;ldquo;nipped&amp;rdquo; his leg on Monday to NBC News. Animal control officers captured one fox — a little guy seen peering up from inside a cage — at 3:35 p.</description></item><item><title>Justice Clarence Thomas hospitalized with 'flu-like symptoms'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237ef5ea0c2fa89cc91603c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 03:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237ef5ea0c2fa89cc91603c/</guid><description>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was admitted to Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, DC, on Friday evening &amp;quot;after experiencing flu-like symptoms,&amp;quot; the court&amp;rsquo;s public information office said Sunday evening, but he does not have Covid-19.
Highlights Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was admitted to Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, DC, on Friday evening. Thomas was diagnosed with an infection, and is being treated with intravenous antibiotics. Thomas is expected to be released from the hospital in a day or two.</description></item><item><title>As U.S. ‘trucker convoy’ picks up momentum, foreign meddling adds to fray</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207bfcffd4958efa37613e6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207bfcffd4958efa37613e6/</guid><description>There is growing momentum in the U.S. anti-vaccination community to conduct rallies similar to the “Freedom Convoy” that has paralyzed Ottawa, Canada.
Highlights The majority of the people behind the content mills are not clear, but Joan Donovan, director of the Shorenstein Center, said the pattern fits existing efforts to make money off U.S. It’s normal political activity,” Donovan said. “In other ways, we have to look at how some of the.</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump's children refuse to testify in fraud inquiry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d499502791905072787a38/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d499502791905072787a38/</guid><description>Donald Jr and Ivanka are being asked to give evidence to a civil investigation into the family business.
Summary Ms James&amp;rsquo;s spokesperson said: &amp;ldquo;We are confident that our questions will be answered and the truth will be uncovered because no one is above the law.&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon Carjacked in South Philly</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3e65221baf63d51a3e48d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 03:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3e65221baf63d51a3e48d/</guid><description>Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon (D-5th District) was carjacked at gunpoint in South Philadelphia Wednesday afternoon, her spokesperson confirmed&amp;hellip;
Summary Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon (D-5th District) was carjacked in South Philadelphia Wednesday afternoon, her spokesperson confirmed with NBC10. The spokesperson said Scanlon, 62, was carjacked at gunpoint at 2:45 p.m. at FDR Park. I&amp;rsquo;m appalled to learn of this violent crime that was perpetrated against my friend and colleague, Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon.</description></item></channel></rss>