<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>house on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/house/</link><description>Recent content in house on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 14:12:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida house passes “don’t say gay” bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218e3a61831cfd71df2e441/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 14:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218e3a61831cfd71df2e441/</guid><description>Florida&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives passed a bill Thursday that would prohibit &amp;quot;classroom discussion about sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;quot; in the state’s
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives passed a bill that would prohibit &amp;ldquo;classroom discussion about sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;rdquo; in the state&amp;rsquo;s primary schools. The bill heads to the Republican-held Senate, where it is expected to pass. Critics have said the bill could open districts to lawsuits from parents who believe any conversation about LGBTQ people or issues to be inappropriate.</description></item><item><title>US House candidate apologizes to girls after sleepover</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A U.S. House candidate in Oklahoma has apologized after reports that she became intoxicated at a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day weekend sleepover for middle-school-aged girls, berated several of the children and vomited in a hamper.
Highlights Democrat Abby Broyles is apologizing after reports that she became intoxicated, berated several middle-school-aged girls at a sleepover and vomited in a hamper. Broyles told television station KFOR that she had an adverse reaction after drinking wine and taking medication given to her by a friend.</description></item><item><title>Jan. 6 investigators find gaps in White House call logs -NYT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205b183c7756574d0b7a166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205b183c7756574d0b7a166/</guid><description>The U.S. House committee probing the Jan. 6, 2021 attack on Congress has found gaps in official White House telephone logs on the day of the deadly riot, with few records of calls by then President Donald Trump during the hours investigators know he was making them, the New York Times reported.
Highlights Report: Few records of calls by then President Donald Trump during the hours investigators know he was making them.</description></item><item><title>White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine 'at any point'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</guid><description>White House press secretary Jen Psaki told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S.
Summary White House press secretary Jen Psaki Jen PsakiBiden commends wireless giants for delaying 5G rollout near key airports Briefing in brief: Free COVID-19 test site in testing phase before launch Wednesday White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;at any point&amp;rsquo; MORE told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S. believes that Russia could carry out an attack on Ukraine “at any point,” underscoring the immediacy of the threat should Moscow decide to take action.</description></item></channel></rss>