<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>house on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/house/</link><description>Recent content in house on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 18:13:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Juveniles Crash Stolen Car into White House Security Barrier: Secret Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d2020b2d62a0e0bbd5325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 18:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d2020b2d62a0e0bbd5325/</guid><description>Two juveniles were injured Monday after crashing a stolen car into a concrete security barrier near the White House, the U.S. Secret Service said.
Highlights The car slammed into a concrete barrier and a telephone pole at 17th Street and Pennsylvania Avenue NW, officials said. Video shows a silver sedan partly crumpled in the front across the street from a Secret Service guard post. The two juveniles were taken to a hospital and are now in stable condition.</description></item><item><title>78,000 pounds of infant formula arrives in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b5d77a2a6b703f4225660/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b5d77a2a6b703f4225660/</guid><description>The White House says enough specialty infant formula for more than half a million baby bottles is about to arrive in the United States from Europe.
Highlights NEW: White House announces two new Defense Production Act authorizations for infant formula. Air Force plane carrying enough infant formula for more than half a million bottles arrives in Indianapolis. The White House says 1.5 million 8-ounce bottles of the three formulas are expected to arrive this week.</description></item><item><title>‘Pharma bro’ Martin Shkreli released from federal prison and into New York halfway house</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285fbd7332bbbf1f5ae6e4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 08:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285fbd7332bbbf1f5ae6e4e/</guid><description>Martin Shkreli will his securities fraud sentence in September. He gained infamy for raising the price of a drug by more than 4,000%.
Highlights Martin Shkreli, 39, was sentenced to 7 years in prison in March 2018. &amp;ldquo;Getting out of real prison is easier than getting out of Twitter prison,&amp;rdquo; he wrote on Facebook. He gained infamy for raising the price of a drug by more than 4,000%. He was convicted of securities fraud in 2017.</description></item><item><title>Multiple people shot outside Atlanta Waffle House</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265bd1ff7d43fb2c21b1815/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 21:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265bd1ff7d43fb2c21b1815/</guid><description>UPDATE: Our sister station reports that APD has confirmed five people were shot in the area of John Portman Boulevard and Centennial Olympic Park Drive. The victims were all kids or young adults, ranging from age 15 to 19. Police said they found three people, and two other people carjacked someone and drove to the hospital. WSB-TV reports all five victims are in stable condition. Officers recovered three guns and a stolen vehicle.</description></item><item><title>After a debate citing Hitler, bill penalizing homelessness passes Tennessee legislature</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f9afbe338a297d5343bd5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 05:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f9afbe338a297d5343bd5/</guid><description>Tennessee Republican lawmakers passed legislation to make camping on public property a misdemeanor crime, which critics say criminalizes homelessness.
Highlights House Republicans pass legislation to make camping on public property a misdemeanor crime. Critics say the legislation criminalizes homelessness. The legislation will now go to Gov. Bill Lee&amp;rsquo;s desk. Supporters say it&amp;rsquo;s a tool local law enforcement could use to address homelessness. Democrats and some Republicans opposed the legislation, which passed the Senate with a 22-10 vote last week after a lengthy debate.</description></item><item><title>White House to extend student loan pause through August</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cb0abaca20f0c20dc01a4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cb0abaca20f0c20dc01a4/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration plans to freeze federal student loan payments through Aug. 31, extending a moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to postpone payments during the coronavirus pandemic, according to an administration official familiar with the White House&amp;rsquo;s decision-making.
Highlights The Biden administration plans to freeze federal student loan payments through Aug. 31, extending a moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to postpone payments during the coronavirus pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse faces US probe after telling investors to 'destroy documents' linked to oligarch yacht loans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242591daecc02c922eada32/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242591daecc02c922eada32/</guid><description>The House Oversight Committee launched a probe Monday into Credit Suisse, demanding documents linked to the bank&amp;rsquo;s compliance with sanctions on Russian oligarchs.
Highlights House Oversight Committee asks for documents related to sanctions on Russian oligarchs. House Democrats say it is concerned that the deal may be &amp;ldquo;disguarded&amp;rdquo; by the U.S. Congress. The Committee says it wants to know if Russian investors are complying with the sanctions imposed by the West.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Senate approves bill to make daylight saving time permanent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231491754d88fbf030094da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 02:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231491754d88fbf030094da/</guid><description>The U.S. Senate on Tuesday passed legislation that would make daylight saving time permanent starting in 2023, ending the twice-annual changing of clocks in a move promoted by supporters advocating brighter afternoons and more economic activity.
Highlights The U.S. Senate on Tuesday passed legislation that would make daylight saving time permanent starting in 2023. The Senate approved the measure, called the Sunshine Protection Act, unanimously by voice vote. The House of Representatives must still pass the bill before it can go to President Joe Biden to sign it.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Joe Biden, Hillary Clinton and senior White House officials banned from entering Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230f3844097207c39ce6940/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 20:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230f3844097207c39ce6940/</guid><description>Joining Joe Biden and Hillary Clinton on a Kremlin &amp;quot;stop list&amp;quot; are the president&amp;rsquo;s secretary of state Antony Blinken, CIA chief William Burns, the US defence secretary Lloyd Austin, and national security adviser Jake Sullivan.
Highlights Joe Biden has not visited Russia since 2011, when he was vice president to Barack Obama. Joining the 79-year-old on a Kremlin &amp;ldquo;stop list&amp;rdquo; are his secretary of state Antony Blinken, CIA chief William Burns, defence secretary Lloyd Austin, and national security adviser Jake Sullivan.</description></item><item><title>Dunkin’ worker sentenced to house arrest after fatally punching irate customer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62280d160c25dd8eb6d8926e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 02:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62280d160c25dd8eb6d8926e/</guid><description>Corey Pujols, 27, is ordered to complete 200 hours of community service and attend anger management course. He pleaded guilty to felony battery and was sentenced to two years of house arrest. He was initially charged with manslaughter. Puj
Highlights Corey Pujols, 27, is ordered to complete 200 hours of community service and attend anger management course. He pleaded guilty to felony battery and was sentenced to two years of house arrest.</description></item><item><title>Florida house passes “don’t say gay” bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218e3a61831cfd71df2e441/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 14:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218e3a61831cfd71df2e441/</guid><description>Florida&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives passed a bill Thursday that would prohibit &amp;quot;classroom discussion about sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;quot; in the state’s
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives passed a bill that would prohibit &amp;ldquo;classroom discussion about sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;rdquo; in the state&amp;rsquo;s primary schools. The bill heads to the Republican-held Senate, where it is expected to pass. Critics have said the bill could open districts to lawsuits from parents who believe any conversation about LGBTQ people or issues to be inappropriate.</description></item><item><title>US House candidate apologizes to girls after sleepover</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A U.S. House candidate in Oklahoma has apologized after reports that she became intoxicated at a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day weekend sleepover for middle-school-aged girls, berated several of the children and vomited in a hamper.
Highlights Democrat Abby Broyles is apologizing after reports that she became intoxicated, berated several middle-school-aged girls at a sleepover and vomited in a hamper. Broyles told television station KFOR that she had an adverse reaction after drinking wine and taking medication given to her by a friend.</description></item><item><title>Jan. 6 investigators find gaps in White House call logs -NYT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205b183c7756574d0b7a166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205b183c7756574d0b7a166/</guid><description>The U.S. House committee probing the Jan. 6, 2021 attack on Congress has found gaps in official White House telephone logs on the day of the deadly riot, with few records of calls by then President Donald Trump during the hours investigators know he was making them, the New York Times reported.
Highlights Report: Few records of calls by then President Donald Trump during the hours investigators know he was making them.</description></item><item><title>White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine 'at any point'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</guid><description>White House press secretary Jen Psaki told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S.
Summary White House press secretary Jen Psaki Jen PsakiBiden commends wireless giants for delaying 5G rollout near key airports Briefing in brief: Free COVID-19 test site in testing phase before launch Wednesday White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;at any point&amp;rsquo; MORE told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S. believes that Russia could carry out an attack on Ukraine “at any point,” underscoring the immediacy of the threat should Moscow decide to take action.</description></item></channel></rss>