<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cut on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cut/</link><description>Recent content in cut on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:39:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Target says it will cut prices as Americans’ spending habits drop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fef91e791d2fa4b28a517/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fef91e791d2fa4b28a517/</guid><description>Target said yesterday it will reduce prices and cancel orders in order to reduce an excessive amount of inventory. The retailer also plans to improve growth in its “upstream supply chain” by adding five distribution centers over the next two fiscal
Highlights Target announced it will reduce prices and cancel orders in order to reduce an excessive amount of inventory. Last month, Target reported its fiscal first quarter profit fell by 52% as compared to the same period last year.</description></item><item><title>Meta employees left to do their own laundry as perks get cut | Silicon Valley | The Guardian</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</guid><description>Facebook parent company tells workers they will no longer receive free valet service and meals will be delayed
Highlights Facebook parent company tells employees it will be cutting down on onsite perks including free laundry, dry cleaning and valet service. The daily free dinner will be pushed back from 6pm to 6.30pm due to company cutbacks. Employees will now have to decide between a free meal or a free ride home.</description></item><item><title>U.S. plans to cut ties with targeted Russian banks if Ukraine is invaded - sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213bae4ea9ae74210f6c6e4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213bae4ea9ae74210f6c6e4/</guid><description>President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has prepared an initial package of sanctions against Russia that includes barring U.S. financial institutions from processing transactions for major Russian banks, three people familiar with the matter said.
Highlights President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has prepared an initial package of sanctions against Russia that includes barring U.S. financial institutions from processing transactions for major Russian banks, three people familiar with the matter said. The measures aim to hurt the Russian economy by cutting the &amp;ldquo;correspondent&amp;rdquo; banking relationships between targeted targeted Russian banks and American banks that enable international payments.</description></item></channel></rss>