<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>urges on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/urges/</link><description>Recent content in urges on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 12:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/urges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zelenskyy urges Russian troops not to fight</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e7b88f638ac8553fbedbf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e7b88f638ac8553fbedbf/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine &amp;ndash; Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy switched into Russian in his nightly video address to urge Russian soldiers not to fight in Ukraine, saying even their generals expected that thousands of them would die.
Highlights Sweden says a Russian military plane has violated Swedish airspace. Up to 1,000 civilians are living beneath a Soviet-era steel plant in Mariupol, Ukrainian officials say. Russia has been recruiting new troops “with little motivation and little combat experience” for units gutted during the early weeks of the war.</description></item><item><title>Russian embassy in Dublin short on fuel as companies refuse to deliver supplies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cbedcbf30eb6830749886/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 22:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cbedcbf30eb6830749886/</guid><description>EXCLUSIVE: The Irish Mirror also understands that Bank of Ireland have decided to suspend their accounts with the Russian Embassy in Ireland
Highlights The Russian Embassy in Ireland is running out of fuel for heating and hot water. It has written a letter to Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney asking for help. Bank of Ireland also has decided to suspend their accounts with the Russian Embassy. A source said: “The embassy is struggling because no one wants to do business with them as a result of what’s happening in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>EU ready to impose "never-seen-before" sanctions if Russia attacks Ukraine, Denmark says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eedb268ccd5ae13ee82547/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eedb268ccd5ae13ee82547/</guid><description>The European Union called on Russia on Monday to defuse tensions over Ukraine and reaffirmed that Moscow would face &amp;quot;massive&amp;quot; consequences if it attacked its neighbour.
Summary The EU&amp;rsquo;s 27 foreign ministers, meeting in Brussels, said the bloc &amp;ldquo;condemns Russia&amp;rsquo;s continued aggressive actions and threats against Ukraine and calls on Russia to de-escalate.&amp;rdquo; Denmark said the EU would be ready to impose &amp;ldquo;never-seen-before&amp;rdquo; economic sanctions on Russia. The European Commission, the EU executive body, proposed a 1.</description></item></channel></rss>