<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>continues on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/continues/</link><description>Recent content in continues on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 05:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/continues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'The war for talent' continues. 40% of recent job switchers are again looking for a new position, survey finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62550a361fc32a12d31dc3ad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 05:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62550a361fc32a12d31dc3ad/</guid><description>Many recent job switchers may fuel the Great Resignation trend in the near term, a new survey suggests.
Highlights Survey: Two of every five workers who switched jobs over the past year are looking for work again. Of those recent job-switchers, 40% are already actively looking for another job. Employers may need to reconsider pay, benefits and other workplace issues. Almost 60% of those who recently took new jobs had two or more competing offers when they made their decision, the survey found.</description></item><item><title>More Contagious BA.2 Sub-Variant Spreading in Canada, Complicating Opening Plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62137346595b03912d8a6205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 11:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62137346595b03912d8a6205/</guid><description>The highly contagious Omicron sub-variant known as BA.2 is gaining a foothold in Canada just as provinces begin removing pandemic restrictions, according to newly released data.
Highlights BA.2 is 1.4 times as contagious as the already highly transmissible original Omicron sub-variant. Experts say it will have an influence on case counts in Ontario, but will likely not be a complete game changer. It could extend the current wave of the pandemic, increase case counts, or slow the decrease in cases at a time when provinces are dropping gathering restrictions and mask mandates.</description></item><item><title>Germany continues blocking arms exports to Ukraine due to new foreign ‘peace’ policy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e762b377d0755de7d787b7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 01:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e762b377d0755de7d787b7/</guid><description>Germany reiterated its refusal to send defensive weapons to Ukraine that according to Kyiv would help the country fend off a potential Russian invasion. This comes as part of a new German peace policy that aims at restricting arms exports and fostering peace via diplomacy.
Summary Germany reiterated its refusal to send defensive weapons to Ukraine that according to Kyiv would help the country fend off a potential Russian invasion. This comes as part of a new German peace policy that aims at restricting arms exports and fostering peace via diplomacy.</description></item><item><title>Quebec to impose a tax on people who are unvaccinated from COVID-19 | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de608acc344cf0856937e3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 05:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de608acc344cf0856937e3/</guid><description>Premier François Legault said the tax is under consideration over the burden those who aren&amp;rsquo;t vaccinated are having on the health-care system.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailQuebec is announcing it will impose a health tax on Quebecers who refuse to be vaccinated against COVID-19. Quebec Premier François Legault made the announcement in Montreal on Tuesday afternoon, as the number of pandemic-related hospitalizations continues to climb. Read more: COVID-19: Quebec tops 12,000 deaths as hospitalizations increase2:13 Quebec to introduce health tax for the unvaccinated Quebec to introduce health tax for the unvaccinatedLegault said he felt the ire of the vaccinated towards the unvaccinated, whom he blamed for clogging up the province’s hospitals.</description></item><item><title>Calgary therapists hail 'legalization' of medicinal psychedelic drugs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dab258abc2b2c546fb3c9c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dab258abc2b2c546fb3c9c/</guid><description>Local therapists say Ottawa’s move allowing physicians to prescribe psychedelics is a “seismic shift” towards legalizing their medicinal use.
Summary Share this Story: Therapists hail &amp;rsquo;legalization&amp;rsquo; of medicinal psychedelic drugsTherapists hail &amp;rsquo;legalization&amp;rsquo; of medicinal psychedelic drugs Photo by Jim Wells/PostmediaArticle content Local therapists say Ottawa’s move allowing physicians to prescribe psychedelics is a “seismic shift” towards legalizing their medicinal use. Advertisement Story continues below This advertisement has not loaded yet, but your article continues below.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew makes 'unprecedented' request for all witness testimony in sex abuse case to be kept secret</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce643ed24df844e06c718b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce643ed24df844e06c718b/</guid><description>The request was made in a letter submitted to court as part of a fresh attempt to get the civil proceedings thrown out
Summary Share this Story: Prince Andrew makes &amp;lsquo;unprecedented&amp;rsquo; request for all witness testimony in sex abuse case to be kept secretPrince Andrew makes &amp;lsquo;unprecedented&amp;rsquo; request for all witness testimony in sex abuse case to be kept secret The request was made in a letter submitted to court as part of a fresh attempt to get the civil proceedings thrown out Photo by Steve Parsons/PA Wire/Pool via Reuters/FileArticle content LONDON — Prince Andrew, the Duke of York, has made an “unprecedented” request for all witness testimony taken in his sexual abuse case to be kept secret, it has emerged.</description></item></channel></rss>