<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>violence on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/violence/</link><description>Recent content in violence on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 02:06:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/violence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Transgender woman who fled to US to escape violence in Latin America murdered</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622416f55adfa3f52395d09d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 02:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622416f55adfa3f52395d09d/</guid><description>HOUSTON, Texas (WKRC) - A transgender woman fled Latin America to escape high rates of gender-based violence, only to be murdered in her apartment. &amp;quot;She had just moved into her new apartment and was very excited about decorating,&amp;quot; said Gia Pacheco, a friend of the victim. 29-year-oldPaloma Vazquez was found shot to death inside her Houston, Texas apartment on Saturday. Police say there were no signs of forced entry.
Highlights 29-year-old Paloma Vazquez was found shot to death inside her Houston, Texas apartment on Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item></channel></rss>