<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>violence on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/violence/</link><description>Recent content in violence on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 23:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/violence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Students walk out of schools in protest of gun violence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62915a41d6a6b29e547b124a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62915a41d6a6b29e547b124a/</guid><description>Days after 19 students and 2 teachers were killed in a mass shooting, students walked out of class protesting gun violence.
Highlights Days after 19 students and 2 teachers were killed in a mass shooting at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, students at schools around the country staged walkouts to protest gun violence. Students at Oxford High School in Michigan, where a school shooting occurred in November, staged a walkout at 12 p.</description></item><item><title>Pro-choice group claims arson attack on Wisconsin anti-abortion office</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b0c0fe8de2acade183381/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 01:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b0c0fe8de2acade183381/</guid><description>Madison police investigate attack on Wisconsin Family Action after claim by group calling itself Jane’s revenge
Highlights Wisconsin Family Action headquarters attacked in early hours of Sunday morning. Molotov cocktail thrown through window, started fire and graffiti sprayed on wall. Jane’s Revenge said it launched the attack because of the organization&amp;rsquo;s anti-abortion stance. Federal agents and detectives from the Madison police department are investigating the claim. Madison police chief, Shon Barnes, said no suspects had so far been identified.</description></item><item><title>Swedish police shoot 3 during fresh riots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dab574b086a07f485d7f7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 18:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dab574b086a07f485d7f7/</guid><description>Three people were injured as police fired warning shots at rioters in the eastern city of Norrkoping. The unrest had started after a far-right politician threatened to burn a copy of the Quran.
Highlights Police fire warning shots at rioters in city of Norrkoping in eastern Sweden. Rioters had gathered after far-right politician threatened to burn copies of the Quran. Sweden&amp;rsquo;s Justice Minister Morgan Johansson tells rioters to &amp;ldquo;Go home, immediately&amp;rdquo; Similar clashes in recent days have caused damage and injuries in several Swedish cities.</description></item><item><title>New Secret Service report details growing incel terrorism threat</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62309edbba16ce3418eaf40d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62309edbba16ce3418eaf40d/</guid><description>Since 2014, attacks inspired by the &amp;quot;incel movement&amp;quot; and spanning the U.S. and Canada have left dozens dead.
Highlights The federal government released a study on the growing terrorism threat from men who call themselves &amp;ldquo;anti-feminists&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;involuntary celibates&amp;rdquo; Since 2014, attacks inspired by the &amp;ldquo;incel movement&amp;rdquo; and spanning the U.S. and Canada have left dozens dead. Early intervention and behavioral threat assessments could be the difference between life and death for women targeted by the growing ideology, according to the 26-page report.</description></item><item><title>Transgender woman who fled to US to escape violence in Latin America murdered</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622416f55adfa3f52395d09d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 02:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622416f55adfa3f52395d09d/</guid><description>HOUSTON, Texas (WKRC) - A transgender woman fled Latin America to escape high rates of gender-based violence, only to be murdered in her apartment. &amp;quot;She had just moved into her new apartment and was very excited about decorating,&amp;quot; said Gia Pacheco, a friend of the victim. 29-year-oldPaloma Vazquez was found shot to death inside her Houston, Texas apartment on Saturday. Police say there were no signs of forced entry.
Highlights 29-year-old Paloma Vazquez was found shot to death inside her Houston, Texas apartment on Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item></channel></rss>