<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>records on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/records/</link><description>Recent content in records on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 03:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘I hope I hit one of them kids’: Woman fires shots into home with children inside, records show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629c23a5b582322eba73eb13/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629c23a5b582322eba73eb13/</guid><description>Johari Jenkins is charged with multiple counts of criminal attempt first-degree murder, aggravated assault and more. A witness said she heard Jenkins state, “I might as well get another one today by killing you and your kids b****
Highlights Johari Jenkins is charged with multiple counts of criminal attempt first-degree murder, aggravated assault and more after an incident on May 2. Jenkins allegedly fired four to five times into the living room window of a Memphis home.</description></item><item><title>Sex worker gets 30 years for fatally drugging men for ‘a few quick dollars’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270131fe020ba2ae06fd4c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 17:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270131fe020ba2ae06fd4c8/</guid><description>Angelina Barini’s pattern was nearly identical, authorities said. In motel rooms in Queens, she gave four men high doses of drugs, robbed them and left them unresponsive.
Highlights Angelina Barini, 43, met with clients at motels in New York City before giving them drugs that incapacitated them. Then, she would rob the men and leave with their personal belongings. Four of them, including a prominent Italian chef, died of overdoses from the drugs, court records state.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Trump's bid to shield January 6 records, bringing end to legal battle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62152846663c5b6e90e95e31/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62152846663c5b6e90e95e31/</guid><description>The Supreme Court already rejected Trump&amp;rsquo;s emergency request to block the release of his records to the January 6 select committee.
Highlights The Supreme Court turned away the former president&amp;rsquo;s legal fight with the House select committee investigating the January 6 assault on the U.S. Capitol. The panel received more than 700 pages of records sought by the panel earlier this month. Trump asserted executive privilege over more than 750 pages of documents related to the events of January 6, including presidential diaries, visitor logs, handwritten notes from then-White House chief of staff Mark Meadows, binders from then White House press secretary Kayleigh McEnany, and a draft executive order on election integrity.</description></item><item><title>The United States records an average of 700,000 new cases per day; Fauci says the nation could grow to 1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 12:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</guid><description>Summary The country reported about 4.91 million cases in the week ending Saturday. “I would not be surprised at all if we go over a million cases per day,” Dr. Anthony Fauci, the president’s chief medical adviser, told News 4 New York in an interview Saturday. But Fauci told the TV station the dismal numbers could start to decline by month’s end. 📈Today’s numbers: The U.S. has recorded more than 60 million confirmed COVID-19 cases and more than 837,000 deaths, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description></item><item><title>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records were subpoenaed by House Jan. 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</guid><description>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol.
Summary My Pillow CEO Michael Lindell is seen outside the door of the West Wing at the White House on Friday, Jan 15, 2021 in Washington, DC. MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, an ally of former President Donald Trump, said his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the origins of the deadly riot that took place on Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>