<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>records on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/records/</link><description>Recent content in records on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 12:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The United States records an average of 700,000 new cases per day; Fauci says the nation could grow to 1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 12:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</guid><description>Summary The country reported about 4.91 million cases in the week ending Saturday. “I would not be surprised at all if we go over a million cases per day,” Dr. Anthony Fauci, the president’s chief medical adviser, told News 4 New York in an interview Saturday. But Fauci told the TV station the dismal numbers could start to decline by month’s end. 📈Today’s numbers: The U.S. has recorded more than 60 million confirmed COVID-19 cases and more than 837,000 deaths, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description></item><item><title>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records were subpoenaed by House Jan. 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</guid><description>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol.
Summary My Pillow CEO Michael Lindell is seen outside the door of the West Wing at the White House on Friday, Jan 15, 2021 in Washington, DC. MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, an ally of former President Donald Trump, said his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the origins of the deadly riot that took place on Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>