<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suspends on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspends/</link><description>Recent content in suspends on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 23:12:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US suspends Mexican avocado imports on eve of Super Bowl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620990356b835a0817e10827/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 23:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620990356b835a0817e10827/</guid><description>MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico has acknowledged that the U.S. government has suspended all imports of Mexican avocados after a U.S. plant safety inspector in Mexico received a threat. The surprise suspension was confirmed late Saturday on the eve of the Super Bowl, the biggest sales opportunity of the year for Mexican avocado growers — though it would not affect game-day consumption since those avocados had already been shipped.
Highlights Mexico has acknowledged that the U.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey plow driver who sprayed Orthodox Jews with snow during storm facing criminal probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</guid><description>The snow plow driver in Lakewood, New Jersey, who cast a wave of snow and ice from his plow onto two Orthodox Jewish men walking along a roadway has been suspended from his job and could face criminal charges, pending the outcome of a police investigation. Video of the act, which appears to have been intentional, was posted on social media. A passenger recorded the video with his phone as the driver approached the two men walking along County Line Road near the Jackson Township border.</description></item><item><title>Twitter permanently suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene's personal account</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</guid><description>Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep.
Summary Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene after &amp;ldquo;repeated violations&amp;rdquo; of the Covid-19 misinformation policy, the company said Sunday. &amp;ldquo;We permanently suspended the account you referenced (@mtgreenee) for repeated violations of our COVID-19 misinformation policy,&amp;rdquo; Twitter said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;We’ve been clear that, per our strike system for this policy, we will permanently suspend accounts for repeated violations of the policy.</description></item></channel></rss>