<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fall on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fall/</link><description>Recent content in fall on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:41:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US-born figure skater Zhu Yi under attack after fall on Olympic debut for China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62006a7c6c503473c9f73125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62006a7c6c503473c9f73125/</guid><description>Representing China, California-born figure skater Zhu Yi is facing a firestorm of attack on Chinese social media after she fell flat on the ice and finished last in a women&amp;rsquo;s short program team event Sunday.
Highlights The hashtag &amp;ldquo;Zhu Yi has fallen&amp;rdquo; gained 200 million views in just a few hours on China&amp;rsquo;s Twitter-like platform. Many questioned why Zhu, an American-born skater, was picked to represent China at the expense of an athlete born in the country.</description></item><item><title>Spotify stocks fall as executives seek to reassure amid Rogan controversy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</guid><description>Subscriber outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter earnings as the company’s shares fell nearly 18% in late trading
Highlights Spotify forecast current-quarter subscribers lower than Wall Street expectations. Company&amp;rsquo;s shares fell as much as 18% in late trading after Spotify reported the subscriber outlook. The outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter revenue, which came in higher than analysts’ estimates. CEO Daniel Ek acknowledged the Joe Rogan controversy at the outset of the earnings conference call. He said he was proud of the steps Spotify took following the concerns raised by the medical and scientific communities and he said policies were developed with input from external and internal and external exports.</description></item></channel></rss>