<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>free on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/free/</link><description>Recent content in free on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 17:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court backs Navy in fight with anti-vaccine SEALs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f49a299b5b8509d718b49/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f49a299b5b8509d718b49/</guid><description>The U.S. Supreme Court on Friday granted a request by President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration to let the Navy decline to deploy SEALs and other special operations forces personnel who refused mandatory COVID-19 vaccination due to religious objections.
Highlights The U.S. Supreme Court granted a request by President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration to let the Navy decline to deploy SEALs and other special operations forces personnel who refused mandatory COVID-19 vaccination due to religious objections.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Airbnbs being booked in effort to get money to residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221bbd371fca3782c26cb9e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 07:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221bbd371fca3782c26cb9e/</guid><description>People are paying but not staying, as rental platform offers free housing to 100,000 Ukrainian refugees
Highlights Members of the public are paying for Airbnb rentals in Ukraine to help get money to residents who are facing extreme financial hardship because of the Russian invasion. Airbnb has already moved to offer free housing to 100,000 Ukrainian refugees. The rental platform is waiving all guest and host fees on all bookings in Ukraine at this time.</description></item><item><title>A church is suing after a town says it can only give away free meals twice per week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb48501f2f3e111f89e368/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb48501f2f3e111f89e368/</guid><description>St. Timothy&amp;rsquo;s Episcopal Church and the Episcopal Diocese of Oregon sue the city of Brookings, Oregon. The church says a new ordinance limiting them to two free meals per week violates their constitutional right to free religious expression. &amp;quot;We&amp;rsquo;ve
Highlights St. Timothy&amp;rsquo;s Episcopal Church says it has been doing free meals for those in need for decades. The city of Brookings, Oregon, recently approved a new ordinance limiting the church&amp;rsquo;s free meals.</description></item><item><title>France to make birth control free for women aged 18-25 | After making birth control free for underage girls, France is now expanding the program to include women aged 18 to 25.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfedfcfbbcf8f9a460b274/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfedfcfbbcf8f9a460b274/</guid><description>After making birth control free for underage girls, France is now expanding the program to include women aged 18 to 25.
Summary Starting in 2022, birth control will be available to women in France aged 18 to 25 for free, expanding an existing program for minors that seeks to prevent unwanted pregnancies because of the cost of birth control. French officials believe that up to 3 million women could benefit from enhanced access to the pill, IUDs, contraceptive patches and jabs.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item></channel></rss>