<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>worlds on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worlds/</link><description>Recent content in worlds on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 03:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worlds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tech giants lost more than $1 trillion in value in the last three trading days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279dac4e63481987b9b0d59/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279dac4e63481987b9b0d59/</guid><description>The biggest names of the technology industry are becoming more affordable as investors take account of the latest U.S. central bank decision.
Highlights Technology has endured more pain than other sectors of the economy. Investors are now pushing more money toward safer pockets of the market, including Campbell Soup, General Mills and J.M. Smucker. The biggest names of the technology industry are becoming more affordable as investors take account of the latest U.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine has retaken towns 35km east of Kyiv, UK says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623deb52c4f242fe8b959ced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 16:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623deb52c4f242fe8b959ced/</guid><description>Ukraine has retaken towns and defensive positions up to 35 kilometres east of Kyiv, helped by Russian forces falling back on overextended supply lines, Britain&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said on Friday.
Highlights Ukraine retaken towns and defensive positions up to 35 kilometres east of Kyiv, UK defence ministry says. Russia forces falling back on overextended supply lines, British defence ministry said. Russia says it has fallen back on over-stretched supply lines. Ukraine retaking towns helped by Russian forces, Britain&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry has said.</description></item><item><title>Russian submarines threatening undersea network of internet cables, says UK defence chief Sir Tony Radakin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</guid><description>Any attempt to damage the underwater cables on which &amp;quot;predominantly all the world&amp;rsquo;s information and traffic travels&amp;quot; could be considered an &amp;quot;act of war&amp;quot;, the UK&amp;rsquo;s newly appointed head of the armed forces tells The Times.
Summary The head of Britain&amp;rsquo;s armed forces is warning Russian submarines are threatening a crucial network of underwater cables that carry information around the world. Admiral Sir Tony Radakin, who was appointed chief of the defence staff in October, said the undersea cables that transmit internet data are &amp;ldquo;the world&amp;rsquo;s real information system&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>The world’s biggest offshore wind farm, Hornsea 2, generates first power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdc98cc33c0e1181821e8a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdc98cc33c0e1181821e8a/</guid><description>Summary First power on Hornsea 2, which is located 89 km off the UK&amp;rsquo;s east coast, was achieved after its offshore substation (OSS), the world’s largest offshore AC substation, and reactive compensation station (RCS), were installed in late October 2021. Since that time, Ørsted and its partner companies have been working hard to commission and energise the wind farm in preparation for its anticipated operational date next year. A further two projects in the Hornsea Zone are also underway with Hornsea 3 receiving a Development Consent Order in December 2020 and Hornsea 4 currently going through the planning process.</description></item><item><title>Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. This increase was exacerbated during the Covid pandemic. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 13:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</guid><description>Report calls for a “modest progressive wealth tax on global multimillionaires” in order to redistribute wealth.
Summary PARIS: The share of global wealth of the world’s richest people soared at a record pace during the Covid pandemic, a report on inequality showed on Tuesday. Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires’ share of wealth on record,” the document said.</description></item><item><title>United States is world’s biggest plastic polluter, report finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c41e9670811afb6b1c14a8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c41e9670811afb6b1c14a8/</guid><description>None
Summary The United States is by far the biggest contributor to global plastic waste in the world, according to a new report submitted to the federal government Wednesday that called for a national strategy to tackle the growing crisis. On average, every American generates 130 kilograms (286 pounds) of plastic waste per year, with Britain next on the list at 99 kilos per person per year, followed by South Korea at 88 kilos per year.</description></item></channel></rss>