<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>billion on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/billion/</link><description>Recent content in billion on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 22:13:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/billion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Germany to buy dozens of US fighter jets in spending spree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fbdf920e4a7f7bf4e31b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fbdf920e4a7f7bf4e31b2/</guid><description>Germany plans to buy up to 35 US-made F-35 fighter jets and 15 Eurofighter jets, a parliamentary source said Monday, as part of a major push to modernise the armed forces in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s inva…
Highlights Germany plans to buy up to 35 F-35 fighter jets and 15 Eurofighter jets, a parliamentary source said Monday. The jets made by Lockheed Martin would replace Germany&amp;rsquo;s decades-old Tornado fleet, the source said.</description></item><item><title>US casinos won $53 billion in 2021, their best year ever</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d3f15aafeee50bb843b62/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 18:16:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d3f15aafeee50bb843b62/</guid><description>ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — America&amp;rsquo;s commercial casinos won $53 billion in 2021, their best year ever according to figures released Tuesday. The American Gaming Association, the gambling industry&amp;rsquo;s national trade group, released year-end figures showing that in-person gambling continues to be the main source of revenue for the gambling industry, even as internet and sports betting continue to grow in the U.S.
Highlights U.S. commercial casinos won $53 billion in 2021, making it the gambling industry&amp;rsquo;s best year ever.</description></item><item><title>FBI: Americans Lost $1 Billion to Romance Scams in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bd563650f6c85d32cc422/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bd563650f6c85d32cc422/</guid><description>Organized Crime and Corruption Reporting Project
Highlights Romance scams have been on the rise since the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic and cost Americans more than US$1 billion in 2021 alone. Perpetrators mainly target women over 40 who are widowed, divorced, elderly or disabled. “The victim just wants connection and companionship. The bad guy generally wants cold hard cash,” the FBI warned. Phishing attacks and social engineering, like romance scams, remain two of the most common crimes on the web.</description></item></channel></rss>