<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mask on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mask/</link><description>Recent content in mask on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 19:18:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mask/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multiple airlines allowing passengers to go maskless following judge's ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f0ad58f990e57c936e6b4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 19:18:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f0ad58f990e57c936e6b4/</guid><description>Though customers are free to continue wearing masks if they choose, passengers will not be required to mask up on many carriers for the first time in years.
Highlights In the wake of a judge&amp;rsquo;s ruling, major U.S. airlines have made mask-wearing optional for both passengers and employees. Many airlines note that while their new policies apply on all domestic flights, masks may still be required to fly to some international destinations.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn Subway Shooting: Multiple Shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255974d1ff65f9627ad4b56/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 15:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255974d1ff65f9627ad4b56/</guid><description>It happened in Sunset Park, near 4th Avenue and 36th Street. The suspect is said to be a man in a gas mask.
Highlights At least five people were shot Tuesday on a moving Brooklyn subway by a man in a gas mask and orange construction vest who may have tossed a smoke canister on the platform to distract the rush hour crowd, according to NYPD officials and senior law enforcement officials.</description></item><item><title>Florida governor: school districts that defied no-mask mandate to lose $200m</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62123e96962cd6013a8137e4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 13:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62123e96962cd6013a8137e4/</guid><description>Ron DeSantis is backing a bill that would strip education funding from Democratic counties that retained Covid precautions
Highlights Florida governor backs controversial plan to strip $200m in education funding from Democratic counties that defied his executive order banning mask mandates in schools. DeSantis, who is widely seen as a leading heir to Donald Trump in the Republican party, plans to send the money instead to mostly Republican counties that supported him.</description></item><item><title>Walmart drops mask mandate for vaccinated employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</guid><description>Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. State-mandated masks will no longer be required unless required by state or local government. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in pharmacies will be required to
Highlights Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in clinical care settings will be required to keep wearing masks. Several states, from New York to California, have issued their own plans to lift indoor mask mandates.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch again doesn't wear mask on bench, Sotomayor and Breyer log in remotely</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de7ca8993b9a45497b3e57/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de7ca8993b9a45497b3e57/</guid><description>Two justices, Sonia Sotomayor and Stephen Breyer, appeared remotely due to apparent concerns about Covid-19 as Neil Gorsuch did not wear a mask.
Summary Associate Justice Neil Gorsuch poses during a group photo of the Justices at the Supreme Court in Washington, April 23, 2021. Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch did not wear a mask for a hearing Tuesday, even as all the other justices in attendance did so, while two colleagues appeared remotely due to apparent concerns about Covid-19 infection.</description></item></channel></rss>