<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>customers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/customers/</link><description>Recent content in customers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:12:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/customers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. consumer bureau sues TransUnion, executive for continued deceptive marketing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256b000be6d1668e32d0584/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256b000be6d1668e32d0584/</guid><description>A U.S. consumer watchdog on Tuesday sued TransUnion and one of its former executives, accusing the credit reporting agency of tricking consumers into making recurring payments after the company was fined in 2017 for similar activity.
Highlights Consumer Financial Protection Bureau sues TransUnion and one of its former executives. Suit accuses the credit reporting agency of tricking consumers into making recurring payments after the company was fined in 2017 for similar activity.</description></item><item><title>Uber charging customers new fuel fee for rides, delivery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ed40557294e5f30e6f34b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 05:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ed40557294e5f30e6f34b/</guid><description>Citing record-high prices for gasoline, Uber is charging customers a new fuel fee to help offset costs for ride-hail and delivery drivers.
Highlights Uber is charging customers a new fuel fee to help offset costs for ride-hail and delivery drivers. The temporary surcharge will be either 45 cents or 55 cents for each Uber trip and 35 cents for Uber Eats order. All the money will go directly to drivers, San Francisco-based Uber said.</description></item></channel></rss>