<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>potentially on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/potentially/</link><description>Recent content in potentially on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 10:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/potentially/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Potentially historic’ wildfire event threatens New Mexico, Southwest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277984aa8daed53f2b16f57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277984aa8daed53f2b16f57/</guid><description>The entire state of New Mexico is under a red flag warning for dangerous fire conditions
Highlights The National Weather Service is calling it a “dangerous, long duration and potentially historic critical fire weather event” Tinderbox conditions conducive to the rapid spread of blazes are expected to persist well into next week. New ignitions are also anticipated, which could rapidly grow out of control. The Calf Canyon fire became New Mexico’s second-largest on record this week, now the state&amp;rsquo;s second largest on record.</description></item><item><title>FDA warns of raw oysters potentially contaminated with norovirus - CBS News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62501890ae6af5c972b0dd6a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 11:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62501890ae6af5c972b0dd6a/</guid><description>Health officials are working to curtail outbreak that has sickened at least 91 people in 13 states and 279 Canadians.
Highlights Public health officials are warning restaurants and retailers not to serve or sell potentially contaminated raw oysters linked to a norovirus outbreak that&amp;rsquo;s sickened at least 91 people in more than a dozen U.S. states and 279 more in Canada. Possibly tainted oysters harvested in British Columbia, Canada, were distributed in California, Colorado, Florida, Hawaii, Illinois, Massachusetts, Minnesota, New Jersey, Nevada, New York, Oregon, Texas and Washington.</description></item></channel></rss>