<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ban on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ban/</link><description>Recent content in ban on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Utah bans transgender athletes in girls sports despite veto</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e4c6f849e5d2b8b9ad0b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e4c6f849e5d2b8b9ad0b6/</guid><description>SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — GOP lawmakers in Utah pushed through a ban on transgender youth athletes playing on girls teams Friday, overriding a veto and joining 11 other states with similar laws amid a nationwide culture war.
Highlights Utah lawmakers override a ban on transgender youth athletes playing on girls teams Friday, overriding a veto. Lawmakers successfully flipped 10 Republicans in the House and five in the Senate who had previously voted against the proposal.</description></item><item><title>Judge makes ban on Saget autopsy records release permanent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62303c9170868e55436857d8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 07:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62303c9170868e55436857d8/</guid><description>A judge in Florida has agreed to make permanent an order that prohibits the release of photos, video or other records related to the investigation into the death of comedian Bob Saget
Highlights A judge in Florida has agreed to make permanent an order that prohibits the release of photos, video or other records related to the investigation into the death of comedian Bob Saget. The order was requested by Saget&amp;rsquo;s widow, Kelly Rizzo, and his three daughters.</description></item><item><title>El Salvador frees women jailed after miscarriages | The women had been jailed for terms ranging from 6 to 13 years under some of the region’s harshest anti-abortion laws</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c804fb31d174404881d81f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c804fb31d174404881d81f/</guid><description>The women had been jailed for terms ranging from six to 13 years under some of the region’s harshest anti-abortion laws.
Summary The women had lost their fetuses due to “health emergencies” during pregnancy, said the ACDATEE abortion rights group. El Salvador bans abortion in all cases, and terminating a pregnancy can send a woman to jail for up to eight years. “We continue fighting for the freedom of the rest of the women imprisoned,” said Herrera.</description></item><item><title>Spain will ban smoking on all beaches and fine anyone caught lighting up £1,700</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c626f95d27db58a4624dec/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c626f95d27db58a4624dec/</guid><description>The national law, a first for Europe, will aim to combat pollution caused by cigarette butts which are a major pollutant on the country&amp;rsquo;s 3,000 miles of coastline.
Summary Spain is set to ban smoking on all of its beaches, allowing councils to fine offenders up to 2,000 euros (£1,700). Several Spanish regions, including Barcelona and the Canary islands, have already introduced similar smoking bans on beaches. Spain is set to ban smoking on all of its beaches months after a petition was signed by more than 283,000 people and delivered to the government.</description></item><item><title>Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</guid><description>Description A B.C. Supreme Court judge has banned Nanaimo fisherman Scott Stanley Matthew Steer from fishing for life.
Summary The sentence was delivered on Nov. 12, 2021, and it is the first lifetime ban for a Pacific region fisherman in more than a decade. Along with the lifetime ban, Steer&amp;rsquo;s sentence includes:A prohibition from being aboard a fishing vessel. Steer was caught illegally fishing for crab in the Vancouver harbour after Vancouver SeaBus officials tipped off police.</description></item></channel></rss>