<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ban on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ban/</link><description>Recent content in ban on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:40:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canada's Trudeau announces plan for national freeze on handguns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629563c4166e08fef4f508a9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629563c4166e08fef4f508a9/</guid><description>Canada&amp;rsquo;s government introduced legislation Monday to implement a &amp;quot;national freeze&amp;quot; on the sale and purchase of handguns as part of a gun control package that would also limit magazine capacities and ban some toys that look like guns.
Highlights Canada&amp;rsquo;s government introduces legislation to implement a &amp;ldquo;national freeze&amp;rdquo; on the sale and purchase of handguns as part of a gun control package. The new legislation would also limit magazine capacities and ban some toys that look like guns.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs the nation’s strictest abortion ban</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f89f3cd3741808d78f4c8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f89f3cd3741808d78f4c8/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt on Wednesday signed into law the nation’s strictest abortion ban, making the state the first in the nation to effectively end availability of the procedure.
Highlights The law takes effect immediately upon Stitt’s signature and prohibits all abortions with few exceptions. The ban enforced by civil lawsuits rather than criminal prosecution, similar to a Texas law that was passed last year. The only exceptions in the Oklahoma law are to save the life of a pregnant woman or if the pregnancy is the result of rape or incest that has been reported to law enforcement.</description></item><item><title>Court: California's under-21 gun sales ban unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cb3ca51c5b0ab13d60e8d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cb3ca51c5b0ab13d60e8d/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A U.S. appeals court ruled Wednesday that California’s ban on the sale of semiautomatic weapons to adults under 21 is unconstitutional. In a 2-1 ruling, a panel of the San Francisco-based 9th U.S.
Highlights A U.S. appeals court ruled Wednesday, May 11, that California’s ban on the sale of semiautomatic weapons to adults under 21 is unconstitutional. The court said the law violates the Second Amendment right to bear arms.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs Texas-style ban on most abortions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62720093b4de16de1e44862b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62720093b4de16de1e44862b/</guid><description>Oklahoma’s Republican Gov. Kevin Stitt has signed a Texas-style abortion ban that prohibits abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy
Highlights Gov. Kevin Stitt signs a Texas-style abortion ban that prohibits abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy. A similar bill approved in Texas last year led to a dramatic reduction in the number of abortions performed in that state. Stitt&amp;rsquo;s signing of the bill comes on the heels of a leaked draft opinion from the nation&amp;rsquo;s high court that it is considering weakening or overturning the landmark Roe v.</description></item><item><title>Taliban bans drug cultivation, including lucrative opium</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a29f15a1cee428ffac0c7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a29f15a1cee428ffac0c7/</guid><description>The Taliban announced on Sunday a ban on the cultivation of narcotics in Afghanistan, the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest opium producer.
Highlights The Taliban announced on Sunday a ban on the cultivation of narcotics in Afghanistan, the world’s biggest opium producer. The order said the production, use or transportation of other narcotics was also banned. The Taliban banned poppy growing towards the end of their last rule in 2000 as they sought international legitimacy, but faced a popular backlash and later mostly changed their stance, according to experts.</description></item><item><title>Utah bans transgender athletes in girls sports despite veto</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e4c6f849e5d2b8b9ad0b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e4c6f849e5d2b8b9ad0b6/</guid><description>SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — GOP lawmakers in Utah pushed through a ban on transgender youth athletes playing on girls teams Friday, overriding a veto and joining 11 other states with similar laws amid a nationwide culture war.
Highlights Utah lawmakers override a ban on transgender youth athletes playing on girls teams Friday, overriding a veto. Lawmakers successfully flipped 10 Republicans in the House and five in the Senate who had previously voted against the proposal.</description></item><item><title>Judge makes ban on Saget autopsy records release permanent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62303c9170868e55436857d8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 07:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62303c9170868e55436857d8/</guid><description>A judge in Florida has agreed to make permanent an order that prohibits the release of photos, video or other records related to the investigation into the death of comedian Bob Saget
Highlights A judge in Florida has agreed to make permanent an order that prohibits the release of photos, video or other records related to the investigation into the death of comedian Bob Saget. The order was requested by Saget&amp;rsquo;s widow, Kelly Rizzo, and his three daughters.</description></item><item><title>El Salvador frees women jailed after miscarriages | The women had been jailed for terms ranging from 6 to 13 years under some of the region’s harshest anti-abortion laws</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c804fb31d174404881d81f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c804fb31d174404881d81f/</guid><description>The women had been jailed for terms ranging from six to 13 years under some of the region’s harshest anti-abortion laws.
Summary The women had lost their fetuses due to “health emergencies” during pregnancy, said the ACDATEE abortion rights group. El Salvador bans abortion in all cases, and terminating a pregnancy can send a woman to jail for up to eight years. “We continue fighting for the freedom of the rest of the women imprisoned,” said Herrera.</description></item><item><title>Spain will ban smoking on all beaches and fine anyone caught lighting up £1,700</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c626f95d27db58a4624dec/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c626f95d27db58a4624dec/</guid><description>The national law, a first for Europe, will aim to combat pollution caused by cigarette butts which are a major pollutant on the country&amp;rsquo;s 3,000 miles of coastline.
Summary Spain is set to ban smoking on all of its beaches, allowing councils to fine offenders up to 2,000 euros (£1,700). Several Spanish regions, including Barcelona and the Canary islands, have already introduced similar smoking bans on beaches. Spain is set to ban smoking on all of its beaches months after a petition was signed by more than 283,000 people and delivered to the government.</description></item><item><title>Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</guid><description>Description A B.C. Supreme Court judge has banned Nanaimo fisherman Scott Stanley Matthew Steer from fishing for life.
Summary The sentence was delivered on Nov. 12, 2021, and it is the first lifetime ban for a Pacific region fisherman in more than a decade. Along with the lifetime ban, Steer&amp;rsquo;s sentence includes:A prohibition from being aboard a fishing vessel. Steer was caught illegally fishing for crab in the Vancouver harbour after Vancouver SeaBus officials tipped off police.</description></item></channel></rss>