<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>incident on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/incident/</link><description>Recent content in incident on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/incident/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A dying Uvalde teacher was on the phone with her husband -- a school police officer whose boss decided not to enter her classroom, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629975d9766eab870f824e13/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629975d9766eab870f824e13/</guid><description>Eva Mireles spent some of her final monents on the phone with her police officer husband, The New York Times reported. But he couldn&amp;rsquo;t save his wife and 20 others massacred at Robb Elementary. And a negotiator&amp;rsquo;s attempts to reach the gunman were futile.
Highlights Texas State Sen. Roland Gutierrez questions whether 911 calls from inside Texas elementary school were relayed properly to responders at the scene of the shooting. Gutierrez promised to share that information with media once received.</description></item><item><title>Southern California woman who accused Black teen of stealing phone, pleads guilty to hate crime charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255ddb34392a0bec8121f93/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255ddb34392a0bec8121f93/</guid><description>Miya Ponsetto, 23, pleads guilty to unlawful imprisonment in the second degree as a hate crime. She falsely accused Keyon Harrold Jr. of stealing her cell phone and then attacking him in a New York
Highlights Miya Ponsetto pleads guilty to unlawful imprisonment in the second degree as a hate crime. She falsely accused Keyon Harrold Jr. of stealing her cell phone and then attacking him in a New York hotel lobby.</description></item><item><title>Car rams Russian Embassy gate in Romania, driver dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ed7d9ace124b5e59a5c4a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 12:24:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ed7d9ace124b5e59a5c4a/</guid><description>Police in the Romanian capital say a car carrying containers of flammable materials has crashed into the gate of the Russian Embassy, bursting into flames and killing the driver
Highlights The sedan rammed into the gate at about 6 a.m. Wednesday but did not enter the Bucharest embassy compound. Video of the aftermath showed the car engulfed in flames as security personnel ran through the area. The Russian embassy said no employees were injured and expressed condolences to the family of the driver.</description></item><item><title>‘The Flash’ actor Ezra Miller arrested on Hawaii Island after incident at karaoke bar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242dbfed7db214331be9f95/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 10:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242dbfed7db214331be9f95/</guid><description>Miller was arrested, charged and released after posting $500 bail.
Highlights Police say Ezra Miller grabbed the microphone from a 23-year-old woman mid-song. Police say Miller later lunged at a 32-year old man playing darts. Miller was arrested, charged and released after posting $500 bail. The actor was arrested and charged with disorderly conduct and harassment, police say. The arrest stemmed from an incident at a karaoke bar on Silva Street on Sunday, police said.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky mayoral candidate survives being targeted by a gunman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ac51b841d6a9187817cff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ac51b841d6a9187817cff/</guid><description>Craig Greenberg is unharmed after someone entered and fired shots at him. A suspect has been arrested.
Highlights Craig Greenberg was unharmed after being shot at him in his office. Suspect has been arrested in connection with the incident. Mr James James did not witness the incident himself but said he had spoken to staff in Mr Greenberg&amp;rsquo;s office shortly afterward. He said he did not see the incident but said staff in the office had been alerted to the shooting.</description></item><item><title>An American Airlines flight was diverted to Kansas City due to an 'unruly passenger'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209f34b2022a813384b0d08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209f34b2022a813384b0d08/</guid><description>An American Airlines flight was diverted to Kansas City International Airport in Missouri on Sunday afternoon because of &amp;quot;an unruly passenger,&amp;quot; the airline said in a statement.
Highlights Flight 1775 with service from Los Angeles (LAX) to Washington, D.C. diverted to Kansas City (MCI) due to an unruly passenger. The FBI confirmed the incident in a statement to CNN, adding the individual in question had been taken into custody. The flight landed safely at MCI at 2:28 p.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey plow driver who sprayed Orthodox Jews with snow during storm facing criminal probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</guid><description>The snow plow driver in Lakewood, New Jersey, who cast a wave of snow and ice from his plow onto two Orthodox Jewish men walking along a roadway has been suspended from his job and could face criminal charges, pending the outcome of a police investigation. Video of the act, which appears to have been intentional, was posted on social media. A passenger recorded the video with his phone as the driver approached the two men walking along County Line Road near the Jackson Township border.</description></item><item><title>John Kuczwanski killed in Tallahassee road rage incident</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3d0c94a3c147d9f63256e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 08:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3d0c94a3c147d9f63256e/</guid><description>Kuczwanski was arrested for a separate road rage incident at the same intersection in 2014.
Summary John Kuczwanski, the Legislative Affairs Director for the State Board of Administration, was killed in a shootout triggered by a road rage incident in north Tallahassee. The sources said the incident began after Kuczwanski’s BMW drifted out of its lane while heading north on Thomasville Road. The Prius’ driver then returned to his car to wait for law enforcement’s arrival after confronting Kuczwanski.</description></item></channel></rss>