<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>female on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/female/</link><description>Recent content in female on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:15:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/female/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Birth of second wolfpack litter to Colorado's naturally migrating wolves expected soon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f1845d1718cf901b44880/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f1845d1718cf901b44880/</guid><description>State wildlife officials said there is no sign yet of pups being born to the Jackson County pack. Wolves have pups mid-April through mid-May.
Highlights The team will attempt to find the best potential for each other at the center of the study. The study is called &amp;ldquo;vibrant&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;thoroughly researched&amp;rdquo; by the team of researchers from Colorado, Montana and New Mexico. The team must complete the study before giving birth in early June.</description></item><item><title>Jackson confirmed as first Black female high court justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f46293f1eb44866a7eef0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f46293f1eb44866a7eef0/</guid><description>The Senate confirmed Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Thursday, shattering a historic barrier by securing her place as the first Black female justice.
Highlights The Senate confirmed Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Thursday. She will take her seat when Justice Stephen Breyer retires this summer, solidifying the liberal wing of the 6-3 conservative-dominated court. Jackson will be just the third Black justice, after Thurgood Marshall and Clarence Thomas.</description></item><item><title>Black female WWII unit recognized with congressional honor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dd62e05407eb0b7a77687/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 08:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dd62e05407eb0b7a77687/</guid><description>BOSTON (AP) — The House voted Monday to award the only all-female, Black unit to serve in Europe during World War II with the Congressional Gold Medal. The 422-0 vote follows a long-running campaign to recognize the 6888th Central Postal Directory Battalion.
Highlights The 6888th Central Central. Central. Center for the New York Democratic Rep. Brian Higgins, who sponsored the. post office bill, was given the “Indiana. Hunt-Martin” after veteran Indiana.</description></item></channel></rss>