<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>election on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/election/</link><description>Recent content in election on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records were subpoenaed by House Jan. 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</guid><description>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol.
Summary My Pillow CEO Michael Lindell is seen outside the door of the West Wing at the White House on Friday, Jan 15, 2021 in Washington, DC. MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, an ally of former President Donald Trump, said his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the origins of the deadly riot that took place on Jan.</description></item><item><title>4th resident of The Villages arrested for allegedly casting multiple ballots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6313e0353c8342089944f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6313e0353c8342089944f/</guid><description>A fourth resident of The Villages has been arrested for allegedly casting multiple ballots in the 2020 election.
Summary THE VILLAGES, Fla. – A fourth resident of The Villages has been arrested as part of an ongoing investigation into voter fraud. Voter registration records show Barnes was not affiliated with a political party in Florida when he voted in the 2020 election. Barnes was also registered to vote in his original home state of Connecticut in 2020, records show.</description></item></channel></rss>