<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>election on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/election/</link><description>Recent content in election on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Australia election: conservative government voted out after nearly a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62890eee438ffbdadf2ff675/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62890eee438ffbdadf2ff675/</guid><description>Anthony Albanese’s Labor party defeats the ruling Coalition, but may lack the numbers to form majority government
Highlights Australia&amp;rsquo;s rightwing Coalition government has lost power after nearly a decade in office. Liberal leader Scott Morrison conceded defeat and announced he would step down as leader of his party. The biggest surprise of the night was the surge in support for the Greens. But Labor opposition failed to sweep to power in its own right, winning just 31.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis signs bill creating new Florida election police force</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267444b833797860a701fbe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 01:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267444b833797860a701fbe/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the latest controversial law signed by the Florida Republican in recent days.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signs a new election police force. Florida is one of the first states in the country with a unit focused on election fraud. The new law marks the second major overhaul of Florida&amp;rsquo;s election laws since the 2020 election. It&amp;rsquo;s the latest controversial law signed by the Florida GOP governor in recent days, including two bills that target Disney and legislation that imposes restrictions on how schools and businesses can talk about race and gender.</description></item><item><title>Viktor Orban, Hungary's authoritarian leader, calls Zelensky an 'opponent' after winning reelection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a8d3873d0c22a5474ee06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 06:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a8d3873d0c22a5474ee06/</guid><description>Hungary&amp;rsquo;s authoritarian leader and longtime Russian ally, Viktor Orban, has declared victory in the country&amp;rsquo;s parliamentary elections, clinching a fourth consecutive term in power.
Highlights Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Fidesz party had a commanding lead with 71% of the votes counted. The election campaign was dominated by Moscow&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Hungary is heavily reliant on Russian energy and Orban has dodged opportunities to condemn Putin&amp;rsquo;s assault on its neighboring state. Opposition leader Peter Marki-Zay even failed to win in his own district, where he had served as mayor in the previous district.</description></item><item><title>Federal judge blocks Florida restrictive voting law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246d0a4218d330f871ce3ff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246d0a4218d330f871ce3ff/</guid><description>A federal judge barred Florida from enforcing the bulk of its new restrictive voting law on Thursday, siding with advocates who said the law was discriminatory.
Highlights A federal judge declared the bulk of Florida&amp;rsquo;s new voting rules unconstitutional and issued a permanent injunction barring their enforcement. The Florida law, known as Senate Bill 90, added new restrictions on drop boxes, third-party voter registration, mail voting, and &amp;ldquo;line warming&amp;rdquo; activities like giving voters food and water while they wait in line to cast a ballot.</description></item><item><title>Ginni Thomas, Justice Clarence Thomas' wife, exchanged texts with Mark Meadows about efforts to overturn the 2020 election</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d42381b75583fed9e97c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d42381b75583fed9e97c5/</guid><description>CBS News and The Washington Post have obtained copies of numerous text messages exchanged between Thomas and Trump&amp;rsquo;s White House chief of staff.
Highlights Virginia Thomas, a conservative activist married to Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas, repeatedly pressed White House chief of staff Mark Meadows to pursue efforts to overturn the 2020 presidential election. Among Thomas&amp;rsquo; stated goals in the messages was for lawyer Sidney Powell, who promoted incendiary and unsupported claims about the election, to become &amp;ldquo;the lead and the face&amp;rdquo; of Trump&amp;rsquo;s legal team.</description></item><item><title>Debra Meadows appears to have filed three false voter forms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c0ca7e358639258f7c5d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 06:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c0ca7e358639258f7c5d3/</guid><description>&amp;quot;What we do know is a number of times as we have mail-in ballots, if there is not a chain&amp;hellip;
Highlights Mark Meadows, then White House chief of staff, is under investigation for potential voter fraud in 2020. Mark and Debra Meadows submitted voter registration forms that listed as their home a mobile home with a rusted metal roof that sold for $105,000 in 2021, even though they had never lived there.</description></item><item><title>Smartmatic can pursue election-rigging claims against Fox News, Giuliani</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</guid><description>A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming that Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.S. presidential election to favor Democrat Joe Biden.
Highlights A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.</description></item><item><title>Reuters wins Polk Award for series on intimidation of U.S. election workers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62149bd925ba5d1c613288b7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62149bd925ba5d1c613288b7/</guid><description>The staff of Reuters has received a George Polk Award for its coverage of widespread intimidation of U.S. election workers by supporters of former President Donald Trump.
Highlights The staff of Reuters has received a George Polk Award for its coverage of widespread intimidation of U.S. election workers by supporters of former President Donald Trump. The prestigious Polk Awards, presented by Long Island University in the United States, honor special achievement in journalism.</description></item><item><title>'We're done. This is the end of the 2020 election': Maricopa County officials rebut error-plagued review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</guid><description>Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election.
Summary (CNN) Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election . Presenting the rebuttal to the Maricopa County Board of Supervisors in a four-hour meeting Wednesday, county elections officials said that 76 of the 77 claims made in the Cyber Ninjas report were false or misleading.</description></item><item><title>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records were subpoenaed by House Jan. 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</guid><description>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol.
Summary My Pillow CEO Michael Lindell is seen outside the door of the West Wing at the White House on Friday, Jan 15, 2021 in Washington, DC. MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, an ally of former President Donald Trump, said his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the origins of the deadly riot that took place on Jan.</description></item><item><title>4th resident of The Villages arrested for allegedly casting multiple ballots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6313e0353c8342089944f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6313e0353c8342089944f/</guid><description>A fourth resident of The Villages has been arrested for allegedly casting multiple ballots in the 2020 election.
Summary THE VILLAGES, Fla. – A fourth resident of The Villages has been arrested as part of an ongoing investigation into voter fraud. Voter registration records show Barnes was not affiliated with a political party in Florida when he voted in the 2020 election. Barnes was also registered to vote in his original home state of Connecticut in 2020, records show.</description></item></channel></rss>