<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>drunk on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/drunk/</link><description>Recent content in drunk on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 20:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/drunk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police: Drunk driver crashes, heads straight to dealership to try to sell damaged car with missing tire</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62967654b817b260a51cfd60/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62967654b817b260a51cfd60/</guid><description>Police say they arrested a driver who was 3.5 times the legal alcohol limit after at least five people called 911.
Highlights Police say they arrested a driver who was 3.5 times the legal alcohol limit after at least five people called 911. The calls started coming in around 4:40 p.m. Monday. Police say witnesses reported seeing a SUV hit the median of the Lloyd Expressway. They say the crash caused a flat tire and the car to smoke, but the driver kept going.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson's staff got drunk, brawled and abused cleaners during Covid lockdowns, damning report finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fa6bae579c9652352d1f9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fa6bae579c9652352d1f9/</guid><description>Parties that went on until the early hours of the morning. Drunken staff vomiting and fighting with each other. Downing Street walls stained with red wine. And an illegal birthday party for Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prime Minister, complete with six-packs of beer and dozens of sandwiches.
Highlights British Prime Minister Boris Johnson facing a battle to save his premiership after a new report criticizes a culture of rule-breaking events. Report published on Wednesday by senior civil servant Sue Gray criticized a culture that allowed the parties to take place.</description></item></channel></rss>