<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>public on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/public/</link><description>Recent content in public on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 07:13:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biden Administration to cancel $6 billion worth of student loan debt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c47dd8702bfd6a3f7f12e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c47dd8702bfd6a3f7f12e/</guid><description>The Biden administration is canceling more than $6 billion worth of federal student debt.
Highlights The Biden Administration is canceling more than $6 billion worth of federal student debt. 100,000 people are eligible for the ‘Forgiveness Program’ The program was launched 15 years ago, but has been changed in October. Some have until October to apply for the forgiveness program, which means they have until November 1 to get their debt back on the books.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds of US geographic sites to be renamed to eliminate offensive words</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</guid><description>A task force will prioritize a list of replacement names and present them to the federal Board on Geographic Names later this year
Highlights US officials have come up with a list of potential replacement names for hundreds of geographic sites in three dozen states. The list includes more than 660 sites in New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada, California, Idaho and many other states. US Interior secretary Deb Haaland in November formally declared the term “squaw’s derogatory and initiated a process to remove the word from use by the federal government and to replace other derogatory place names.</description></item><item><title>Anthony Fauci says ‘full-blown pandemic phase’ of COVID is ending</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62058d959c6b4d3e4ae5d1c4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62058d959c6b4d3e4ae5d1c4/</guid><description>White House’s chief medical adviser Dr. Anthony Fauci said he believes the “full-blown pandemic phase” of COVID-19 is beginning to end. He said the coming months would bring an end
Highlights Dr. Anthony Fauci said he believes the “full-blown pandemic phase” of COVID-19 is beginning to end. The White House’s chief medical adviser predicted a period in which immunity and treatments would together help make the virus more manageable. He said he would not call the virus “endemic,” but that it would instead reach a stage of “equilibrium” in which government leaders did not have to monitor infection levels as closely.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma National Guard members can’t sue anonymously over COVID-19 vaccine mandate, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff74d04b7a6aefc2747021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 07:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff74d04b7a6aefc2747021/</guid><description>The state of Oklahoma argued that naming the Guard members challenging the federal COVID vaccine mandate could expose them to a range of harms.
Highlights Oklahoma National Guard members can&amp;rsquo;t sue anonymously over COVID-19 vaccine mandate, judge rules. Governor, attorney general and 16 unnamed Guard members filed a lawsuit in December seeking to block the mandate. Judge rules that the public interest overrides concerns about privacy or personal safety. Guard members say they are willing to make their names known to the court and to the U.</description></item><item><title>France passes law to exclude unvaccinated people from public places</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6f23d58b2711d84245870/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6f23d58b2711d84245870/</guid><description>Up until now, a Covid-19 pass has been required in France to go to public sites throughout the country, but unvaccinated people have been allowed in if they show a negative test or proof of recent recovery.
Summary The French parliament has approved a law that will exclude unvaccinated people from all restaurants, sports areas, tourist sites and even trains. Left wing politician François Ruffin said the vaccine pass made unvaccinated people &amp;lsquo;second class citizens&amp;rsquo; and asked &amp;lsquo;what have you done with our souls?</description></item><item><title>No vaccine, no French Open for Djokovic, says French Sports ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5849cf8817b6581d9da0c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 15:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5849cf8817b6581d9da0c/</guid><description>Novak Djokovic could be barred from playing in the French Open as things stand now after the Sports Ministry said on Monday there would be no exemption from France&amp;rsquo;s new vaccine pass law.
Summary Serbian tennis player Novak Djokovic walks in Melbourne Airport before boarding a flight, after the Federal Court upheld a government decision to cancel his visa to play in the Australian Open, in Melbourne, Australia, January 16, 2022.</description></item><item><title>New York governor declares racism 'public health emergency' amid new anti-discrimination legislation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</guid><description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul declared racism a public health emergency and has implemented new laws to combat discrimination.
Summary Kathy Hochul has declared racism a &amp;ldquo;public health crisis,&amp;rdquo; signing an entire package of legislation Dec. 23 aimed at addressing discrimination and racial injustice in the state. &amp;ldquo;For far too long, communities of color in New York have been held back by systemic racism and inequitable treatment,&amp;rdquo; Hochul said in a statement last week.</description></item><item><title>Chinese companies vanish from world's top 10 by market cap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</guid><description>Description TOKYO &amp;ndash; Tencent Holdings and Alibaba Group Holding have dropped out of the global top 10 companies in market capitalization, new data shows, leaving
Summary Alibaba Group Holding founder Jack Ma, then executive chairman, celebrates at the New York Stock Exchange on Sept. 19, 2014, the day that the company held its initial public offering and began trading there. © Getty ImagesMANAMI OGAWA, Nikkei staff writer READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>