<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>public on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/public/</link><description>Recent content in public on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 15:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>No vaccine, no French Open for Djokovic, says French Sports ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5849cf8817b6581d9da0c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 15:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5849cf8817b6581d9da0c/</guid><description>Novak Djokovic could be barred from playing in the French Open as things stand now after the Sports Ministry said on Monday there would be no exemption from France&amp;rsquo;s new vaccine pass law.
Summary Serbian tennis player Novak Djokovic walks in Melbourne Airport before boarding a flight, after the Federal Court upheld a government decision to cancel his visa to play in the Australian Open, in Melbourne, Australia, January 16, 2022.</description></item><item><title>New York governor declares racism 'public health emergency' amid new anti-discrimination legislation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</guid><description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul declared racism a public health emergency and has implemented new laws to combat discrimination.
Summary Kathy Hochul has declared racism a &amp;ldquo;public health crisis,&amp;rdquo; signing an entire package of legislation Dec. 23 aimed at addressing discrimination and racial injustice in the state. &amp;ldquo;For far too long, communities of color in New York have been held back by systemic racism and inequitable treatment,&amp;rdquo; Hochul said in a statement last week.</description></item><item><title>Chinese companies vanish from world's top 10 by market cap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</guid><description>Description TOKYO &amp;ndash; Tencent Holdings and Alibaba Group Holding have dropped out of the global top 10 companies in market capitalization, new data shows, leaving
Summary Alibaba Group Holding founder Jack Ma, then executive chairman, celebrates at the New York Stock Exchange on Sept. 19, 2014, the day that the company held its initial public offering and began trading there. © Getty ImagesMANAMI OGAWA, Nikkei staff writer READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>