<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>public on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/public/</link><description>Recent content in public on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:09:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. to phase out single-use plastic on public lands, national parks by 2032</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a12c07580efa5cde5ba9ba/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a12c07580efa5cde5ba9ba/</guid><description>The U.S. Interior Department said on Wednesday it will phase out single-use plastic products on public lands by 2032, including in national parks, in a move aimed at tackling a major source of U.S. plastic waste as recycling efforts falter.
Highlights Interior Department to phase out single-use plastic products on public lands by 2032. Move aimed at tackling major source of U.S. plastic waste as recycling efforts falter. Announcement comes as part of a broader package of announcements from Biden administration to recognize World Ocean Day.</description></item><item><title>Gun makers lose challenge to New York law allowing lawsuits against industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293e0d4532a6e812a4117f8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293e0d4532a6e812a4117f8/</guid><description>A federal judge threw out a lawsuit by a group of gun manufacturers, distributors and retailers challenging the constitutionality of a New York law.
Highlights A federal judge threw out a lawsuit by a group of gun manufacturers, distributors and retailers challenging the constitutionality of a New York law. The law allows the state and people affected by gun violence to sue the industry. The National Shooting Sports Foundation argued the law wrongly imposes liability on companies operating anywhere in the country that make, sell or market guns or ammunition that are misused by criminals in New York.</description></item><item><title>Endangered sea turtle nest found at Galveston Island State Park for the first time in a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c498be90b4095e8c123a3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 02:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c498be90b4095e8c123a3/</guid><description>The nest contained more than one hundred eggs laid by a Kemp’s Ridley Sea Turtle &amp;ndash; one of the most endangered sea turtle species in the world.
Highlights The nest contained more than one hundred eggs laid by a Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Ridley sea turtle. Kemp&amp;rsquo;s is one of the most endangered sea turtle species in the world. The species was almost lost in the 1980s until intensive conservation efforts were implemented on nesting beaches and through fisheries management.</description></item><item><title>Oregon sued over failure to provide public defenders | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283249f24a5fcb01d44172e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 04:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283249f24a5fcb01d44172e/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Criminal defendants in Oregon who have gone without legal representation for long periods of time amid a critical shortage of public defense attorneys filed a lawsuit Monday that alleges the state violated their constitutional right to legal counsel and a speedy trial.
Highlights Criminal defendants in Oregon who have gone without legal representation for long periods of time amid a critical shortage of public defense attorneys filed a lawsuit Monday.</description></item><item><title>Afghanistan: Taliban leader orders women to wear all-covering burqa in public: Decree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62769bac94efd22970e66069/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62769bac94efd22970e66069/</guid><description>Afghanistan’s supreme leader and Taliban chief on Saturday ordered the country’s women to wear the all-covering burqa in public - one of the harshest
Highlights Afghanistan&amp;rsquo;s supreme leader and Taliban chief orders women to wear all-covering burqa in public: Decree. Decree issued by Hibatullah Akhundzada that was released by Taliban authorities at a function in Kabul. It is one of the harshest controls imposed on women’s lives since Taliban seized power.</description></item><item><title>Nashville Public Library debuts limited edition 'I read banned books' library cards</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62735e5c6daa06ff0bb8b4eb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 05:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62735e5c6daa06ff0bb8b4eb/</guid><description>The debate over banned books in school libraries and classrooms has taken place across the country, even putting Tennessee under the national spotlight. Now the Nashville Public Library wants to ensure everyone has the &amp;lsquo;Freedom to Read&amp;rsquo;.
Highlights The Nashville Public Library wants to ensure everyone has the &amp;lsquo;Freedom to Read&amp;rsquo; The goal is to get the 5,000 limited edition library cards in the hands of new sign-ups this month. The debate over banned books in school libraries and classrooms has taken place across the country, even putting Tennessee under the national spotlight.</description></item><item><title>Germany will provide training and maintenance to Ukrainian military, foreign minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260771f926d2271050d0132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260771f926d2271050d0132/</guid><description>Germany will provide training and maintenance to the Ukrainian military, German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock said in Latvia Wednesday.
Highlights Germany will provide training and maintenance to the Ukrainian military, German foreign minister says. Annalena Baerbock said that Germany could not provide further weaponry as the country had no weapons it could “deliver quickly and without delay right now. Germany has chosen not to make public all the weapons it has previously sent to Ukraine, she said.</description></item><item><title>Official Age of Adulthood in Japan Lowered to 18</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</guid><description>The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. This makes it possible for 18- or 19-year-olds to sign a smartphone contract or take out a loan without parental consent, but also means that they need to take responsibility for such decisions.
Highlights The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. It means that 18- or 19-year-olds will be able to sign a contract for a smartphone or credit card, lease an apartment, or enter an expensive loan contract for an automobile or English conversation school, without parental consent.</description></item><item><title>Maryland’s last public Confederate monument removed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623004e7a92592caa2f2de9b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623004e7a92592caa2f2de9b/</guid><description>A statue that was thought to be the last Confederate monument on a courthouse lawn in Maryland has been removed.
Highlights The “Talbot Boys Statue’ was relocated Monday. The statue stood on the Talbot County courthouse lawn in Easton for more than a century. A coalition raised more than $80,000 to relocate it to a historic battlefield in Virginia. The sculpture features a boy holding a Confederate flag and names the men from the Eastern Shore county who joined the Confederacy and died in the war.</description></item><item><title>Biden Administration to cancel $6 billion worth of student loan debt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c47dd8702bfd6a3f7f12e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c47dd8702bfd6a3f7f12e/</guid><description>The Biden administration is canceling more than $6 billion worth of federal student debt.
Highlights The Biden Administration is canceling more than $6 billion worth of federal student debt. 100,000 people are eligible for the ‘Forgiveness Program’ The program was launched 15 years ago, but has been changed in October. Some have until October to apply for the forgiveness program, which means they have until November 1 to get their debt back on the books.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds of US geographic sites to be renamed to eliminate offensive words</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</guid><description>A task force will prioritize a list of replacement names and present them to the federal Board on Geographic Names later this year
Highlights US officials have come up with a list of potential replacement names for hundreds of geographic sites in three dozen states. The list includes more than 660 sites in New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada, California, Idaho and many other states. US Interior secretary Deb Haaland in November formally declared the term “squaw’s derogatory and initiated a process to remove the word from use by the federal government and to replace other derogatory place names.</description></item><item><title>Anthony Fauci says ‘full-blown pandemic phase’ of COVID is ending</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62058d959c6b4d3e4ae5d1c4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 22:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62058d959c6b4d3e4ae5d1c4/</guid><description>White House’s chief medical adviser Dr. Anthony Fauci said he believes the “full-blown pandemic phase” of COVID-19 is beginning to end. He said the coming months would bring an end
Highlights Dr. Anthony Fauci said he believes the “full-blown pandemic phase” of COVID-19 is beginning to end. The White House’s chief medical adviser predicted a period in which immunity and treatments would together help make the virus more manageable. He said he would not call the virus “endemic,” but that it would instead reach a stage of “equilibrium” in which government leaders did not have to monitor infection levels as closely.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma National Guard members can’t sue anonymously over COVID-19 vaccine mandate, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff74d04b7a6aefc2747021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 07:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff74d04b7a6aefc2747021/</guid><description>The state of Oklahoma argued that naming the Guard members challenging the federal COVID vaccine mandate could expose them to a range of harms.
Highlights Oklahoma National Guard members can&amp;rsquo;t sue anonymously over COVID-19 vaccine mandate, judge rules. Governor, attorney general and 16 unnamed Guard members filed a lawsuit in December seeking to block the mandate. Judge rules that the public interest overrides concerns about privacy or personal safety. Guard members say they are willing to make their names known to the court and to the U.</description></item><item><title>France passes law to exclude unvaccinated people from public places</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6f23d58b2711d84245870/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6f23d58b2711d84245870/</guid><description>Up until now, a Covid-19 pass has been required in France to go to public sites throughout the country, but unvaccinated people have been allowed in if they show a negative test or proof of recent recovery.
Summary The French parliament has approved a law that will exclude unvaccinated people from all restaurants, sports areas, tourist sites and even trains. Left wing politician François Ruffin said the vaccine pass made unvaccinated people &amp;lsquo;second class citizens&amp;rsquo; and asked &amp;lsquo;what have you done with our souls?</description></item><item><title>No vaccine, no French Open for Djokovic, says French Sports ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5849cf8817b6581d9da0c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 15:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5849cf8817b6581d9da0c/</guid><description>Novak Djokovic could be barred from playing in the French Open as things stand now after the Sports Ministry said on Monday there would be no exemption from France&amp;rsquo;s new vaccine pass law.
Summary Serbian tennis player Novak Djokovic walks in Melbourne Airport before boarding a flight, after the Federal Court upheld a government decision to cancel his visa to play in the Australian Open, in Melbourne, Australia, January 16, 2022.</description></item><item><title>New York governor declares racism 'public health emergency' amid new anti-discrimination legislation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</guid><description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul declared racism a public health emergency and has implemented new laws to combat discrimination.
Summary Kathy Hochul has declared racism a &amp;ldquo;public health crisis,&amp;rdquo; signing an entire package of legislation Dec. 23 aimed at addressing discrimination and racial injustice in the state. &amp;ldquo;For far too long, communities of color in New York have been held back by systemic racism and inequitable treatment,&amp;rdquo; Hochul said in a statement last week.</description></item><item><title>Chinese companies vanish from world's top 10 by market cap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</guid><description>Description TOKYO &amp;ndash; Tencent Holdings and Alibaba Group Holding have dropped out of the global top 10 companies in market capitalization, new data shows, leaving
Summary Alibaba Group Holding founder Jack Ma, then executive chairman, celebrates at the New York Stock Exchange on Sept. 19, 2014, the day that the company held its initial public offering and began trading there. © Getty ImagesMANAMI OGAWA, Nikkei staff writer READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>