<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>guns on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/guns/</link><description>Recent content in guns on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 13:45:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/guns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More guns are being stolen out of cars in alarming trend across the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a6c3c9148e73e81069aa2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 13:45:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a6c3c9148e73e81069aa2/</guid><description>More guns are being stolen out of vehicles in many U.S. cities, according to a new data analysis, which was first obtained and independently verified by NBC New
Highlights Everytown for Gun Safety analyzed FBI crime data from 2011 to 2020. At least 180 cities saw a rise in gun thefts from vehicles, the nonprofit says. It&amp;rsquo;s an alarming trend as shootings rise nationwide, propelled in large part by firearms obtained illegally.</description></item><item><title>Guns now leading cause of death among children and teenagers in US, data suggests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262d5908b84ea03312d5d80/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262d5908b84ea03312d5d80/</guid><description>More people aged one to 19 died from gun-related injuries in 2020 than in vehicle crashes or drugs overdoses, according to analysis of federal data by researchers at the University of Michigan.
Highlights More people aged one to 19 died from gun-related injuries in 2020 than in vehicle crashes or drugs overdoses, according to analysis of federal data by researchers at the University of Michigan. The figure includes suicides, homicides and unintentional deaths.</description></item><item><title>New federal rule requires serial numbers, background checks for ‘ghost gun’ kits</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254a82e3e45f1f08639f5d8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 22:14:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254a82e3e45f1f08639f5d8/</guid><description>The aim is to rein in privately made firearms without serial numbers. They&amp;rsquo;re increasingly cropping up at crime scenes across the U.S. The new rule requires homemade gun kits to be treated like other guns made and sold in the U
Highlights The Biden administration is expected to come out within days with its long-awaited ghost gun rule. The aim is to rein in privately made firearms without serial numbers. The rule requires homemade gun kits to be treated like other guns made and sold in the U.</description></item><item><title>US far-right podcaster charged after machine guns found in basement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083eb1f56717984e2c4926/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083eb1f56717984e2c4926/</guid><description>Joseph Paul Berger and his father, Joseph Raymond Berger, arrested last week and charged with multiple firearms offenses
Highlights Joseph Paul Berger, 32, and Joseph Raymond Berger, 67, charged with multiple firearms offenses. Federal prosecutors claim they found cache of weapons in locked basement at home in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania. Prosecutors claim he espouses strong anti-government and anti-law enforcement views. Joseph Berger goes by the moniker “GlockDoctor1488” – 1488 being a popular coded signal among neo-Nazi neo-Nazis, with “14” referencing the slogan “We must secure the existence of our people and a future for white children” and “Heil Hitler” in the Alt-Right Armory podcast.</description></item></channel></rss>