<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>killing on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/killing/</link><description>Recent content in killing on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 16:29:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/killing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israel will not hold criminal inquiry into killing of journalist Shireen Abu Aqleh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628670273b78ed211ef9d111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 16:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628670273b78ed211ef9d111/</guid><description>Military police say they are satisfied with assurances of Israeli troops over death of US-Palestinian despite international demands
Highlights Israel will not launch a criminal investigation into the killing of US-Palestinian journalist Shireen Abu Aqleh, which Palestinian officials and witnesses have blamed on Israeli soldiers. The Israeli military police branch has accepted assurances of Israeli troops that they were not aware she was in a village adjacent to the Jenin refugee camp when she was killed on 11 May.</description></item><item><title>Ex-cop pleads guilty to manslaughter in George Floyd killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285604b04b797a582783e3e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285604b04b797a582783e3e/</guid><description>A former Minneapolis police officer has pleaded guilty to a state charge of aiding and abetting second-degree manslaughter in the death of George Floyd
Highlights Thomas Lane pleads guilty to aiding and abetting second-degree manslaughter. He will avoid what could have been a lengthy state sentence if he was convicted of murder. Lane and two other officers have already been convicted on federal counts of willfully violating Floyd&amp;rsquo;s rights. The guilty plea comes a week before the two-year anniversary of Floyd’s May 25, 2020, killing.</description></item><item><title>Kyiv: Video shows Russian soldiers killing 2 civilians before they ransack a business</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d16a15e342270e8ee26f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 14:16:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d16a15e342270e8ee26f1/</guid><description>CNN has obtained surveillance video showing two men being shot in the back, in an incident now being investigated as a war crime by Ukrainian prosecutors.
Highlights Russian soldiers shot two unarmed civilians as they walked away after an encounter in the Ukrainian capital of Kyiv. CNN has obtained surveillance video of what is now being investigated as a war crime by Ukrainian prosecutors. One was the owner of the vehicle dealership that was looted, whose family does not want to be named.</description></item><item><title>Vermont man accused of killing mom, grandfather in attempt to get millions in inheritance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bac21884a163cd02193aa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:29:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bac21884a163cd02193aa/</guid><description>A 28-year-old Vermont man is accused of killing his grandfather to obtain trust fund money and later killing his mother while they were at sea for a purported
Highlights Nathan Carman, 28, is accused of killing his grandfather to obtain trust fund money. His mother, Linda, disappeared during a 2016 fishing trip on her son&amp;rsquo;s boat, prosecutors say. He is expected to be arraigned Wednesday in U.S. District Court in Rutland, Vermont.</description></item><item><title>Gabby Petito's parents sue Brian Laundrie's parents, claiming they knew of her killing and were helping son escape</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cf044f4b1dc96fc818b42/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 19:11:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cf044f4b1dc96fc818b42/</guid><description>Gabby Petito&amp;rsquo;s parents are suing Christopher and Roberta Laundrie, alleging they knew their son&amp;rsquo;s murder and were working to help him flee the country. The lawsuit lists blunt force injuries to her head and neck as well as
Highlights Family of Gabby Petito has filed a civil lawsuit against Christopher and Roberta Laundrie. The lawsuit alleges the Laundries knew their son&amp;rsquo;s murder and were working to help him flee the country.</description></item><item><title>3 officers found guilty on federal charges in George Floyd’s killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218393e9285cd3dae3fde40/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218393e9285cd3dae3fde40/</guid><description>A federal jury has reached a verdict in the trial of three former Minneapolis police officers charged with violating the civil rights of George Floyd.
Highlights Three Minneapolis police officers convicted of violating civil rights of George Floyd. Floyd&amp;rsquo;s brother: &amp;ldquo;It can never be justice because I can never get George back&amp;rdquo; Former officers J. Alexander Kueng, Thomas Lane and Tou Thao found guilty of depriving Floyd of his civil rights.</description></item><item><title>SoCal man gets life for killing 2 women with meat cleaver as wife, son waited in car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffbc230f72e3b3986275c5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffbc230f72e3b3986275c5/</guid><description>Christopher Ken Ireland killed two women with a meat cleaver after a New Year’s Eve party in 2017 while his wife and son waited in a car outside. He was sentenced Friday to life in prison without the possibility of parole.
Highlights Christopher Ken Ireland killed two women with a meat cleaver after a New Year’s Eve party in 2017 while his wife and 11-year-old son waited in a car outside.</description></item></channel></rss>