<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>harris on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/harris/</link><description>Recent content in harris on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:17:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/harris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Estranged husband shot wife, 4-year-old daughter, mother-in-law before killing himself, sheriff says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287cd0be0040f439efdbe12/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287cd0be0040f439efdbe12/</guid><description>The Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office is investigating a shooting with at least four people dead. Murder-suicide may be involved.
Highlights NEW: Harris County Sheriff Ed Gonzalez says the man appeared to have shot his wife and his mother-in-law before turning the gun on himself. NEW: The husband and wife were going through a divorce in recent months, and there were reports of the man being abusive to his 4-year-old daughter, the sheriff says.</description></item><item><title>Vice President Kamala Harris tests positive for Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268606c938e436982988a0c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268606c938e436982988a0c/</guid><description>Vice President Kamala Harris tested positive for Covid-19 on Tuesday after returning from a weeklong trip to California.
Highlights Vice President Joe Biden last tested negative for Covid-19 on Monday, White House says. Vice President Harris tested positive for the disease on both rapid and rapid tests, official says. Democratic Sens. Chris Murphy and Ron Wyden also tested positive on Tuesday. Senate Democrats had hoped to confirm Lisa Cook and Alvaro Bedoya to the Federal Reserve Board.</description></item></channel></rss>