<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>department on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/department/</link><description>Recent content in department on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 23:09:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/department/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Militia member believed to have shot and killed a former judge in Juneau County; sources say suspect hit list included Governor Evers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629be5eb7b17bb4c90916d83/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 23:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629be5eb7b17bb4c90916d83/</guid><description>Douglas K. Uhde, 56, is being identified as the shooter in the case. A hit list was recovered as well in the suspects vehicle which included Wisconsin Governor Tony Evers and Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer. The victim was
Highlights Douglas K. Uhde, 56, is being identified as the shooter in the case. He was found in the basement of the home of former Juneau County Judge John Roemer. The victim was found dead and the suspect was taken to the hospital where he remains in critical condition.</description></item><item><title>Grandfather, 4 grandchildren killed by escaped Texas inmate are identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bd7d209442298c44c1ea2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 22:08:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bd7d209442298c44c1ea2/</guid><description>The Texas family killed by an escaped inmate was identified as a 66-year-old man and his four grandchildren, authorities said.
Highlights The victims were Mark Collins, 66; Waylon Collins, 18; Carson Collins, 16; Carson. Carson, 16, Hudson, 11; and Bryson Collins, 11. Gonzalo Lopez, 46, had no connection to the family, authorities say. Lopez was a convicted murderer who escaped on May 12 after stabbing a prison bus driver in the hand and fleeing on foot after the vehicle went off the road.</description></item><item><title>78,000 pounds of infant formula arrives in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b5d77a2a6b703f4225660/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b5d77a2a6b703f4225660/</guid><description>The White House says enough specialty infant formula for more than half a million baby bottles is about to arrive in the United States from Europe.
Highlights NEW: White House announces two new Defense Production Act authorizations for infant formula. Air Force plane carrying enough infant formula for more than half a million bottles arrives in Indianapolis. The White House says 1.5 million 8-ounce bottles of the three formulas are expected to arrive this week.</description></item><item><title>Possible case of monkeypox reported in Broward County, FL</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b4f8204451c4136d6be53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b4f8204451c4136d6be53/</guid><description>A “presumptive” case of monkeypox is being investigated in South Florida, state health officials say. The case appears to be related to international travel, the Florida Department of Health in Broward County says. The person
Highlights A “presumptive” case of monkeypox is being investigated in South Florida, state health officials say. The case appears to be related to international travel, and the risk to the community is low, they say. As of Friday, there were 80 confirmed cases worldwide, including at least two in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Indiana firefighter killed when stranded motorist he stopped to help opened fire, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289e19826ed64cf3abb186d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289e19826ed64cf3abb186d/</guid><description>A firefighter was fatally shot and an officer was injured when a stranded motorist they stopped to help opened fire, Indiana State Police said.
Highlights Incident unfolded shortly before 9:30 p.m. Monday on SR 135 just south of Palmyra, Indiana. A firefighter was fatally shot and an officer was injured when a stranded motorist they stopped to help opened fire. The motorist, identified as Justin Moore of Owensboro, Kentucky, also died after he was shot by the officer.</description></item><item><title>Bird flu makes jump to mammals: three baby foxes die in Michigan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281dee89b5ad7acaa7c391c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 05:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281dee89b5ad7acaa7c391c/</guid><description>Three red fox kits died from highly pathogenic avian influenza in Michigan, which is the state&amp;rsquo;s first confirmation of the virus in wild mammals. The fox kits came from three separate dens in Lapeer, Macomb and St. Clair counties.
Highlights Three red fox kits died from highly pathogenic avian influenza in Michigan. This is the state&amp;rsquo;s first confirmation of the virus in wild mammals. The kits were observed circling, tremoring and seizing.</description></item><item><title>An off-duty officer put his knee on a 12-year-old girl’s neck to break up a school fight. The girl is now being charged</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e13c1f322b805e2d8985e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 08:16:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e13c1f322b805e2d8985e/</guid><description>Back in March, an off-duty police officer was seen on video putting his knee on the neck of a 12-year-old girl in Kenosha, Wisconsin, for more than 20 seconds in an attempt to break up a school fight.
Highlights A 12-year-old girl is being criminally charged with disorderly conduct, her family attorney says. The full contents of the criminal complaint were not immediately available because she is a minor. The charge comes three months after video showed two students in a fight at Lincoln Middle School in Kenosha, Wisconsin.</description></item><item><title>Justice Department files challenge to Alabama transgender law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d29a8548737dfba693dd7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d29a8548737dfba693dd7/</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Justice on Friday challenged an Alabama law making it a felony for doctors to treat transgender people under age 19 with puberty-blockers and hormones to help affirm their new gender identity.
Highlights The Justice Department filed a motion seeking to intervene in an ongoing lawsuit challenging the law as unconstitutional and seeking to block it from taking effect on May 8. The department sent a letter to all 50 state attorneys general warning that blocking transgender and nonbinary youth from receiving gender-affirming care could be an infringement of federal constitutional protections.</description></item><item><title>Houston Police: Woman shoots ex when he shows up with new girlfriend to child custody exchange</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62590def26affbddb9ca6bf4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62590def26affbddb9ca6bf4/</guid><description>According to investigators, Harris and the man were in a prior dating relationship and have two children together when the victim was bringing on the children back from a visit and had his current girlfriend in the car.
Highlights Keshante Shamirra Harris, 27, is charged with aggravated robbery with a deadly weapon and deadly conduct. Harris and Aaron Konte Williams were in a prior dating relationship and have two children together.</description></item><item><title>In Bizarre Robbery, 60-Foot Bridge Stolen In Bihar, India</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62526737239ed08cc0421b16/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62526737239ed08cc0421b16/</guid><description>A gang of thieves haspulled off an extraordinary heist by stealing a 60-foot abandoned bridge in Bihar&amp;rsquo;s Rohtas district in broad daylight.
Highlights Thieves used gas cutters and earthmover machines to demolish the bridge in Bihar&amp;rsquo;s Rohtas district. The bridge was built over the Ara canal in Amiyavar around 1972. Arshad Kamal Shamshi, a junior engineer of the irrigation department, said that the villagers informed them that some people pretending as irrigation department officials had uprooted the bridge using machines like JCB and gas-cutters.</description></item><item><title>On-duty police officer accused of selling cocaine from patrol car, DEA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e0f79c3c4ea5693f6f939/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 12:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e0f79c3c4ea5693f6f939/</guid><description>According to the Drug Enforcement Administration, Kevin Rodriguez, 33 with the Raleigh Police Department, allegedly met with a confidential source for a drug exchange on Jan. 24, 2022.
Highlights Kevin Rodriguez, 33, with the Raleigh Police Department, allegedly met with a confidential source for a drug exchange on Jan. 24, 2022. The DEA said the confidential source gave Rodriguez $2,600 in cash for about 56 grams of cocaine. Rodriguez faces a mandatory minimum penalty of 5 years in prison if convicted, and a maximum of life in prison.</description></item><item><title>Woman attacked with hammer in New York subway station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</guid><description>A 57-year-old woman was hit in the head with a hammer several times and robbed in one of the latest violent crimes in a New York subway station, police said.
Highlights The woman&amp;rsquo;s family identified her as Nina Rothschild, a scientist for the New York City Department of Health. She was attacked about 11 p.m. Thursday by a 6-foot tall male wearing a dark jacket, bluejeans and holding a cane, police say.</description></item><item><title>South Lake Tahoe police say calls about massive bear Hank the Tank are disrupting operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218652706e83fbe08484056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218652706e83fbe08484056/</guid><description>South Lake Tahoe police have had it with people calling about the 500-pound bear nicknamed &amp;quot;Hank the Tank.&amp;quot;
Highlights Bear nicknamed Hank the Tank is known in the area for breaking into homes and eating people&amp;rsquo;s food. The 500-pound bear is being blamed for dozens of break-ins since last July. South Lake Tahoe police say they&amp;rsquo;re getting so many calls, it&amp;rsquo;s affecting their ability to take real emergency calls. The department says they have no say in what happens to Hank.</description></item><item><title>U.S. agency refers 80 unruly airplane passengers for potential prosecution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 04:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</guid><description>A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Wednesday, as onboard disruptions rose sharply in 2021, many over COVID-19 mask requirements.
Highlights A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday. The Justice Department said Wednesday it was prosecuting a record number of passengers for interfering with flight crews.</description></item><item><title>US suspends Mexican avocado imports on eve of Super Bowl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620990356b835a0817e10827/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 23:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620990356b835a0817e10827/</guid><description>MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico has acknowledged that the U.S. government has suspended all imports of Mexican avocados after a U.S. plant safety inspector in Mexico received a threat. The surprise suspension was confirmed late Saturday on the eve of the Super Bowl, the biggest sales opportunity of the year for Mexican avocado growers — though it would not affect game-day consumption since those avocados had already been shipped.
Highlights Mexico has acknowledged that the U.</description></item><item><title>White father and son charged for chasing and shooting at Black FedEx driver</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 07:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</guid><description>Two White men are facing criminal charges after a Black FedEx Express driver alleged that he was chased and shot at while delivering packages in Brookhaven, Mississippi.
Highlights D&amp;rsquo;Monterrio Gibson, 24, says he was delivering packages to a home when he was shot at. He says he heard &amp;ldquo;at least five shots and heard the bullets hitting the van,&amp;rdquo; police report says. Two men have been charged with conspiracy and shooting into a vehicle.</description></item><item><title>The unvaccinated are now forbidden to use public transportation in the Philippines starting tomorrow</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e479a4d7f61f495c257432/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e479a4d7f61f495c257432/</guid><description>Summary The Department of Transportation (DOTr) and its attached agencies are all geared up to implement the “No Vaccination, No Ride” policy in all public transportation to, from, and within Metro Manila starting Monday, Jan. 17. (Ali Vicoy / MANILA BULLETIN)The railway, road, maritime, and aviation sectors have issued the guidelines for the implementation of Department Order No. 2022–001 which prohibits unvaccinated individuals from using public transportation in the National Capital Region (NCR).</description></item><item><title>Neo-Nazi leader sentenced to 7 years for plot to intimidate Jews, journalists</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</guid><description>A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison.
Summary A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison. The man, Kaleb Cole, 25, the former leader of the Neo-Nazi group Atomwaffen Division, was convicted in September of conspiracy, mailing threatening communications and interfering with a federally protected activity, the Justice Department said in a statement Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>2021 ends as Chicago's deadliest year in a quarter century</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1a1fae52d831bd5ce5081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1a1fae52d831bd5ce5081/</guid><description>CHICAGO (AP) — The year of 2021 ended as one of the most violent on record in Chicago, as a rise in the number of shootings left more people dead than in any single year in a quarter century, according to statistics released by the police department on Saturday.
Summary French was killed and her partner was seriously wounded during an Aug. 7 traffic stop on the city&amp;rsquo;s South Side. The year 2021 ended as one of the deadliest on record in recent years in Chicago, according to statistics released by the city&amp;rsquo;s police department on Saturday, Jan.</description></item><item><title>Virginia AG sues town where police threatened Black Army lieutenant during stop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</guid><description>Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.
Summary Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging Thursday that the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.</description></item><item><title>COVID-positive Vermonters with no symptoms clog up ERs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8838b26f38c72e71ab4ef/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8838b26f38c72e71ab4ef/</guid><description>Some Vermonters who are able to find antigen tests and then test positive are clogging up emergency rooms.
Summary RUTLAND, Vt. (WCAX) - Some Vermonters who are able to find antigen tests and then test positive are clogging up emergency rooms. He says some people who test positive with a rapid test go to the emergency room looking for a PCR test. He says the only time to go to the ER is if you have a positive test and are very sick.</description></item></channel></rss>