<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>department on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/department/</link><description>Recent content in department on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 05:12:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/department/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>South Lake Tahoe police say calls about massive bear Hank the Tank are disrupting operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218652706e83fbe08484056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218652706e83fbe08484056/</guid><description>South Lake Tahoe police have had it with people calling about the 500-pound bear nicknamed &amp;quot;Hank the Tank.&amp;quot;
Highlights Bear nicknamed Hank the Tank is known in the area for breaking into homes and eating people&amp;rsquo;s food. The 500-pound bear is being blamed for dozens of break-ins since last July. South Lake Tahoe police say they&amp;rsquo;re getting so many calls, it&amp;rsquo;s affecting their ability to take real emergency calls. The department says they have no say in what happens to Hank.</description></item><item><title>U.S. agency refers 80 unruly airplane passengers for potential prosecution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 04:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</guid><description>A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Wednesday, as onboard disruptions rose sharply in 2021, many over COVID-19 mask requirements.
Highlights A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday. The Justice Department said Wednesday it was prosecuting a record number of passengers for interfering with flight crews.</description></item><item><title>US suspends Mexican avocado imports on eve of Super Bowl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620990356b835a0817e10827/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 23:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620990356b835a0817e10827/</guid><description>MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico has acknowledged that the U.S. government has suspended all imports of Mexican avocados after a U.S. plant safety inspector in Mexico received a threat. The surprise suspension was confirmed late Saturday on the eve of the Super Bowl, the biggest sales opportunity of the year for Mexican avocado growers — though it would not affect game-day consumption since those avocados had already been shipped.
Highlights Mexico has acknowledged that the U.</description></item><item><title>White father and son charged for chasing and shooting at Black FedEx driver</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 07:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</guid><description>Two White men are facing criminal charges after a Black FedEx Express driver alleged that he was chased and shot at while delivering packages in Brookhaven, Mississippi.
Highlights D&amp;rsquo;Monterrio Gibson, 24, says he was delivering packages to a home when he was shot at. He says he heard &amp;ldquo;at least five shots and heard the bullets hitting the van,&amp;rdquo; police report says. Two men have been charged with conspiracy and shooting into a vehicle.</description></item><item><title>The unvaccinated are now forbidden to use public transportation in the Philippines starting tomorrow</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e479a4d7f61f495c257432/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e479a4d7f61f495c257432/</guid><description>Summary The Department of Transportation (DOTr) and its attached agencies are all geared up to implement the “No Vaccination, No Ride” policy in all public transportation to, from, and within Metro Manila starting Monday, Jan. 17. (Ali Vicoy / MANILA BULLETIN)The railway, road, maritime, and aviation sectors have issued the guidelines for the implementation of Department Order No. 2022–001 which prohibits unvaccinated individuals from using public transportation in the National Capital Region (NCR).</description></item><item><title>Neo-Nazi leader sentenced to 7 years for plot to intimidate Jews, journalists</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</guid><description>A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison.
Summary A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison. The man, Kaleb Cole, 25, the former leader of the Neo-Nazi group Atomwaffen Division, was convicted in September of conspiracy, mailing threatening communications and interfering with a federally protected activity, the Justice Department said in a statement Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>2021 ends as Chicago's deadliest year in a quarter century</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1a1fae52d831bd5ce5081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1a1fae52d831bd5ce5081/</guid><description>CHICAGO (AP) — The year of 2021 ended as one of the most violent on record in Chicago, as a rise in the number of shootings left more people dead than in any single year in a quarter century, according to statistics released by the police department on Saturday.
Summary French was killed and her partner was seriously wounded during an Aug. 7 traffic stop on the city&amp;rsquo;s South Side.</description></item><item><title>Virginia AG sues town where police threatened Black Army lieutenant during stop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</guid><description>Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.
Summary Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging Thursday that the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.</description></item><item><title>COVID-positive Vermonters with no symptoms clog up ERs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8838b26f38c72e71ab4ef/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8838b26f38c72e71ab4ef/</guid><description>Some Vermonters who are able to find antigen tests and then test positive are clogging up emergency rooms.
Summary RUTLAND, Vt. (WCAX) - Some Vermonters who are able to find antigen tests and then test positive are clogging up emergency rooms. He says some people who test positive with a rapid test go to the emergency room looking for a PCR test. He says the only time to go to the ER is if you have a positive test and are very sick.</description></item></channel></rss>