<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>department on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/department/</link><description>Recent content in department on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/department/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Virginia AG sues town where police threatened Black Army lieutenant during stop</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</guid><description>Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.
Summary Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging Thursday that the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.</description></item><item><title>COVID-positive Vermonters with no symptoms clog up ERs</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c8838b26f38c72e71ab4ef/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c8838b26f38c72e71ab4ef/</guid><description>Some Vermonters who are able to find antigen tests and then test positive are clogging up emergency rooms.
Summary RUTLAND, Vt. (WCAX) - Some Vermonters who are able to find antigen tests and then test positive are clogging up emergency rooms. He says some people who test positive with a rapid test go to the emergency room looking for a PCR test. He says the only time to go to the ER is if you have a positive test and are very sick.</description></item></channel></rss>