<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>resigned on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/resigned/</link><description>Recent content in resigned on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 11:13:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/resigned/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>800 employees resign after company asks them to work from office</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f8ea528063013b5ee7d3b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 11:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f8ea528063013b5ee7d3b/</guid><description>Over 800 WhiteHat Jr employees have resigned from the kids online coding learning edtech start-up in the last two months after being asked to work from home. The company asked remote employees to return to office within a month’s
Highlights Over 800 WhiteHat Jr employees have resigned from the kids online coding learning edtech start-up in the last two months after being asked to work from home. This comes after the company asked its employees to return to office within a month’s time.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutors in charge of Trump criminal probe have resigned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216d5492a86165971587e05/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216d5492a86165971587e05/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The two prosecutors in charge of the Manhattan district attorney’s criminal investigation into former President Donald Trump and his business dealings suddenly resigned Wednesday, throwing the future of the probe into question just as pressure was building on Trump on several legal fronts.
Highlights Carey Dunne and Mark Pomerantz, top deputies who had been tasked with running the investigation on a day-to-day basis, have suddenly resigned throwing the future of the probe into question.</description></item></channel></rss>