<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>residents on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/residents/</link><description>Recent content in residents on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 11:13:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/residents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flood saves Ukrainian village from Russian occupation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628231af7abe16d3e534ab68/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 11:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628231af7abe16d3e534ab68/</guid><description>The intentional flooding of a small village north of Kyiv that created a quagmire and submerged cellars and fields, but prevented a Russian attack on the capital, was worth all the sacrifice, residents said.
Highlights Ukrainian forces opened a dam early in the war in Demydiv, causing the Irpin River to flood the village and thousands of acres around. The move has since been credited with stopping Russian soldiers and tanks from breaking through Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s lines.</description></item><item><title>‘They are going to starve to death’: Shanghai residents in lockdown with ‘no end in sight’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62533a951fb059b9ac4a5f07/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 20:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62533a951fb059b9ac4a5f07/</guid><description>Shanghai, China’s largest city and financial hub, has been under a total lockdown since April 5 as Covid-19 cases skyrocket. The city’s 26 million inhabitants have been barred from leaving their home…
Highlights Chinese authorities have been under a total lockdown since April 5 as Covid-19 cases continue to rise to unseen levels in Shanghai. The city&amp;rsquo;s 26 million inhabitants have been barred from leaving their homes or apartment buildings and are now depending on government supplies and overloaded grocery delivery apps for food.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine crisis: claims Mariupol women and children forcibly sent to Russia | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62377c4f724c580c6303ab2e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 19:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62377c4f724c580c6303ab2e/</guid><description>Thousands of resident illegally taken across border, says Mariupol council, as reports emerge its art school has been bombed while 400 were sheltering inside
Highlights Mariupol authorities say Russian forces have deported several thousand residents to Russia. Reports emerge that Russian forces bombed an art school where 400 people were taking shelter. The claims have not been independently verified, but the council’s statement is one of several reports about residents being taken to Russia, where authorities have referred to “refugees” arriving from the strategic port.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Airbnbs being booked in effort to get money to residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221bbd371fca3782c26cb9e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 07:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221bbd371fca3782c26cb9e/</guid><description>People are paying but not staying, as rental platform offers free housing to 100,000 Ukrainian refugees
Highlights Members of the public are paying for Airbnb rentals in Ukraine to help get money to residents who are facing extreme financial hardship because of the Russian invasion. Airbnb has already moved to offer free housing to 100,000 Ukrainian refugees. The rental platform is waiving all guest and host fees on all bookings in Ukraine at this time.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey notifies 186,000 buildings, homes drinking water comes through lead pipes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216a3312ed622f97b752e15/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 21:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216a3312ed622f97b752e15/</guid><description>Water systems are required to notify residents of the lead pipes.
Highlights New Jersey announced Thursday it is notifying nearly 200,000 homes and businesses that they are receiving drinking water from service lines contaminated with lead. The 186,830 known lead service lines feed into buildings all over the state, officials said. Water systems are required to notify residents of the lead pipes. The state&amp;rsquo;s Lead Service Line Replacement law was enacted in July 2021, the law calls for the replacement of these lines by 2031.</description></item></channel></rss>