<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>inmate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inmate/</link><description>Recent content in inmate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 09:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inmate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Authorities are searching for a corrections officer and inmate who never made it to court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cfd94c4c3a3ed1951b713/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 09:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cfd94c4c3a3ed1951b713/</guid><description>Lauderdale County, Alabama, authorities are searching for a sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office employee and an inmate who went missing on their way to the courthouse on Friday at around 9:30 a.m.
Highlights Missing Assistant Director of Corrections Vicki White broke protocol when she escorted inmate Casey White from jail to the courthouse. Casey White was being held on capital murder charges and two sworn deputies should have been with him at all times, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Man who has spent more than two decades on death row in South Carolina, has a choice of firing squad or electric chair for his execution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625140876355bfcd23fce9d3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 08:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625140876355bfcd23fce9d3/</guid><description>Lawyers for 57-year-old Richard Moore say he shouldn’t face execution until judges can determine if either method is cruel and unusual punishment.
Highlights Richard Moore is set to die on April 29 unless a court steps in. He has until next Friday to choose between electric chair or firing squad. Moore has spent more than two decades on death row after he was convicted of killing a convenience store clerk.</description></item></channel></rss>