<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>inmate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inmate/</link><description>Recent content in inmate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 21:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inmate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supreme Court makes it more difficult for prisoners to argue they had ineffective counsel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bf7dbb07cfbfad9b5be73/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 21:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bf7dbb07cfbfad9b5be73/</guid><description>The Supreme Court said Monday that state prisoners may not present new evidence in federal court in support of a claim that their post-conviction counsel in state court was ineffective in violation of the Constitution.
Highlights The 6-3 opinion was penned by Justice Clarence Thomas. In dissent, Justice Sonia Sotomayor called the decision &amp;ldquo;perverse&amp;rdquo; and said the court had gutted precedent. The ruling is a major defeat for two inmates on death row who said they had compelling claims that their lawyers failed to pursue.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Marshals offering $10,000 for missing Alabama inmate and officer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f2d5f875ba6b6bea16cda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 01:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f2d5f875ba6b6bea16cda/</guid><description>The U.S.
Highlights The U.S. Marshals Service is offering up to $10,000 for information leading to the capture of Casey White, a murder suspect. Vicky White, 38, a Lauderdale County corrections officer, left a detention center around 9:40 a.m. Saturday to go to a courthouse but never arrived. Casey White was charged with two counts of capital murder in September 2020 in the stabbing of Connie Ridgeway, 58, and he was already in jail for a series of crimes he committed in 2015, including home invasion, carjacking and a police chase.</description></item><item><title>Authorities are searching for a corrections officer and inmate who never made it to court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cfd94c4c3a3ed1951b713/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 09:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cfd94c4c3a3ed1951b713/</guid><description>Lauderdale County, Alabama, authorities are searching for a sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office employee and an inmate who went missing on their way to the courthouse on Friday at around 9:30 a.m.
Highlights Missing Assistant Director of Corrections Vicki White broke protocol when she escorted inmate Casey White from jail to the courthouse. Casey White was being held on capital murder charges and two sworn deputies should have been with him at all times, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Man who has spent more than two decades on death row in South Carolina, has a choice of firing squad or electric chair for his execution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625140876355bfcd23fce9d3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 08:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625140876355bfcd23fce9d3/</guid><description>Lawyers for 57-year-old Richard Moore say he shouldn’t face execution until judges can determine if either method is cruel and unusual punishment.
Highlights Richard Moore is set to die on April 29 unless a court steps in. He has until next Friday to choose between electric chair or firing squad. Moore has spent more than two decades on death row after he was convicted of killing a convenience store clerk. Lawmakers altered the state’s capital punishment law last year in an effort to work around a decade-long pause in executions.</description></item></channel></rss>