<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shared on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shared/</link><description>Recent content in shared on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 07:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shared/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Netflix is finally going after password sharing. Here’s how it’s likely to work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264f882b1aea6a4bc7ab5c0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 07:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264f882b1aea6a4bc7ab5c0/</guid><description>Netflix doesn&amp;rsquo;t plan to shut down password sharers overnight. Rather, it intends to bill shared accounts an extra fee in a global rollout that may take a year.
Highlights Netflix plans to charge an extra fee for shared accounts being used by multiple people outside of the home. The company has already started a test of this feature in Peru, Costa Rica and Chile. Netflix didn&amp;rsquo;t say how much revenue it expects to generate from implementing its strategy worldwide, though it didn&amp;rsquo;t survey how many current account payers would be willing to pay more to share with others.</description></item><item><title>Gilbert Gottfried, iconic comedian, dies at 67 after long illness</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255f97481357ac9be254fa5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 22:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255f97481357ac9be254fa5/</guid><description>Gottfried died at 2:35 p.m. ET on Tuesday from Recurrent Ventricular Tachycardia due to Myotonic Dystrophy type II.
Highlights Gilbert Gottfried died at 2:35 p.m. ET on Tuesday from Recurrent Ventricular Tachycardia due to Myotonic Dystrophy type II. Gottfried has been performing stand-up comedy for over 50 years. He is survived by his wife Dara, daughter Lily, 14, son Max, 12, sister Karen and nephew Graham. His comedic career led to roles in films including &amp;ldquo;Beverly Hills Cop II,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Problem Child,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Look Who&amp;rsquo;s Talking II&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;The Aristocrats&amp;rdquo; He was also the voice of the wise cracking parrot Iago in Disney&amp;rsquo;s iconic animated film &amp;ldquo;Aladdin&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>‘They are going to starve to death’: Shanghai residents in lockdown with ‘no end in sight’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62533a951fb059b9ac4a5f07/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 20:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62533a951fb059b9ac4a5f07/</guid><description>Shanghai, China’s largest city and financial hub, has been under a total lockdown since April 5 as Covid-19 cases skyrocket. The city’s 26 million inhabitants have been barred from leaving their home…
Highlights Chinese authorities have been under a total lockdown since April 5 as Covid-19 cases continue to rise to unseen levels in Shanghai. The city&amp;rsquo;s 26 million inhabitants have been barred from leaving their homes or apartment buildings and are now depending on government supplies and overloaded grocery delivery apps for food.</description></item><item><title>Police officer 'shared sensitive images of sexual assault case'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241df9a9a3cfd15a9230ab8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 16:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241df9a9a3cfd15a9230ab8/</guid><description>DC Joseph Gilligan met a vulnerable victim of domestic abuse through his investigation into her case. He abused his power by misusing police computer systems to gather information on the woman and her partner. He also accessed her mobile phone to read her
Highlights DC Joseph Gilligan met the victim of domestic abuse through his investigation into her case. He also abused his power by misusing police computer systems to gather information on the woman and her partner.</description></item></channel></rss>