<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dan/</link><description>Recent content in dan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 20:15:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gravity Payments CEO Dan Price charged with sexual assault amid ongoing felony rape investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62630ca7995bccd28c2b8bc3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 20:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62630ca7995bccd28c2b8bc3/</guid><description>Gravity Payments CEO Dan Price has been charged with two counts of fourth-degree assault and one count of reckless driving. The charges stem from an alleged assault with sexual motivation. Price is also being investigated for “felony rape of
Highlights Dan Price has been charged with two counts of fourth-degree assault and one count of reckless driving in Seattle Municipal Court. The charges stem from an alleged assault with sexual motivation.</description></item><item><title>Melbourne man sets himself on fire while screaming about Dan Andrews' Covid vaccine mandates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</guid><description>A man has lit himself on fire in front of horrified diners in Richmond on Saturday while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates.
Summary A man has set himself and his car on fire in front of horrified diners while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates. The man emerged from a silver MG3 hatchback engulfed in flames near Church St in Richmond about 8pm on Saturday. A man has set himself and his MG3 hatch on fire in Richmond while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 mandates on Saturday (pictured)The bystanders helped restrain the man before police officers pinned him to the ground.</description></item></channel></rss>