<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pic on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pic/</link><description>Recent content in pic on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 04:16:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>80 Ukrainian soldiers believed dead after Russian missile strikes hit barracks as they slept</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236aa7fd7c8d7d117b5c2bf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 04:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236aa7fd7c8d7d117b5c2bf/</guid><description>Up to 200 people are thought to have been inside the barracks in Mykolaiv when they were attacked.
Highlights Up to 200 troops were thought to have been inside the barracks in Mykolaiv when they were targeted. At least 50 bodies have been recovered, a Ukrainian serviceman said. The death toll has not been confirmed by Ukrainian authorities because the attack involved a military site, according to reports. A soldier who survived the attack said he was woken by the sound of explosions at 6am.</description></item><item><title>Grieving mum shares footage of moment her son is killed by a single punch to the head | UK News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eabf07bfad2bd34420a36/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 20:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eabf07bfad2bd34420a36/</guid><description>Brandon Sillence, a boxing enthusiast, punched Dean so violently he was brain dead before he hit the ground.
Highlights Brandon Luke Sillence, 25, launched an attack on Dean Skillin outside a hotel in Bangor, Wales. Boxing enthusiast punched Dean so violently he was brain dead before he hit the ground. His mother Becky White, who released the footage online, has called for tougher sentences for one-punch killers. She said: &amp;ldquo;What sort of coward hits someone from behind and leaves him on the floor, then walks away knowing the damage he had done?</description></item></channel></rss>