<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fear on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fear/</link><description>Recent content in fear on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 18:15:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine defence: Red lights and painted arrows fuel fear of Russian agents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240a9986fcbe1d53c6846b5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 18:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240a9986fcbe1d53c6846b5/</guid><description>Fear of Russian saboteurs operating in Ukraine has soared, but is it based on intelligence and arrests?
Highlights Fear of Russian saboteurs operating in Ukraine has soared, but is it based on intelligence and arrests? How much is fact, backed up by intelligence reports and arrests, and how much is something closer to understandable paranoia fuelled by social media rumours about mysterious lights and signs? What is the real fear that the war in Ukraine is hardening into a certainty?</description></item><item><title>Conservative Disney employees fear retaliation for “Don’t be gay” bill.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d87be4203066f34294097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d87be4203066f34294097/</guid><description>A new petition asks Disney to be more politically neutral on issues like the “Don’t Say Gay’s” bill. The bill would ban discussion of sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade. The
Highlights An open letter to Disney employees asks them to remain neutral on issues like the &amp;lsquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rsquo; bill. The bill would ban discussion about sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade.</description></item><item><title>500-pound bear known as "Hank the Tank" breaks into another Lake Tahoe home: "Lost all fear of people"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62116b5205b11c0db223cf6f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 22:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62116b5205b11c0db223cf6f/</guid><description>The bear has broken into dozens of homes and become quite a problem for locals.
Highlights Bear has broken into dozens of homes in South Lake Tahoe and is responsible for more than 150 calls. California Department of Fish and Wildlife have been trying to track the bear for six months. The Bear League says it&amp;rsquo;s still waiting to hear back from the state about a possible sanctuary move. A meeting on the issue is set for Wednesday night in Tahoe Keys.</description></item></channel></rss>