<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bridge on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bridge/</link><description>Recent content in bridge on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:45:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bridge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trucks are gone from Ambassador Bridge, but more protesters arrive on foot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208547dc4a16ec8da59b553/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208547dc4a16ec8da59b553/</guid><description>About 50 police officers have gathered near protesters who have been blocking the Ambassador Bridge for six days.
Highlights About 50 police officers have gathered near protesters who have been blocking the Ambassador Bridge for six days. Truckers have been ordered to clear the bridge or face arrest. Crews use earth-moving equipment to position concrete barricades on Huron Church Road. Trucks are gone from Ambassador Bridge, but more protesters arrive on foot, growing their ranks to several hundred.</description></item><item><title>Canada police arrive to remove protesters at US border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208149f539e7d5486bccfc5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 20:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208149f539e7d5486bccfc5/</guid><description>WINDSOR, Ontario (AP) — A tense standoff at a U.S.-Canadian border crossing crucial to both countries&amp;rsquo; economies appeared to be dissolving peacefully Saturday as Canadian police moved in to disperse the nearly weeklong blockade and protesters began leaving without resistance.
Highlights Canadian police move in to disperse nearly weeklong blockade of U.S.-Canada border crossing. Protesters began leaving without resistance as scores of police approached shortly after dawn. Many demonstrators drove away from the Ambassador Bridge spanning the river between Detroit and Windsor, Ontario.</description></item></channel></rss>