<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stolen on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stolen/</link><description>Recent content in stolen on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:40:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stolen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Phoenix cops find 1,200 catalytic converters as thefts soar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292c0ce9c917c756d459b5e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292c0ce9c917c756d459b5e/</guid><description>An Arizona man is facing multiple theft charges after detectives found a huge stash of stolen catalytic converters packed into a storage unit in Phoenix
Highlights An Arizona man is facing multiple theft charges after detectives found a huge stash of stolen catalytic converters packed into a storage unit in Phoenix. The bust came amid a national surge in thefts of the pricy auto parts that play a critical in reducing vehicle emissions and has led lawmakers in 36 states and in Washington D.</description></item><item><title>Gun stolen during 1970s found in middle school student's backpack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289c59b8f2f57f81f86ca12/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 05:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289c59b8f2f57f81f86ca12/</guid><description>BERKELEY COUNTY, S. C. (WCIV) — A handgun stolen from a state trooper during the 1970s was recently found in a middle school student’s backpack. Caption: A gun that was stolen from an Alaskan state trooper during the 1970s has been found in the backpack of a middle school student in South Carolina. (WCIV) Now, Berkeley County Sheriff Duane Lewis said he is determined to find out how the gun traveled 4,600 miles from South Carolina to Alaska.</description></item><item><title>More guns are being stolen out of cars in alarming trend across the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a6c3c9148e73e81069aa2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 13:45:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a6c3c9148e73e81069aa2/</guid><description>More guns are being stolen out of vehicles in many U.S. cities, according to a new data analysis, which was first obtained and independently verified by NBC New
Highlights Everytown for Gun Safety analyzed FBI crime data from 2011 to 2020. At least 180 cities saw a rise in gun thefts from vehicles, the nonprofit says. It&amp;rsquo;s an alarming trend as shootings rise nationwide, propelled in large part by firearms obtained illegally.</description></item><item><title>In Bizarre Robbery, 60-Foot Bridge Stolen In Bihar, India</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62526737239ed08cc0421b16/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62526737239ed08cc0421b16/</guid><description>A gang of thieves haspulled off an extraordinary heist by stealing a 60-foot abandoned bridge in Bihar&amp;rsquo;s Rohtas district in broad daylight.
Highlights Thieves used gas cutters and earthmover machines to demolish the bridge in Bihar&amp;rsquo;s Rohtas district. The bridge was built over the Ara canal in Amiyavar around 1972. Arshad Kamal Shamshi, a junior engineer of the irrigation department, said that the villagers informed them that some people pretending as irrigation department officials had uprooted the bridge using machines like JCB and gas-cutters.</description></item><item><title>Yale employee stole $40M from medical school for homes, luxury cars, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62452b0f033c9973692b923f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 04:16:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62452b0f033c9973692b923f/</guid><description>A Yale School of Medicine administrator stole $40 million in computers and electronics to buy luxury cars and real estate, prosecutors said.
Highlights Jamie Petrone, 42, pleaded guilty to wire fraud and filing a false tax return Monday in federal court. She is alleged to have run a scheme for eight years starting in 2013, causing Yale to lose $40,504,200, prosecutors said. Petrone used money from the sales of the stolen goods for real estate, travel, expensive cars and other personal expenses.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds of bulletproof vests donated for Ukraine stolen in Manhattan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233c0607b84b6a173eaecb8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 23:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233c0607b84b6a173eaecb8/</guid><description>They were swiped from the Ukrainian Congress Committee of America building. Police are seeking the culprits.
Highlights About 400 bulletproof vests stolen from Ukrainian Congress Committee of America building. The vests were donated to be sent to Ukraine to help in its war against Russia. The NYPD is seeking those responsible for the theft of the vests. Police are seeking the culprits and are searching for those responsible. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Stolen box of human heads investigated by Denver police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62258703dafc5397725852a6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 04:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62258703dafc5397725852a6/</guid><description>Denver police are investigating the theft of a box containing human heads from a parked freight company truck, officials said Saturday.
Highlights Box was being transported for medical research purposes. Box was marked with a label that said “Exempt Human Specimen” A dolly was also stolen from the truck. No arrests had been made as of Saturday and investigators asked anyone who finds the box to call police. Someone broke into the truck while it was parked between Wednesday afternoon and Thursday morning, Denver TV station KDVR reports.</description></item><item><title>OpenSea confirms hacker stole NFTs 'worth £1.25m' from 32 users</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213d68af4ee53c4e95e0176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213d68af4ee53c4e95e0176/</guid><description>According to the blockchain analysis company PeckShield, at least 254 non-fungible tokens were stolen as a result of an unknown attack.
Highlights At least 254 non-fungible tokens (NFTs) were stolen from dozens of users on the popular trading platform OpenSea. The company&amp;rsquo;s chief executive confirmed on Twitter that the company believed the hacker made $1.7m (£1.25m) from selling the stolen NFTs. The thefts have prompted a scare in the cryptocurrency community, where many people are attempting to realise enormous gains by investing in largely unregulated assets.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas bartender robbed at gunpoint was forced to repay bosses stolen money, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620aa964de20c8dc82c39738/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620aa964de20c8dc82c39738/</guid><description>A Las Vegas bartender was robbed at gunpoint and then forced to repay his company the stolen money, according to a lawsuit filed by the employee.
Highlights A Las Vegas bartender was robbed at gunpoint and then forced to repay his company the stolen money, lawsuit says. Edward Parker was working at the Lodge Hualapai early Dec. 4, 2020, when a gunman entered and ordered him to kneel on the ground.</description></item></channel></rss>