<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elon on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elon/</link><description>Recent content in elon on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk's company confirms monkeys died in brain chip testing project, denies animal cruelty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213c817d66ca29fe393f824/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213c817d66ca29fe393f824/</guid><description>Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s implant company Neuralink has acknowledged that monkeys died as part of its testing procedures but denies allegations of animal cruelty.
Highlights Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s Neuralink says monkeys died as part of its testing procedures. University of California, Davis Primate Center euthanized two macaque monkeys at the end of the testing process. Neuroimplantable chips are implanted into monkeys&amp;rsquo; brains to enable brains to communicate with computers. In April last year, Neuralink claimed monkeys can play Pong &amp;ndash; a computer game - using just their minds.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk owes a massive $11 billion in taxes after wrapping up his Tesla stock sales</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccbe676621b24eb005f362/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccbe676621b24eb005f362/</guid><description>Elon Musk appears to have wrapped up a busy year of trading his Tesla shares Tuesday. He&amp;rsquo;ll end up with one of the largest tax bills in history to show for it.
Summary New York (CNN Business) Elon Musk appears to have wrapped up a busy year of trading his Tesla shares Tuesday. The trades completed the exercise of the 22.9 million options he held that were due to expire in August.</description></item></channel></rss>