<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>environmental on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/environmental/</link><description>Recent content in environmental on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:18:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/environmental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>USPS gets final signoff to order new delivery vehicles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62178571f1a4709d62d2c04f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:18:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62178571f1a4709d62d2c04f/</guid><description>The U.S. Postal Service says it has cleared the final regulatory hurdle to placing orders for next-generation mail vehicles
Highlights The U.S. Postal Service says it has cleared the final regulatory hurdle to placing orders for next-generation mail vehicles. Environmental groups have pushed back because only 10% of the vehicles would be electric-powered under the Postal Service contract with the manufacturer, Oshkosh Defense. The new vehicles boast modern amenities like climate control and safety features like air bags, backup cameras and collision avoidance — all currently lacking on the aging Grumman vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Kosovo bans cryptocurrency mining after blackouts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d63f382b3a4dcd352d28de/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 01:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d63f382b3a4dcd352d28de/</guid><description>The Balkan country is enforcing blackouts amid an electricity shortage caused by high global prices.
Summary Concerned about the environmental impact of the practice, other countries such as China and Iran have cracked down on crypto mining. Last year, Iran announce a four-month ban because it was draining more than 2GW from the grid each day. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>