<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>smith on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/smith/</link><description>Recent content in smith on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/smith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Secret Service seizes more than $102 million in crypto assets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fdd12cd742f57e158df69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fdd12cd742f57e158df69/</guid><description>The U.S. Secret Service, known for protecting the president, is taking aim at illicit digital currencies, seizing over $102 million in the past seven years.
Highlights U.S. Secret Service is cracking down on illicit digital currency transactions. The Secret Service has seized more than $102 million in illicit digital currencies in the past seven years. Agents and analysts actively track the flow of bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies on the blockchain, similar to an old-fashioned surveillance.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina police chief placed on unpaid leave for telling officers about 'clinic' to obtain Covid-19 vaccination cards without getting the shots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c48f0e1c2c279f3766c6ad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 15:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c48f0e1c2c279f3766c6ad/</guid><description>A North Carolina police chief has been placed on unpaid leave and probation for telling officers about a &amp;quot;clinic&amp;quot; that would issue them a Covid-19 vaccination card without actually receiving the shot, local officials said.
Summary (CNN) A North Carolina police chief has been placed on unpaid leave and probation for telling officers about a &amp;ldquo;clinic&amp;rdquo; that would issue them a Covid-19 vaccination card without actually receiving the shot, local officials said.</description></item></channel></rss>