<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>help on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/help/</link><description>Recent content in help on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 06:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>President Zelensky says first wave of foreign fighters has arrived to assist Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221ae7a19a53b57effd14b7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 06:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221ae7a19a53b57effd14b7/</guid><description>The first foreign fighters have arrived in Ukraine to help defend the country against the Russian invasion, according to Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky.
Highlights First foreign fighters have arrived in Ukraine to help defend against Russian invasion. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky: &amp;ldquo;The first 16,000 are already on their way to protect freedom and life for us, and for all&amp;rdquo; He did not specify where the fighters have come from, but praised allies for sending weapons to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky sheriff honors prisoner who pulled people from rubble of collapsed candle factory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d6e713b607b100522ed5c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d6e713b607b100522ed5c/</guid><description>A Kentucky prisoner who pulled people from the rubble of a collapsed candle factory in December was honored by a local sheriff last week for going &amp;quot;above and beyond&amp;quot; to help people.
Highlights A Kentucky prisoner who pulled people from the rubble of a collapsed candle factory in December was honored by a local sheriff last week. Marco Sanchez, a prisoner who worked at the Mayfield, Kentucky, candle factory, was injured in the collapse.</description></item><item><title>An unsent text message and desperate phone calls detail California family's last moments before they died while hiking</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62108af88c8a60f239d3b693/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 06:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62108af88c8a60f239d3b693/</guid><description>Family selfies, nature photos, an unanswered text and several calls that were never connected detail the final hours of a California couple and their child before they died on a hiking trail near Yosemite last August.
Highlights Jonathan Gerrish, Ellen Chung and their 1-year-old daughter, Miju, died from hyperthermia. Authorities were able to pull a text message from Gerrish&amp;rsquo;s phone at 11:56 a.m. asking for help. It was never received due to lack of cell service in the area.</description></item><item><title>U.S. to let teens drive big rigs in test program to help ease supply chain shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e843bbe2889b93705a3bd4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e843bbe2889b93705a3bd4/</guid><description>The federal government is moving forward with a plan to let teenagers drive big rigs from state to state in a test program.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos After more than 5 million people signed an online petition, the governor of Colorado has reduced the 110-year sentence for truck driver Rogel Aguilera-Mederos to just 10 years. They say it&amp;rsquo;s unwise to let teenage drivers be responsible for rigs that can weigh 80,000 pounds and cause catastrophic damage when they hit lighter vehicles.</description></item><item><title>CNN Exclusive: US intel and satellite images show Saudi Arabia is now building its own ballistic missiles with help of China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4f18423cdd004762cb169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4f18423cdd004762cb169/</guid><description>US intelligence agencies have assessed that Saudi Arabia is now actively manufacturing its own ballistic missiles with the help of China, CNN has learned, a development that could have significant ripple effects across the Middle East and complicate the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s efforts to restrain the nuclear ambitions of Iran, the Saudis&amp;rsquo; top regional rival.
Summary Iran and Saudi Arabia are bitter enemies and it is unlikely Tehran will agree to stop making ballistic missiles if Saudi Arabia has begun manufacturing its own.</description></item></channel></rss>