<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>invasion on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/invasion/</link><description>Recent content in invasion on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 10:14:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/invasion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Top Kremlin adviser becomes first high-ranking official to quit since invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c447b4642aa8e5374ed73/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 10:14:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c447b4642aa8e5374ed73/</guid><description>Russian government official Anatoly Chubais is reported to be the first high-ranking Kremlin representative to quit his post following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine
Highlights Anatoly Chubais was Putin&amp;rsquo;s special representative for ties with international organisations. He is the first high-ranking official to quit his post since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The 66-year-old oversaw privatisation in Russia following the collapse of the Soviet Union. Comes amid reports of Russia’s defence minister, Sergey Shoigu, disappearing with ‘heart problems’ Defence Minister is said to be carrying out a witch hunt of his closest allies to prevent information from being leaked to the West.</description></item><item><title>"Russian cruelty is so brutal": Ukrainians cope with devastation as government says 10 hospitals have been completely destroyed in invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b47ecb91be55524367fc2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b47ecb91be55524367fc2/</guid><description>The U.S. has evidence that Russia is deliberately and intentionally targeting civilians, including hospitals and places of shelter, a senior Defense official told CBS News.
Highlights The U.S. said it has seen clear evidence the Russians are committing war crimes as civilians are killed in their homes and on the street. Yet Russia&amp;rsquo;s ground forces have made surprisingly slow progress. President Biden said Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;back is against the wall&amp;rdquo; and Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s resistance and Russia&amp;rsquo;s slow progress are raising concerns that he may use chemical or biological weapons to regain the upper hand in war.</description></item><item><title>The Russian Tea Room in New York City suffers as Ukraine invasion escalates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226a70ec5adda755162de6a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226a70ec5adda755162de6a/</guid><description>The Russian Tea Room is a 100-year-old New York City icon that has long drawn in locals and tourists alike. It was opened in 1927 by, perhaps apocryphally, “White Russian expatriates who had
Highlights The Russian Tea Room is a 100-year-old New York City icon that has long drawn in locals and tourists alike. It was opened in 1927 by, perhaps apocryphally, “White Russian expatriates who had fled the Bolsheviks,” according to the restaurant’s website.</description></item><item><title>Zara and Paypal suspend business in Russia over Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62239a0dc3a04433ebcea83d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 17:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62239a0dc3a04433ebcea83d/</guid><description>Inditex, which owns Zara and several other major brands, will close all of its 502 stores in Russia.
Highlights Inditex, which owns Zara and several other major brands, will close all of its 502 stores in Russia. &amp;ldquo;We believe that such actions will motivate the youth and active population of Russia to proactively stop the disgraceful military aggression,&amp;rdquo; Mr Fedorov said in a letter posted on his Twitter account on Friday.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine accuses Russia of 'war crimes' targeting civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bb11aaf65ae32a734ab78/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bb11aaf65ae32a734ab78/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin ordered his country&amp;rsquo;s deterrence forces &amp;ndash; which include nuclear arms &amp;ndash; onto their highest state of alert on Sunday, as Ukrainian forces engaged in fierce fighting with Russian troops in multiple cities across Ukraine.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin orders his country&amp;rsquo;s deterrence forces on combat alert. Putin says Western sanctions against Russia are unlawful. Fighting breaks out in Kharkiv, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second largest city, after Russian forces enter the city.</description></item><item><title>Explosions in Kyiv as UK reports ‘fierce resistance’ across the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218abe0d07b0625b40728bb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 10:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218abe0d07b0625b40728bb/</guid><description>Public urged to report Russian troop movements and prepare molotov cocktails, with heavy gunfire heard in residential district
Highlights US secretary of state, Antony Blinken, said Russia intends to “incircle and threaten” the city. Russian forces have vowed to stay in the capital in Ukraine. Russian president, Volodymyr Zelenskiy, accused Vladimir Putin of targeting civilian as well as military sites. “Russia will have to talk to us sooner or later about how to end hostilities and stop this invasion.</description></item><item><title>Biden says he'd consider slapping Putin with personal sanctions if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f28ac59ed72783ee509b72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f28ac59ed72783ee509b72/</guid><description>Russia has warned that sanctioning Vladimir Putin would lead to US-Russia ties being cut. Leaked documents suggest Putin has secret assets abroad.
Highlights Joe Biden said a Russian invasion of Ukraine could be the &amp;ldquo;largest invasion since World War II.&amp;rdquo; Biden said the US could sanction Vladimir Putin personally if an invasion went ahead. He said that if Russia invaded Ukraine, it would have &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; and could be the &amp;ldquo;largest invasion since World War II.</description></item><item><title>'Every indication' Putin plans force by mid-February: US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</guid><description>The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday.
Summary The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;I have no idea whether he&amp;rsquo;s made the ultimate decision, but we certainly see every indication that he is going to use military force sometime perhaps (between) now and the middle of February,&amp;rdquo; Deputy Secretary of State Wendy Sherman told a forum.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item></channel></rss>