<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>car on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/car/</link><description>Recent content in car on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/car/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A father says he put 1,000 miles on his car to find specialty formula for premature infant daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a5242bb66ba91358270f6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a5242bb66ba91358270f6/</guid><description>Mac Jaehnert said he put 1,000 miles on his car in the last week looking for a specialty nutritional formula for daughter MacKenzie and other premature babies in his southeastern Washington state community.
Highlights Mac Jaehnert described empty store shelves in his search for Similac NeoSure in Richland, Washington state. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been a frustrating, heartbreaking, unnecessary challenge for a kid who has already overcome so much,&amp;rdquo; he said. The Biden administration has ordered the use of military aircraft to expedite the delivery of baby formula to the U.</description></item><item><title>An 8-month-old died in a hot car after her father's arrest, Georgia police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273881fd1ab0bbc3ca59d15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 08:18:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273881fd1ab0bbc3ca59d15/</guid><description>The father of an 8-month-old girl who died after she was left inside of a hot car has been charged with second-degree murder, Georgia Bureau of Investigation officials said during a news conference on Wednesday.
Highlights Davav Japez McCorry Whatley, 20, was taken into custody Wednesday morning in connection with the child&amp;rsquo;s death. He is accused of leaving his 8-month-old daughter inside his vehicle for several hours on Tuesday afternoon. The entire interaction with Whatley was recorded on body camera, investigators said.</description></item><item><title>Ex-officer charged with murder in shooting of 12-year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270c8d4671d67dea435713a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 06:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270c8d4671d67dea435713a/</guid><description>A fired Philadelphia police officer has been charged with murder in the shooting of a fleeing 12-year-old boy
Highlights Thomas &amp;ldquo;T.J.&amp;rdquo; Siderio, 12, was shot in the back of the neck after he fired at an unmarked police car, prosecutors say. A grand jury presentment unsealed Monday shows video contradicts the officer&amp;rsquo;s version of events. The boy&amp;rsquo;s great-grandmother: &amp;ldquo;I’m so heartbroken, none of us can’t sleep’s horrible” The officer is also charged with voluntary manslaughter and other charges.</description></item><item><title>Three OU meteorology students die in car crash Friday on way home from storm chasing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e5dcc2e25ac30e7c662bb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 10:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e5dcc2e25ac30e7c662bb/</guid><description>The three OU meteorology students had been storm chasing in Kansas and died when they were struck by a semi while southbound on I-35.
Highlights Nicholas Nair, Gavin Short and Drake Brooks were returning from storm chasing in Kansas. They were driving southbound on a wet Interstate 35 near Tonkawa when their SUV hydroplaned. The three were pronounced dead at the scene about 85 miles north of Oklahoma City. The accident took place around 11:23 p.</description></item><item><title>Dwayne Haskins struck by car and killed - ProFootballTalk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251e904cc81975bb86583fc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 20:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251e904cc81975bb86583fc/</guid><description>Dwayne Haskins was hit by a car in South Florida early this morning. The 24-year-old was a first-round draft pick in Washington and most recently played in Pittsburgh. At Ohio State he became one of the
Highlights Dwayne Haskins was killed when he was hit by a car early this morning in South Florida. He was a first-round draft pick in Washington and most recently played in Pittsburgh. At Ohio State, he became one of the best players in college football, finishing third in Heisman Trophy voting in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Black man grabbing tea from car shot by New Jersey police and paralyzed, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62354a47f05cf05715d21fc8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62354a47f05cf05715d21fc8/</guid><description>Jajuan R. Henderson, 29, was unarmed and grabbing an iced tea before he was paralyzed by Trenton police on Feb. 12, a lawsuit alleges.
Highlights Jajuan R. Henderson, 29, was getting the drink from a Saturn Ion parked outside of his home shortly after midnight on Feb. 12 in Trenton, New Jersey. A group of men in dark clothing and masks driving an unidentified vehicle boxed in the Saturn, which was parallel parked, according to the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>DA: Teacher fearing exposure to COVID-19 places 13-year-old son in trunk of car while driving to testing site</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9c330626c96d1b636d8be/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9c330626c96d1b636d8be/</guid><description>A mother has been charged after her 13-year-old son was found in the trunk of her car at a Cy-Fair ISD drive-thru COVID testing site, the Harris County District Attorney’s Office confirmed.
Summary HOUSTON – A mother has been charged after her 13-year-old son was found in the trunk of her car at a Cy-Fair ISD drive-thru COVID testing site, the Harris County District Attorney’s Office confirmed. Cy-Fair ISD Police Department said a warrant has been issued for her arrest.</description></item><item><title>NYC police officer shot while resting in car between shifts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 06:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</guid><description>Authorities say a New York City police officer&amp;rsquo;s skull was broken when he was shot New Year&amp;rsquo;s morning while sleeping in his personal vehicle between shifts but he is expected to fully recover
Summary The officer left the vehicle and was aided by a sergeant who saw blood coming from his head before an ambulance took him to the hospital, Sewell said. She said it was unknown whether the seven-year member of the force was targeted, but the round was apparently fired from “a significant distance away” and other officers sleeping in their vehicles nearby did not hear gunfire.</description></item></channel></rss>