<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>criminal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/criminal/</link><description>Recent content in criminal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/criminal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reward grows to $22,500 for arrest of escaped inmate serving life for murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280f0e03ac5ff8dc8bd0c21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280f0e03ac5ff8dc8bd0c21/</guid><description>A Texas inmate serving life for murder managed to break free from his shackles, overpower a bus driver and escape from custody, officials said.
Highlights Gonzalo Lopez, 46, was on a transport bus en route from Gatesville to Huntsville for a medical appointment when he escaped. Lopez cut out the bottom of a door that separates inmates and the driver, Texas Department of Criminal Justice says. Lopez is serving a life sentence for a capital murder in Hidalgo County and an attempted capital murder.</description></item><item><title>No charges for cop who fatally shot Amir Locke</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e8f139662a51d696712b6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 07:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e8f139662a51d696712b6/</guid><description>No criminal charges will be filed in the fatal police shooting of Amir Locke.
Highlights Amir Locke, a legal gun owner, was fatally shot by Minneapolis police officers in February. Locke was not a suspect in the crime for which the warrant was issued and was not named in the document. Locke&amp;rsquo;s mother: &amp;ldquo;Can you imagine knowing that you&amp;rsquo;ll never get to see your 22-year-old baby ever again?&amp;rdquo; Locke&amp;rsquo;s legal team says it is &amp;ldquo;deeply disappointed&amp;rdquo; by the decision.</description></item><item><title>Texas Court Upholds Conviction, Sentence of Amber Guyger</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249578d278eac8fb3bbd0f5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249578d278eac8fb3bbd0f5/</guid><description>Texas’ highest criminal court upheld the murder conviction and 10-year prison sentence of Amber Guyger, the former Dallas police officer who fatally shot&amp;hellip;
Highlights Court of Criminal Appeals refused to hear Amber Guyger’s petition to review her 2019 conviction. The former Dallas police officer fatally shot Botham Jean in his apartment in 2018 after she said she mistook him for an intruder. Two justices — Judge Kevin Yeary and Judge Michelle Slaughter — filed a dissent.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutors resigned after New York DA said he wasn't prepared to move forward with indictment of Trump</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226915f3a4150fb2029b642/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 23:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226915f3a4150fb2029b642/</guid><description>Two top prosecutors in the Trump investigation into former President Donald Trump resigned last month. The resignations followed weeks of internal debate and discussion over the strength of the evidence against Trump. Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg said he wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared to
Highlights Two senior prosecutors on the team resigned last month after the Manhattan district attorney said he was not prepared to authorize an indictment against the former President. The resignations followed weeks of internal debate and discussion over the strength of the evidence against Trump.</description></item></channel></rss>