<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>investigating on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/investigating/</link><description>Recent content in investigating on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/investigating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CDC investigating 109 cases of severe hepatitis in kids across two dozen states, including 5 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627664556300ace33b5a0929/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627664556300ace33b5a0929/</guid><description>The cases of severe hepatitis have been found across 25 states and territories.
Highlights The CDC is investigating 109 cases of severe hepatitis in children, including five deaths. More than 90% of the kids were hospitalized and 14% required liver transplants. The cases occurred over the past seven months across 25 states and territories. Hepatitis is an inflammation of the liver that is often caused by viral infections, but environmental factors can also play a role.</description></item><item><title>Chipmaker Nvidia investigating potential cyberattack - report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a89a1751b7660b684ecb1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 20:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a89a1751b7660b684ecb1/</guid><description>U.S chipmaker Nvidia Corp said on Friday it was investigating a potential cyberattack, following a news report that said the attack may have had taken parts of its business offline for two days.
Highlights U.S. chipmaker Nvidia Corp (NVDA.O) said on Friday it was investigating a potential cyberattack. A news report said the attack may have had taken parts of its business offline for two days. A malicious network intrusion caused outages in Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s email systems and developer tools over the last two days, the Telegraph reported earlier on Friday.</description></item></channel></rss>