<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cost on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cost/</link><description>Recent content in cost on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 19:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Airline ticket prices have risen 40 percent since the beginning of 2022</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626843d0cc32197ea53d7c8e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 19:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626843d0cc32197ea53d7c8e/</guid><description>Surging demand, high fuel prices and an ongoing pilot shortage have combined to create&amp;hellip;
Highlights Average cost of airfare for U.S. travelers in April rose to $330 for a single domestic round-trip ticket. Hopper expects prices to increase a further 10 percent by the end of May. Air carriers excitedly eyeing current &amp;ldquo;strong revenue environment&amp;rdquo; brought about by high fuel prices, increased labor costs and a shortage of pilots in the United States.</description></item><item><title>As inflation heats up, 64% of Americans are now living paycheck to paycheck</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</guid><description>The number of Americans living paycheck to paycheck is climbing, despite rising wages.
Highlights The cost of living is growing at the fastest annual pace in about four decades. At the start of 2022, 64% of the U.S. population was living paycheck to paycheck, up from 61% in December. Even among those earning six figures, 48% said they are now living paycheck-to-paycheck. When wages rise at a slower pace than inflation, those paychecks won&amp;rsquo;t go as far at the grocery store and at the gas pump.</description></item></channel></rss>