<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>occurred on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/occurred/</link><description>Recent content in occurred on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 11:12:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/occurred/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Injuries reported after reported shooting at South Carolina mall, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bf5e00c8cd6c62f43e527/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 11:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bf5e00c8cd6c62f43e527/</guid><description>Twelve people were injured and three people have been detained following a shooting at a Columbia, South Carolina, mall on Saturday afternoon, police said.
Highlights Incident occurred on the premises of Columbiana Centre Mall, Columbia Police Chief William H. &amp;ldquo;Skip&amp;rdquo; Holbrook said. Three armed people were detained by police, although it is not clear how many people fired a weapon. There were no fatalities reported from the shooting, he said. Of those injured, 10 received gunshot wounds, with eight who were transported for treatment and two who were self-transporting for care, police said.</description></item><item><title>One-third of all US child Covid deaths occurred during Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d7e0260c54b0d52289523/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 05:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d7e0260c54b0d52289523/</guid><description>Children seem to be facing increasing risks as mask mandates are abandoned and vaccination rates stall
Highlights 550 children have died from Covid-19 in the US, compared with 1,017 in the preceding 22 months. Omicron is less severe than Delta, but it is three to five times worse than previous variants, recent CDC research shows. Florida’s surgeon general recently recommended against vaccinating ‘health’ kids given the possibility of side-effects, which remain extremely rare and are outweighed by the vaccines’ protection.</description></item></channel></rss>