<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>review on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/review/</link><description>Recent content in review on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 05:18:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nunavut Inuit ready to forgo $2 billion to protect environment.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62808cfef5ae379211fce779/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 05:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62808cfef5ae379211fce779/</guid><description>The Nunavut Impact Review board has recommended Baffinland&amp;rsquo;s Phase 2 expansion not be be allowed to proceed, citing &amp;quot;the potential to result in significant adverse ecosystemic effects.&amp;quot;
Highlights Nunavut Impact Review Board has recommended Baffinland&amp;rsquo;s Phase 2 expansion not be allowed to proceed. The long-awaited recommendation was released on Friday after a four-year review process. The board said the mine has potential for &amp;ldquo;significant adverse ecosystemic effects&amp;rdquo; on marine mammals, fish, caribou and other wildlife.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis staff delayed release of Gaetz associate Halsey Beshears’ spending records</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c8766ef25cabba021e200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c8766ef25cabba021e200/</guid><description>In a move criticized by advocates of Florida’s open government laws, Gov. Ron DeSantis’ staff intervened in a public records request related to a former appointee who is reportedly connected to a federal sex trafficking investigation, documents obtained by News 6 show.
Highlights Gov. Ron DeSantis intervened in a public records request, documents obtained by News 6 show. The governor&amp;rsquo;s staff delayed the release of Halsey Beshears&amp;rsquo; financial records for more than two months.</description></item><item><title>Guantanamo Bay detainee allowed to return to Saudi Arabia after 20 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62279d227c071d2575c88541/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 18:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62279d227c071d2575c88541/</guid><description>Mohammad Ahmad al-Qahtani was accused of attempting to enter the US to hijack planes in the September 11 attack
Highlights Mohammad Ahmad al-Qahtani has been flown back to Saudi Arabia for mental health treatment. The 46-year-old prisoner has suffered from mental illness, including schizophrenia, since childhood. He was accused of attempting to join hijackers in carrying out the September 11 attacks. The US dropped plans to try him after a Bush administration legal official concluded he had been tortured at Guantánamo.</description></item><item><title>Man was shot by police after officer mistook his gun for a Taser, police in Florida say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 03:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</guid><description>A police officer in Florida shot a man after mistaking his gun for a Taser, an initial review of the case suggests, police said in a statement.
Highlights Michael Ortiz is paralyzed and requires round-the-clock care, the complaint alleges. The Hollywood Police Department says the officer mistakenly fired a gun instead of a Taser. Ortiz was naked and handcuffed when police shot him in the back, his attorney says. Ortiz &amp;ldquo;was having a mental health crisis&amp;rdquo; on the day of the shooting after losing his dog, the lawyer says.</description></item><item><title>Conservative group trying to ban 16 books from Polk Schools, calling them pornographic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fef6ec6c15d692ed4120d8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 22:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fef6ec6c15d692ed4120d8/</guid><description>A conservative political group in Florida complained that 16 books in public schools&amp;rsquo; libraries contain pornographic material harmful to children.
Highlights Conservative group trying to ban 16 books from Polk Schools, calling them pornographic. Polk County Public Schools Regional Assistant Superintendent John Hill and several of his colleagues gathered 16 books out of media centers Tuesday morning. County Citizens Defending Freedom, a conservative political group, complained to Superintendent Frederick Heid that the novels, graphic novels, autobiographies, and sex education books contain pornographic material harmful to children.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell’s little black book under FBI review, says report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf6164c9a353d7cfdf6db2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf6164c9a353d7cfdf6db2/</guid><description>Ghislaine Maxwell’s little black book under FBI review, says report
Summary Convicted sex trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell’s “little black book” of contacts is under FBI review according to a report. A source told The Mirror : “Whereas Epstein brought the cash, Maxwell brought the contacts.”“She opened up a world to her then-lover he could only have dreamt of,” they continued. During Maxwell’s four-week trial, the 97-page contact book was not made public under an agreement reached between the defence and prosecution.</description></item></channel></rss>