<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>policy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/policy/</link><description>Recent content in policy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:17:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Investors force Home Depot to review wood-sourcing policy over logging concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c6a2fffa2675311b3dfb1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c6a2fffa2675311b3dfb1/</guid><description>Environmental science and conservation news
Highlights Some of Home Depot&amp;rsquo;s plywood is allegedly sourced from vulnerable forests in Ecuador’s Chocó region and the Brazilian Cerrado. A proposal passed requiring the home improvement giant to reevaluate policies related to sustainability certifications of wood suppliers. Investors and conservationists have pressured Home Depot to clean up its supply chain. Home Depot has around 2,300 locations across North America and a significant wood importer. The company doesn’t offer specific figures on how much it imports from where wood comes from, but has no specific limits on where it buys it.</description></item><item><title>Nasdaq wraps its worst month in nearly 14 years as recession fears grow stronger</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e0d5361eafff5df2305ff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 04:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e0d5361eafff5df2305ff/</guid><description>The Nasdaq fell 4.2% on Friday, dragged down by Amazon&amp;rsquo;s 15% drop. The S&amp;amp;P 500 dropped about 3.6% and the Dow dropped about 940 points, or 2.8%. The
Highlights The Nasdaq fell 4.2% on Friday, dragged down by Amazon&amp;rsquo;s 15% drop. The S&amp;amp;P 500 dropped about 3.6% and the Dow dropped about 940 points, or 2.8%, on Friday. An ever-growing number of headwinds are leaving investors unsure of what comes next.</description></item><item><title>FAA chief wants zero tolerance for unruly air passengers to continue</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62448233ba0b47bd0a24ed86/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:16:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62448233ba0b47bd0a24ed86/</guid><description>The outgoing head of the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Tuesday the agency&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;zero tolerance policy&amp;quot; for addressing unruly passengers should remain in place indefinitely.
Highlights The outgoing head of the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Tuesday the agency&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;zero tolerance policy&amp;rdquo; for addressing unruly passengers should remain in place indefinitely. FAA Administrator Steve Dickson told reporters the policy first imposed in January 2021 should remain even if the Biden administration decides to lift a mandate requiring masks onboard airplanes.</description></item><item><title>TikTok bans misgendering, deadnaming trans people</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620470a7cf6175ed7d91ce69/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620470a7cf6175ed7d91ce69/</guid><description>The social media giant TikTok on Tuesday explicitly banned certain types of anti-LGBTQ content and speech on its platform.
Highlights The social media giant TikTok on Tuesday explicitly banned certain types of anti-LGBTQ content and speech on its platform. The company is also prohibiting “content that supports or promotes conversion therapy programs,” referring to a discredited practice that seeks to stop someone from being LGBTQ. The policy update follows pressure from GLAAD, an LGBTQ media advocacy nonprofit, and UltraViolet, a national gender justice advocacy group.</description></item><item><title>The unvaccinated are now forbidden to use public transportation in the Philippines starting tomorrow</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e479a4d7f61f495c257432/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e479a4d7f61f495c257432/</guid><description>Summary The Department of Transportation (DOTr) and its attached agencies are all geared up to implement the “No Vaccination, No Ride” policy in all public transportation to, from, and within Metro Manila starting Monday, Jan. 17. (Ali Vicoy / MANILA BULLETIN)The railway, road, maritime, and aviation sectors have issued the guidelines for the implementation of Department Order No. 2022–001 which prohibits unvaccinated individuals from using public transportation in the National Capital Region (NCR).</description></item></channel></rss>