<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>head on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/head/</link><description>Recent content in head on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 22:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/head/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An Indiana teacher granted early retirement after hitting a student in the face is charged with battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223e0464af0841f6b89842e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223e0464af0841f6b89842e/</guid><description>A now-retired Indiana high school teacher who was arrested after video showed him hitting a student during a confrontation over wearing a hooded sweatshirt on school grounds was charged Friday with battery, according to court documents.
Highlights Michael Hosinski, 61, was arrested after video showed him hitting a student during a confrontation over wearing a hooded sweatshirt on school grounds. The incident occurred February 25 at Jimtown High School in Elkhart, Indiana.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina officer accidentally shoots son in the head, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbf97b9f7774fa6b661a1b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 06:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbf97b9f7774fa6b661a1b/</guid><description>A Jacksonville police officer is under investigation after authorities said he accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head.
Summary Authorities in North Carolina said a 15-year-old male was seriously hurt after his father, a police officer, shot him in the head. The father and the son were not immediately identified, though investigators said the father is a part of the nearby Jacksonville Police Department. The review was not comprehensive, due to the sheer number of U.</description></item></channel></rss>