<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>apologizes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/apologizes/</link><description>Recent content in apologizes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 03:47:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/apologizes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disney apologizes to couple whose marriage proposal was thwarted by employee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eca18c638c967bf1e0dc6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eca18c638c967bf1e0dc6/</guid><description>Disney says, &amp;lsquo;We regret how this was handled.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights A viral video first posted on Reddit last week showed a man getting on one knee to propose to his girlfriend on a platform in front of the Sleeping Beauty Castle at Disneyland, Paris. An employee rushed up and snatches the ring box out of the man’s hands and ushers the couple off the platform, the video shows. &amp;ldquo;We have apologized to the couple involved and offered to make it right,&amp;rdquo; a Disney spokesperson said.</description></item><item><title>Will Smith Apologizes To Chris Rock After Slapping Him At The Oscars: “I Was Out Of Line And I Was Wrong”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242705bb1aa29accb57e836/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 02:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242705bb1aa29accb57e836/</guid><description>Will Smith Apologizes To Chris Rock After Slapping Him At The Oscars: &amp;quot;I Was Out Of Line And I Was Wrong&amp;quot;
Highlights The best way to compete is to find the best and worst of the best of the year. The best ways to compete are to compete with the best, the worst and the best. CNN will try to find out what the best way possible to compete in the best forum to compete against each other on CNN.</description></item><item><title>School apologizes after teacher leads California preschoolers in anti-Biden chant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bfdb18d179c860cc88f3a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bfdb18d179c860cc88f3a/</guid><description>A Southern California private school apologized to parents after a teacher shared a video last month of her leading preschool students in a chant denouncing President Joe Biden.
Highlights The video shows the unnamed teacher asking the 4- and 5-year-olds, &amp;ldquo;Who’s our president?” The teacher then asks, “What do we want to do with him?&amp;rdquo; The students shout back, &amp;ldquo;We want him out!” It&amp;rsquo;s unclear what, if any, disciplinary action was taken against the teacher.</description></item><item><title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. apologized Tuesday after critics, including members of his own family, blasted him for implying Anne Frank had more freedom in hiding from the Nazis than people have today under U.S. vaccine policies.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f140a5e4130d8cb46016b1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f140a5e4130d8cb46016b1/</guid><description>Robert F.
Summary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. apologized Tuesday after critics, including members of his own family, blasted him for implying that Anne Frank had more freedom in hiding from the Nazis than people have today under U.S. vaccination policies. &amp;ldquo;I apologize for my reference to Anne Frank, especially to families that suffered the Holocaust horrors,&amp;rdquo; he tweeted. You could hide in an attic like Anne Frank did,” he said at the Defeat the Mandates rally.</description></item><item><title>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</guid><description>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds
Summary Hamtramck judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weedsHamtramck Judge Alexis Krot has apologized to an elderly cancer patient she berated and threatened with jail time over some unkempt weeds outside his home. &amp;ldquo;I made a mistake,&amp;rdquo; Krot said in a statement shared with the Free Press by the court Thursday. Related: Michigan lawmaker to file complaint against Hamtramck judge who berated elderly manKrot has drawn widespread condemnation and media attention over her comments made during an online court hearing last week that was captured on a Zoom video that circulated on social media.</description></item></channel></rss>