<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>apologizes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/apologizes/</link><description>Recent content in apologizes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:18:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/apologizes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. apologized Tuesday after critics, including members of his own family, blasted him for implying Anne Frank had more freedom in hiding from the Nazis than people have today under U.S. vaccine policies.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f140a5e4130d8cb46016b1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:18:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f140a5e4130d8cb46016b1/</guid><description>Robert F.
Summary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. apologized Tuesday after critics, including members of his own family, blasted him for implying that Anne Frank had more freedom in hiding from the Nazis than people have today under U.S. vaccination policies. &amp;ldquo;I apologize for my reference to Anne Frank, especially to families that suffered the Holocaust horrors,&amp;rdquo; he tweeted. You could hide in an attic like Anne Frank did,” he said at the Defeat the Mandates rally.</description></item><item><title>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</guid><description>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds
Summary Hamtramck judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weedsHamtramck Judge Alexis Krot has apologized to an elderly cancer patient she berated and threatened with jail time over some unkempt weeds outside his home. &amp;ldquo;I made a mistake,&amp;rdquo; Krot said in a statement shared with the Free Press by the court Thursday. Related: Michigan lawmaker to file complaint against Hamtramck judge who berated elderly manKrot has drawn widespread condemnation and media attention over her comments made during an online court hearing last week that was captured on a Zoom video that circulated on social media.</description></item></channel></rss>