<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>victim on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/victim/</link><description>Recent content in victim on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 10:12:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/victim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Argument leads to fatal shooting in checkout line of grocery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200f0870c2638ac3acadb69/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 10:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200f0870c2638ac3acadb69/</guid><description>An argument in the checkout line of a South Florida grocery store escalated into a fatal shooting
Highlights Argument started in checkout line of Publix in upscale neighborhood of Coral Gables. Four people were shot Saturday night at Player’s Sports Bar and Grill in North Lauderdale. In Orlando, police are searching for a suspect in a fatal shooting at a banquet hall early Sunday. One victim has injuries that are believed to be life-threatening, sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said in a news release.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pushed to Her Death in Front of Oncoming Train at Times Square Station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</guid><description>Police have taken a person of interest into custody with a history of prior arrests.
Summary An Asian woman was pushed to her death at a subway station in Times Square on Saturday morning in what city officials are calling an &amp;ldquo;unprovoked&amp;rdquo; attack. At an afternoon press conference held a host of city officials, police said there appeared to be no connection between the victim and her attacker. #BREAKING: @NYPDTransit says a woman was killed after being shoved onto the subway tracks and into the path of a southbound R train at Times Square this morning.</description></item></channel></rss>