<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>duke on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/duke/</link><description>Recent content in duke on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/duke/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prince Andrew faces calls to pay for his own security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</guid><description>Growing clamour for royal to lose dukedom and taxpayer-funded Scotland Yard security detail
Summary The Duke of York faces calls to pay for his own security and relinquish his dukedom after being stripped of his military affiliations and royal patronages in the fallout over the civil sexual assault case against him. The calls come as his accuser, Virginia Giuffre, welcomed the New York court ruling that paved the way for her lawsuit against Prince Andrew to proceed to trial, as she pledged to “continue to expose the truth”.</description></item><item><title>Veterans ask Queen to strip Prince Andrew of honorary military titles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</guid><description>Duke will no longer use HRH title in any official capacity, and will fight US sexual assault lawsuit as private citizen
Summary In a devastating blow to Prince Andrew, who was born His Royal Highness, Buckingham Palace also said he would no longer use the HRH royal style in any official capacity. Buckingham Palace said in a statement on Thursday: “With the Queen’s approval and agreement, the Duke of York’s military affiliations and royal patronages have been returned to the Queen.</description></item><item><title>Judge says Prince Andrew cannot block lawsuit from accuser Virginia Giuffre on grounds she no longer lives in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1f65925409083e7270f82/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1f65925409083e7270f82/</guid><description>The written order comes three days before the release of details of a 2009 settlement agreement between Jeffrey Epstein and Virginia Giuffre - an agreement lawyers for the Duke of York say protects him from claims such as those brought by Ms Giuffre.
Summary Ms Giuffre alleges she was abused by the prince multiple times in 2001, while she was being sexually assaulted by financier Jeffrey Epstein. The written order was filed three days before the release of details of a 2009 settlement agreement between Epstein and Ms Giuffre.</description></item></channel></rss>