<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ice on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ice/</link><description>Recent content in ice on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 11:10:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hudson mayor suggests ice fishing could lead to prostitution in ice shanties</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204f28e00f6a39d1a23da81/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 11:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204f28e00f6a39d1a23da81/</guid><description>Hudson Mayor Craig Shubert suggests ice fishing could lead to prostitution. Shubert made the comments during a Hudson City Council meeting on Tuesday. Council president: &amp;quot;A number of residents&amp;quot; have requested permission to ice fish on Hudson Springs Lake.
Highlights Hudson Mayor Craig Shubert suggests ice fishing in the city could lead to prostitution. Shubert made the comments during a Hudson City Council meeting on Tuesday. Council President Chris Foster said &amp;ldquo;a number of residents&amp;rdquo; have requested permission to ice fish on Hudson Springs Lake.</description></item><item><title>Mt. Everest's highest glacier lost 2,000 years worth of ice since the 1990s</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62049e916292795fa96f27cf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62049e916292795fa96f27cf/</guid><description>Even the world&amp;rsquo;s tallest mountain is not safe from climate change.
Highlights Scientists found that the South Col Glacier is losing ice 80 times faster than it took for ice to accumulate on the glacier&amp;rsquo;s surface. The glacier is currently losing several decades worth of ice accumulation every year. The melt could have serious impacts on the mountain, and those who live near it. Future research must focus on how widely these melting trends apply to other glaciers at the top of the world, the researchers concluded.</description></item><item><title>US Coast Guard working to rescue 20 people trapped on floating ice on Lake Erie</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62008ec76df7554c6bb71dc4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62008ec76df7554c6bb71dc4/</guid><description>Eighteen people were rescued from an ice floe that separated from land near Catawba Island in Lake Erie, the US Coast Guard said Sunday.
Highlights A sheet of floating ice broke away while the individuals were snowmobiling. Authorities used a Coast Guard Station Marblehead airboat and an Air Station Detroit helicopter to rescue the group. A &amp;ldquo;good Samaritan&amp;rdquo; with an airboat also assisted with the operation. The helicopter lifted seven people, the Coast Guard airboat rescued four and the person helping with another airboat rescue the other seven, Coast Guard says.</description></item></channel></rss>