<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>la on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/la/</link><description>Recent content in la on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/la/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FOX 11 Los Angeles: 2 maintenance workers die after fentanyl exposure at downtown LA apartment complex.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fc758b7d9f8ec1d8d5e42/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fc758b7d9f8ec1d8d5e42/</guid><description>Two maintenance workers are dead after police believe they may have been exposed to fentanyl at a downtown Los Angeles apartment complex.
Highlights Los Angeles Police Department responded to a hazmat call in the 800 block of South Olive Street a little before 11 a.m. Thursday. When officers arrived at the apartment complex, they found two unconscious men unconscious. Luis Garcia and John Black, who were maintenance workers at the building, were pronounced dead at the scene.</description></item><item><title>LA jail guards routinely punch incarcerated people in the head, monitors find | Los Angeles sheriff’s department accused of hours-long group strip-search as court report adds to string of scandals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251249317adc028ae6f48a6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 06:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251249317adc028ae6f48a6/</guid><description>Los Angeles sheriff’s department accused of hours-long group strip-search as court report adds to string of scandals
Highlights Los Angeles sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department appears to be routinely violating use-of-force policies, court-appointed monitors say. Guards have punched incarcerated people in the head and subjected them to a “humiliating” group strip-search where they were forced to wait undressed for hours. Guards who used force in violation of policy were at times sent to “remedial training” but that “actual discipline is seldom imposed” The report raises further concerns about the department’s use of the “Wrap” device, which functions like a full-body restraining jacket and is used to ‘immobilize’ people.</description></item><item><title>France seizes luxury yacht of Russian energy boss and Putin confidant Sechin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221e651b8e17bb41496f8a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 10:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221e651b8e17bb41496f8a4/</guid><description>The French government on Thursday said it had seized a superyacht owned by a company linked to Igor Sechin, chief executive of Russian energy giant Rosneft and close confidant of President Vladimir P…
Highlights The vessel, Amore Vero, was seized at a shipyard at La Ciotat, near Marseille, the finance ministry said. The 85.6-metre (280 ft) boat was made by Netherlands-based yacht builder Oceanco and includes a swimming pool that turns into a helipad, as well as multi-decks including one with a jacuzzi.</description></item><item><title>Actress Lindsey Pearlman found dead after going missing in LA</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62121417c05200d0928ec69f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62121417c05200d0928ec69f/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Actor Lindsey Erin Pearlman, who had roles in “General Hospital,” “American Housewife” and other shows, was found dead days after she was reported missing in Los Angeles, authorities said.
Highlights Lindsey Erin Pearlman, 43, was last seen around noon last Sunday, ABC 7 reported. Her body was found Friday morning, Feb. 18, 2022, when officers responded to a call for a death investigation in a residential neighborhood of Hollywood.</description></item><item><title>LA schools to require students to wear non-cloth face masks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread. Starting Monday, students must wear “well-fitted, non-cloth masks with a nose wire” at all times, including outdoors, the district announced.
Summary LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread.</description></item></channel></rss>