<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gofundme on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gofundme/</link><description>Recent content in gofundme on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 17:15:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gofundme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trucker convoy GoFundMe suspended after reaching $10.1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc0d892aa115f6a9ab0c9c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 17:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc0d892aa115f6a9ab0c9c/</guid><description>GoFundMe has suspended a fundraiser for the &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; of truckers and supporters who have tied up downtown Ottawa while protesting vaccine mandates.
Highlights GoFundMe suspends fundraiser for the &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; of truckers and supporters. The fundraiser has raised more than $10 million and is currently under review. It&amp;rsquo;s the second time the website has suspended access to the money. Truckers have tied up downtown Ottawa while protesting vaccine mandates. The Freedom Convoy 2022 fundraiser states in its description that money will go towards paying for the cost of the truckers’ journey to Ottawa, including fuel, food and shelter, with leftover funds being given to “a credible Veterans organization which will be chosen by the donors’s donors” The fundraiser had been declared the second largest in Canada, smaller only than the fundraiser created for the Humboldt Broncos in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Michigan diner owner who defied state shutdown dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c448bf11f4d88429c1eebc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c448bf11f4d88429c1eebc/</guid><description>Summary BRANCH COUNTY, MI – A diner owner who kept his restaurant open in defiance of state shutdowns has died after more than a two-month battle with COVID-19. He owned the Quincy Diner, 174 E. Chicago St. (U.S. 12) in the village of Quincy. He kept the restaurant open in December 2020, in violation of the partial shutdown ordered by the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services. Related: ‘I’d have lost the business.</description></item></channel></rss>