<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suspend on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspend/</link><description>Recent content in suspend on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 08:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Coast Guard in Louisiana searching for 3 minors last seen entering Mississippi River | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626659147c37159639781d22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 08:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626659147c37159639781d22/</guid><description>The search for three children who were last seen entering the Mississippi River in New Orleans Saturday evening has been suspended, the Coast Guard said.
Highlights The search for three children who were last seen entering the Mississippi River in New Orleans has been suspended. A 15-year-old boy and two girls, ages 14 and eight, have been missing since Saturday evening. Officials didn&amp;rsquo;t say how and why the children entered the water.</description></item><item><title>Spotify says it will suspend service in Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e7863fec466ed1fa751f4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 02:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e7863fec466ed1fa751f4/</guid><description>Spotify Technology SA said on Friday it will suspend its streaming service in Russia in response to the country&amp;rsquo;s new media law.
Highlights Spotify Technology SA said on Friday it will suspend its streaming service in Russia in response to the country&amp;rsquo;s new media law. The audio streaming platform closed its office in Russia indefinitely earlier this month, citing what it described as Moscow&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;unprovoked attack on Ukraine&amp;rdquo; Russia&amp;rsquo;s new legislation makes it illegal to report any event that could discredit the Russian military.</description></item><item><title>Besieged Ukrainian city cancels evacuations, accuses Russia of breaking cease-fire</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245174e0f923e3e185f8ca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 06:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245174e0f923e3e185f8ca/</guid><description>Russia said Saturday it was declaring a temporary cease-fire in the key Ukrainian port city Mariupol, which it has besieged for days, to allow the creation of humanitarian corridors to evacuate civilians.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin says western sanctions are “the equivalent of war’s” Putin warns that any move to create a no-fly zone above Ukraine would be viewed as “participation” in the conflict. Israel&amp;rsquo;s prime minister meets with Putin in Moscow to discuss security, financial support for Ukraine and the continuation of sanctions.</description></item></channel></rss>