<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>foreign on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/foreign/</link><description>Recent content in foreign on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:10:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/foreign/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ireland tells Russia that naval exercises off our coast 'not welcome'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</guid><description>Mr Coveney said that Foreign Ministers will be pushing Russia to &amp;quot;defuse tensions&amp;quot; along the Ukrainian border, where it has amassed troops in recent &amp;hellip;
Summary The Government has told Russia that naval exercises off the Irish coast are &amp;ldquo;not welcome&amp;rdquo;, but Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney has accepted that they are legal. Russian naval exercises are due to take place in early February, approximately 240km off the southwest coast and within Ireland’s Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) but not in Ireland’s territorial waters.</description></item><item><title>EU ready to impose "never-seen-before" sanctions if Russia attacks Ukraine, Denmark says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eedb268ccd5ae13ee82547/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eedb268ccd5ae13ee82547/</guid><description>The European Union called on Russia on Monday to defuse tensions over Ukraine and reaffirmed that Moscow would face &amp;quot;massive&amp;quot; consequences if it attacked its neighbour.
Summary The EU&amp;rsquo;s 27 foreign ministers, meeting in Brussels, said the bloc &amp;ldquo;condemns Russia&amp;rsquo;s continued aggressive actions and threats against Ukraine and calls on Russia to de-escalate.&amp;rdquo; Denmark said the EU would be ready to impose &amp;ldquo;never-seen-before&amp;rdquo; economic sanctions on Russia. The European Commission, the EU executive body, proposed a 1.</description></item><item><title>Germany signals it could halt gas pipeline if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</guid><description>Germany signalled on Tuesday that it could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if Moscow invades Ukraine, and Western nations rallied behind Kyiv over a Russian troop buildup that has stoked fears of war.
Summary As fears of conflict rose, Britain said this week it had begun supplying Ukraine with anti-tank weapons, Canada&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister visited Ukraine and German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock held talks in Moscow and Kyiv to try to ease tensions.</description></item><item><title>‘There is no money left’: Covid crisis leaves Sri Lanka on brink of bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</guid><description>Half a million people have sunk into poverty since the pandemic struck, with rising costs forcing many to cut back on food
Summary Sri Lanka is facing a deepening financial and humanitarian crisis with fears it could go bankrupt in 2022 as inflation rises to record levels, food prices rocket and its coffers run dry. One of the most pressing problems for Sri Lanka is its huge foreign debt burden.</description></item></channel></rss>