<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>foreign on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/foreign/</link><description>Recent content in foreign on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/foreign/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finland's parliament votes yes to NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283f315e7677f707da6610e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283f315e7677f707da6610e/</guid><description>Finland&amp;rsquo;s parliament on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a proposal to apply for membership of the NATO military alliance in a historic policy shift prompted by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Finland&amp;rsquo;s parliament on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a proposal to apply for membership of the NATO military alliance in a historic policy shift prompted by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Of 200 lawmakers, 188 voted in favour and eight against the application, Speaker Matti Vanhanen said.</description></item><item><title>Israel denounced Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov for suggesting that Nazi leader Adolf Hitler had Jewish roots, and demanded an apology from Moscow</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627004ad3a8ef829637c910f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 16:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627004ad3a8ef829637c910f/</guid><description>Israel lambasted Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov on Monday for claiming that Adolf Hitler had Jewish origins, saying it was an &amp;quot;unforgivable&amp;quot; falsehood that debased the horrors of the Nazi Holocaust.
Highlights Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov says Adolf Hitler had Jewish origins. Israeli foreign ministry summons Russian ambassador and demands apology. Claims were made in a signal of sharply deteriorating relations with Moscow. Ukraine says Russia is &amp;ldquo;full of hatred&amp;rdquo; for other nations.</description></item><item><title>S&amp;amp;P downgrade indicates Russia headed for historic default</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252760fbed6069a1a9b2bc3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 06:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252760fbed6069a1a9b2bc3/</guid><description>BOSTON (AP) — The credit ratings agency Standard &amp;amp; Poor&amp;rsquo;s has downgraded its assessment of Russia’s ability to repay foreign debt, signaling rising prospects that Moscow will soon default on external loans for the first time in more than a century.
Highlights S&amp;amp;P Global Ratings issued the downgrade to “selective default” late Friday after Russia arranged to make foreign bond payments in rubles on Monday when they were due in dollars.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin vet says aides would kill Putin before sharing ‘bad news,’ now Putin orders house arrests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235823fb21e3f2dd3e57fa6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235823fb21e3f2dd3e57fa6/</guid><description>Vladimir Putin has now put some of his own intelligence officials under house arrest, according to sources who spoke to The New York Times, as Russia suffers a high death toll in its Ukraine invasion. The report suggests Putin may be insulated from solid information, or worried that these aides might try to overthrow him, as former Russian Foreign Minister Andrei Kozyrev told MSNBC in a recent interview. In this segment, MSNBC’s Ari Melber reports on the intrigue at the Kremlin, with analysis from Council on Foreign Relations President Richard Haass, who says Putin may be &amp;quot;paranoid&amp;quot; about his aides trying to oust him, and NYU history professor, Ruth Ben-Ghiat.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s Foreign Affairs Minister: Russian troops will launch missiles on Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62223b774fe8e8b6d8a1da28/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62223b774fe8e8b6d8a1da28/</guid><description>Ukrainian Minister of Foreign Affairs Dmytro Kuleba stated that in order to execute its information attack on Ukraine, Russia intends to strike its own territory.
Highlights Minister of Foreign Affairs Dmytro Kuleba said Russia will lose the information war with Ukraine. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s tactic has been to &amp;ldquo;uncover these provocations before they are committed,&amp;rdquo; he said. Russia is preparing provocations to improve its position in the information field, he said. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defence publishes this information to block misinformation along the lines of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s attack on Russian territory, he added.</description></item><item><title>Ireland tells Russia that naval exercises off our coast 'not welcome'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</guid><description>Mr Coveney said that Foreign Ministers will be pushing Russia to &amp;quot;defuse tensions&amp;quot; along the Ukrainian border, where it has amassed troops in recent &amp;hellip;
Summary The Government has told Russia that naval exercises off the Irish coast are &amp;ldquo;not welcome&amp;rdquo;, but Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney has accepted that they are legal. Russian naval exercises are due to take place in early February, approximately 240km off the southwest coast and within Ireland’s Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) but not in Ireland’s territorial waters.</description></item><item><title>EU ready to impose "never-seen-before" sanctions if Russia attacks Ukraine, Denmark says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eedb268ccd5ae13ee82547/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eedb268ccd5ae13ee82547/</guid><description>The European Union called on Russia on Monday to defuse tensions over Ukraine and reaffirmed that Moscow would face &amp;quot;massive&amp;quot; consequences if it attacked its neighbour.
Summary The EU&amp;rsquo;s 27 foreign ministers, meeting in Brussels, said the bloc &amp;ldquo;condemns Russia&amp;rsquo;s continued aggressive actions and threats against Ukraine and calls on Russia to de-escalate.&amp;rdquo; Denmark said the EU would be ready to impose &amp;ldquo;never-seen-before&amp;rdquo; economic sanctions on Russia. The European Commission, the EU executive body, proposed a 1.</description></item><item><title>Germany signals it could halt gas pipeline if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</guid><description>Germany signalled on Tuesday that it could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if Moscow invades Ukraine, and Western nations rallied behind Kyiv over a Russian troop buildup that has stoked fears of war.
Summary As fears of conflict rose, Britain said this week it had begun supplying Ukraine with anti-tank weapons, Canada&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister visited Ukraine and German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock held talks in Moscow and Kyiv to try to ease tensions.</description></item><item><title>‘There is no money left’: Covid crisis leaves Sri Lanka on brink of bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</guid><description>Half a million people have sunk into poverty since the pandemic struck, with rising costs forcing many to cut back on food
Summary Sri Lanka is facing a deepening financial and humanitarian crisis with fears it could go bankrupt in 2022 as inflation rises to record levels, food prices rocket and its coffers run dry. One of the most pressing problems for Sri Lanka is its huge foreign debt burden. “When the economic crisis deepens beyond redemption, it is inevitable that the country will have a financial crisis too,” he said.</description></item></channel></rss>