<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>standards on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/standards/</link><description>Recent content in standards on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/standards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moscow Exchange won't resume stock trading on Wednesday - cenbank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fb43e61b0b7aaa278d207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fb43e61b0b7aaa278d207/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank kept stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange suspended for a third day in a row on Wednesday, but said it would allow a limited range of operations for the first time this week.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank kept stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange suspended for a third day in a row on Wednesday. The central bank said it would allow a limited range of operations for the first time this week.</description></item><item><title>Russia calls in Canadian envoy, complains over protests outside its embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</guid><description>Russia threatened Canada on Monday with retaliation if it failed to ensure the safety of its diplomats and complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates.
Highlights Russia says it has called in Canada&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to Moscow to lodge a formal protest. Russia has complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates. Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry says it had called in the ambassador to Russia&amp;rsquo;s embassy in Moscow.</description></item></channel></rss>