<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vegas on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vegas/</link><description>Recent content in vegas on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 13:34:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vegas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>7 wounded in Vegas biker gangs freeway shooting, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62961940cce8589daff9d9bf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62961940cce8589daff9d9bf/</guid><description>Police say rival motorcycle gangs were involved in a metro Las Vegas freeway shooting that injured seven people over the weekend
Highlights Police say rival motorcycle gangs were involved in a metro Las Vegas freeway shooting. Police say the shooting involved people associated with the Hells Angels and the Vagos gangs. Seven people were injured in the shooting over the weekend, police say. Three men were arrested on suspicion on charges of attempted murder with a deadly weapon and other crimes, police said.</description></item><item><title>A slot machine in Las Vegas malfunctioned and didn't tell a tourist they won. The gaming board tracked them down</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200b8fbf7224fc35a9c695f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 06:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200b8fbf7224fc35a9c695f/</guid><description>A tourist in Las Vegas hit the jackpot on a slot machine last month, but he was never informed due to a malfunction in the machine, according to gaming officials.
Highlights A tourist in Las Vegas hit the jackpot on a slot machine last month, but he was never informed due to a malfunction in the machine. Now after an exhaustive search, the Nevada Gaming Control Board says they have identified the winner of the nearly $230,000 prize.</description></item><item><title>Harry Reid, former Senate majority leader and Democratic kingmaker, dies at 82 - The Nevada Independent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</guid><description>Over more than three decades of service in Congress, Reid earned a reputation for fighting relentlessly to protect his home state and everyday Americans. As Senate Democratic leader for a dozen years, he played an instrumental role in passing the Affordable Care Act and shepherding through Congress pivotal economic recovery legislation in the wake of the Great Recession.
Summary He also turned the Nevada State Democratic Party into a well-oiled political operation — nicknamed the Reid Machine — responsible for securing numerous Democratic victories in close races over the last decade.</description></item></channel></rss>