<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>administration on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/administration/</link><description>Recent content in administration on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 08:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amid boycotts, US scrambling to make Summit of the Americas a success</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62932aabe9234171a7654b98/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 08:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62932aabe9234171a7654b98/</guid><description>President Joe Biden is hosting the high-profile summit starting June 8 in Los Angeles.
Highlights The Summit of the Americas is slated to start June 8 in Los Angeles. Several leaders are threatening to boycott the summit because the U.S. has decided to not invite the governments of Venezuela and Nicaragua. The leaders of Bolivia, Antigua and Barbuda, and Guatemala have announced they will not attend. Mexico&amp;rsquo;s president Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has repeatedly said all of the region&amp;rsquo;s countries must be invited.</description></item><item><title>FAA chief wants zero tolerance for unruly air passengers to continue</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62448233ba0b47bd0a24ed86/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:16:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62448233ba0b47bd0a24ed86/</guid><description>The outgoing head of the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Tuesday the agency&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;zero tolerance policy&amp;quot; for addressing unruly passengers should remain in place indefinitely.
Highlights The outgoing head of the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Tuesday the agency&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;zero tolerance policy&amp;rdquo; for addressing unruly passengers should remain in place indefinitely. FAA Administrator Steve Dickson told reporters the policy first imposed in January 2021 should remain even if the Biden administration decides to lift a mandate requiring masks onboard airplanes.</description></item><item><title>U.S. plans to cut ties with targeted Russian banks if Ukraine is invaded - sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213bae4ea9ae74210f6c6e4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213bae4ea9ae74210f6c6e4/</guid><description>President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has prepared an initial package of sanctions against Russia that includes barring U.S. financial institutions from processing transactions for major Russian banks, three people familiar with the matter said.
Highlights President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has prepared an initial package of sanctions against Russia that includes barring U.S. financial institutions from processing transactions for major Russian banks, three people familiar with the matter said. The measures aim to hurt the Russian economy by cutting the &amp;ldquo;correspondent&amp;rdquo; banking relationships between targeted targeted Russian banks and American banks that enable international payments.</description></item><item><title>US President Biden predicts Russia will invade Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e979074defe592b9b65ea2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 15:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e979074defe592b9b65ea2/</guid><description>President Joe Biden predicted Wednesday that Russia will invade Ukraine, just as the United States launched a fresh effort to resolve the standoff.
Summary President Joe Biden predicted Wednesday that Russia will invade Ukraine, just as the United States launched a fresh effort to resolve the standoff and Moscow continued to mass troops on its neighbor&amp;rsquo;s doorstep. Biden said Putin “will be held accountable” and has “never have seen sanctions like the ones I promised will be imposed” if Russia makes further moves against Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Biden says his administration will make free high-quality face masks available to all Americans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0f57088a5c3d6cee53246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0f57088a5c3d6cee53246/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Thursday announced his administration would make &amp;quot;high-quality masks&amp;quot; available to Americans for free, as the US struggles to contain the new surge of the Omicron variant and hospitalizations from Covid-19 reach new highs.
Summary Washington (CNN) President Joe Biden on Thursday announced his administration would make &amp;ldquo;high-quality masks&amp;rdquo; available to Americans for free, as the US struggles to contain the new surge of the Omicron variant and hospitalizations from Covid-19 reach new highs.</description></item></channel></rss>