<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>administration on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/administration/</link><description>Recent content in administration on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 15:10:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US President Biden predicts Russia will invade Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e979074defe592b9b65ea2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 15:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e979074defe592b9b65ea2/</guid><description>President Joe Biden predicted Wednesday that Russia will invade Ukraine, just as the United States launched a fresh effort to resolve the standoff.
Summary President Joe Biden predicted Wednesday that Russia will invade Ukraine, just as the United States launched a fresh effort to resolve the standoff and Moscow continued to mass troops on its neighbor&amp;rsquo;s doorstep. Biden said Putin “will be held accountable” and has “never have seen sanctions like the ones I promised will be imposed” if Russia makes further moves against Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Biden says his administration will make free high-quality face masks available to all Americans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0f57088a5c3d6cee53246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0f57088a5c3d6cee53246/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Thursday announced his administration would make &amp;quot;high-quality masks&amp;quot; available to Americans for free, as the US struggles to contain the new surge of the Omicron variant and hospitalizations from Covid-19 reach new highs.
Summary Washington (CNN) President Joe Biden on Thursday announced his administration would make &amp;ldquo;high-quality masks&amp;rdquo; available to Americans for free, as the US struggles to contain the new surge of the Omicron variant and hospitalizations from Covid-19 reach new highs.</description></item></channel></rss>