<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>taken on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/taken/</link><description>Recent content in taken on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:11:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/taken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Marijuana violations have taken over 10,000 truck drivers off the road this year, adding more supply chain disruptions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289f009b321671c04f3045a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289f009b321671c04f3045a/</guid><description>The first quarter of 2022 saw a nearly 33% increase year over year in marijuana violations among commercial vehicle drivers. Stacker looks at the rise in truckers being pulled from the road and the potential effects on the supply chain.
Highlights As of April 1, 2022, 10,276 commercial vehicle drivers have tested positive for marijuana use. That’s a 32.6% increase year over year. Truck drivers who travel cross-country face inconsistent state regulations as 19 states have legalized recreational marijuana and 37 states permit it for medicinal purposes.</description></item><item><title>Horror in Shanghai as elderly man taken to morgue in body bag while still alive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272711640e9c85e802d4f69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 12:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272711640e9c85e802d4f69/</guid><description>An elderly Shanghai resident was mistakenly declared dead and taken to a morgue in a body bag, in the latest sign of dysfunction in the Covid-stricken city where millions of people remain under government-enforced lockdown.
Highlights Video shows the head of the man appearing from a yellow body bag. It is the latest sign of dysfunction in China&amp;rsquo;s most progressive and modern city. The video has since gone viral on China&amp;rsquo;s Twitter-like platform Weibo.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting: Suspect Frank James posted racist rants to YouTube for years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6257134ca769d476db4dc20e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 18:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6257134ca769d476db4dc20e/</guid><description>Frank James, now considered a suspect in connection with the Brooklyn subway shooting, posted a string of antagonistic video rants to a YouTube channel for years.
Highlights Frank James posted hour-long, profanity-laced rants on YouTube channel for years. Police have identified James as a person of interest in the Brooklyn subway shooting. James posted rants about race, politics and current events. At times, he sharply criticized Black Europeans and Americans using strings of slurs and racism, as well as women and the homeless.</description></item><item><title>War in Ukraine: Russian helicopter shot down by missile in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223c41f88bf8831307278f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 20:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223c41f88bf8831307278f9/</guid><description>The video, shared by Ukrainian armed forces, shows the helicopter being hit by a missile.
Highlights &amp;lsquo;Kherson is Ukraine&amp;rsquo;: Protests in city taken by Russia. Video, shared by Ukrainian armed forces, shows helicopter being hit by missile. Helicopter hit by a missile in video shared by Ukraine armed forces. Protests take place in the city of Kherson, which has been seized by Russia since 2008. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Melbourne man sets himself on fire while screaming about Dan Andrews' Covid vaccine mandates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</guid><description>A man has lit himself on fire in front of horrified diners in Richmond on Saturday while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates.
Summary A man has set himself and his car on fire in front of horrified diners while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates. The man emerged from a silver MG3 hatchback engulfed in flames near Church St in Richmond about 8pm on Saturday. A man has set himself and his MG3 hatch on fire in Richmond while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 mandates on Saturday (pictured)The bystanders helped restrain the man before police officers pinned him to the ground.</description></item></channel></rss>