<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>official on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/official/</link><description>Recent content in official on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 03:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/official/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia's 40-mile convoy has stalled on its way to Kyiv, a U.S. official says : NPR</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ee111d2f020d9d3bb14da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ee111d2f020d9d3bb14da/</guid><description>The convoy is apparently being hampered by fuel and food shortages, the official says. The news comes as Russia continues to concentrate attacks on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s largest cities: Kyiv and Kharkiv.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s 40-mile convoy has stalled on its way to Kyiv, a U.S. official says. The convoy is apparently being hampered by fuel and food shortages. Some elements within the military column are &amp;ldquo;literally out of gas&amp;rdquo; and having difficulty feeding their troops.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian president signs formal request to join EU</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d3a73cbe9d491678a4a05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d3a73cbe9d491678a4a05/</guid><description>European Union leaders may discuss the possibility of Ukrainian membership at an informal summit in March, a senior EU official said on Monday, adding the issue was important for Ukraine in discussions with Russia on ending the conflict. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said on Monday that he had signed an official request…
Highlights EU leaders may discuss possibility of Ukrainian membership at an informal summit in March, a senior EU official said on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Official: Police used fake DNA reports during interrogations.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03087cd2c300f48f763a1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03087cd2c300f48f763a1/</guid><description>VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — Virginia Beach police used forged documents that linked people&amp;rsquo;s DNA to a crime to get them to confess or cooperate with investigators, Virginia&amp;rsquo;s outgoing attorney general announced Wednesday.
Summary VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — Virginia Beach police used forged documents that linked people’s DNA to a crime to get them to confess or cooperate with investigators, Virginia’s outgoing attorney general announced Wednesday. Virginia Beach police serve a city of about 450,000 people along the state’s coast.</description></item><item><title>Capitol Police intelligence official says she sounded alarm about potential violence days before January 6 riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</guid><description>&amp;quot;We knew there were going to be thousands of protesters. And we knew there were gonna be extremists there,&amp;quot; the official said.
Summary Three days before the January 6 riot, a top Capitol Police intelligence official sounded the alarm about potential violence at the U.S. Capitol. Julie Farnam, now the acting director of intelligence for the Capitol Police, had been with the department for 72 days when violent protestors attacked the Capitol on January 6th.</description></item><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item></channel></rss>