<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>post on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/post/</link><description>Recent content in post on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 04:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Megachurch pastor arrested in sexual assault investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a023f4f3910eeab4fc630d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 04:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a023f4f3910eeab4fc630d/</guid><description>Bruxy Cavey, 57, has been arrested by Hamilton Policce for alleged sexual assault.
Highlights Pastor Bruxy Cavey, 57, has been arrested and charged with sexual assault by Hamilton police. An external investigation concluded he allegedly abused his power and sexually harassed a parishioner. Cavey was placed on leave at the end of last year as the church board investigated an allegation of sexual misconduct. He confirmed his resignation in a Mar.</description></item><item><title>Pulitzer Prizes award Washington Post for Jan. 6 coverage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a2cf6b08508efa4e49524/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a2cf6b08508efa4e49524/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The Washington Post won the Pulitzer Prize in public service journalism Monday for its coverage of the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol, an attack on democracy that was a shocking start to a tumultuous year that also saw the end of the United States’ longest war, in Afghanistan.
Highlights The Washington Post won the Pulitzer Prize in public service journalism for its coverage of the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Top Kremlin adviser becomes first high-ranking official to quit since invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c447b4642aa8e5374ed73/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 10:14:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c447b4642aa8e5374ed73/</guid><description>Russian government official Anatoly Chubais is reported to be the first high-ranking Kremlin representative to quit his post following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine
Highlights Anatoly Chubais was Putin&amp;rsquo;s special representative for ties with international organisations. He is the first high-ranking official to quit his post since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The 66-year-old oversaw privatisation in Russia following the collapse of the Soviet Union. Comes amid reports of Russia’s defence minister, Sergey Shoigu, disappearing with ‘heart problems’ Defence Minister is said to be carrying out a witch hunt of his closest allies to prevent information from being leaked to the West.</description></item><item><title>Kanye West Barred From Performing at Grammys, His Rep Confirms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623679dab9d8585295dd0692/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623679dab9d8585295dd0692/</guid><description>Kanye West&amp;rsquo;s planned performance at the 2022 Grammy Awards has been scrapped following his online posts, his rep has confirmed to E! News.
Highlights Kanye West was supposed to perform at the 2022 Grammy Awards. His rep confirmed a March 18 report from &amp;ldquo;The Blast&amp;rdquo; that the rapper has been canceled. The Recording Academy had never confirmed a planned performance by Kanye. The rapper is nominated for five Grammys for the 2022 show, which is set to take place on April 3.</description></item><item><title>Congress passes bill to shore up Postal Service, delivery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62281b7810efd61309c59e84/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62281b7810efd61309c59e84/</guid><description>The long-fought postal overhaul has been years in the making and comes amid widespread complaints about mail service slowdowns. Many Americans became dependent on the Postal Service during the COVID-19 crisis, but officials have repeatedly warned that without congressional action it would run out of cash by 2024.
Highlights The long-fought postal overhaul has been years in the making and comes amid widespread complaints about mail service slowdowns. The bill would end a requirement that the Postal Service finance workers’ health care benefits ahead of time for the next 75 years.</description></item><item><title>'I thought it was a joke': Canada Post employee sent home for wearing N95 mask instead of company-provided cloth or disposable mask</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</guid><description>A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks.
Summary WINNIPEG -A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks. &amp;ldquo;Right away a supervisor came up to me and told me I can&amp;rsquo;t wear that mask,&amp;rdquo; said Gallagher.</description></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather sued by investors over alleged crypto scam</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df87d1dc5106ca49ff2b0b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df87d1dc5106ca49ff2b0b/</guid><description>A class action lawsuit accuses Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather of artificially inflating the price of the cryptocurrency EthereumMax.
Summary Kim Kardashian arrives for the 2018 Met Gala on May 7, 2018, at the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York. Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather are being sued over allegations they misled investors when promoting a little-known cryptocurrency called EthereumMax to their millions of social media followers. Kardashian caused a stir last year when she made an Instagram post promoting the EthereumMax token.</description></item><item><title>UK DJ Dimension becomes New Zealand's first Omicron community case after breaking quarantine rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd2eed5b3a592ea0807b3d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd2eed5b3a592ea0807b3d/</guid><description>On social media, UK drum and bass artist Dimension told followers he had tested positive for the Omicron variant while in New Zealand.
Summary UK DJ Dimension posted images of himself at a Waiheke Beach on Christmas Day. In a social media post late on Wednesday night, Dimension confirmed he had tested positive for the Omicron variant while in New Zealand. On social media, Dimension posted images of himself at a Waiheke Island beach on Christmas Day.</description></item><item><title>11-week Kellogg’s strike to end after multi-year agreement reached</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</guid><description>Description Summary The 11-week strike at Kellogg’s has come to an end after workers approved a contract with the company. Read more trending newsUnionized workers had been on strike since Oct. 5 in Michigan, Nebraska, Pennsylvania and Tennessee, The Washington Post reported.
The Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers’ International Union president Anthony Shelton said the contract makes gains for the 1,400 union workers and has no concessions. The five-year agreement has wage increases and cost-of-living adjustments the first year, in addition to the expansion of health care and retirement, the Post reported.</description></item></channel></rss>