<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>post on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/post/</link><description>Recent content in post on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK DJ Dimension becomes New Zealand's first Omicron community case after breaking quarantine rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd2eed5b3a592ea0807b3d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd2eed5b3a592ea0807b3d/</guid><description>On social media, UK drum and bass artist Dimension told followers he had tested positive for the Omicron variant while in New Zealand.
Summary UK DJ Dimension posted images of himself at a Waiheke Beach on Christmas Day. In a social media post late on Wednesday night, Dimension confirmed he had tested positive for the Omicron variant while in New Zealand. On social media, Dimension posted images of himself at a Waiheke Island beach on Christmas Day.</description></item><item><title>11-week Kellogg’s strike to end after multi-year agreement reached</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</guid><description>Description Summary The 11-week strike at Kellogg’s has come to an end after workers approved a contract with the company. Read more trending newsUnionized workers had been on strike since Oct. 5 in Michigan, Nebraska, Pennsylvania and Tennessee, The Washington Post reported.
The Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers’ International Union president Anthony Shelton said the contract makes gains for the 1,400 union workers and has no concessions.</description></item></channel></rss>