<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plans on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plans/</link><description>Recent content in plans on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 15:14:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Over Sandy Hook families’ objections, federal judge gives Alex Jones time to defend bankruptcy plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d523564eac54187309fcf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 15:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d523564eac54187309fcf/</guid><description>A federal judge gave Sandy Hook families awaiting defamation damages trials in&amp;hellip;
Highlights A federal judge agreed to hear motions to dismiss Alex Jones’ bankruptcies as “bad faith’s” filings. The judge also gave Jones attorneys enough breathing room to prepare an unhurried defense of their plan to pay the Sandy Hook families defamation damages Jones owes without putting Infowars out of business. Jones has suffered financially since he called the worst crime in Connecticut history “staged” and “manufactured” “a giant hoax,” his representatives said in court.</description></item><item><title>County grants approval for Amazon's helix-shaped HQ tower</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265cb71c87c0f62ccf02913/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 22:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265cb71c87c0f62ccf02913/</guid><description>FALLS CHURCH, Va. (AP) — The Arlington County Board gave unanimous approval Saturday to Amazon&amp;rsquo;s plans to build a unique, helix-shaped tower as the centerpiece of its emerging second headquarters in northern Virginia.
Highlights Amazon announced plans in February 2021 for the eye-catching, 350-foot tower to anchor the second phase of its redevelopment plans. The spiral design features a walkable ramp wrapping around the building with trees and greenery planted to resemble a mountain hike.</description></item><item><title>Google plans privacy change similar to Apple's, which wiped $230 billion off Facebook's market cap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620df5447e908e3320a09c77/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 07:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620df5447e908e3320a09c77/</guid><description>Google said it will continue to support the current identifiers for the next two years.
Highlights Google said it&amp;rsquo;s developing new privacy-focused replacements for its advertising ID, a unique string of characters that identifies the user&amp;rsquo;s device. The digital IDs in smartphones often help ad-tech companies track and share information about consumers. The changes could affect big companies that have relied on tracking users across apps, like Facebook parent Meta. Apple&amp;rsquo;s adjustments hit Meta particularly hard, with the social media company&amp;rsquo;s parent company losing $232 billion from its market cap in a single day, eventually pushing the total below $600 billion.</description></item><item><title>India's richest man is pouring more than $80 billion into green energy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1f29352ca7e76cd3ad3c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1f29352ca7e76cd3ad3c5/</guid><description>Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani is going big on green energy.
Summary Hong Kong (CNN Business) Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani is going big on green energy. The bulk of that money — about $67.7 billion — will go toward a new power plant and hydrogen system, the company said in a stock exchange filing . Reliance plans to make the massive investment over a 10-to-15-year period, and has already begun scouting for land for the 100-gigawatt capacity site.</description></item></channel></rss>