<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>search on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/search/</link><description>Recent content in search on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 20:12:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/search/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Oconto County Sheriff’s office is investigating allegations that Suring Public Schools officials stripped students down to their underwear while searching for vaping devices.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ab79adceec35b7221dc34/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 20:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ab79adceec35b7221dc34/</guid><description>SURING, Wis. (WLUK) – The Oconto County Sheriff’s office is investigating allegations that Suring Public Schools officials, including at least one administrator, stripped students down to their underwear while searching for vaping devices. Sheriff Todd Skarban tells FOX 11 an investigator has been conducting interviews and gathering information and he expects the findings will be sent to the Oconto County District Attorney on Monday or Tuesday.
Highlights Oconto County Sheriff’s office is investigating allegations that Suring Public Schools officials stripped students down to their underwear while searching for vaping devices.</description></item><item><title>Amir Locke shooting: hundreds protest in Minneapolis after police killing of Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200399b222e57fce50c1459/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 21:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200399b222e57fce50c1459/</guid><description>Demonstrators demand unconditional ban on ‘no-knock’ warrants after Locke, 22, was killed during a raid on an apartment this week
Highlights Police killed Amir Locke, 22, during &amp;lsquo;no-knock&amp;rsquo; raid on apartment earlier this week. Video showed Locke holding a gun as he twisted beneath blanket on sofa moments before he was shot. Police have said the officers were exercising a ‘no’knock” search warrant, which authorizes police to enter private property without first alerting occupants or announcing their presence.</description></item></channel></rss>