<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shows on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shows/</link><description>Recent content in shows on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 20:15:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maury Povich retires, ending a 31-season run of revealing who is the father</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238dcdbe2962bd436cfd660/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238dcdbe2962bd436cfd660/</guid><description>Get those paternity tests in now because “Maury” won’t help you find out whether you’re the father beyond this September. “Maury” is the latest daytime talker to announce that it’s ceasing production in 2022, in what is now amounting to a major shift in the daypart.
Highlights Maury Povich is ending his run and retiring after 24 seasons of hosting “Maury” for NBCUniversal Syndication Studios (and its predecessors) Povich’s exit comes as NBCUniversal also ends another first-run syndicated series, “Judge Jerry,” hosted by Jerry Springer, after three seasons.</description></item><item><title>Video shows man violently attack workers at COVID vaccine clinic in Tustin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db853837e71bddfba7f512/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db853837e71bddfba7f512/</guid><description>Video shows a man lash out and assault workers at a vaccine clinic in Tustin after he verbally attacked them and called staff &amp;quot;murderers.&amp;quot;
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos A violent attack on staff members that occurred last month at a COVID-19 vaccination clinic in Tustin resulted in a man&amp;rsquo;s arrest, police said. TUSTIN, Calif. (KABC) &amp;ndash; Staff at Families Together of Orange County said Friday they hoped the judicial system ensures employees and other health care workers are protected by the law following a violent attack at their clinic at the end of December.</description></item></channel></rss>