<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ruling on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ruling/</link><description>Recent content in ruling on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 05:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ruling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Calling a man bald counts as sexual harassment, UK judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f3cf888623cdc9d5ea1d5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 05:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f3cf888623cdc9d5ea1d5/</guid><description>Calling a man &amp;quot;bald&amp;quot; is now classed as sexual harassment, a judge in a U.K. employment tribunal has ruled.
Highlights U.K. employment tribunal ruled that the use of the word &amp;ldquo;bald&amp;rdquo; as an insult related to a &amp;ldquo;protected characteristic of sex&amp;rdquo; The tribunal compared calling a man bald to commenting on the size of woman&amp;rsquo;s breasts. The ruling was made on a case where the insult was alleged to have been used against Tony Finn, an electrician for the British Bung Manufacturing Company.</description></item><item><title>Brazil Supreme Court judge suspends messaging app Telegram, a key Bolsonaro platform</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236637dfab7621246b4b00d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236637dfab7621246b4b00d/</guid><description>A Supreme Court judge in Brazil ruled to block popular messaging application Telegram nationwide, barring one of far-right President Jair Bolsonaro&amp;rsquo;s favourite communication channels, in a decision p…
Highlights A Supreme Court judge in Brazil blocks Telegram, barring one of far-right President Jair Bolsonaro&amp;rsquo;s favourite communication channels. Judge cites Telegram&amp;rsquo;s failure to comply with orders from Brazilian authorities and remove messages found to contain disinformation. Decision comes as far right leader Bolsonara gears up to seek reelection in October, facing a popularity slump.</description></item></channel></rss>