<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>party on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/party/</link><description>Recent content in party on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:13:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Third night of unrest in Sweden over far-right anti-Islam rally | Sweden</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c2e8896148e3cee44190e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c2e8896148e3cee44190e/</guid><description>Demonstrators threw stones and burned vehicles during a protest against an anti-Islam event organised by Danish far-right Stram Kurs party
Highlights Police in Sweden move protest to a new location after violent clashes in Malmo. Stram Kurs party had planned to burn a Qur&amp;rsquo;an among other things. 12 police officers injured and four police vehicles set on fire in the city of Malmo, police say. Police say no injuries have been reported, but the situation is still tense in the town of Malmö, near Stockholm.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Corbyn barred from rejoining UK Labour party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f19a519d4c7d986087968b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 19:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f19a519d4c7d986087968b/</guid><description>The opposition leader for the better part of the 2010s was suspended by the party in October 2020 after his party was accused of systematic antisemitism.
Summary Jeremy Corbyn, a Labour Party MP and the United Kingdom’s former opposition leader from 2015-2020, was not reinstated as an MP in the party following a vote on Tuesday, international media reports. Today’s NEC vote and Keir Starmer’s ongoing decision to bar me from sitting as a Labour MP is disappointing.</description></item></channel></rss>