<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>millions on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/millions/</link><description>Recent content in millions on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 13:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/millions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Millions in Bitcoin pouring into Ukraine from donors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b79632c14cf4697ef1bad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b79632c14cf4697ef1bad/</guid><description>Thousands of anonymous donations are being made to the Ukrainian military in Bitcoin.
Highlights Thousands of anonymous donations are being made to the Ukrainian military in Bitcoin. At least one social media post was found to copy a legitimate tweet from an NGO, but with the author swapping the Bitcoin address, presumably for one of their own. The author of the post is believed to have swapped Bitcoin address for that of his own, according to Elliptic.</description></item><item><title>Scotland hopes to save wild salmon by planting millions of trees next to rivers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbe2804c3c50c0fbe89b0f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 14:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbe2804c3c50c0fbe89b0f/</guid><description>River Dee initiative comes as rising water temperature from climate heating threatens species’ survival
Highlights Scientists found that only 35% of Scotland’s rivers have adequate tree cover. In 2018, the year Scotland recorded the lowest rod catch for salmon since records began. Temperatures in 70% of salmon rivers were too warm for at least one day that summer. A coldwater species, Atlantic salmon prefer summer temperatures above 10C; at 33C, they cannot survive.</description></item></channel></rss>