<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>forces on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/forces/</link><description>Recent content in forces on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:14:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/forces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Harsh conditions mean Russian troops near Ukraine will need to be moved soon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62175a4ae9f12b29d3de9a6a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62175a4ae9f12b29d3de9a6a/</guid><description>Analysis: advance forces’ battle readiness will quickly degrade, giving Putin only days to choose invasion or retreat
Highlights Russian forces massing near Ukraine’s borders can only be used for a few days before they have to be sent back to nearby bases, experts believe. Russia&amp;rsquo;s President Vladimir Putin will come under increasing pressure to use them in a full invasion of Ukraine – or send them back to staging areas, but tens of thousands of kilometres away.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine warns Russia has 'almost completed' build-up of forces near border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</guid><description>Ukraine has warned that Russia has &amp;quot;almost completed&amp;quot; its build-up of forces that could be used for an offensive against the country, compounding fears that Moscow could launch an invasion at any time.
Summary The assessment called the situation &amp;ldquo;difficult,&amp;rdquo; and said Ukraine believes Russia is &amp;ldquo;trying to split and weaken the European Union and NATO.&amp;rdquo; Ukrainian military intelligence said Russia has deployed troops from its central and eastern regions to its western border &amp;ldquo;on a permanent basis.</description></item><item><title>Canada deploys special forces to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</guid><description>Global News has learned that a small contingent of Canadian special forces soldiers sent to aid Ukrainian government, plan for potential embassy evacuation should Russia invade.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailCanadian special forces operators have been deployed to Ukraine amid rising tensions between the NATO military alliance and Russia, Global News has learned. Sources told Global News that the Canadian special operations presence is part of an attempt by NATO allies to deter Russian aggression in Ukraine, and to identify ways to assist the Ukrainian government.</description></item></channel></rss>