<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>forces on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/forces/</link><description>Recent content in forces on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:12:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/forces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK says quarter of Russian battalion groups that invaded Ukraine are likely "ineffective"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62702cfbbe58e80ad7618a13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62702cfbbe58e80ad7618a13/</guid><description>A quarter of the Russian battalion groups that invaded Ukraine have likely now been rendered &amp;quot;ineffective,&amp;quot; according to the UK&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defence.
Highlights Russian forces are putting pressure on the front lines in Luhansk, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s easternmost region, as part of its renewed offensive. Head of military administration: Russian forces were laying waste to villages along front lines of the region and pressing forward. This scorched-earth strategy has forced Ukrainian military forces to pull back in some places, to avoid significant losses of life.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy urges Russian troops not to fight</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e7b88f638ac8553fbedbf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e7b88f638ac8553fbedbf/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine &amp;ndash; Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy switched into Russian in his nightly video address to urge Russian soldiers not to fight in Ukraine, saying even their generals expected that thousands of them would die.
Highlights Sweden says a Russian military plane has violated Swedish airspace. Up to 1,000 civilians are living beneath a Soviet-era steel plant in Mariupol, Ukrainian officials say. Russia has been recruiting new troops “with little motivation and little combat experience” for units gutted during the early weeks of the war.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine rejects deadline to surrender in Mariupol as Russia threatens to eliminate resistance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c597b9b07feed7b6ad22c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c597b9b07feed7b6ad22c/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces besieged in Mariupol have rejected Russia&amp;rsquo;s demands to surrender and are still resisting an unrelenting assault on the southeastern port city, top Ukrainian officials said on Sunday.
Highlights NEW: Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says &amp;ldquo;not one big city in Ukraine has fallen&amp;rdquo; NEW: He says more than 900 cities, towns and villages have been freed from Russian occupation since Moscow took control. Russia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defense called on the Ukrainian soldiers still in Mariupol to surrender by 1 p.</description></item><item><title>Israeli forces shoot 3 Palestinians, kill at least 2</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254378a6af04a52c420a862/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 14:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254378a6af04a52c420a862/</guid><description>TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israeli forces shot and killed two Palestinians, including an unarmed woman, in confrontations across Israel and the occupied West Bank on Sunday, Israeli and Palestinian officials said.
Highlights Israeli forces shoot and kill two Palestinians, including an unarmed woman, in confrontations across Israel and the occupied West Bank. The shootings came as Israeli troops combed the northern West Bank city of Jenin and the surrounding area, home to two of the Palestinians who staged deadly attacks against Israelis in recent weeks.</description></item><item><title>Mayor of Chernobyl workers town says Russian forces have left</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241c27f9e6ec78ee445e706/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 14:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241c27f9e6ec78ee445e706/</guid><description>Russian forces have left the Ukrainian town of Slavutych, home to workers at the defunct nuclear plant of Chernobyl, after completing their task of surveying it, the mayor said early on Monday.
Highlights Russian forces have left the Ukrainian town of Slavutych, home to workers at the defunct Chernobyl plant, after completing their task of surveying it. Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine has caused a major humanitarian crisis and displaced an estimated 10 million people, nearly a quarter of the population.</description></item><item><title>300 dead in airstrike on theatre in Mariupol, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ecbb3b643fcf6f25fe0db/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ecbb3b643fcf6f25fe0db/</guid><description>In what could signal an important narrowing of Moscow&amp;rsquo;s military objectives, the U.S. said Russian forces appear to have halted, at least for now, their ground offensive aimed at capturing the capital, Kyiv, and are concentrating more on the fighting for control of the Donbas region in the country&amp;rsquo;s southeast &amp;ndash; a shift the Kremlin seemed to confirm.
Highlights NEW: U.S. official: Russian forces appear to have halted ground offensive aimed at capturing the capital, Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Russian invaders have three days of supplies left, says Ukraine military</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b10e803132e104eab3649/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 12:22:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b10e803132e104eab3649/</guid><description>Ukrainian commanders say fuel, food and ammunition in short supply after breakdown in Russian supply chains
Highlights Claims of major shortages described as ‘plausible’ by western officials. Western officials said they were unable to corroborate the analysis. Report said to be consistent with evidence that the Russian advance had stalled. Pentagon official said there were continuing morale issues among Russian troops, with food and fuel shortages, as well as frostbite due to a lack of adequate clothing.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Russian forces shoot and kill 10 people queuing for bread in Chernihiv - US embassy says | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231fe9c2437ef6503213ae2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 15:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231fe9c2437ef6503213ae2/</guid><description>The US embassy in Kyiv says it is &amp;quot;considering all available options to ensure accountability for any atrocity crimes in Ukraine&amp;quot;.
Highlights 10 people shot and killed in Chernihiv, northern Ukraine, US embassy in Kyiv says. US embassy: &amp;ldquo;Such horrific attacks must stop. We are considering all available options to ensure accountability for atrocity crimes&amp;rdquo; UK Ministry of Defence says Ukraine exploiting Russia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;lack of manoeuvre&amp;rdquo; and inflicting heavy losses. Russian troops are continuing to fire missiles at Ukrainian targets, and rockets are hitting civilian buildings and infrastructure, an adviser says.</description></item><item><title>McDonald's will temporarily close 850 restaurants in Russia, nearly 2 weeks after Putin invaded Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia after the company took heat for staying silent on the war in Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s says it will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia. The decision comes nearly two weeks after Russian forces invaded Ukraine. PepsiCo, Starbucks and Coco-Cola also announced similar step-backs from the country. McDonald&amp;rsquo;s restaurants in Russia and Ukraine account for 2% of its systemwide sales, 9% of revenue and 3% of operating income.</description></item><item><title>Minister Reznikov: Kremlin not willing to admit its fiasco yet, but this time is almost here</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224a69e2698a75a13b77716/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 12:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224a69e2698a75a13b77716/</guid><description>Dissatisfaction and demoralization among the Russian occupation forces are growing. The Kremlin is not willing to admit its fiasco yet, but this time is almost here. — Ukrinform.
Highlights Ukrainian Defense Minister Oleksii Reznikov posted a statement on his Facebook page. The Kremlin is not willing to admit its fiasco yet, but this time is almost here, he writes. Reznikov: “The situation on the positions is controlled. Indeed, we have losses.</description></item><item><title>Putin puts Russia's nuclear forces on alert, cites sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bbfe519af4fd00ee355b4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 18:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bbfe519af4fd00ee355b4/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Sunday said that Ukraine and Russia would conduct the first diplomatic talks since the Kremlin-launched invasion.
Highlights Russian forces are using siege tactics against Chernihiv, a senior defense official says. The move raises the specter of more civilian casualties as the fighting worsens in Ukraine. The Pentagon says the Russian military still has not seized control of any Ukrainian cities. Russia has put about two-thirds of the fighting force it had amassed around Ukraine into the country already, the official adds.</description></item><item><title>'Let's help them get straight to hell': Ukraine tears down road signs so Russians get lost</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621adbd759367d70b37aa606/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 02:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621adbd759367d70b37aa606/</guid><description>In a Facebook post, the Ukrainian road agency said: &amp;lsquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s help them get straight to hell&amp;rsquo;
Highlights State Agency of Motor Roads of Ukraine posted plea to Facebook alongside image of sign with all directions instructing Russian soldiers to &amp;lsquo;f*** off&amp;rsquo; Earlier it had asked people to take action if they saw &amp;rsquo;enemy vehicles&amp;rsquo; and block them. Ministry of Defence tweeted intelligence update on the situation in Ukraine. It said: &amp;lsquo;Russian casualties are likely to be heavy and greater than anticipated or acknowledged by the Kremlin&amp;rsquo; Video emerged of man telling stranded Russians he could ‘tow them back to Russia” It came as ministry of defence tweeted: “Russian forces have continued their advance on Kyiv with the bulk of their forces now 30km from the centre of the city” READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Harsh conditions mean Russian troops near Ukraine will need to be moved soon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62175a4ae9f12b29d3de9a6a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62175a4ae9f12b29d3de9a6a/</guid><description>Analysis: advance forces’ battle readiness will quickly degrade, giving Putin only days to choose invasion or retreat
Highlights Russian forces massing near Ukraine’s borders can only be used for a few days before they have to be sent back to nearby bases, experts believe. Russia&amp;rsquo;s President Vladimir Putin will come under increasing pressure to use them in a full invasion of Ukraine – or send them back to staging areas, but tens of thousands of kilometres away.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine warns Russia has 'almost completed' build-up of forces near border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</guid><description>Ukraine has warned that Russia has &amp;quot;almost completed&amp;quot; its build-up of forces that could be used for an offensive against the country, compounding fears that Moscow could launch an invasion at any time.
Summary The assessment called the situation &amp;ldquo;difficult,&amp;rdquo; and said Ukraine believes Russia is &amp;ldquo;trying to split and weaken the European Union and NATO.&amp;rdquo; Ukrainian military intelligence said Russia has deployed troops from its central and eastern regions to its western border &amp;ldquo;on a permanent basis.</description></item><item><title>Canada deploys special forces to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</guid><description>Global News has learned that a small contingent of Canadian special forces soldiers sent to aid Ukrainian government, plan for potential embassy evacuation should Russia invade.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailCanadian special forces operators have been deployed to Ukraine amid rising tensions between the NATO military alliance and Russia, Global News has learned. Sources told Global News that the Canadian special operations presence is part of an attempt by NATO allies to deter Russian aggression in Ukraine, and to identify ways to assist the Ukrainian government.</description></item></channel></rss>