<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>portland on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/portland/</link><description>Recent content in portland on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:15:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/portland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alleged killer in Portland’s Normandale Park protest shooting identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215b4d93a6de5fd52c009c9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215b4d93a6de5fd52c009c9/</guid><description>Benjamin Jeffrey Smith, 43, is suspected of shooting and killing a racial justice demonstrator Saturday night in Portland, Oregon. Police confirmed Tuesday morning that Smith remains hospitalized in serious condition. Smith&amp;rsquo;s roommate and neighbors said he had grown increasingly angry
Highlights Benjamin Jeffrey Smith, 43, is suspected of shooting and killing a racial justice demonstrator Saturday night. Police confirmed Tuesday morning that Smith remains hospitalized in serious condition. Smith&amp;rsquo;s roommate and neighbors said he had grown increasingly angry with protests in the neighborhood and across the city.</description></item><item><title>Shooting at a Portland Protest Against Police Violence Leaves One Dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212bcc461ec54ddef583463/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212bcc461ec54ddef583463/</guid><description>Authorities describe confrontation in Normandale Park between homeowner and participants in police violence protest
Highlights One person killed and five wounded in Portland shooting at Normandale Park. Incident happened during confrontation between armed homeowner and armed protesters. Police responded to six shootings in nine hours on Thursday night and Friday morning. At the time of the shooting a march was planned for Amir Locke, a Black man shot dead by police in Minneapolis.</description></item></channel></rss>