<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cases on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cases/</link><description>Recent content in cases on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 21:09:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dogs can detect Covid with high accuracy, even asymptomatic cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629926fdde9992a6194cc70e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 21:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629926fdde9992a6194cc70e/</guid><description>In a new study, dogs accurately identified 97 percent of positive Covid cases after smelling human sweat samples.
Highlights French researchers say dogs can be trained to sniff out Covid. The dogs accurately identified 97 percent of positive cases after sniffing human sweat samples. The researchers found the dogs were especially good at detecting asymptomatic infections, with a sensitivity nearing 100 percent. The study suggests that dogs might be useful for detecting Covid in airports, nursing homes, schools or sporting events.</description></item><item><title>More than 100 confirmed or suspected cases of monkeypox have been reported in 12 countries, including the US - CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b6b39695a67b92a49b0a9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b6b39695a67b92a49b0a9/</guid><description>More cases of a rare disease have been reported worldwide, including in the United States &amp;ndash; where one health official said he expects more cases in the days ahead.
Highlights 92 confirmed cases and 28 suspected cases of monkeypox are under investigation in 12 countries, WHO says. The White House Covid-19 response coordinator says he expects &amp;ldquo;a few more&amp;rdquo; cases in the coming days. The United States had between one and five confirmed monkeypox cases as of Saturday.</description></item><item><title>World Health Organization confirms 80 cases of monkeypox with outbreaks in 11 countries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ba4920f9d673880d6257/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:09:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ba4920f9d673880d6257/</guid><description>The WHO said the recent monkeypox outbreaks are unusual because they are occurring in countries where the virus is not endemic.
Highlights About 80 cases of monkeypox have been reported in 11 countries, the WHO says. The U.S. has confirmed at least one case, and Canada has confirmed two. Monkeypox is a disease caused by a virus in the same family as smallpox but is not as severe. The disease is usually found in Central and West African rainforests where animals that carry the virus live.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook parents sue Alex Jones again, accuse him of trying to ‘shield assets’ in defamation cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625115a9ffdd0b673864fc31/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 05:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625115a9ffdd0b673864fc31/</guid><description>In the latest lawsuit, the families accuse the Infowars host of transferring&amp;hellip;
Highlights Four Sandy Hook parents who won two defamation suits against Alex Jones in Texas sue him. They say he &amp;ldquo;transferred millions of dollars from his fortune&amp;rdquo; to shield his assets from them. Jones, the host of the internet program “Infowars,” faces the first of three jury trials to award damages later this month in Texas. He called the 2012 shooting of 26 first-graders and educators at Sandy Hook Elementary School “staged” and “synthetic” Jones could not be reached for comment late Friday at his Texas-based “infowars” studio.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19: Surge in Hong Kong coronavirus cases pushes neighbouring Chinese city of Shenzhen into lockdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f32feacb8f0ef4095ee9c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f32feacb8f0ef4095ee9c/</guid><description>Although infection numbers on the mainland are relatively low, the authorities are enforcing a &amp;quot;zero tolerance&amp;quot; strategy to find and quarantine every infected person, and have imposed fresh restrictions in a number of areas.
Highlights Authorities reported 1,938 new cases on the Chinese mainland on Sunday, more than triple the previous day&amp;rsquo;s total. Hong Kong authorities are enforcing a &amp;lsquo;zero tolerance&amp;rsquo; strategy to find and isolate every infected person. Access to Shanghai has been restricted with bus services suspended and a negative test required from anyone wanting to enter.</description></item><item><title>COVID cases continue steep decline in U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222040052acfee18920c8ba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 12:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222040052acfee18920c8ba/</guid><description>COVID case rates continued a steep decline over the last few weeks with the seven-day rolling average dropping to roughly 59,000 cases a day.
Highlights COVID case rates continued a steep decline over the last two weeks with the seven-day rolling average dropping to roughly 59,000 cases a day. The lowest case rates were seen in Nebraska with six cases per 100,000 people, followed by Delaware and Maryland. Montana and Alaska had the highest rates at 49 cases per cent and 47 in Alaska.</description></item><item><title>Global spread of autoimmune disease blamed on western diet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db3ee616931e95ee3d7f2c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db3ee616931e95ee3d7f2c/</guid><description>New DNA research by London-based scientists hopes to find cure for rapidly spreading conditions
Summary “Numbers of autoimmune cases began to increase about 40 years ago in the west,” Lee told the Observer. For example, the biggest recent increase in inflammatory bowel disease cases has been in the Middle East and east Asia. Internationally, it is now estimated that cases of autoimmune diseases are rising by between 3% and 9% a year.</description></item><item><title>China locks down Yuzhou, city of 1.2 million, after recording 3 Covid-19 cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4edae87a2bdb3c28e3422/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4edae87a2bdb3c28e3422/</guid><description>Yuzhou, a city with a population of around 1.17 million people in Henan province, announced that from Monday night all citizens were required to stay home to control the spread of the virus. | World News
Summary More than one million people in a city in central China were being confined to their homes on Tuesday after three asymptomatic coronavirus cases were recorded in the country&amp;rsquo;s latest mass lockdown. Yuzhou, a city with a population of around 1.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated People Ordered to Stay Home or Face Jail in Philippines' Capital Manila</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4a76e739e6722aeed5579/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4a76e739e6722aeed5579/</guid><description>After weeks of its lowest caseloads in the pandemic, the Philippines’ capital region is seeing a frightening rise in coronavirus infections.
Summary Under the order, unvaccinated people must stay at home except to buy essential goods or for medical purposes. Some officials criticized the council’s stay-at-home order for unvaccinated people, noting that even vaccinated people can contract and transmit the virus. “The recent exponential COVID-19 surge in Metro Manila happened even when 102 percent of the target population is already vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Puerto Rico’s COVID-19 positive rate jumps from 2% to over 30% in just two weeks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3fea20e2741ee1efd3566/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 08:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3fea20e2741ee1efd3566/</guid><description>Summary Just two weeks ago, Puerto Rico had a COVID-19 test positivity rate of 2% &amp;ndash; the lowest it had ever been, according to the island’s health department COVID-19 dashboard. “This is not the time to get together, “ said Puerto Rico’s Health Secretary Carlos Mellado in a press conference ahead of New Year’s Eve gatherings. “What happened was a perfect storm,” said the president of Puerto Rico’s Scientific Coalition Daniel Colón-Ramos.</description></item><item><title>Ontario to stop logging COVID-19 school cases, memo says; NDP calls it 'terrifying for parents'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d24aae0458d582732d8086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d24aae0458d582732d8086/</guid><description>Ontario will stop reporting COVID-19 cases in schools and child-care settings, prompting criticism from the opposition New Democratic Party, which called the move &amp;quot;terrifying for parents.&amp;quot;
Summary Ontario will stop reporting COVID-19 cases in schools and child-care settings, memos from the Ministry of Education say, prompting criticism from the opposition New Democratic Party, which called the move &amp;ldquo;terrifying for parents.&amp;rdquo; The changes come as record-breaking COVID numbers strain public health resources.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioters’ tears, remorse don’t spare them from jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1da39b41e6d4d720586bc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1da39b41e6d4d720586bc/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Florida business owner Robert Palmer cheered on the violence at the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 before he joined the fray. Screaming obscenities, he hurled a wooden plank and a fire extinguisher at police officers trying to ward off the mob.
Summary The Justice Department has undertaken the largest investigation in its history with the probe into rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6. The Justice Department has undertaken the largest investigation in its history with the probe into rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan.</description></item><item><title>Wearing masks outdoors mandatory in Paris starting Friday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8066c775ab3f79990e35/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8066c775ab3f79990e35/</guid><description>Wearing masks even outdoors will be mandatory in Paris starting on Friday, French authorities have announced, as the country struggles to come to grips with an Omicron surge. France is leading Europe…
Summary People wearing face masks walk on the Palais Royal grounds in Paris on January 16, 2021Wearing masks even outdoors will be mandatory in Paris starting on Friday, French authorities have announced, as the country struggles to come to grips with an Omicron surge.</description></item><item><title>Florida reports 46,923 new coronavirus cases, shattering state daily record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd6722f3238650c09f2f4f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd6722f3238650c09f2f4f/</guid><description>Florida&amp;rsquo;s 46,923 new daily coronavirus cases shattered the state record for residents and became the third state in the nation to pass 4 million infections, according to data submitted to the Centers for Disease Control. Also, hospitalizations have risen to 3,836, the highest in 2 1/2 months.
Summary The first cases were reported in Florida on March 1, 2020. Twice week a CDC revises new daily cases in data provided by the state.</description></item><item><title>Germany's top court orders government to protect people with disabilities and pre-existing conditions to ensure they are not discriminated against if over-streteched hospitals are forced to decide who gets care</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb7aee0e3b631155cc0c63/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb7aee0e3b631155cc0c63/</guid><description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s highest court has said officials must draw up rules to protect disabled people during pandemic triage situations. It&amp;rsquo;s an urgent issue, with Germany facing a huge new COVID wave fueled by the omicron variant.
Summary Germany&amp;rsquo;s Constitutional Court ruled on Tuesday that lawmakers must set out legally binding criteria to protect people with disabilities and preexisting conditions in pandemic-related triage situations. The court said legislators had violated the constitution by not previously setting out such rules.</description></item><item><title>Chicago to Require Vaccine Proof for Indoor Spaces Like Restaurants, Bars, Gyms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24e80f93c348e1487b143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24e80f93c348e1487b143/</guid><description>Description Chicago will soon require proof of vaccination for indoor public spaces like restaurants, bars and gyms in the new year, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor announced Tuesday,&amp;hellip;
Summary Chicago will soon require proof of vaccination for indoor public spaces like restaurants, bars and gyms in the new year, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor announced Tuesday, joining other big cities like New York and Los Angeles in adding the requirement as COVID cases surge. The city said the policy is &amp;ldquo;in response to an alarming rise in COVID-19 cases both locally and nationally, driven in part by the omicron variant.</description></item><item><title>Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of US COVID-19 cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</guid><description>Description NEW YORK (AP) — Omicron has raced ahead of other variants and is now the dominant version of the coronavirus in the U.S., accounting for 73% of new infections last week, federal health officials said Monday.
Summary Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of new US COVID casesTravelers wait for a shuttle but to arrive at the Los Angeles International Airport in Los Angeles, Monday, Dec. 20, 2021. (AP Photo/Jae C.</description></item></channel></rss>