<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hook on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hook/</link><description>Recent content in hook on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 09:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas school shooting victims take action against gunmaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b214e7cfe123158370b5d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 09:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b214e7cfe123158370b5d/</guid><description>The father of a 10-year-old girl slain in the Uvalde, Texas, school shooting and a school employee have taken initial steps that could lead to lawsuits against Daniel Defense, the maker of the semiautomatic rifle used in last week&amp;rsquo;s massacre that killed 21 people.
Highlights Father of slain girl and school employee have taken initial steps that could lead to lawsuits against Daniel Defense, maker of the semiautomatic rifle used in last week&amp;rsquo;s massacre that killed 21 people.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones' attorney Norm Pattis asks to be dropped from Sandy Hook defamation case as trial looms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62998a4eedcb1dfda076937f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62998a4eedcb1dfda076937f/</guid><description>A Connecticut judge rejected a request that Alex Jones’ New Haven-based attorney be dropped from the defamation case he lost to Sandy Hook families.
Highlights Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; attorneys want to be dropped from a defamation case involving Sandy Hook families. Jones lost two defamation cases to Sandy Hook parents last year. Jones is seeking to forestall a similar damages award trial in Texas where he lost two other defamation cases. Jones has spent $10 million on attorneys fees and lost at least $20 million because of the Sandy Hook lawsuits, his representatives say.</description></item><item><title>Newtown families ask judge to dismiss Alex Jones’ ‘bad faith’ bankruptcies as they await defamation damages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269c06c78fd5ccf1046f72d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 22:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269c06c78fd5ccf1046f72d/</guid><description>Eight Sandy Hook families and an FBI agent who won a defamation case against conspiracy&amp;hellip;
Highlights Eight Sandy Hook families and an FBI agent who won a defamation case against conspiracy extremist Alex Jones have asked a federal judge to dismiss bankruptcies Jones filed for three of his business entities. The families are challenging the bankruptcy filings of three Jones-controlled business entities last week. The first of those trials for the parents of a slain Sandy Hook first-grader was scheduled to being on Monday in Austin - the business home of Jones’ conspiracy-based website Infowars.</description></item><item><title>Judge orders Alex Jones to pay $1M in fees to 4 Sandy Hook parents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f25c25da9c3972d99d0ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f25c25da9c3972d99d0ac/</guid><description>The order is from the same Texas judge who is overseeing two upcoming trials to determine&amp;hellip;
Highlights The order is from the same Texas judge who is overseeing two upcoming trials to determine damages from defamation lawsuits Jones lost to Sandy Hook parents. Jones and his businesses have 30 days to pay the attorney fees and expenses for Neil Heslin and Scarlett Lewis, the parents of slain first-grader Jesse Lewis and Lenny Pozner.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones' Infowars files for bankruptcy in wake of defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook massacre was a hoax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:23:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</guid><description>Jones was found liable in at least two defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.
Highlights Infowars and two other companies owned by radio host Alex Jones have filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in light of several defamation lawsuits. The filings were made in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas. A judge has ruled that Jones get back $75,000 in fines he paid to a Connecticut court for failing to appear at a deposition last month in a lawsuit over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones’ escalating $25K fine starts Friday; judge denies motion to lift sanction while he appeals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624778ee18cd63398b2ad11e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624778ee18cd63398b2ad11e/</guid><description>An escalating $25,000 daily fine began on Friday for Alex Jones as part of the defamation&amp;hellip;
Highlights Infowars host Alex Jones faces three jury trials to determine damages in defamation case he lost to Sandy Hook families. Judge Barbara Bellis says Jones defying her orders to answer questions under oath last week. Jones says he will sit for two days of depositions starting April 11. Bellis: If Jones does travel to Connecticut to answer pretrial questions, he can apply to the court for a refund.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families reject Alex Jones settlement offer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243d971dd15a452375a2b70/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243d971dd15a452375a2b70/</guid><description>HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — Infowars host Alex Jones offered to pay $120,000 per plaintiff to resolve a lawsuit by relatives of Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting victims who said he defamed them by asserting the massacre never happened, according to court filings Tuesday.
Highlights Infowars host Alex Jones offered to pay $120,000 per plaintiff to resolve lawsuit by relatives of Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting victims. Relatives said he defamed them by asserting the massacre never happened, according to court filings.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families seek Alex Jones arrest after 2nd no-show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e6309148241c2ccd593bb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:49:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e6309148241c2ccd593bb/</guid><description>Relatives of some victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting are asking a Connecticut judge to order the arrest of Infowars host Alex Jones for missing a court-ordered deposition this week
Highlights Relatives of some victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting are asking a Connecticut judge to order the arrest of Infowars host Alex Jones for missing a court-ordered deposition this week. Jones missed both days of a scheduled deposition Wednesday and Thursday in Austin, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families settle with gun maker in historic first</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</guid><description>Nine Sandy Hook Elementary School families have announced a settlement with Remington Arms, maker of the AR-15 used in the massacre.
Highlights Remington Arms agrees to pay families $73 million in settlement. Settlement comes seven years after families sued the maker of the Bushmaster XM15-E2S semiautomatic rifle. Remington&amp;rsquo;s version of the AR-15 is substantially similar to the standard issue M16 military service rifle used by the U.S. Army and other nations’ armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones lists $6.2 million in assets as judge adds new sanctions in Sandy Hook cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas — A Travis County judge imposed additional sanctions against Alex Jones on&amp;hellip;
Summary According to information Jones provided in December as part of the case, he listed more than $6.2 million in assets, including three properties worth about $2.35 million and about $458,000 in the bank. Free Speech Systems, according to Jones, has about $525,000 in the bank, inventory worth about $1.3 million and $2.1 million in fixed and intangible assets.</description></item></channel></rss>