<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sued on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sued/</link><description>Recent content in sued on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:17:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sued/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Credit Suisse sued in U.S. over alleged business related to oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d60f36784b3688d74faa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d60f36784b3688d74faa9/</guid><description>A group of people and entities have filed a class action lawsuit against Credit Suisse , alleging that the Swiss bank misled investors over business dealings related to Russian oligarchs, law firm Pomerantz LLP said.
Highlights Law firm Pomerantz LLP says Credit Suisse misled investors over dealings related to Russian oligarchs. Lawsuit filed in New York district court is on behalf of people and entities who acquired credit Suisse securities between March 19, 2021 and March 25, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Arkansas jail sued over ivermectin treatments has alleged history of leaving ailing inmates "harmed and worse off"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb8ecbb70d6ed393be6bc5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 08:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb8ecbb70d6ed393be6bc5/</guid><description>At least 37 federal lawsuits have been filed against the jail and/or its doctor since his contract began in 2016.
Highlights Walt Kelly was taken to Washington County Detention Center in Arkansas in November 2017 for two counts of delivering an ounce of marijuana. Kelly, 49, was undergoing treatment for bipolar disorder. Kelly said he was left &amp;ldquo;left to die in my own misery, in my mental health nightmare&amp;rdquo; last year.</description></item></channel></rss>