<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shootings on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shootings/</link><description>Recent content in shootings on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 18:11:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shootings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>At least 12 dead in another weekend of mass shootings across America</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e431cd5e8306359b43cf0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e431cd5e8306359b43cf0/</guid><description>The first weekend of June marked a greater number of mass shooting deaths in the United States than the previous three-day weekend, which ended with Memorial Day.
Highlights The first weekend of June had a greater number of mass shooting deaths in the United States than the previous three-day weekend, which ended with Memorial Day. The tally for weekend violence through Sunday night was at least 12 killed and at least 38 injured in mass shootings.</description></item><item><title>21 people were injured in shootings in downtown Milwaukee; Mayor Johnson imposes curfew Saturday night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628127e5baac9bf6b4717134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628127e5baac9bf6b4717134/</guid><description>Eleven people are in custody, 10 guns were recovered and all the victims are expected to survive after three shootings near the Deer District and Water Street in Milwaukee following the Bucks Game 6 playoff game.
Highlights Milwaukee Mayor Cavalier Johnson imposes curfew Saturday night for under-21s. Mayor: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re going to do something about what happened here in this neighborhood last night&amp;rdquo; 11 people, ranging in age from 19 to 30, were arrested and 10 guns were recovered.</description></item><item><title>Gun Kyle Rittenhouse used in deadly Kenosha shootings destroyed by Wisconsin crime lab</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c7fba4379feb44c9a84d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 11:11:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c7fba4379feb44c9a84d6/</guid><description>Wisconsin officials have destroyed the rifle Kyle Rittenhouse used to shoot three people during protests in Kenosha in 2020.
Highlights Rittenhouse shot and killed Joseph Rosenbaum and Anthony Huber and wounded Gaige Grosskreutz. The state crime lab destroyed the rifle on Feb. 25, WISN reported. The shootings began after a white police officer shot Jacob Blake, a Black man, during a domestic disturbance. The demonstrations began after Blake was shot by police in a domestic dispute.</description></item></channel></rss>