<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wear on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wear/</link><description>Recent content in wear on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 16:18:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Afghanistan: Taliban leader orders women to wear all-covering burqa in public: Decree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62769bac94efd22970e66069/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62769bac94efd22970e66069/</guid><description>Afghanistan’s supreme leader and Taliban chief on Saturday ordered the country’s women to wear the all-covering burqa in public - one of the harshest
Highlights Afghanistan&amp;rsquo;s supreme leader and Taliban chief orders women to wear all-covering burqa in public: Decree. Decree issued by Hibatullah Akhundzada that was released by Taliban authorities at a function in Kabul. It is one of the harshest controls imposed on women’s lives since Taliban seized power.</description></item><item><title>U.S. CDC urges Americans to wear 'most protective mask you can'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e48793a791f785bddde106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e48793a791f785bddde106/</guid><description>The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) on Friday revised its guidance for Americans on wearing masks to protect against COVID-19, recommending donning &amp;quot;the most protective mask you can&amp;quot; while stopping short of advocating nationwide usage of N95 respirators.
Summary Americans should &amp;ldquo;wear the most protective mask you can that fits well and that you will wear consistently,&amp;rdquo; the CDC added. The CDC said it wants to encourage Americans to wear masks rather than push them to wear the highest-grade face protection, but also explicitly said that respirators provide the best level of protection.</description></item><item><title>Fauci says U.S. should consider vaccine mandate for domestic air travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</guid><description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said in an interview on MSNBC that such a requirement should be &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot; considered.
Summary The federal government should consider requiring Covid-19 vaccines for domestic flights, the nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said Monday. &amp;ldquo;If you want to do that with domestic flights, I think that&amp;rsquo;s something that seriously should be considered.&amp;rdquo; There is no indication at this point that a vaccine mandate is on its way for U.</description></item></channel></rss>