<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plastic on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plastic/</link><description>Recent content in plastic on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 11:12:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plastic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. plastic recycling rate drops to close to 5% - report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273b10be042fe9f5187ce4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 11:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273b10be042fe9f5187ce4e/</guid><description>The rate of plastic waste recycling in the United States fell to between 5%-6% in 2021 as some countries stopped accepting U.S. waste exports and as plastic waste generation surged to new highs, according to a report released on Wednesday.
Highlights Report: U.S. plastic waste recycling rate fell to between 5-6% in 2021. Decline coincides with a sharp drop in plastic waste exports, which had counted as recycled plastic. China and Turkey have since implemented plastic import bans and other countries set plastic waste contamination limits.</description></item><item><title>Microplastics found in human blood for first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cc2384530170bc3c6625b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cc2384530170bc3c6625b/</guid><description>Exclusive: The discovery shows the particles can travel around the body and may lodge in organs
Highlights Microplastic particles found in almost 80% of people tested in their blood. Impact on human health is as yet unknown but researchers are concerned as microplastics cause damage to human cells in the laboratory and air pollution particles are already known to enter the body and cause millions of early deaths a year. Microplastics are 10 times higher in the faeces of babies compared with adults and that babies fed with plastic bottles are swallowing millions of microplastic particle a day.</description></item><item><title>UN agrees to create world's first-ever plastics pollution treaty in a blow to big oil</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62204102804c52a74a5df8c1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 04:16:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62204102804c52a74a5df8c1/</guid><description>The United Nations approved a landmark agreement to create the world&amp;rsquo;s first-ever global plastic pollution treaty on Wednesday, describing it as the most significant environmental deal since the 2015 Paris climate accord.
Highlights The United Nations approved a landmark agreement to create the world&amp;rsquo;s first-ever global plastic pollution treaty on Wednesday. The deal is the most significant environmental deal since the Paris climate accord. The agreement is due to be finalized by 2024 and will have ripple effects on businesses and the environment.</description></item></channel></rss>