<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stay on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stay/</link><description>Recent content in stay on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine urges calm, saying Russian invasion not imminent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s leaders sought Tuesday to reassure the nation that an invasion from neighboring Russia was not imminent, even as they acknowledged the threat is real and received a shipment of U.S.
Summary British Prime Minister Boris Johnson also said he is prepared to send troops to protect NATO allies in Europe. Fighting between Ukrainian forces and Russia-backed rebels has killed over 14,000 people, and efforts to reach a settlement have stalled.</description></item><item><title>'Like a slap in the face': Nurses told to use vacation and sick days to stay home if they test positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1036ffdaad0efa69433b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1036ffdaad0efa69433b8/</guid><description>Early in the pandemic, nurses were celebrated as heroes, with nightly symphonies of clapping or banging pots and pans.
Summary Now, many are being asked to go into work despite positive Covid tests — or they say they are being told they must use their vacation and sick days to stay home when they contract the coronavirus. In some instances, nurses who test positive have also been instructed to return to work if they are asymptomatic, according to another internal memo, also reviewed by NBC News.</description></item></channel></rss>