<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>saidthe on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/saidthe/</link><description>Recent content in saidthe on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 08:17:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/saidthe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former Woodbridge, N.J. resident says 65 people who either attended or worked at Colonia High School have had rare brain tumors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246b507265e51e43e58fdb8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 08:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246b507265e51e43e58fdb8/</guid><description>Al Lupiano started researching a connection when he and others family members were diagnosed as well.
Highlights Al Lupiano started researching a connection when he and others family members were diagnosed. He has confirmed 65 cases of people with rare brain tumors. The common denominator is they were all Colonia High School graduates or worked at the school. The school was built in 1967 and has no records of when it was built 55 years ago.</description></item><item><title>Quebec says it will tax those who remain unvaccinated against COVID-19 without a medical reason</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfc012615c48af4a17a4b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfc012615c48af4a17a4b1/</guid><description>Quebec Premier François Legault said it was a measure for &amp;quot;fairness&amp;quot; for the 90% of residents who are vaccinated.
Summary The Premier of Quebec François Legault at a press conference on November 18, 2021 in Montreal, Canada. Minas Panagiotakis/Getty Images10% of Quebec&amp;rsquo;s adult population is unvaccinated for COVID-19, Premier François Legault said. The unvaccinated, however, make up half of all ICU beds in the province, Legault said. Quebec&amp;rsquo;s Premier François Legault announced on Tuesday that the province plans to tax people who are unvaccinated against COVID-19 for non-medical reasons.</description></item></channel></rss>