<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>worth on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worth/</link><description>Recent content in worth on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 17:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Connecticut mechanic found hundreds of pieces of art in a dumpster. They’re worth 'millions.'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251bed49c26c09ae4c3ce2a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 17:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251bed49c26c09ae4c3ce2a/</guid><description>A contractor found hundreds of art pieces wrapped in plastic and covered in dirt in a dumpster in Watertown, Connecticut. The art was created by Francis Hines, a Washington, D.C.-born artist that resided in Connecticut and
Highlights A contractor found hundreds of art pieces wrapped in plastic and covered in dirt in a dumpster in Watertown, Connecticut. The art was created by Francis Hines, a Washington, D.C.-born artist that resided in Connecticut and New York.</description></item><item><title>More than $10M worth of masks, protective gear left in the rain outside Bay Area event center</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e27f43f23420957a6276d0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 08:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e27f43f23420957a6276d0/</guid><description>Thousands of boxes filled with masks and protective gear worth more than $10 million were left in the rain outside a Bay Area event center.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos After nearly $10 million of PPE was rained on outside the San Mateo County Event Center, the Marines have been called in to do an inspection. SAN MATEO, Calif. (KGO) &amp;ndash; San Mateo County workers are scrambling to clean up a mess uncovered by the ABC7 I-Team .</description></item></channel></rss>