<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>couple on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/couple/</link><description>Recent content in couple on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 03:47:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/couple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disney apologizes to couple whose marriage proposal was thwarted by employee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eca18c638c967bf1e0dc6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eca18c638c967bf1e0dc6/</guid><description>Disney says, &amp;lsquo;We regret how this was handled.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights A viral video first posted on Reddit last week showed a man getting on one knee to propose to his girlfriend on a platform in front of the Sleeping Beauty Castle at Disneyland, Paris. An employee rushed up and snatches the ring box out of the man’s hands and ushers the couple off the platform, the video shows. &amp;ldquo;We have apologized to the couple involved and offered to make it right,&amp;rdquo; a Disney spokesperson said.</description></item><item><title>GoFundMe effort in honor of Uvalde couple raises more than $2.6 million in four days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294c821b0c124704150254f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 13:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294c821b0c124704150254f/</guid><description>A GoFundMe campaign started in honor of Irma Garcia, one of the two teachers killed in the Texas school shooting, and her husband, Joe, who died Thursday, has
Highlights A GoFundMe campaign started in honor of Irma Garcia, one of the two teachers killed in the Texas school shooting, and her husband, Joe, who died Thursday, has raised more than $2.6 million in just four days. Irma Garcia was a fourth grade teacher who had been teaching at Robb Elementary in Uvalde for 23 years.</description></item><item><title>Gay parents called 'rapists' and 'pedophiles' in Amtrak incident</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625af97eef317c75de59bb88/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625af97eef317c75de59bb88/</guid><description>Gay parents were called &amp;quot;pedophiles&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;rapists&amp;quot; while riding an Amtrak train on Tuesday, amid a recent uptick in charged rhetoric about LGBTQ issues.
Highlights Robbie Pierce, his husband and their two young children were enjoying a scenic train ride on the Pacific coast. The couple said a man sitting across the aisle turned their family vacation into a nightmare. The man continued to shout at the family of four, yelling, “That’s not a family!</description></item><item><title>A man was fatally shot by his rescuer after falling in a South Carolina lake. The shooting has been ruled self-defense</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237534082a80b97e446ef2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237534082a80b97e446ef2f/</guid><description>South Carolina prosecutors decided not to file charges in a case where a man who fell off a recreational watercraft was fatally shot by his rescuer, according to the Oconee County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.
Highlights A man and a woman fell off a boat in Oconee County, South Carolina. A sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office says the incident occurred Tuesday afternoon. The man &amp;ldquo;became agitated and began assaulting the couple on the boat,&amp;rdquo; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s statement says.</description></item><item><title>Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 22:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</guid><description>The 44-year-old woman who was filmed in a TikTok video, had been sold at least three times, Chinese officials said.
Highlights Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say. Chinese authorities say she had been sold at least three times, first when she was 20 years old. She was discovered after being filmed in a TikTok video. A man claiming to be her husband said she was mentally ill.</description></item><item><title>Gun-waving St. Louis couple placed on probation as lawyers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62045f4634b7b4d588f9c6e6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62045f4634b7b4d588f9c6e6/</guid><description>The Missouri Supreme Court on Tuesday placed a St. Louis couple who gained national attention for waving guns at racial injustice protesters on probation as attorneys. The court suspended Mark and Patricia McCloskeys&amp;rsquo; law licenses but delayed the suspension and put the two on probation for a year.
Highlights Mark and Patricia McCloskey, a Republican candidate for U.S. Senate in Missouri, and his wife, Patricia, received national attention for waving guns at racial injustice protesters in June 2020 encounter.</description></item></channel></rss>