<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>london on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/london/</link><description>Recent content in london on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 23:15:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/london/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Julian Assange extradition order issued by London court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62609404289beedc5358ee22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 23:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62609404289beedc5358ee22/</guid><description>WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange has closer to being extradited to the United States, after a London court sent his handover to the British government for approval.
Highlights WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange moved one step closer to being extradited to the United States. A London court sent his handover order to the British government for approval. Assange is wanted in the US on 18 criminal charges after WikiLeaks published thousands of classified files and diplomatic cables in 2010.</description></item><item><title>Russian oligarch Roman Abramovich has $7 billion in assets frozen in Jersey in latest Ukraine fallout</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62588e305e508f8ea62a2bc6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 21:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62588e305e508f8ea62a2bc6/</guid><description>The freezing of assets of Roman Abramovich in Jersey is the latest financial hit to that Russian oligarch as a result of the Ukraine war.
Highlights Roman Abramovich&amp;rsquo;s assets frozen in Jersey. It is the latest financial fallout for that Russian oligarch as a result of the Ukraine war. The actions come a month after the UK announced financial sanctions against the 56-year-old. It was not clear if the 50-meter-long Aquamarine, which remains in dry dock in the Netherlands, is one of the assets frozen by Jersey authorities in that country.</description></item></channel></rss>