<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tied on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tied/</link><description>Recent content in tied on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 10:16:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tied/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Church linked to San Jose kidnapping also tied to apparent exorcism death of 3-year-old girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2fc63cee467d12289735/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 10:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2fc63cee467d12289735/</guid><description>Disturbing details have come to light regarding a San Jose church where an alleged exorcism claimed the life of a 3-year-old girl.
Highlights Police were called to the South Bay church in September for a separate incident that involved the death of a 3-year-old girl. The death occurred at the Iglesia Evangelicas Apostoles y Profetas as family members were trying to rid the girl of an evil spirit. The medical examiner said ultimately the child died of asphyxia due to suffocation.</description></item><item><title>'Hands tied, shot in ear and limbs': Bodies of men tortured, killed by Russian forces found in Bucha grave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d89d9d06c5329b3acb3d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 19:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d89d9d06c5329b3acb3d6/</guid><description>According to a Ukraine media reports, Ukrainian authorities filed criminal charges Thursday (April 28) against Russian soldiers allegedly involved in mass killings in Bucha.
Highlights Ukrainian authorities filed criminal charges Thursday (April 28) against Russian soldiers allegedly involved in mass killings in Bucha. According to police, on 29 April, a pit containing the bodies of three men who had been beaten up by Russian soldiers and then brutally killed was found.</description></item><item><title>One in five applicants to white supremacist group tied to US military | The far right</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62043c30ee4e8a58bf074d70/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62043c30ee4e8a58bf074d70/</guid><description>Leaked documents show that about 18 out of 87 applicants, or 21%, to Patriot Front were currently or formerly affiliated with military
Highlights Leaked documents show that about 18 out of 87 applicants to the white supremacist group Patriot Front claimed to hold current or former ties to the US military. The Southern Poverty Law Center and alternative media collective Unicorn Riot published over 400 gigabytes of data that included “ostensibly private, unedited videos and direct messages” The group recruits “members through the internet who are still legally minors, indoctrinating them with white supremacist ideology and even encouraging them to lie to their parents so the group can transport them across state lines for fascist events” Patriot Front emerged as a rebrand of the neo-Nazi organization Vanguard America in the aftermath of the 2017 Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville.</description></item><item><title>Woman tied to Jan. 6 Capitol riot involved in fatal crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</guid><description>UNION, Mo. (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.
Summary (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.</description></item></channel></rss>