<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>products on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/products/</link><description>Recent content in products on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 12:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recall alert: Nearly 121,000 pounds of ground beef sold nationwide recalled amid E. coli concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626935bf8a9e0f7a9fe6e1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626935bf8a9e0f7a9fe6e1ca/</guid><description>Lakeside Refrigerated Services recalled 120,872 pounds of beef that may be contaminated with E. coli O103. The potential contamination was discovered during routine FSIS testing of imported products. The particular strain of E.coli
Highlights Lakeside Refrigerated Services recalled 120,872 pounds of ground beef that may be contaminated with E. coli O103. The potential contamination was discovered during routine FSIS testing of imported products. The particular strain of E.coli typically causes diarrhea and vomiting.</description></item><item><title>Legal Weed Sales in New Jersey to Begin April 21</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259007cf3aed1b98939f770/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 05:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259007cf3aed1b98939f770/</guid><description>Legal sales of marijuana in New Jersey will begin April 21, Gov. Phil Murphy said Thursday.
Highlights People aged 21 and over in the state will be able to purchase cannabis and cannabis products without a medical card on that date. Voters approved the legal sale of marijuana in New Jersey in 2020, but the state has taken this long to establish the rules governing its sale and approve companies to sell it.</description></item><item><title>Potent protest: Bars drop Russian vodka, promote Ukraine’s</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c75e9878706c929ffd3de/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 07:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c75e9878706c929ffd3de/</guid><description>By PAUL WISEMAN AP Business Writer Some bars and liquor stores think they&amp;rsquo;ve found a potent way to punish Russia for invading Ukraine: They&amp;rsquo;re pulling Russ
Highlights Some bars and liquor stores think they&amp;rsquo;ve found a potent way to punish Russia for invading Ukraine. Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine directed the state’s Commerce Department to cease the purchase and sale of Russian Standard, the only Russian vodka sold in Ohio (under the brand names Green Mark and Russian Standard) New Hampshire Gov.</description></item><item><title>Intel and AMD suspended product deliveries to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b245ffc189aecd980ec06/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b245ffc189aecd980ec06/</guid><description>AMD and Intel have suspended deliveries of their products to Russia. This can lead to a shortage of computers, servers and other products, which will lead to higher prices. The Chinese office of Intel notified partners about introduction of a ban on the
Highlights AMD and Intel have suspended deliveries of their products to Russia. This is reported by RBC citing own sources. This can lead to a shortage of computers, servers and other products, which will lead to higher prices.</description></item><item><title>Food disruptions feared in UK as new Brexit rules kick in</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d282ebd7a102723b0588f2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d282ebd7a102723b0588f2/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — New post-Brexit custom rules for goods arriving from the European Union to Britain are taking effect on Saturday, and a leading food industry body has warned that the new border controls could lead to food shortages.
Summary Beginning on Jan. 1, importers must make a full customs declaration on goods entering the U.K. from the EU or other countries. Beginning on Jan. 1, importers must make a full customs declaration on goods entering the U.</description></item></channel></rss>