<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>resigns on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/resigns/</link><description>Recent content in resigns on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/resigns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu Resigns After FBI Reveals Anaheim Corruption Probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c7745216ed39f72f0727e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c7745216ed39f72f0727e/</guid><description>Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu abruptly resigns following FBI corruption probe into city hall. Mayor&amp;rsquo;s lawyer Paul Meyer issued a statement defending the mayor’s actions while in office. An FBI affidavit alleges that Sidhu shared city information with the
Highlights Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu abruptly resigns Monday. The resignation comes after an FBI corruption probe into Anaheim City Hall was revealed. Sidhu&amp;rsquo;s lawyer Paul Meyer issued a statement defending the mayor’s actions while in office.</description></item><item><title>Apple's Director of Machine Learning Resigns Due to Return to Office Work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627921530193eb8c84e9e93c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627921530193eb8c84e9e93c/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s director of machine learning, Ian Goodfellow, has resigned from his role a little over four years after he joined the company after&amp;hellip;
Highlights Apple&amp;rsquo;s director of machine learning, Ian Goodfellow, has resigned from his role. He reportedly broke the news to staff in an email, saying his resignation is in part due to Apple&amp;rsquo;s plan to return to in-person work. Apple employees began returning to Apple Park last month, with the three-day in-office work policy being enacted on May 23.</description></item><item><title>“Heartbroken” Will Smith Resigns From Academy Ahead Of Decision On His Future After Oscar Slap Of Chris Rock</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247b47cd1c46ee289a090ec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 02:27:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247b47cd1c46ee289a090ec/</guid><description>He will keep his King Richard award, but the former Fresh Prince will no longer be a member of the group that gave it to him on March 27
Highlights Will Smith has left the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences. Sources say he was told by the Academy that he likely could be expelled for a decade or more. Sources tell us that the traditional invite of the previous year’s Best Actor winner to hand out the Best Actress award had become a non-starter for Smith for the 95th Academy Awards.</description></item></channel></rss>