<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tutu on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/tutu/</link><description>Recent content in tutu on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/tutu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>South African anti-apartheid campaigner Archbishop Tutu dies aged 90</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c89fa9e539d76f30371600/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c89fa9e539d76f30371600/</guid><description>Archbishop Desmond Tutu, Nobel Peace Prize laureate and veteran of South Africa&amp;rsquo;s struggle against white minority rule, died on Sunday at the age of 90.
Summary In 1984 Tutu won the Nobel Peace Prize for his non-violent opposition to apartheid. &amp;ldquo;The passing of Archbishop Emeritus Desmond Tutu is another chapter of bereavement in our nation’s farewell to a generation of outstanding South Africans who have bequeathed us a liberated South Africa,&amp;rdquo; President Cyril Ramaphosa said.</description></item><item><title>Desmond Tutu has passed away at age 90</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c8676ea6784f206f2396bf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c8676ea6784f206f2396bf/</guid><description>Archbishop Emeritus Desmond Tutu has died at the age of 90.
Summary Archbishop Emeritus Desmond Tutu died on Sunday at the age of 90. Archbishop Emeritus Desmond Tutu has died at the age of 90. Tutu, the last surviving South African laureate of the Nobel Peace Prize, died in Cape Town on Sunday. &amp;ldquo;The passing of Archbishop Emeritus Desmond Tutu is another chapter of bereavement in our nation&amp;rsquo;s farewell to a generation of outstanding South Africans who have bequeathed us a liberated South Africa.</description></item></channel></rss>