<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deaths on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deaths/</link><description>Recent content in deaths on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deaths/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CDC investigating 109 cases of severe hepatitis in kids across two dozen states, including 5 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627664556300ace33b5a0929/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627664556300ace33b5a0929/</guid><description>The cases of severe hepatitis have been found across 25 states and territories.
Highlights The CDC is investigating 109 cases of severe hepatitis in children, including five deaths. More than 90% of the kids were hospitalized and 14% required liver transplants. The cases occurred over the past seven months across 25 states and territories. Hepatitis is an inflammation of the liver that is often caused by viral infections, but environmental factors can also play a role.</description></item><item><title>Covid's toll in the U.S. reaches a once unfathomable number: 1 million deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627321eefe701f275e6b622f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 01:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627321eefe701f275e6b622f/</guid><description>The U.S. on Wednesday recorded its 1 millionth Covid death, a once unthinkable toll even for the country with the world&amp;rsquo;s highest recorded toll from the virus.
Highlights The U.S. has the world&amp;rsquo;s highest recorded death toll from the Covid-19 pandemic. The number is equivalent to the population of San Jose, California, the 10th largest city in the United States. Brazil has recorded just over 660,000 confirmed Covid deaths; Peru has the highest number.</description></item><item><title>China reports first COVID deaths in more than a year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62360f056b0b6ee0e8b09830/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 17:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62360f056b0b6ee0e8b09830/</guid><description>Mainland China reported its first COVID-19 deaths in more than a year on Saturday, according to a post on the National Health Commission&amp;rsquo;s website that said two people died in the northeastern region of Jilin.
Highlights Mainland China reported its first COVID-19 deaths in more than a year on Saturday. Two people died in the northeastern region of Jilin, China&amp;rsquo;s northeastern region. One of the dead was not vaccinated, a senior official with the National Health Commission said.</description></item><item><title>One-third of all US child Covid deaths occurred during Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d7e0260c54b0d52289523/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 05:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d7e0260c54b0d52289523/</guid><description>Children seem to be facing increasing risks as mask mandates are abandoned and vaccination rates stall
Highlights 550 children have died from Covid-19 in the US, compared with 1,017 in the preceding 22 months. Omicron is less severe than Delta, but it is three to five times worse than previous variants, recent CDC research shows. Florida’s surgeon general recently recommended against vaccinating ‘health’ kids given the possibility of side-effects, which remain extremely rare and are outweighed by the vaccines’ protection.</description></item><item><title>US has suffered more than 1m excess deaths during pandemic, CDC finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ec83d73f565cb456f3193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 22:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ec83d73f565cb456f3193/</guid><description>The latest statistic hints at the breadth of Covid-19’s impact on health in the United States
Highlights There have been more than 1m excess deaths in the US during the pandemic. The deaths are mainly attributable to Covid-19, as well as conditions that may have resulted from delayed medical care and overwhelmed health systems. At least 923,000 Americans have died from confirmed Covid cases, according to the CDC. Other causes of death above the normally expected number have included heart disease, hypertension and Alzheimer’s disease.</description></item><item><title>CDC forecast predicts more than 62,000 Covid-19 deaths in the US in the next four weeks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfb20ba609b542595513bc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 05:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfb20ba609b542595513bc/</guid><description>An ensemble forecast from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention published Wednesday predicts that over 62,000 more people could die from Covid-19 over the next four weeks.
Summary (Joseph Prezioso/AFP/Getty Images)An ensemble forecast from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention published Wednesday predicts that over 62,000 more people could die from Covid-19 over the next four weeks. The forecast could mean an average of 2,624 Covid-19 deaths a day, up from a current average of 1,715 per day, according to JHU data.</description></item><item><title>Omicron could burn through the U.S. — and potentially hasten the Covid pandemic's end, says expert</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5d28689b7563d3d8f7fec/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 14:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5d28689b7563d3d8f7fec/</guid><description>Some researchers say omicron could hasten Covid&amp;rsquo;s transition from pandemic to endemic, albeit with large numbers of illnesses and potential deaths along the way. Here&amp;rsquo;s how.
Summary Now, some researchers say omicron could actually hasten the virus&amp;rsquo; transition from pandemic to endemic, albeit with large numbers of illnesses and potential deaths along the way. Omicron is highly contagious, but its influence on hospitalizations and deaths is yet unconfirmed by researchers. That means the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s future timeline is highly uncertain, even as experts broadly agree that Covid will eventually become an endemic and potentially seasonal disease.</description></item></channel></rss>