<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sheriff on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sheriff/</link><description>Recent content in sheriff on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 06:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sheriff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sheriff: Caretaker kills terminally ill women, then himself</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628731406f4747d56f8c57d8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 06:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628731406f4747d56f8c57d8/</guid><description>Officials say a 64-year-old Florida man whose wife and stepdaughter were terminally ill fatally shot the women and then called 911 before killing himself
Highlights Thomas Schultz, 64, called 911 saying family was &amp;ldquo;in an impossible situation with no way out,&amp;rdquo; sheriff says. Deputies found Thomas Schultz dead on the back porch, with a revolver next to him. The body of his wife, Joy, was in one bedroom; stepdaughter, in her 50s, in another room.</description></item><item><title>Casey White manhunt ends in Indiana, accomplice Vicky White hospitalized, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279cc3fdd92052d282307db/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 02:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279cc3fdd92052d282307db/</guid><description>Vicky White, a former Alabama corrections officer, died of self-inflicted gunshot wound, authorities say. Casey White and his suspected accomplice, Vicky, have been on the run since April 29. They were captured after a
Highlights Vicky White, a former Alabama corrections officer, died Monday night from self-inflicted gunshot wounds. Casey White, the fugitive inmate awaiting trial for capital murder, was arrested in Evansville, Indiana. The pair had been on the run since April 29 when the 56-year-old jailer told the Alabama jailer that she was transporting the inmate for a mental evaluation.</description></item><item><title>14-year old girl was accidentally shot by another child, says sheriff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e36603cf5629272aefb85/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e36603cf5629272aefb85/</guid><description>Alexis Sky Pierson, 14, died after being shot Tuesday when another child picked up what was believed to be an unloaded weapon and fired it towards her.
Highlights Alexis Sky Pierson, 14, died after being shot by another child in Hancock County, Mississippi. A 10-year-old picked up what appeared to be an unloaded weapon and fired it towards her. A bullet was discharged from the weapon, striking the girl just below her left eye.</description></item><item><title>Trial resumes for 4 men accused of Michigan governor plot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233d7083ac441ec052f6c1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233d7083ac441ec052f6c1c/</guid><description>A key figure in an alleged plot to kidnap Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer told an undercover FBI agent that he wanted to restrain the “tyrant” on a table then pose for a photo “like we just made the biggest drug bust,&amp;quot; according to a secret recording played for jurors Thursday.
Highlights Jury selection begins Tuesday, March 8, 2022, in the trial of four men who are accused of conspiring to snatch Michigan Gov.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky sheriff honors prisoner who pulled people from rubble of collapsed candle factory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d6e713b607b100522ed5c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d6e713b607b100522ed5c/</guid><description>A Kentucky prisoner who pulled people from the rubble of a collapsed candle factory in December was honored by a local sheriff last week for going &amp;quot;above and beyond&amp;quot; to help people.
Highlights A Kentucky prisoner who pulled people from the rubble of a collapsed candle factory in December was honored by a local sheriff last week. Marco Sanchez, a prisoner who worked at the Mayfield, Kentucky, candle factory, was injured in the collapse.</description></item><item><title>Former sheriff gets 4 life sentences in rape, incest case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62156e20b59bc10d2da0c442/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 23:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62156e20b59bc10d2da0c442/</guid><description>Jack Strain was sentenced to serve the rest of his life in prison after being found guilty of rape and incest.
Highlights Jack Strain was sentenced to serve the rest of his life in prison after being found guilty of rape and incest. He was convicted in November on four counts of aggravated rape, two counts of incest, one count of indecent behavior with a juvenile, and five years for sexual battery.</description></item><item><title>2nd guilty plea planned in alleged plot to kidnap Whitmer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201bc14806c5f17d8b054fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:41:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201bc14806c5f17d8b054fd/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A man charged in an alleged plot to kidnap Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer has agreed to plead guilty, according to documents filed Monday, giving prosecutors another insider who could be a key witness at a March trial.
Highlights Kaleb Franks said he would join Ty Garbin as the second person to admit guilt in a scheme to snatch the Democratic governor before FBI agents arrested them in October 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>