<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>happened on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/happened/</link><description>Recent content in happened on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:18:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/happened/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Someone Shot The Johnny Cash Water Tower In Kingsland, Arkansas, And Now It’s Taking A Leak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62833e17482ab39c59261f00/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62833e17482ab39c59261f00/</guid><description>Ok, well that&amp;rsquo;s just hilarious. Kingsland, Arkansas, is a tiny little town in Cleveland County, that&amp;rsquo;s not known for anything really&amp;hellip; except being the birthplace of Johnny Cash. And in honor of the Man In Black, Kingsland&amp;rsquo;s water tower features a silhouette of Johnny holding a guitar. However, according to the Arkansas Democrat Gazette, somebody recently put
Highlights In honor of the Man In Black, Kingsland’s water tower features a silhouette of Johnny Cash holding a guitar.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine win Eurovision with UK in second</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62810a59db3813eb5c2d34ea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62810a59db3813eb5c2d34ea/</guid><description>Ukraine wins the final of the Song Contest, followed by the UK, Spain, Sweden and then Serbia.
Highlights Kalush Orchestra wins the Song Contest, followed by the UK, Spain, Sweden and then Serbia. Ukraine fans flocked to Telegram to share their excitement at the news. Many people have been describing the country&amp;rsquo;s win as a &amp;ldquo;victory&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;glory to the heroes&amp;rdquo; Others have thanked friendly countries for voting and sharing their support for the country.</description></item><item><title>George Floyd’s 4-year-old niece shot after someone fired several shots into Houston apartment, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</guid><description>A 4-year-old girl was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.
Summary The shooting happened on Houston&amp;rsquo;s southside when someone fire multiple shots into the apartmentHOUSTON – George Floyd’s four-year-old niece was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.</description></item></channel></rss>