<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>far on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/far/</link><description>Recent content in far on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/far/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Like an inferno:' US West burning at furious pace so far</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ebc8bc73006448b9d24b0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ebc8bc73006448b9d24b0/</guid><description>LAGUNA NIGUEL, Calif. (AP) — Wildfires are on a furious pace early this year — from a California hilltop where mansions with multimillion-dollar Pacific Ocean views were torched to remote New Mexico mountains charred by a month-old monster blaze.
Highlights Wind-driven flames have torn through vegetation that is extraordinarily dry from years-long drought exacerbated by climate change. More than 2,000 square miles (5,180 square kilometers) have burned so far this year — the most at this point since 2018.</description></item><item><title>AP News: US finds 500 Native American boarding school deaths so far</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c8bcb2b988446f8bb453d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 04:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c8bcb2b988446f8bb453d/</guid><description>FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. (AP) — A first-of-its-kind federal study of Native American boarding schools that for over a century sought to assimilate Indigenous children into white society has identified more than 500 student deaths at the institutions, but officials expect that figure to grow exponentially as research continues.
Highlights First-of-its-kind federal study of Native American boarding schools has identified more than 500 student deaths at the institutions. Officials expect that figure to grow exponentially as research continues.</description></item><item><title>Evacuations ordered at Florida building deemed unsafe not far from site of Surfside collapse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c33ad61157a0f9ede858c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 12:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c33ad61157a0f9ede858c/</guid><description>Residents were ordered to evacuate an apartment building in North Miami Beach, Florida, after engineers found the five-story structure unsafe months after the
Highlights Engineers found excessive &amp;ldquo;deflection&amp;rdquo; — or sagging — in concrete slabs on the building&amp;rsquo;s second and third floors. Bayview 60 Homes&amp;rsquo; owners began examining the building in July, just after 98 people were killed when a Surfside, Florida, condo building collapsed. Tenants will be compensated for accommodations for the next three nights at up to $150 per night, and they will be refunded their April rent and security deposits.</description></item><item><title>Fox's Neil Cavuto said a second case of Covid-19 nearly killed him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214e28aa60336e59135c446/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214e28aa60336e59135c446/</guid><description>Neil Cavuto, an immunocompromised Fox anchor who has dissented from the loudest voices at the right-wing network and spoken out in favor of Covid-19 vaccines, revealed on Monday that he had been hospitalized for weeks with a serious case of coronavirus and nearly died.
Highlights Fox Business anchor Neil Cavuto, an immunocompromised Fox anchor who has dissented from the loudest voices at the right-wing network and spoken out in favor of Covid-19 vaccines, revealed on Monday that he had been hospitalized for weeks with a serious case of coronavirus and nearly died.</description></item><item><title>India has “substantially greater” COVID-19 deaths than official reports suggest—close to 3 million, which is more than six times higher than the government has acknowledged and the largest number of any country. The finding could prompt scrutiny of other countries with anomalously low death rates.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</guid><description>Summary India, from the earliest days of the pandemic, has reported far fewer COVID-19 deaths than expected given the toll elsewhere—an apparent death “paradox” that some believed was real and others thought would prove illusory. That’s 340 COVID-19 deaths per million—about one-seventh the per capita COVID-19 mortality tallied in the United States. “The Indian government very much is trying to suppress the numbers in the way that they coded the COVID deaths,” Jha says.</description></item></channel></rss>