<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>far on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/far/</link><description>Recent content in far on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 13:18:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/far/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fox's Neil Cavuto said a second case of Covid-19 nearly killed him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214e28aa60336e59135c446/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214e28aa60336e59135c446/</guid><description>Neil Cavuto, an immunocompromised Fox anchor who has dissented from the loudest voices at the right-wing network and spoken out in favor of Covid-19 vaccines, revealed on Monday that he had been hospitalized for weeks with a serious case of coronavirus and nearly died.
Highlights Fox Business anchor Neil Cavuto, an immunocompromised Fox anchor who has dissented from the loudest voices at the right-wing network and spoken out in favor of Covid-19 vaccines, revealed on Monday that he had been hospitalized for weeks with a serious case of coronavirus and nearly died.</description></item><item><title>India has “substantially greater” COVID-19 deaths than official reports suggest—close to 3 million, which is more than six times higher than the government has acknowledged and the largest number of any country. The finding could prompt scrutiny of other countries with anomalously low death rates.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</guid><description>Summary India, from the earliest days of the pandemic, has reported far fewer COVID-19 deaths than expected given the toll elsewhere—an apparent death “paradox” that some believed was real and others thought would prove illusory. That’s 340 COVID-19 deaths per million—about one-seventh the per capita COVID-19 mortality tallied in the United States. “The Indian government very much is trying to suppress the numbers in the way that they coded the COVID deaths,” Jha says.</description></item></channel></rss>