<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>calif on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/calif/</link><description>Recent content in calif on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:13:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/calif/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man kills 3 daughters, 1 other, himself at California church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e9a517842b39f085c053d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e9a517842b39f085c053d/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — A man shot and killed his three daughters, their chaperone and himself during a supervised visit with the girls Monday at a church in Sacramento, California, authorities said.
Highlights Deputies responding to reports of gunfire around 5 p.m. found five people dead, including the shooter, at the church in the Arden-Arcade neighborhood. Shooter was estranged from his daughters’ mother, who had a restraining order against him, sheriff says.</description></item><item><title>Black Lives Matter 'delinquent' on finances, Calif. AG warns BLM risks tax-exempt status</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbaa8f42bfb14c703585b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 10:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbaa8f42bfb14c703585b0/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (TND) — California&amp;rsquo;s Department of Justice is reportedly warning a Black Lives Matter (BLM) organization it will hold leaders accountable if they fail to provide financial information regarding the charity group&amp;rsquo;s supposed current $60 million bankroll. The Washington Examiner published a letter it obtained fromAttorney General Rob Bonta which says, for the 2020 tax year, &amp;quot;the organization BLACK LIVES MATTER GLOBAL NETWORK FOUNDATION, INC.
Highlights California&amp;rsquo;s Department of Justice is reportedly warning a Black Lives Matter organization it will hold leaders accountable if they fail to provide financial information regarding the charity group&amp;rsquo;s supposed current $60 million bankroll.</description></item></channel></rss>