<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>library on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/library/</link><description>Recent content in library on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 14:17:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/library/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conservative parents take aim at library apps meant to expand access to books</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e6869d878ff238f6a4995/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 14:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e6869d878ff238f6a4995/</guid><description>E-reader apps that expand access to books for students are now under fire by conservative parents in a culture war over book bans in schools.
Highlights E-reader apps that expand access to books for students are now under fire by conservative parents in a culture war over books in schools and public libraries. Some parents want the apps to be banned for their children or even for all students. The apps often market themselves to schools and libraries as a way to diversify their digital shelves, especially after racial justice protests in spring 2020 drew attention to the lack of diversity in many traditional institutions.</description></item><item><title>Book banning in Texas schools: Titles are pulled off library shelves in record numbers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fae5d2cca3859fd01ec996/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 20:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fae5d2cca3859fd01ec996/</guid><description>Texas schools are pulling books from libraries amid pressure from GOP politicians and parents and threats of criminal charges.
Highlights Parents and conservative politicians in Texas are trying to ban books dealing with race, sexuality and gender from schools, an NBC News investigation has found. Hundreds of titles have been pulled from libraries across the state for review, sometimes over the objections of school librarians. Some titles were removed after parents formally complained, but others were quietly banned by the district without official reviews.</description></item></channel></rss>