<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reservoirs on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reservoirs/</link><description>Recent content in reservoirs on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 18:18:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reservoirs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More human remains found at Lake Mead as reservoir's water level plunges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62795ad0b0abf73599607b72/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 18:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62795ad0b0abf73599607b72/</guid><description>More human remains were found at Lake Mead over the weekend, days after a body was found in a barrel.
Highlights The West&amp;rsquo;s megadrought is already at &amp;lsquo;critically low levels&amp;rsquo; and the dry season is just starting. The Colorado River irrigates farms, powers electric grids and provides drinking water for 40 million people. Experts say the term &amp;lsquo;drought&amp;rsquo; may be insufficient to capture what is happening in the West. More human remains were found at Lake Mead over the weekend, days after a body was found in a barrel.</description></item><item><title>New government maps show nearly all of the West is in drought and it's not even summer yet: "This is unprecedented"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e9558a2248a51edafc57f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e9558a2248a51edafc57f/</guid><description>The latest government maps show 95% of California is suffering severe or extreme drought.
Highlights Southern California officials ask residents to limit outdoor watering to once a week. Nearly all of the West is in drought, and 95% of California is suffering severe or extreme drought. Lake Mead, the largest reservoir in the nation formed by the Hoover Dam on the Colorado River, needs a new pump to ensure water can flow to Las Vegas.</description></item></channel></rss>