<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>agency on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/agency/</link><description>Recent content in agency on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 02:03:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/agency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Let's help them get straight to hell': Ukraine tears down road signs so Russians get lost</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621adbd759367d70b37aa606/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 02:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621adbd759367d70b37aa606/</guid><description>In a Facebook post, the Ukrainian road agency said: &amp;lsquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s help them get straight to hell&amp;rsquo;
Highlights State Agency of Motor Roads of Ukraine posted plea to Facebook alongside image of sign with all directions instructing Russian soldiers to &amp;lsquo;f*** off&amp;rsquo; Earlier it had asked people to take action if they saw &amp;rsquo;enemy vehicles&amp;rsquo; and block them. Ministry of Defence tweeted intelligence update on the situation in Ukraine. It said: &amp;lsquo;Russian casualties are likely to be heavy and greater than anticipated or acknowledged by the Kremlin&amp;rsquo; Video emerged of man telling stranded Russians he could ‘tow them back to Russia” It came as ministry of defence tweeted: “Russian forces have continued their advance on Kyiv with the bulk of their forces now 30km from the centre of the city” READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>U.S. agency refers 80 unruly airplane passengers for potential prosecution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 04:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</guid><description>A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Wednesday, as onboard disruptions rose sharply in 2021, many over COVID-19 mask requirements.
Highlights A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday. The Justice Department said Wednesday it was prosecuting a record number of passengers for interfering with flight crews.</description></item><item><title>Too little, too late: 500K nurses are leaving the bedside by the end of 2022</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd884ee25e4e8cf8ac6b62/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd884ee25e4e8cf8ac6b62/</guid><description>The pandemic accelerated an anticipated nurse shortage by 20 years. What does it mean for the future of healthcare?
Highlights Before the pandemic, Brittany Kennedy was working for a family and their child, picking up shifts as she — and they — needed. The added strain caused many healthcare workers to lose the passion they previously had for the job. The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics projects that 500,000 seasoned nurses are expected to retire between now and the end of 2022, creating a shortage of 1.</description></item><item><title>Kim Jong Un pictured looking noticeably slimmer, fanning rumours of health issues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd9f68eb6857e5cbec9b7c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd9f68eb6857e5cbec9b7c/</guid><description>Authorities have insisted Kim is simply eating less &amp;quot;for the sake of the country,&amp;quot; which is grappling with severe food shortages
Summary The Workers&amp;rsquo; Party&amp;rsquo;s Central Committee met to decide policies meant to &amp;ldquo;guide the struggle of our party and people … to the next stage of victory,&amp;rdquo; according to the official Korean Central News Agency. The agency did not carry any remarks by Kim. The meeting comes as Kim marks 10 years since assuming power after the death of his father, Kim Jong Il, in 2011.</description></item></channel></rss>