<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bag on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bag/</link><description>Recent content in bag on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 22:09:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bag/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emmett grandmother gets up to 20 years after granddaughter found dead in trash bag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628962ff1e2fe405912b6987/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 22:09:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628962ff1e2fe405912b6987/</guid><description>An Emmett woman accused of failing to notify authorities of her granddaughter&amp;rsquo;s death last year has been sentenced to up to 20 years. Earlier this year, Connie Ann Smith pleaded guilty to felony injury to a child and failure to notify of a death. She is the grandmother of 8-year-old Taryn Summers&amp;rsquo; (aka Quinton), whose remains were found on Smith&amp;rsquo;s property inside a trash bag on April 14. She&amp;rsquo;ll have to serve a minimum of five years before she&amp;rsquo;ll be eligible for parole, court records state.</description></item><item><title>Body found in duffel bag in Queens park; Orsolya Gaal identified, police questioning teen son</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d3a54ac3c8570c8a697be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d3a54ac3c8570c8a697be/</guid><description>A woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a duffel bag in a New York City park Saturday. Police are now questioning her teen son.
Highlights A woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a duffel bag in a Queens park early Saturday morning. Police say she was not dismembered but placed in the bag and closed off. Police are now questioning her teen son. The family of four lives in the home where she was found dead in Queens park.</description></item></channel></rss>