<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plan/</link><description>Recent content in plan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 19:13:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida students win yearbook flap over "Don't Say Gay" bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c0aad3e9eff1fa90caf41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c0aad3e9eff1fa90caf41/</guid><description>Students at a central Florida high school are declaring victory after taking their protest to their school board over plans to censor a yearbook page showing a student walkout against the state&amp;rsquo;s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law
Highlights Florida school board overruled superintendent&amp;rsquo;s plan to cover up a yearbook page showing a student walkout. Page showed students waving rainbow flags and a “love is love” sign during a walkout against the state&amp;rsquo;s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law.</description></item><item><title>Judge: 'More likely than not' that Trump 'corruptly attempted' to block Congress from counting votes on January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624224b07d71fc0d9e494070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 21:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624224b07d71fc0d9e494070/</guid><description>A federal judge said Monday that former President Donald Trump and right-wing attorney John Eastman may have been planning a crime as they sought to disrupt the January 6 congressional certification of the presidential election.
Highlights Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson, President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s pick to replace retiring Justice Stephen Breyer on the U.S. Supreme Court, would become the first Black woman to serve on the Supreme Court if confirmed. Former President Donald Trump and right-wing attorney John Eastman may have been planning a crime as they sought to disrupt the January 6 congressional certification of the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Ohio village scraps plan with affordable housing after Dave Chappelle threatens to pull his businesses</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204d6da056d4f6d744efc22/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204d6da056d4f6d744efc22/</guid><description>Yellow Springs, Ohio, failed to approve a zoning ordinance that included dozens of affordable housing units after opposition from comedian Dave Chappelle.
Highlights Yellow Springs, Ohio, failed to approve a zoning ordinance that included dozens of affordable housing units. Comedian Dave Chappelle called the Village Council &amp;ldquo;clowns&amp;rdquo; and threatened that his business ventures would be &amp;ldquo;off the table&amp;rdquo; The vote deadlocked at 2-2, ensuring that the new housing development cannot proceed.</description></item><item><title>Irish fishermen plan to disrupt Russian military exercise</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f03acd01546fdb0857fb25/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f03acd01546fdb0857fb25/</guid><description>The Chief Executive Officer of the Irish South and West Fish Producers Organisation has said some of their members plan to peacefully disrupt Russia&amp;rsquo;s plans to conduct a military exercise in waters off the Irish coast next month.
Summary The Chief Executive Officer of the Irish South and West Fish Producers Organisation has said some of their members plan to peacefully disrupt Russia&amp;rsquo;s plans to conduct a military exercise in waters off the Irish coast next month.</description></item><item><title>Ohio's high court overturns new congressional map saying it 'unduly favors' Republicans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e263310c9630cf76136ffc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e263310c9630cf76136ffc/</guid><description>Ohio&amp;rsquo;s state supreme court ruled Friday that the state&amp;rsquo;s newly-drawn congressional map, which was passed by the GOP-controlled legislature, violates the state constitution because it &amp;quot;unduly favors the Republican Party and disfavors the Democratic Party.&amp;quot;
Summary (CNN) Ohio&amp;rsquo;s state supreme court ruled Friday that the state&amp;rsquo;s newly-drawn congressional map, which was passed by the GOP-controlled legislature, violates the state constitution because it &amp;ldquo;unduly favors the Republican Party and disfavors the Democratic Party.</description></item><item><title>Ireland Will Soon Pay Arts and Culture Workers a Basic Income to Help the Sector Bounce Back From the Pandemic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</guid><description>Ireland announces a basic income plan for artists in an effort to counter the ongoing effects of the pandemic and lockdown.
Summary Artists and culture workers in Ireland will soon be eligible for some much-needed financial support as the government readies a new basic income program. Ireland will commit roughly €25 million ($28.3 million) to the program, which it expects to implement early this year. It will pay some 2,000 people a basic income for three years.</description></item></channel></rss>