<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>owner on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/owner/</link><description>Recent content in owner on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/owner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Doc Antle, Myrtle Beach Safari owner featured in Netflix documentary "Tiger King", arrested by FBI</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b83cae026d884c385ad41/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b83cae026d884c385ad41/</guid><description>No charges have been listed for Antle as of 6:30 p.m. Friday.
Highlights Bhagavan “Doc” Antle was booked into the J. Reuben Long Detention Center on Friday. No charges have been listed for Antle as of 10 a.m. Saturday. PETA recently called for an investigation into the Myrtle Beach Safari and nonprofit Rare Species Fund. The organization claimed Antle used charitable donations to fund the zoo while claiming to support wildlife conservation.</description></item><item><title>Art Rupe, label owner who helped launch Little Richard and Sam Cooke, dies at 104 | Music</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c8294126e693559f18929/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 21:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c8294126e693559f18929/</guid><description>Rock and Roll Hall of Fame member Rupe founded Specialty Records, whose artists also included John Lee Hooker and Lloyd Price
Highlights Art Rupe was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2011. Rupe founded Specialty Records in 1946 and helped launch careers of Little Richard, Sam Cooke and others. Little Richard&amp;rsquo;s Tutti Frutti was one of rock’n’roll’s first major hits, released in September 1955. He was known for how little he paid his artists and engaged in an exploitative practice common among label owners in the early rock era: having performers sign contracts with much of the royalties and publishing rights.</description></item><item><title>Rep. Jeff Fortenberry resigns from Congress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f9dff62cf537b9c986a8e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 23:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f9dff62cf537b9c986a8e/</guid><description>Rep. Jeff Fortenberry has announced he is resigning from Congress.
Highlights Rep. Jeff Fortenberry has announced he is resigning from Congress. All stories about him and any declared candidates in the Nebraska First Congressional District race have been and will be written by outside media outlets. Mike Flood is the founder and owner of Flood Communications and News Channel Nebraska. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>