<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>university on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/university/</link><description>Recent content in university on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 03:04:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ferdinand Marcos Jr urged to stop pretending he has an Oxford degree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628310a576d1b4d894c00a06/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628310a576d1b4d894c00a06/</guid><description>University has said Philippines leader was awarded ‘special diploma in social studies’ in 1978, not a BA
Highlights Ferdinand Marcos Jr is facing calls to stop misrepresenting the circumstances of his studies at Oxford University. The university has confirmed that he did not complete his BA in Philosophy, Politics and Economics after enrolling in 1975. Marcos Jr has claimed in interviews that Oxford issued him with a bachelor’s degree, while his official spokesperson has said that the politician and his team “stand by the degree confirmation which was issued by the University of Oxford” Marcos failed two of his three preliminary exams at Oxford in the summer of 1976, later doing only enough to pass one of two resits – failing politics for a second time.</description></item><item><title>'Holy cow ... are you kidding me?' Scientists stunned to see plants grow in soil from the moon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e60c5e75291a0898d262e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 13:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e60c5e75291a0898d262e/</guid><description>Researchers had no idea if anything would sprout in harsh moon dirt and wanted to see if it could be used to grow food by the next generation of lunar explorers. The results stunned them.
Highlights Researchers had no idea if anything would sprout in the harsh moon dirt and wanted to see if it could be used to grow food by the next generation of lunar explorers. The downside was that after the first week, the coarseness and other properties of the lunar soil stressed the small, flowering weeds so much that they grew more slowly than seedlings planted in fake moon dirt from Earth.</description></item><item><title>Bogus test taker to be sentenced in college admissions scam</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625169d4cf46c084cb94cc43/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 11:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625169d4cf46c084cb94cc43/</guid><description>A former Florida prep school administrator has been sentenced to prison and a University of Southern California water polo coach has been convicted in the long running college admissions bribery scandal
Highlights A former Florida prep school administrator has been sentenced to prison and a University of Southern California water polo coach has been convicted in the long running college admissions bribery scandal. Mark Riddell, who was paid handsomely to take college entrance exams for wealthy students, was handed a four-month prison sentence, ordered to serve two years of supervised release and forfeit nearly $240,000.</description></item><item><title>US man who got 1st pig heart transplant dies after 2 months</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228e086c5d6a1a2c0f17cd9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228e086c5d6a1a2c0f17cd9/</guid><description>The first person to receive a heart transplant from a pig has died, two months after the groundbreaking experiment, the Maryland hospital that performed the surgery announced Wednesday. David Bennett, 57, died Tuesday at the University of Maryland Medical Center.
Highlights David Bennett, 57, died Tuesday at the University of Maryland Medical Center. Doctors didn’t give an exact cause of death, saying only that his condition had begun deteriorating several days earlier.</description></item><item><title>Germany: Several injured at Heidelberg University after student opens fire in lecture hall; then kills himself.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eef754befb8041d1cd3d53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eef754befb8041d1cd3d53/</guid><description>The attacker entered the theatre in the Neuenheimer Feld area, opened fire and then fled the scene, police said.
Summary Germany: Lone gunman dead after shooting four people at university in HeidelbergGermany: Lone gunman dead after shooting four people at university in Heidelberg The attacker entered the theatre in the Neuenheimer Feld area, opened fire and then fled the scene, police said. Pic: APA lone gunman has shot four people at a university lecture hall in Germany - some of whom are seriously injured.</description></item><item><title>Omicron is ‘not the same disease’ as earlier Covid waves, says UK scientist | Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</guid><description>Sir John Bell says disease ‘appears less severe’ as other scientists criticise lack of new restrictions in England
Summary Omicron is “not the same disease we were seeing a year ago” and high Covid death rates in the UK are “now history”, a leading immunologist has said. Fewer patients were needing high-flow oxygen and the average length of stay was down to three days, he said. George Eustice, the environment secretary, said the government was keeping the level of Covid hospital admissions under “very close review”.</description></item><item><title>University of Hong Kong appears to demolish Tiananmen Massacre monument in dead of night - Hong Kong Free Press HKFP</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</guid><description>Summary Workers at the University of Hong Kong (HKU) removed the Tiananmen Massacre monument late on Wednesday night, months after the university said the statue must go. Pillar of Shame. Jens Galschiøt’s Pillar of Shame monument has stood on campus for over two decades, though – in October – university authorities demanded its removal amid a crackdown on those commemorating the 1989 massacre. The University of Hong Kong ordered the removal of the Pillar of Shame, an eight-metre tall sculpture commemorating the 1989 Tiananmen Massacre, from its campus in October.</description></item><item><title>Utah billionaire leaves Mormon church, donates $600K to LGBTQ group</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</guid><description>Description Jeff Green, a billionaire from Utah, resigned from the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and donated to LGBTQ group Equality Utah.
Summary “The church leadership is not honest about its history, its finances, and its advocacy,” he wrote, according to the Tribune. “We made this investment sizable and publicly to send a message that Equality Utah isn’t going anywhere,” Green wrote, adding that he hopes the donation is the first of many.</description></item></channel></rss>