<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>university on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/university/</link><description>Recent content in university on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Omicron is ‘not the same disease’ as earlier Covid waves, says UK scientist | Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</guid><description>Sir John Bell says disease ‘appears less severe’ as other scientists criticise lack of new restrictions in England
Summary Omicron is “not the same disease we were seeing a year ago” and high Covid death rates in the UK are “now history”, a leading immunologist has said. Fewer patients were needing high-flow oxygen and the average length of stay was down to three days, he said. George Eustice, the environment secretary, said the government was keeping the level of Covid hospital admissions under “very close review”.</description></item><item><title>University of Hong Kong appears to demolish Tiananmen Massacre monument in dead of night - Hong Kong Free Press HKFP</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</guid><description>Summary Workers at the University of Hong Kong (HKU) removed the Tiananmen Massacre monument late on Wednesday night, months after the university said the statue must go. Pillar of Shame. Jens Galschiøt’s Pillar of Shame monument has stood on campus for over two decades, though – in October – university authorities demanded its removal amid a crackdown on those commemorating the 1989 massacre. The University of Hong Kong ordered the removal of the Pillar of Shame, an eight-metre tall sculpture commemorating the 1989 Tiananmen Massacre, from its campus in October.</description></item><item><title>Utah billionaire leaves Mormon church, donates $600K to LGBTQ group</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</guid><description>Description Jeff Green, a billionaire from Utah, resigned from the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and donated to LGBTQ group Equality Utah.
Summary “The church leadership is not honest about its history, its finances, and its advocacy,” he wrote, according to the Tribune. “We made this investment sizable and publicly to send a message that Equality Utah isn’t going anywhere,” Green wrote, adding that he hopes the donation is the first of many.</description></item></channel></rss>