<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>automakers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/automakers/</link><description>Recent content in automakers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 13:19:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/automakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arizona family can sue Jeep after being hit by Jeep Cherokee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f6ea2999fb9a8b37f085f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 13:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f6ea2999fb9a8b37f085f/</guid><description>The Arizona Supreme Court overturned a similar 2019 decision that said automakers were immune to such lawsuits because of the federal agency’s decision not to require the technology. The case now goes back to a trial court, unless Fiat Chrysler files an
Highlights Arizona Supreme Court rejects Fiat Chrysler Automobiles&amp;rsquo; claim that federal agency pre-empted lawsuit. 4-year-old Vivian Varela was killed when her mother’s car was rear-ended by a Jeep on a Phoenix freeway.</description></item><item><title>A Fight Over the Right to Repair Cars Turns Ugly</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fca80b0f1a93c57994551a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 04:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fca80b0f1a93c57994551a/</guid><description>In the wake of a voter-approved law, Subaru and Kia dealers in Massachusetts have disabled systems that allow remote starts and send maintenance alerts.
Highlights Massachusetts voters approved a voter-approved right-to-repair ballot measure in 2020. The measure required automakers to give car owners and independent mechanics more access to data about the car’s internal systems. New vehicles are now computers on wheels, gathering an estimated 25 gigabytes per hour of driving data.</description></item></channel></rss>