<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>right on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/right/</link><description>Recent content in right on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 21:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/right/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. abortion rights activists start 'summer of rage' with Saturday protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62801b553f6a9e6023db2c58/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 21:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62801b553f6a9e6023db2c58/</guid><description>Thousands of abortion rights supporters rallied across the United States on Saturday to express their anger over fears the Roe v. Wade case that legalized abortion nationwide will be overturned by the U.S. Supreme Court.
Highlights Protests held across the U.S. over fears the Roe v. Wade case that legalized abortion nationwide will be overturned. Large gatherings in New York, Washington, Los Angeles and Chicago with some smaller counter-protests. The court&amp;rsquo;s final ruling, which could give states the power to ban abortion, is expected in June.</description></item><item><title>A Fight Over the Right to Repair Cars Turns Ugly</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fca80b0f1a93c57994551a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 04:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fca80b0f1a93c57994551a/</guid><description>In the wake of a voter-approved law, Subaru and Kia dealers in Massachusetts have disabled systems that allow remote starts and send maintenance alerts.
Highlights Massachusetts voters approved a voter-approved right-to-repair ballot measure in 2020. The measure required automakers to give car owners and independent mechanics more access to data about the car’s internal systems. New vehicles are now computers on wheels, gathering an estimated 25 gigabytes per hour of driving data.</description></item></channel></rss>