<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stocks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stocks/</link><description>Recent content in stocks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 04:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Denmark stocks up on iodine pills to bolster nuclear emergency plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254fd1a5bcf24a56997c2c8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254fd1a5bcf24a56997c2c8/</guid><description>Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Health Agency, concerned by the war in Ukraine, will buy 2 million iodine tablets to protect people in the event of a nuclear accident close to the Nordic country, it said on Monday.
Highlights Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Health Agency will buy 2 million iodine tablets to protect people in the event of a nuclear accident close to the Nordic country. The first deliveries are expected within two to three months. Denmark is more than 900 kilometres from the nearest nuclear plants in Ukraine, according to the health agency.</description></item><item><title>Fed approves rules banning its officials from trading stocks, bonds and also cryptocurrencies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621019f25f60ba9d40647356/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 22:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621019f25f60ba9d40647356/</guid><description>Fed officials won&amp;rsquo;t be able to trade stocks and bonds — as well as cryptocurrencies — under new rules that became formal Friday.
Highlights New rules ban officials from trading stocks and bonds from the Federal Reserve. Restrictions apply to members of the Fed and staff who regularly attend board meetings. The new rules were announced in October. They will take effect on May 1, 2015, with most of the rules taking effect until further review is complete.</description></item></channel></rss>