<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>national on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/national/</link><description>Recent content in national on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:09:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/national/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Soccer equalizes pay in milestone with women, men</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62856e8f3d71bf8b8b420f14/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62856e8f3d71bf8b8b420f14/</guid><description>The U.S. Soccer Federation reached milestone agreements to pay its men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams equally, making the American national governing body the first in the sport to promise both sexes matching money.
Highlights The U.S. Soccer Federation reached milestone agreements to pay its men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams equally. The federation on Wednesday announced separate collective bargaining agreements through December 2028 with the unions for both national teams. The deals grew partly out of a push by players on the more successful women’s team, including stars like Alex Morgan and Megan Rapinoe, who were at the forefront of the gender equity fight.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau makes surprise visit to Kyiv as Russia readies ‘Victory Day’ show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277fafcf12bbf65c4cda410/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277fafcf12bbf65c4cda410/</guid><description>During the visit, he is expected to meet in person with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy as Ukrainian forces continue to push back Russian soldiers.
Highlights Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has just made a surprise visit to the Ukrainian capital of Kyiv. The brief trip was supposed to be kept under wraps until after Trudeau left. During the visit, he is expected to meet in person with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy as Ukrainian forces continue to push back Russian soldiers in a stunning show of courage and defiance that has galvanized supporters around the world.</description></item><item><title>Autor of 'How to Murder Your Husband' now on trial for husband's murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d59cc001c1fca641ff5b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 09:14:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d59cc001c1fca641ff5b5/</guid><description>Nancy Crampton Brophy has been accused of fatally shooting her husband, Daniel Brophy.
Highlights Nancy Crampton-Brophy, 71, has been accused of fatally shooting her husband, Daniel Brophy, 63, in June of 2018. She was arrested and charged with the murder three months after his death. Despite the title of her essay, a judge has ruled the online post can’t be presented as evidence against her. The judge said the post was old and was written for a writing seminar, which was written 11 years ago.</description></item><item><title>U.S. soldiers alive, despite Russia 'fake news' report, U.S. military says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 10:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</guid><description>Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well, the Tennessee National Guard said on Thursday.
Highlights Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well. President Joe Biden ordered the withdrawal of U.</description></item><item><title>Endurance is Found</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228fbedd7f79feee7804fcf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 19:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228fbedd7f79feee7804fcf/</guid><description>The Falklands Maritime Heritage Trust is pleased to confirm that the Endurance22 Expedition has located the wreck of Endurance.
Highlights Endurance was found at a depth of 3008 metres in the Weddell Sea, within the search area defined by the expedition team before its departure from Cape Town. The wreck is protected as a Historic Site and Monument under the Antarctic Treaty, ensuring that whilst the wreck is being surveyed and filmed it will not be touched or disturbed in any way.</description></item><item><title>South Florida fraternity suspended for swastika incident amid national wave of campus anti-Semitism</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e29ceb46e0412ee1a3b42/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e29ceb46e0412ee1a3b42/</guid><description>“Campuses today are as politically charged and polarized as I’ve ever seen them, with zero tolerance for individuals whose identities, beliefs or opinions run afoul of dominant campus ideologies,” said Tammi Rossman-Benjamin, director of the AMCHA Initiative.
Highlights A fraternity at the University of South Florida was suspended after photos circulated of a Feb. 11 event in which members of the group, including a Jewish student, reportedly had swastikas drawn on their “shirts or body parts” A meeting between school officials and a representative of the fraternity is scheduled for March 1, at which a hearing officer will determine if the suspension is to “remain, be modified, or be lifted” The suspension of Pi Kappa Phi’s USF chapter comes amid a string of anti-Semitic and anti-Israel activity at colleges and universities across the country in recent weeks.</description></item><item><title>Star witness in Ukraine impeachment saga sues Trump allies and alleges conspiracy to intimidate him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb357790ec5ce7283f38d9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 01:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb357790ec5ce7283f38d9/</guid><description>Retired Army Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman, who served on the National Security Council and emerged as a star witness against then-President Donald Trump during the 2019 Ukraine impeachment, is suing Donald Trump Jr., Rudy Giuliani and former Trump White House staffers, alleging they conspired against him.
Highlights Retired Army Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman served on the National Security Council and emerged as a star witness against then-President Donald Trump during the 2019 Ukraine impeachment.</description></item><item><title>Canada deploys special forces to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</guid><description>Global News has learned that a small contingent of Canadian special forces soldiers sent to aid Ukrainian government, plan for potential embassy evacuation should Russia invade.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailCanadian special forces operators have been deployed to Ukraine amid rising tensions between the NATO military alliance and Russia, Global News has learned. Sources told Global News that the Canadian special operations presence is part of an attempt by NATO allies to deter Russian aggression in Ukraine, and to identify ways to assist the Ukrainian government.</description></item></channel></rss>