<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prepared on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prepared/</link><description>Recent content in prepared on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prepared/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fed Governor Christopher Waller says he’s prepared to take rates past ‘neutral’ to fight inflation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295b1c23b2b93906b7d7718/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295b1c23b2b93906b7d7718/</guid><description>Fed Governor Christopher Waller said he would support hikes that pass through exceed the &amp;quot;neutral&amp;quot; level.
Highlights Fed Governor Christopher Waller says he would support hikes that exceed the &amp;ldquo;neutral&amp;rdquo; level. Waller: &amp;ldquo;I am not taking 50 basis-point hikes off the table until I see inflation coming down closer to our 2 percent target&amp;rdquo; The central bank official said he thinks the Fed can raise rates and tamp down demand without causing a severe economic downturn.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutors resigned after New York DA said he wasn't prepared to move forward with indictment of Trump</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226915f3a4150fb2029b642/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 23:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226915f3a4150fb2029b642/</guid><description>Two top prosecutors in the Trump investigation into former President Donald Trump resigned last month. The resignations followed weeks of internal debate and discussion over the strength of the evidence against Trump. Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg said he wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared to
Highlights Two senior prosecutors on the team resigned last month after the Manhattan district attorney said he was not prepared to authorize an indictment against the former President. The resignations followed weeks of internal debate and discussion over the strength of the evidence against Trump.</description></item></channel></rss>