<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fentanyl on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fentanyl/</link><description>Recent content in fentanyl on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fentanyl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FOX 11 Los Angeles: 2 maintenance workers die after fentanyl exposure at downtown LA apartment complex.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fc758b7d9f8ec1d8d5e42/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fc758b7d9f8ec1d8d5e42/</guid><description>Two maintenance workers are dead after police believe they may have been exposed to fentanyl at a downtown Los Angeles apartment complex.
Highlights Los Angeles Police Department responded to a hazmat call in the 800 block of South Olive Street a little before 11 a.m. Thursday. When officers arrived at the apartment complex, they found two unconscious men unconscious. Luis Garcia and John Black, who were maintenance workers at the building, were pronounced dead at the scene.</description></item><item><title>US drug overdose deaths reach another record high as deaths from fentanyl surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623486d73f0d29ebc8b82f1b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623486d73f0d29ebc8b82f1b/</guid><description>Annual drug overdose deaths have reached another record high in the United States as deaths from fentanyl and other synthetic opioids surge to unprecedented levels.
Highlights An estimated 105,752 people died of drug overdoses in the 12-month period ending October 2021. About two-thirds of those deaths involved synthetic opioids such as fentanyl, a stronger and faster-acting drug than natural opiates. Overdose deaths involving these drugs have nearly doubled over the past two years.</description></item><item><title>‘Extremely alarming:’ Cocaine laced with fentanyl causes 6 overdoses in Wilton Manors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c2b8354a131c89796302a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 05:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c2b8354a131c89796302a/</guid><description>Fort Lauderdale fire rescue is on the scene of what they are calling a mass casualty incident; 6 people have overdosed, according to the fire chief.
Highlights Cocaine laced with fentanyl caused a group of spring breakers to overdose on Thursday in Wilton Manors. Fort Lauderdale Fire Rescue personnel responded about 5 p.m. to a short-term rental vacation home, at 811 NW 29th Ct., and found six people suffering from a drug overdose.</description></item><item><title>13-Year-Old Student Dies of Fentanyl-Related Overdose at Hartford School: PD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</guid><description>A 13-year-old student at The Sport and Medical Sciences Academy in Hartford who was in grave condition because of an overdose has now died, according to police&amp;hellip;.
Summary The Hartford Public Schools superintendent has released a statement. &amp;ldquo;I extend my heart and offer my deepest condolences to the student’s family, friends, and loved ones for their loss. I ask that everyone keep the family, friends, and the entire school community at SMSA in their thoughts and prayers,&amp;rdquo; she said in part.</description></item></channel></rss>