<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kill on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kill/</link><description>Recent content in kill on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Murder Your Husband writer found guilty of murdering husband</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fcff95e196320db24e681/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fcff95e196320db24e681/</guid><description>Portland jury finds Nancy Crampton Brophy guilty of killing chef Daniel Brophy in June 2018
Highlights Nancy Crampton Brophy, 71, found guilty of second-degree murder of her husband. The self-published romance novelist wrote an essay titled How to Murder Your Husband. The essay detailed various options for committing an untraceable killing. It was written in the form of a brainstorming exercise for writers in 2011. Daniel Brophy was killed on 2 June 2018 as he prepared for work at the Oregon Culinary Institute in south-west Portland.</description></item><item><title>Man used ‘ghost gun’ to kill 3 daughters in church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226f480aa1c3a79c001494d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 06:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226f480aa1c3a79c001494d/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The gunman who killed his three daughters, a chaperone who&amp;hellip;
Highlights Gunman killed three daughters, chaperone and himself in Northern California church this week. David Mora, 39, was armed with a homemade semiautomatic rifle-style weapon. He had an illegal 30-round ammunition magazine and 17 bullets were fired. Authorities do not know how or when he obtained the weapon, a sheriff’s spokesman says. He was released from an involuntary mental health hold in April 2021 after threatening to harm himself and his estranged girlfriend.</description></item></channel></rss>