<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>effect on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/effect/</link><description>Recent content in effect on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:14:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/effect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ambassador Bridge blockades will have ‘lasting effect’ on supply chain, experts say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204ad3d89e59d1d9ce7a18f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204ad3d89e59d1d9ce7a18f/</guid><description>Blockades at the Ambassador Bridge will have significant impacts on the flow of consumer goods into Canada and on the automotive sector on both sides of the border, experts say.
Highlights The Ambassador Bridge is a critical trade link for Canada and the U.S. It’s the busiest land border crossing in North America with up to 10,000 trucks travelling across the bridge daily, representing a quarter of all commercial trade between the countries.</description></item><item><title>Philadelphia's ban on pre-hire marijuana testing will take effect in the new year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3b84d86798fc7dd731c6e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 03:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3b84d86798fc7dd731c6e/</guid><description>On Jan. 1, Philadelphia&amp;rsquo;s new law prohibiting many employers from testing job applicants for marijuana use will go into effect. The ordinance was passed by city council in a 15-to-1 vote in April and was signed into law shortly after by Mayor Jim Kenney.
Summary A new law prohibiting many Philadelphia employers from testing job applicants for marijuana use is slated to go into effect on Jan. 1. Also excluded are positions where any federal or state law or valid collective bargaining agreement requires testing.</description></item></channel></rss>