<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shop on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shop/</link><description>Recent content in shop on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business owner paid ex-worker with 91,000 pennies. That's retaliation, feds claim in lawsuit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</guid><description>A Georgia auto repair shop broke the law when it dumped $915 in change on a former employee&amp;rsquo;s driveway, regulator alleges.
Summary The U.S. Department of Labor has filed a lawsuit against the Peachtree, Georgia-based auto repair shop and owner Miles Walker after deciding that the stunt amounted to retaliation. According to the government&amp;rsquo;s complaint, Walker decided to pay Flaten in pennies within hours of learning that he had contacted regulators over his missing paycheck.</description></item><item><title>Feds sue auto repair shop that paid former employee in pennies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d91a6dad1e451818a5d297/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d91a6dad1e451818a5d297/</guid><description>The U.S. Department of Labor is suing the auto repair shop that made headlines last year by paying a former employee his final paycheck in pennies.
Summary The U.S. Department of Labor is suing the auto repair shop that made headlines last year by paying a former employee his final paycheck in pennies. A OK Walker Autoworks did not immediately respond to a request for comment on Friday. After receiving media attention for the penny stunt last year, a page called “Pennies” appeared on OK Walker Autoworks&amp;rsquo; website.</description></item></channel></rss>