<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>evidence on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/evidence/</link><description>Recent content in evidence on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 21:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/evidence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supreme Court makes it more difficult for prisoners to argue they had ineffective counsel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bf7dbb07cfbfad9b5be73/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 21:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bf7dbb07cfbfad9b5be73/</guid><description>The Supreme Court said Monday that state prisoners may not present new evidence in federal court in support of a claim that their post-conviction counsel in state court was ineffective in violation of the Constitution.
Highlights The 6-3 opinion was penned by Justice Clarence Thomas. In dissent, Justice Sonia Sotomayor called the decision &amp;ldquo;perverse&amp;rdquo; and said the court had gutted precedent. The ruling is a major defeat for two inmates on death row who said they had compelling claims that their lawyers failed to pursue.</description></item><item><title>New evidence found in Madeleine McCann case as German prosecutor is 'sure' suspect killed British girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627672c97457334a1bf84a68/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627672c97457334a1bf84a68/</guid><description>A German prosecutor has said he is &amp;quot;sure&amp;quot; that Madeleine McCann &amp;ndash; the British girl who disappeared from a resort in Portugal in 2007 at the age of three &amp;ndash; was killed by suspect Christian Brückner.
Highlights Prosecutor says he is &amp;ldquo;sure&amp;rdquo; Madeleine McCann was killed by suspect Christian Brückner. Prosecutor says investigators have found &amp;ldquo;new evidence&amp;rdquo; that links the convicted rapist and child sex abuser to the child&amp;rsquo;s disappearance. The British girl disappeared from a holiday resort in Portugal in 2007 at the age of three.</description></item><item><title>The $1m challenge: ‘If the Turin Shroud is a forgery, show how it was done’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d477ba3cb67797f7e6416/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d477ba3cb67797f7e6416/</guid><description>Expert on revered relic calls on British Museum to back up the results of its disputed carbon dating tests
Highlights David Rolfe&amp;rsquo;s new film, Who Can He Be? debuts the Shroud of Turin, in which Christ&amp;rsquo;s body was wrapped when he supposedly rose from the dead. New discoveries in the past few years have again opened the question of its authenticity. The film-maker has issued a challenge worth $1m to the British Museum to prove it&amp;rsquo;s not a forgery.</description></item><item><title>Possible Evidence of Russian Atrocities: German Intelligence Intercepts Radio Traffic Discussing the Murder of Civilians in Bucha</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f375e8dcf6be01d07d6d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 19:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f375e8dcf6be01d07d6d3/</guid><description>The images of the murdered civilians in Bucha shocked the world. DER SPIEGEL has learned that German intelligence intercepted radio traffic from suspected perpetrators. It appears that such atrocities were part of the strategy of Putin&amp;rsquo;s army.
Highlights DER SPIEGEL has learned that the BND has new satellite images and has intercepted incriminating radio traffic from Russian military personnel in the region north of Kyiv. Some of the intercepted traffic apparently matches the locations of bodies found along the main road through Bucha.</description></item><item><title>Russian attacks hit at least 9 Ukrainian medical facilities, visual evidence shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d6192b36dc296ba7345b1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d6192b36dc296ba7345b1/</guid><description>A Washington Post analysis verified nine incidents where hospitals faced direct damage as a result of a reported Russian attack. Three of the facilities specifically served women or children.
Highlights The Washington Post examined more than 500 videos and photos, reviewed social media posts from the hospitals, spoke to witnesses and hospital employees. It verified nine incidents, including the strike in Mariupol, where hospitals faced direct damage as a result of a reported Russian attack.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew to face civil sex assault case after US ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df5d94f5a3e4d1fa85e35d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df5d94f5a3e4d1fa85e35d/</guid><description>Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s claims against the Duke of York can continue to be heard, a US court says.
Summary While all this is going on, Ms Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s team will be pressing for the prince&amp;rsquo;s lawyers to disclose evidence. Their current demands - detailed in court papers - include information about the medical condition 20 years ago that prevented him sweating and, secondly, evidence to support his statement that he was at Pizza Express in Woking on the day Ms Giuffre says he abused her.</description></item></channel></rss>