<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>evidence on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/evidence/</link><description>Recent content in evidence on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 03:15:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/evidence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian attacks hit at least 9 Ukrainian medical facilities, visual evidence shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d6192b36dc296ba7345b1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d6192b36dc296ba7345b1/</guid><description>A Washington Post analysis verified nine incidents where hospitals faced direct damage as a result of a reported Russian attack. Three of the facilities specifically served women or children.
Highlights The Washington Post examined more than 500 videos and photos, reviewed social media posts from the hospitals, spoke to witnesses and hospital employees. It verified nine incidents, including the strike in Mariupol, where hospitals faced direct damage as a result of a reported Russian attack.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew to face civil sex assault case after US ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df5d94f5a3e4d1fa85e35d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df5d94f5a3e4d1fa85e35d/</guid><description>Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s claims against the Duke of York can continue to be heard, a US court says.
Summary While all this is going on, Ms Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s team will be pressing for the prince&amp;rsquo;s lawyers to disclose evidence. Their current demands - detailed in court papers - include information about the medical condition 20 years ago that prevented him sweating and, secondly, evidence to support his statement that he was at Pizza Express in Woking on the day Ms Giuffre says he abused her.</description></item></channel></rss>