<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rules on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rules/</link><description>Recent content in rules on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 05:10:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Driver of Tesla on autopilot must stand trial for crash that killed 2 in Gardena, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62887422dfc29770c1b0fa3f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 05:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62887422dfc29770c1b0fa3f/</guid><description>The driver of a Tesla operating on autopilot must stand trial for a crash that killed two people in Gardena, a judge ruled Thursday.
Highlights There is enough evidence to try Kevin George Aziz Riad, 27, on two counts of vehicular manslaughter. It is believed to be the first felony prosecution in the U.S. against a driver using a partially automated driving system. The misuse of Autopilot, which can control steering, speed and braking, has occurred on numerous occasions and is the subject of investigations by two federal agencies.</description></item><item><title>Judge rules Amazon must reinstate fired warehouse worker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e8bc09ce7c6afb8c0be1a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 10:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e8bc09ce7c6afb8c0be1a/</guid><description>A judge has ruled Amazon must reinstate a former employee who was fired in the early days of the pandemic after leading a protest calling for the company to do more to protect workers against COVID-19
Highlights A judge has ruled Amazon must reinstate a former employee who was fired in the early days of the pandemic after leading a protest calling for the company to do more to protect workers against COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>Federal judge rules Kim Davis violated couples’ constitutional rights; will go to trial over damages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623574dce8b7c197ad07c964/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 06:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623574dce8b7c197ad07c964/</guid><description>The former Rowan County Clerk spent time in jail for contempt of court for refusing marriage licenses to same-sex couples.
Highlights A federal judge has ruled that former Rowan County Clerk Kim Davis violated the constitutional rights of two same-sex couples. That decision settles the question of whether Davis violated their constitutional rights. No decision has been made yet on whether Davis will be on the hook for the likely hundreds of thousands of dollars in legal fees accrued over the six-and-a-half years of litigation.</description></item><item><title>U.S. can't expel migrant families to countries where they could be harmed, court rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62231bd78d0073faf930be71/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 08:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62231bd78d0073faf930be71/</guid><description>Both the Trump and Biden administrations have said the Title 42 border policy is necessary to control the spread of COVID-19 inside migrant holding facilities.
Highlights A federal appellate court on Friday upheld the government&amp;rsquo;s authority to expel migrants under a Trump-era pandemic-related order retained by the Biden administration. But the court barred U.S. border officials from expelling families to countries where they could be harmed. The D.C. Circuit Court of Appeals partially affirmed a lower court order against government&amp;rsquo;s expulsion of migrant families under a public health authority known as Title 42.</description></item><item><title>NC Supreme Court rules legislative and congressional maps as unconstitutional gerrymanders</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff1ab99970f93bf8dc47d6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff1ab99970f93bf8dc47d6/</guid><description>On Friday, Attorney General Josh Stein said that the state Supreme Court just struck down the legislative and congressional maps as an “unconstitutional partisan gerrymander.”
Highlights N.C. Supreme Court strikes down redrawn congressional and congressional maps as unconstitutional gerrymanders. Attorney General Josh Stein: The maps violate a voter’s fundamental right to vote. The unanimous decision by the three trial judges will be appealed by the advocacy groups and voters who challenged the new congressional and legislative lines.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Chief Justice says judges need 'rigorous' training on stock-trading rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d00a21f6cb7876130a4306/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d00a21f6cb7876130a4306/</guid><description>U.S. federal judges need &amp;quot;more rigorous&amp;quot; ethics training to ensure they are not hearing disputes in which they have a financial interest, U.S. Chief Justice John Roberts said in a year-end report published on Friday, citing a recent Wall Street Journal investigation.
Summary REUTERS/Jonathan Ernst/Pool/File PhotoDec 31 (Reuters) - U.S. federal judges need &amp;ldquo;more rigorous&amp;rdquo; ethics training to ensure they are not hearing disputes in which they have a financial interest, U.</description></item></channel></rss>