<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>king on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/king/</link><description>Recent content in king on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 08:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/king/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Freedom Convoy leader Pat King arrested live on social media.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210a6e8a8acd94012b9718d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 08:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210a6e8a8acd94012b9718d/</guid><description>“I am being arrested. We will talk to you guys soon.”
Highlights Pat King, one of the most vocal members of the “Freedom Convoy’s movement, went on social media Friday to livestream his arrest. King was approached in his vehicle by a police officer who said: “You are under arrest, sir.” “I am being arrested by this officer right now,” he told viewers to his live Facebook feed. ‘I have the right to a lawyer?</description></item><item><title>Swedish King and Queen test positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d57a5e5508599f50ca391e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d57a5e5508599f50ca391e/</guid><description>STOCKHOLM — Sweden’s King Carl XVI Gustaf and Queen Silvia have tested positive for the COVID-19 virus, the palace said in a statement on Tuesday.
Summary Article contentSTOCKHOLM — Sweden’s King Carl XVI Gustaf and Queen Silvia have tested positive for the COVID-19 virus, the palace said in a statement on Tuesday. “The King and Queen, who are fully vaccinated with three injections, have mild symptoms and are feeling well, given the circumstances,” the palace said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>A Small British Island Is Looking for Someone to Run Its Pub – and Serve as 'King'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4fbce52ddfc5bd29fa794/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4fbce52ddfc5bd29fa794/</guid><description>Piel Island has crowned the pub landlord as king of the island for at least 200 years, and they&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone new to take over the job.
Summary Or maybe you have bigger dreams: An island all to your own or being crowned a king (or queen)? A small British island is currently on the lookout for all three – though the gig may be harder work than it sounds.</description></item></channel></rss>