<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>animals on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/animals/</link><description>Recent content in animals on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk's company confirms monkeys died in brain chip testing project, denies animal cruelty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213c817d66ca29fe393f824/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213c817d66ca29fe393f824/</guid><description>Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s implant company Neuralink has acknowledged that monkeys died as part of its testing procedures but denies allegations of animal cruelty.
Highlights Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s Neuralink says monkeys died as part of its testing procedures. University of California, Davis Primate Center euthanized two macaque monkeys at the end of the testing process. Neuroimplantable chips are implanted into monkeys' brains to enable brains to communicate with computers. In April last year, Neuralink claimed monkeys can play Pong &amp;ndash; a computer game - using just their minds.</description></item><item><title>In an historic vote, Italy to ban fur farming and shut down all mink farms within six months - Humane Society International</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2db180927b787f25953fc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 08:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2db180927b787f25953fc/</guid><description>Description Summary ROME—The Budget Committee of the Italian Senate today voted to approve a modified version of an amendment to the budget law which will see the country’s 10 remaining mink fur farms closed within six months and a permanent ban on fur farming throughout Italy. There are very clear economic, environmental, public health and of course animal welfare reasons to close and ban fur farms. Finally, a parliamentary vote sanctions the end of unspeakable suffering inflicted on animals only in the name of profit and vanity.</description></item></channel></rss>