<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trying on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trying/</link><description>Recent content in trying on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:16:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trying/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AZ water future uncertain as leaders deal with severe shortages on Colorado River</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278e9c10afa37d2a7a8e4e3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278e9c10afa37d2a7a8e4e3/</guid><description>Arizona will have to learn to live with less water from the Colorado River.
Highlights A twenty-two-year drought across the West, compounded by climate change has caused historic shortages on the river and the lakes that store it. The river accounts for 40% of Arizona&amp;rsquo;s water supply. Lake Powell sits on the Arizona-Utah border and is the second-largest reservoir on river. But its water level has fallen within 30 feet of dead pool elevation.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin admits 'significant losses' of troops; Russia expected to shift defeated forces to east Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62507bf027eeb9ab56cf4fae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62507bf027eeb9ab56cf4fae/</guid><description>Ukrainian leaders have warned that the fighting in the Donbas is expected to be brutal and resemble the battles of World War II.
Highlights Rocket attack kills at least 50 people and injures more than 80, local authorities say. Thousands of civilians waiting at train stations in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s east to evacuate as Russian strikes intensify. Moscow denies targeting civilians despite well-documented evidence to the contrary. NATO says it would warmly welcome Finland to the alliance if it were to join the U.</description></item></channel></rss>