<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/</link><description>Recent content on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/afs-prod/media/97c7121e83c446d69399cabbab96604f/3000.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable" />&lt;h2 id="description">Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>WASHINGTON (AP) — More than 12,000 military service members refusing the COVID-19 vaccine are seeking religious exemptions, and so far they are having zero success. That total lack of approvals is creating new tensions within the military, even as the vast majority of the armed forces have gotten vaccinated.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="summary">Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The services, urgently trying to keep the coronavirus pandemic in check by getting troops vaccinated, are now besieged with exemption requests they are unlikely to approve.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Obtaining a religious exemption is rooted in a process that predates the pandemic and has been used for decisions such as whether troops on duty can wear head coverings or beards for religious reasons.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>It’s like rapid fire.”ADVERTISEMENTAir Force officials initially said religious exemption requests would be answered in 30 days.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The Navy has received about 2,700 religious exemption requests, the Marine Corps has 3,100 and the Army about 1,700.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>An Air Force reservist who requested a religious exemption said she’s aware of none approved so far, and she is not optimistic.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p class="article-category">
&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://apnews.com/article/religious-exemptions-vaccines-military-chaplains-ba9cf7c3ec122d5cb614ccf622ae6fd9">READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE&lt;/a>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/abf58d51417583dc1ff36d8f3eb679ca1dc68aab/0_0_4642_2786/master/4642.jpg?width=1200&height=630&quality=85&auto=format&fit=crop&overlay-align=bottom%2Cleft&overlay-width=100p&overlay-base64=L2ltZy9zdGF0aWMvb3ZlcmxheXMvdGctZGVmYXVsdC5wbmc&enable=upscale&s=ade64ec17e585252916518ae609a1f9a" alt="Featured image of post Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims" />&lt;h2 id="description">Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="summary">Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“You can’t be sending these hazardous waste products into the general stream of sanitation.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In every case they found dozens of products that counted as hazardous waste, medical waste or customer records with personal information, Bonta said.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>“So it’s really quite astounding that they continue to violate these hazardous waste control laws,” she said.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p class="article-category">
&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/dec/20/walmart-waste-california-lawsuit-dumping">READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE&lt;/a>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A professor hid a cash prize on campus. All students had to do was read the syllabus.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/211215112107-01-tennessee-professor-syllabus-money-trnd-super-tease.jpg" alt="Featured image of post A professor hid a cash prize on campus. All students had to do was read the syllabus." />&lt;h2 id="description">Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>With every new college semester, students are faced with multiple syllabuses outlining the subjects in their classes. But do students read them thoroughly? One Tennessee professor put it to the test.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="summary">Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>But do students read them thoroughly?&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&amp;ldquo;It an academic trope that no one reads the syllabus,&amp;rdquo; Wilson told CNN.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wilson told CNN that his syllabus typically doesn&amp;rsquo;t change much, but with Covid protocols there was some new information this time around.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wilson told CNN.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Wilson told CNN.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p class="article-category">
&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://edition.cnn.com/2021/12/18/us/tennessee-professor-syllabus-money-trnd/index.html">READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE&lt;/a>
&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>