<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/</link><description>Recent content on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 01:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple CEO Tim Cook 'secretly' signed $275B deal with China in 2016</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/11/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://images.macrumors.com/t/pS3jkTfGe3wiQoo6iCKNLl4ahPg=/1600x/article-new/2017/03/1x-1.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Apple CEO Tim Cook 'secretly' signed $275B deal with China in 2016" />&lt;h2 id="description">Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Apple CEO Tim Cook &amp;lsquo;secretly&amp;rsquo; signed an agreement worth more than $275 billion with Chinese officials, promising that Apple would help to&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="summary">Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In an extensive paywalled report based on interviews and purported internal Apple documents, The Information revealed that ‌Tim Cook‌ personally forged a five-year agreement with the Chinese government during a series of in-person visits to the country in 2016. The need to push for a closer alliance with the Chinese government reportedly came from a number of Apple executives who were concerned about bad publicity in China and the company&amp;rsquo;s poor relationship with Chinese officials, who believed that Apple was not contributing enough to the local economy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Alleged internal documents show that Cook &amp;ldquo;personally lobbied officials&amp;rdquo; in China over threats made against Apple Pay, iCloud, and the App Store. Cook set out to use a &amp;ldquo;memorandum of understanding&amp;rdquo; between Apple and a powerful Chinese government agency called the National Development and Reform Commission to formally agree to a number of concessions in return for regulatory exemptions. The 1,250-word agreement was written by Apple&amp;rsquo;s government affairs team in China and stewarded by Cook as he met with Chinese officials.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In May 2016, Cook announced that Apple would be investing $1 billion in the Chinese ride-hailing startup Didi Chuxing in a pointed attempt to mollify authorities, the report added. Shortly after, Cook, Apple Chief Operating Officer Jeff Williams, and government affairs head Lisa Jackson met with senior government officials in Zhongnanhai, the central headquarters of the Communist Party of China.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Cook&amp;rsquo;s negotiations led to the successful signing of the multibillion-dollar agreement, quashing a number of regulatory actions against the company with exemptions and enabling access to the Chinese market, in return for significant investments, business deals, and worker training in the country.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="article">Article&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/12/07/apple-ceo-tim-cook-secret-deal-with-china/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Read the original article&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The $11B Webb telescope aims to probe the early universe</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/12/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://media.nature.com/lw1024/magazine-assets/d41586-021-03620-1/d41586-021-03620-1_19934208.jpg" alt="Featured image of post The $11B Webb telescope aims to probe the early universe" />&lt;h2 id="description">Description&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Three decades after it was conceived, Hubble’s successor is set for launch. Here’s why astronomers around the world can’t wait.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="summary">Summary&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Lisa Dang wasn’t even born when astronomers started planning the most ambitious and complex space observatory ever built. Now, three decades later, NASA’s James Webb Space Telescope (JWST) is finally about to launch, and Dang has scored some of its first observing time — in a research area that didn’t even exist when it was being designed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Dang, an astrophysicist and graduate student at McGill University in Montreal, Canada, will be using the telescope, known as Webb for short, to stare at a planet beyond the Solar System. Called K2-141b, it is a world so hot that its surface is partly molten rock. She is one of dozens of astronomers who learnt in March that they had won observing time on the telescope. The long-awaited Webb — a partnership involving NASA, the European Space Agency (ESA) and the Canadian Space Agency (CSA) — is slated to lift off from a launch pad in Kourou, French Guiana, no earlier than 22 December.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If everything goes to plan, Webb will remake astronomy by peering at cosmic phenomena such as the most distant galaxies ever seen, the atmospheres of far-off planets and the hearts of star-forming regions swaddled in dust. Roughly 100 times more powerful than its predecessor, the Hubble Space Telescope, which has transformed our understanding of the cosmos over the past 31 years, Webb will reveal previously hidden aspects of the Universe.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A Hubble Space Telescope view of a rich tapestry of 7,500 galaxies stretching back through most of the universe&amp;rsquo;s history
The Webb telescope will spend hundreds of hours surveying this patch of sky, seen here in an image from the Hubble Space Telescope that captures 7,500 galaxies, some more than 13 billion years old.Credit: NASA, ESA, Rogier Windhorst (ASU), S. Cohen (ASU), M. Mechtley (ASU), M. Rutkowski (ASU), Robert O&amp;rsquo;Connell (UVA), P. McCarthy (OCIW), N. Hathi (UC Riverside), R. Ryan (UC Davis), Haojing Yan (OSU), Anton M. Koekemoer (STScI)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“Webb has such transformative capabilities that — to me — it’s going to be the ‘before’ times and the ‘after’ times,” says Jane Rigby, an astrophysicist at NASA’s Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Maryland, who serves as Webb’s operations project scientist.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p class="article-category">
&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-03620-1">READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE&lt;/a>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rich Content</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/rich-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/rich-content/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a class="link" href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugo-s-built-in-shortcodes" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a> for rich content, along with a &lt;a class="link" href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Privacy Config&lt;/a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="youtube-privacy-enhanced-shortcode">YouTube Privacy Enhanced Shortcode&lt;/h2>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZJthWmvUzzc"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="twitter-simple-shortcode">Twitter Simple Shortcode&lt;/h2>
&lt;style type="text/css">
.twitter-tweet {
font: 14px/1.45 -apple-system,BlinkMacSystemFont,"Segoe UI",Roboto,Oxygen-Sans,Ubuntu,Cantarell,"Helvetica Neue",sans-serif;
border-left: 4px solid #2b7bb9;
padding-left: 1.5em;
color: #555;
}
.twitter-tweet a {
color: #2b7bb9;
text-decoration: none;
}
blockquote.twitter-tweet a:hover,
blockquote.twitter-tweet a:focus {
text-decoration: underline;
}
&lt;/style>
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet">&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr">“In addition to being more logical, asymmetry has the advantage that its complete appearance is far more optically effective than symmetry.”&lt;br>— Jan Tschichold &lt;a href="https://t.co/gcv7SrhvJb">pic.twitter.com/gcv7SrhvJb&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&amp;mdash; Graphic Design History (@DesignReviewed) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/DesignReviewed/status/1085870671291310081?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2019&lt;/a>&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="vimeo-simple-shortcode">Vimeo Simple Shortcode&lt;/h2>
&lt;style>
.__h_video {
position: relative;
padding-bottom: 56.23%;
height: 0;
overflow: hidden;
width: 100%;
background: #000;
}
.__h_video img {
width: 100%;
height: auto;
color: #000;
}
.__h_video .play {
height: 72px;
width: 72px;
left: 50%;
top: 50%;
margin-left: -36px;
margin-top: -36px;
position: absolute;
cursor: pointer;
}
&lt;/style>
&lt;div class="s_video_simple __h_video">
&lt;a href="https://vimeo.com/4.8912912e&amp;#43;07" rel="noopener" target="_blank">
&lt;img src="https://i.vimeocdn.com/video/337401969-979f0cc9f55fdf305fb8984e90d92639ec9d7ecc4c9dfbc6536e28edb43784ce-d_640" srcset="https://i.vimeocdn.com/video/337401969-979f0cc9f55fdf305fb8984e90d92639ec9d7ecc4c9dfbc6536e28edb43784ce-d_640 1x, https://i.vimeocdn.com/video/337401969-979f0cc9f55fdf305fb8984e90d92639ec9d7ecc4c9dfbc6536e28edb43784ce-d_640 2x" alt="Sing Jan Swing - Kinetic Type">
&lt;div class="play">&lt;svg version="1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewBox="0 0 61 61">&lt;circle cx="30.5" cy="30.5" r="30.5" opacity=".8" fill="#000">&lt;/circle>&lt;path d="M25.3 19.2c-2.1-1.2-3.8-.2-3.8 2.2v18.1c0 2.4 1.7 3.4 3.8 2.2l16.6-9.1c2.1-1.2 2.1-3.2 0-4.4l-16.6-9z" fill="#fff">&lt;/path>&lt;/svg>&lt;/div>&lt;/a>&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="bilibilibi-shortcode">bilibilibi Shortcode&lt;/h2>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe src="https://player.bilibili.com/player.html?as_wide=1&amp;amp;high_quality=1&amp;amp;page=1&amp;aid=498363026"
scrolling="no"
frameborder="no"
framespacing="0"
allowfullscreen="true"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item></channel></rss>