<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/</link><description>Recent content on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First confirmed US death related to Omicron variant was unvaccinated and had been infected before</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/200213175742-05-coronavirus-0213-super-tease.jpg" alt="Featured image of post First confirmed US death related to Omicron variant was unvaccinated and had been infected before" />Description A Texas man, whose death was the first confirmed Omicron-related in the US, was unvaccinated and had previously been infected with the coronavirus, according to a press release from Harris County Public Health.
Summary A large crowd of people is seen wearing face masks as a preventive measure against the spread of coronavirus as they walk through a zebra crossing in Hong Kong, China, on 12 December 2021. (Miguel Candela/SOPA Images/LightRocket/Getty Images)Hong Kong will mandate all government employees to be fully vaccinated against Covid-19, or get tested for the virus every three days, authorities announced on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>'Enormous': Sercret Service reveals scope of Covid-19 fraud</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1fa1c9cc370130354dcca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 16:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1fa1c9cc370130354dcca/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/211221072005-roy-dotson-new-day-12-21-2021-super-tease.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 'Enormous': Sercret Service reveals scope of Covid-19 fraud" />Description CNN&amp;rsquo;s Erica Hill speaks to special agent Roy Dotson of the US Secret Service, who has been tapped to lead an investigation into the billions of dollars of Covid-19-related fraud.
Summary CNN&amp;rsquo;s Erica Hill speaks to special agent Roy Dotson of the US Secret Service, who has been tapped to lead an investigation into the billions of dollars of Covid-19-related fraud. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Authorities in Qatar, host of next year's football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children's toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours contrary to Islamic values</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1ec0c58d321ac426daacf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 15:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1ec0c58d321ac426daacf/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.deccanherald.com/sites/dh/files/articleimages/2021/12/21/fhdaeg7xsamerbi-1-1063151-1640079307.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Authorities in Qatar, host of next year's football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children's toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours contrary to Islamic values" />Description Authorities in Qatar, host of next year&amp;rsquo;s football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children&amp;rsquo;s toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours &amp;ldquo;contrary to Islamic values&amp;rdquo;. The emirate&amp;rsquo;s commerce and industry ministry did not spell out its objection to the rainbow colours, but some of the toys bore a colour scheme very similar to the LGBTQ+ flag.
Summary Authorities in Qatar, host of next year&amp;rsquo;s football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children&amp;rsquo;s toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours &amp;ldquo;contrary to Islamic values&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/211203215453-02-joe-biden-1203-super-tease.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans" />Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item><item><title>Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.cbc.ca/1.6292880.1640031015!/fileImage/httpImage/image.jpg_gen/derivatives/16x9_620/scott-steer.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour" />Description A B.C. Supreme Court judge has banned Nanaimo fisherman Scott Stanley Matthew Steer from fishing for life.
Summary The sentence was delivered on Nov. 12, 2021, and it is the first lifetime ban for a Pacific region fisherman in more than a decade. Along with the lifetime ban, Steer&amp;rsquo;s sentence includes:A prohibition from being aboard a fishing vessel. Steer was caught illegally fishing for crab in the Vancouver harbour after Vancouver SeaBus officials tipped off police.</description></item><item><title>Idaho man charged with murder and cannibalism after body parts found in microwave</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://s3-assets.eastidahonews.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/20110250/James-Russell-.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Idaho man charged with murder and cannibalism after body parts found in microwave" />Description Summary CLARK FORK — A northern Idaho man faces serious charges after investigators say they found a dead man’s body parts in a microwave. Russell is charged with felony first-degree murder and felony cannibalism in an amended criminal complaint filed Wednesday. Deputies went to Flaget’s truck, where they found the body naked from the waist down positioned awkwardly in the passenger seat. Some of the tissue indicated heat had been applied, possibly in the microwave for one to two minutes, according to court documents.</description></item><item><title>Petition for truck driver given 110 years in fatal crash has 4.3M signatures; truckers show support</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1b3cd60d110ff50804352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1b3cd60d110ff50804352/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.abcotvs.com/dip/images/11361909_122021-truck-split2.jpg?w=1600" alt="Featured image of post Petition for truck driver given 110 years in fatal crash has 4.3M signatures; truckers show support" />Description A change.org petition for truck driver Rogel Lazaro Aguilera-Mederos, sentenced to 110 years in a deadly Colorado pileup, has 4 million+ signatures.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos &amp;ldquo;Your honor, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I&amp;rsquo;m alive.&amp;rdquo; The Houston truck driver spoke emotionally in court as he was sentenced for a fiery crash that killed four people. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not related to Rogel, or any of his family, I simply believe that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t deserve his sentence or these charges.</description></item><item><title>Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of US COVID-19 cases</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/afs-prod/media/2edf16af80b54c5e823090fb544f845e/3000.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of US COVID-19 cases" />Description NEW YORK (AP) — Omicron has raced ahead of other variants and is now the dominant version of the coronavirus in the U.S., accounting for 73% of new infections last week, federal health officials said Monday.
Summary Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of new US COVID casesTravelers wait for a shuttle but to arrive at the Los Angeles International Airport in Los Angeles, Monday, Dec. 20, 2021. (AP Photo/Jae C.</description></item><item><title>Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://storage.googleapis.com/afs-prod/media/97c7121e83c446d69399cabbab96604f/3000.jpeg" alt="Featured image of post Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable" />Description WASHINGTON (AP) — More than 12,000 military service members refusing the COVID-19 vaccine are seeking religious exemptions, and so far they are having zero success. That total lack of approvals is creating new tensions within the military, even as the vast majority of the armed forces have gotten vaccinated.
Summary The services, urgently trying to keep the coronavirus pandemic in check by getting troops vaccinated, are now besieged with exemption requests they are unlikely to approve.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/abf58d51417583dc1ff36d8f3eb679ca1dc68aab/0_0_4642_2786/master/4642.jpg?width=1200&height=630&quality=85&auto=format&fit=crop&overlay-align=bottom%2Cleft&overlay-width=100p&overlay-base64=L2ltZy9zdGF0aWMvb3ZlcmxheXMvdGctZGVmYXVsdC5wbmc&enable=upscale&s=ade64ec17e585252916518ae609a1f9a" alt="Featured image of post Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims" />Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item><item><title>A professor hid a cash prize on campus. All students had to do was read the syllabus.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/211215112107-01-tennessee-professor-syllabus-money-trnd-super-tease.jpg" alt="Featured image of post A professor hid a cash prize on campus. All students had to do was read the syllabus." />Description With every new college semester, students are faced with multiple syllabuses outlining the subjects in their classes. But do students read them thoroughly? One Tennessee professor put it to the test.
Summary But do students read them thoroughly? &amp;ldquo;It an academic trope that no one reads the syllabus,&amp;rdquo; Wilson told CNN. Wilson told CNN that his syllabus typically doesn&amp;rsquo;t change much, but with Covid protocols there was some new information this time around.</description></item></channel></rss>