<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/</link><description>Recent content on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 03:10:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon Carjacked in South Philly</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3e65221baf63d51a3e48d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 03:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3e65221baf63d51a3e48d/</guid><description>Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon (D-5th District) was carjacked at gunpoint in South Philadelphia Wednesday afternoon, her spokesperson confirmed&amp;hellip;
Summary Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon (D-5th District) was carjacked in South Philadelphia Wednesday afternoon, her spokesperson confirmed with NBC10. The spokesperson said Scanlon, 62, was carjacked at gunpoint at 2:45 p.m. at FDR Park. I&amp;rsquo;m appalled to learn of this violent crime that was perpetrated against my friend and colleague, Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon.</description></item><item><title>In milestone deal, Proud Boy pleads guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</guid><description>A New York man pleaded guilty Wednesday to storming the U.S. Capitol with fellow members of the far-right Proud Boys, a milestone in the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s prosecution of extremists who joined the Jan.
Summary At least four others linked to the Oath Keepers also have pleaded guilty to riot-related charges. Proud Boys members describe themselves as a politically incorrect men’s club for “Western chauvinists.” Its members frequently have engaged in street fights with antifascist activists at rallies and protests.</description></item><item><title>Michigan diner owner who defied state shutdown dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 01:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</guid><description>None
Summary BRANCH COUNTY, MI – A diner owner who kept his restaurant open in defiance of state shutdowns has died after more than a two-month battle with COVID-19. He owned the Quincy Diner, 174 E. Chicago St. (U.S. 12) in the village of Quincy. He kept the restaurant open in December 2020, in violation of the partial shutdown ordered by the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services. Related: ‘I’d have lost the business.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer pill becomes 1st US-authorized home COVID treatment</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3a002b485b06b08d59d9e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3a002b485b06b08d59d9e/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health regulators on Wednesday authorized the first pill against COVID-19, a Pfizer drug that Americans will be able to take at home to head off the worst effects of the virus.
Summary This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)WASHINGTON (AP) — U.</description></item><item><title>He wore a wire, risked his life to expose who was in the KKK</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c383d63b857dd3cfa695d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 20:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c383d63b857dd3cfa695d5/</guid><description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — For nearly 10 years, Joseph Moore lived a secret double life. At times the U.S. Army veteran donned a white robe and hood as a hit man for the Ku Klux Klan in North Florida.
Summary He wore a wire, risked his life to expose who was in the KKKJoseph Moore looks out of a window at his home in Jacksonville, Fla., on Tuesday, Dec. 7, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Pause on student loan payments is extended through May 1</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</guid><description>Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1.
Summary WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;ndash; The Biden administration is extending a student loan moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to put off debt payments during the pandemic. Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1. Interest rates will remain at 0% during that period, and debt collection efforts will be suspended.</description></item><item><title>Cleveland-area hospitals battling latest Covid-19 surge put ad in local paper that reads: 'Help'</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 15:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</guid><description>&amp;quot;Help&amp;quot; said the ad Sunday in the Cleveland Plain-Dealer, a response to the latest Covid-19 health crisis exploding in Northern Ohio, nearly two years into a pandemic that has killed more than 810,000 Americans and battered many of the nation&amp;rsquo;s hospitals.
Summary (CNN) &amp;ldquo;Help.&amp;rdquo; That word, in big black letters and surrounded by white space, called out from Ohio&amp;rsquo;s largest newspaper &amp;ndash; a desperate plea from six Cleveland-area medical systems facing a crush of Covid-19 cases.</description></item><item><title>NASA's James Webb Space Telescope launch delayed to Christmas due to bad weather</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c32f8ebb918b17a516fa61/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 14:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c32f8ebb918b17a516fa61/</guid><description>NASA&amp;rsquo;s much-awaited next-generation space telescope is finally ready to launch just as soon as the weather cooperates.
Summary The James Webb Space Telescope folded up for launch before it was encapsulated in the fairing of an Ariane 5 rocket. NASA&amp;rsquo;s much-awaited next-generation space telescope is finally ready to launch — just as soon as the weather cooperates. The James Webb Space Telescope , also known as JWST or Webb, has been in the works for decades.</description></item><item><title>Fox cancels ‘New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022’ telecast due to omicron surge</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3216fec063da1021cd228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 13:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3216fec063da1021cd228/</guid><description>Fox has cancelled its &amp;quot;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022&amp;quot; production in New York due to the recent surge in Covid-19 cases as the omicron variant spreads.
Summary Fox has decided against moving forward with its “New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022” production in New York due to the ongoing surge of Covid-19 and its omicron variant. “While we are confident in the health and safety protocols for ‘Fox’s New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022,’ the recent velocity of the spread of Omicron cases has made it impossible to produce a live special in Times Square that meets our standards,” Fox Entertainment said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Employer must face worker's lawsuit over husband's COVID death -California court</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</guid><description>Description HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CALIFORNIA-WORKERS:Employer must face worker&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit over husband&amp;rsquo;s COVID death -California court
Summary The California Court of Appeal, Second Appellate District, rejected South San Francisco-based See&amp;rsquo;s Candies' argument that the employee, Matilde Ek, must file for workers' compensation rather than seek damages in court because her husband&amp;rsquo;s death was &amp;ldquo;derivative&amp;rdquo; of her own workplace injury. Ek and her three daughters sued See&amp;rsquo;s last year, saying she contracted COVID-19 because the company failed to ensure safety in the workplace.</description></item><item><title>Iowa man arraigned on 7 charges for Jan. 6 US Capitol attack</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</guid><description>Description An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prison
Summary An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prisonDES MOINES, Iowa &amp;ndash; An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest 76-year-old man in cold case of 1978 strangling death of teen in San Francisco</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</guid><description>Description Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City
Summary Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City teen who was found dead after visiting Golden Gate Park. Mark Stanley Personette, of Conifer, Colorado, was arrested Dec.</description></item><item><title>110 Year Sentence For Truck Driver Being Reconsidered</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2e927679e9dc44622769a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 09:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2e927679e9dc44622769a/</guid><description>Description Civil rights advocates are calling for Colorado Gov. Jared Polis to intervene after a truck driver was sentenced to 110 years for a fatal crash after his brakes failed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;As Colorado law required the imposition of the sentence in this case, the law also permits the Court to reconsider its sentence in an exceptional case involving unusual and extenuating circumstances,&amp;rdquo; the motion says. According to The Associated Press, police said that after his brakes failed, Mederos drove past a truck ramp before the crash.</description></item><item><title>In an historic vote, Italy to ban fur farming and shut down all mink farms within six months - Humane Society International</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2db180927b787f25953fc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 08:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2db180927b787f25953fc/</guid><description>Description Summary ROME—The Budget Committee of the Italian Senate today voted to approve a modified version of an amendment to the budget law which will see the country’s 10 remaining mink fur farms closed within six months and a permanent ban on fur farming throughout Italy. There are very clear economic, environmental, public health and of course animal welfare reasons to close and ban fur farms. Finally, a parliamentary vote sanctions the end of unspeakable suffering inflicted on animals only in the name of profit and vanity.</description></item><item><title>Government official swims 12 hours to shore after helicopter crash off Madagascar: "My time to die hasn't come yet"</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2cd05f199143caea32f00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 07:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2cd05f199143caea32f00/</guid><description>Description The helicopter was flying Serge Gelle and others to inspect the site of a deadly shipwreck off the northeastern coast.
Summary A Madagascan minister was one of two survivors to have swum some 12 hours to shore Tuesday after their helicopter crashed off the island&amp;rsquo;s northeastern coast, authorities said. A search was still ongoing for two other passengers after the crash Monday, whose cause was not immediately clear, police and port authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Intel tells unvaccinated employees they face unpaid leave</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</guid><description>Description Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April
Summary Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in AprilPORTLAND, Ore. &amp;ndash; Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don&amp;rsquo;t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest bystander for filming traffic stop, allegedly interfering with investigation</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 05:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</guid><description>Description Killeen police arrest a man for interfering with an officer.
Summary KILLEEN, Texas (KWTX) - The Killeen Police Department arrested a man early Saturday morning for interfering with an officer conducting a traffic stop. “I have a right to be there. I have a right to record and I also have a right to free speech,” could be heard from the unnamed individual in the video. The video which is just over 130 Seconds long shows a man walking down the sidewalk when he sees police conducting a traffic stop.</description></item><item><title>Secret Service: Nearly $100B stolen in pandemic relief funds</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2a2d659180f685a50b3e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2a2d659180f685a50b3e9/</guid><description>Description The U.S. Secret Service says nearly $100 billion has been stolen from COVID-19 relief programs set up to help businesses and people who lost their jobs due to the pandemic.
Summary Nearly $100 billion at minimum has been stolen from COVID-19 relief programs set up to help businesses and people who lost their jobs due to the pandemic, the U.S. Secret Service said Tuesday. The estimate is based on Secret Service cases and data from the Labor Department and the Small Business Administration, said Roy Dotson, the agency’s national pandemic fraud recovery coordinator, in an interview.</description></item><item><title>Mum has arms ripped off, dies stopping pit bull from attacking 4-year-old son</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</guid><description>Description A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says.
Summary A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says. She said, ‘I have no arms, and I’m dying,’” Ms Pingel’s sister, Shannon Pingel, told the Wausau Daily Herald.</description></item><item><title>Missing Utah college student Madelyn Allen found alive, 'covered in coal' in suspect's basement</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 02:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</guid><description>Description Utah college student Madelyn &amp;ldquo;Maddie&amp;rdquo; Allen vanished last week and was found alive, covered in coal, in the basement of 39-year-old suspect Brent Brown.
Summary A Utah college student who vanished last week was found alive and covered in coal in the basement of a 39-year-old suspect&amp;rsquo;s home, according to authorities. The student, Madelyn Allen, 19, was reported missing after she was seen leaving her dorm at Snow College in Ephraim around 9:22 p.</description></item><item><title>Texas QAnon cult is now drinking bleach, member’s family says</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c278b0c8dd262ec076e17a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c278b0c8dd262ec076e17a/</guid><description>Description ‘She was proud to tell us that she was the one mixing it up and giving it to everybody,’ says distressed family member
Summary The family of a woman who joined a fringe QAnon cult in Texas says she’s now drinking toxic chemicals with her peers – and brags that she serves them herself. Despite two occasions when the JFKs failed to show up, Mr Protzman reportedly still has dozens of followers.</description></item><item><title>Utah billionaire leaves Mormon church, donates $600K to LGBTQ group</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</guid><description>Description Jeff Green, a billionaire from Utah, resigned from the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and donated to LGBTQ group Equality Utah.
Summary “The church leadership is not honest about its history, its finances, and its advocacy,” he wrote, according to the Tribune. “We made this investment sizable and publicly to send a message that Equality Utah isn’t going anywhere,” Green wrote, adding that he hopes the donation is the first of many.</description></item><item><title>Perfectly preserved baby dinosaur discovered curled up inside its egg</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c25c9677c8c89a4c593fe5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c25c9677c8c89a4c593fe5/</guid><description>Description An unprecedented fossil of a baby dinosaur curled up perfectly inside its egg is shedding more light on the links between dinosaurs and birds.
Summary (CNN) An unprecedented fossil of a baby dinosaur curled up perfectly inside its egg is shedding more light on the links between dinosaurs and birds. The 70-million-year-old fossil preserves the embryonic skeleton of an oviraptorid dinosaur, which has been nicknamed Baby Yingliang after the name of the Chinese museum which houses the fossil.</description></item><item><title>Chicago to Require Vaccine Proof for Indoor Spaces Like Restaurants, Bars, Gyms</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24e80f93c348e1487b143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24e80f93c348e1487b143/</guid><description>Description Chicago will soon require proof of vaccination for indoor public spaces like restaurants, bars and gyms in the new year, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor announced Tuesday,&amp;hellip;
Summary Chicago will soon require proof of vaccination for indoor public spaces like restaurants, bars and gyms in the new year, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor announced Tuesday, joining other big cities like New York and Los Angeles in adding the requirement as COVID cases surge.</description></item><item><title>Chinese companies vanish from world's top 10 by market cap</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</guid><description>Description TOKYO &amp;ndash; Tencent Holdings and Alibaba Group Holding have dropped out of the global top 10 companies in market capitalization, new data shows, leaving
Summary Alibaba Group Holding founder Jack Ma, then executive chairman, celebrates at the New York Stock Exchange on Sept. 19, 2014, the day that the company held its initial public offering and began trading there. © Getty ImagesMANAMI OGAWA, Nikkei staff writer READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Putin warns of possible military response over ‘aggressive’ Nato</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</guid><description>Description Russian leader’s speech to top commanders comes as tensions grow with the west over Ukraine
Summary Vladimir Putin has said he will consider a military response if Russia feels threatened by Nato, in a sign that he is not ready to de-escalate tensions over a potential invasion of Ukraine. In a combative speech on Tuesday, Putin – who has demanded “security guarantees” from Nato – told his top military commanders that the west was to blame for the rising tensions.</description></item><item><title>CDC director says initial Covid shots 'may not be enough' as omicron rapidly sweeps the nation</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c224461d573b547c66ea61/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c224461d573b547c66ea61/</guid><description>Description Dr. Rochelle Walensky said omicron has &amp;ldquo;over 50 mutations and because of those mutations, just being vaccinated with two doses may not be enough.&amp;rdquo;
Summary CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the omicron variant of the coronavirus has &amp;ldquo;over 50 mutations and because of those mutations, just being vaccinated with two doses may not be enough&amp;rdquo; ahead of the holidays. Even so, Walensky said that vaccines &amp;ldquo;may not prevent infection&amp;rdquo; according to data so far.</description></item><item><title>11-week Kellogg’s strike to end after multi-year agreement reached</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</guid><description>Description Summary The 11-week strike at Kellogg’s has come to an end after workers approved a contract with the company. Read more trending newsUnionized workers had been on strike since Oct. 5 in Michigan, Nebraska, Pennsylvania and Tennessee, The Washington Post reported.
The Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers’ International Union president Anthony Shelton said the contract makes gains for the 1,400 union workers and has no concessions.</description></item><item><title>First confirmed US death related to Omicron variant was unvaccinated and had been infected before</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</guid><description>Description A Texas man, whose death was the first confirmed Omicron-related in the US, was unvaccinated and had previously been infected with the coronavirus, according to a press release from Harris County Public Health.
Summary A large crowd of people is seen wearing face masks as a preventive measure against the spread of coronavirus as they walk through a zebra crossing in Hong Kong, China, on 12 December 2021. (Miguel Candela/SOPA Images/LightRocket/Getty Images)Hong Kong will mandate all government employees to be fully vaccinated against Covid-19, or get tested for the virus every three days, authorities announced on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>'Enormous': Sercret Service reveals scope of Covid-19 fraud</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1fa1c9cc370130354dcca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 16:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1fa1c9cc370130354dcca/</guid><description>Description CNN&amp;rsquo;s Erica Hill speaks to special agent Roy Dotson of the US Secret Service, who has been tapped to lead an investigation into the billions of dollars of Covid-19-related fraud.
Summary CNN&amp;rsquo;s Erica Hill speaks to special agent Roy Dotson of the US Secret Service, who has been tapped to lead an investigation into the billions of dollars of Covid-19-related fraud. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Authorities in Qatar, host of next year's football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children's toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours contrary to Islamic values</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1ec0c58d321ac426daacf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 15:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1ec0c58d321ac426daacf/</guid><description>Description Authorities in Qatar, host of next year&amp;rsquo;s football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children&amp;rsquo;s toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours &amp;ldquo;contrary to Islamic values&amp;rdquo;. The emirate&amp;rsquo;s commerce and industry ministry did not spell out its objection to the rainbow colours, but some of the toys bore a colour scheme very similar to the LGBTQ+ flag.
Summary Authorities in Qatar, host of next year&amp;rsquo;s football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children&amp;rsquo;s toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours &amp;ldquo;contrary to Islamic values&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item><item><title>Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</guid><description>Description A B.C. Supreme Court judge has banned Nanaimo fisherman Scott Stanley Matthew Steer from fishing for life.
Summary The sentence was delivered on Nov. 12, 2021, and it is the first lifetime ban for a Pacific region fisherman in more than a decade. Along with the lifetime ban, Steer&amp;rsquo;s sentence includes:A prohibition from being aboard a fishing vessel. Steer was caught illegally fishing for crab in the Vancouver harbour after Vancouver SeaBus officials tipped off police.</description></item><item><title>Idaho man charged with murder and cannibalism after body parts found in microwave</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</guid><description>Description Summary CLARK FORK — A northern Idaho man faces serious charges after investigators say they found a dead man’s body parts in a microwave. Russell is charged with felony first-degree murder and felony cannibalism in an amended criminal complaint filed Wednesday. Deputies went to Flaget’s truck, where they found the body naked from the waist down positioned awkwardly in the passenger seat. Some of the tissue indicated heat had been applied, possibly in the microwave for one to two minutes, according to court documents.</description></item><item><title>Petition for truck driver given 110 years in fatal crash has 4.3M signatures; truckers show support</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1b3cd60d110ff50804352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1b3cd60d110ff50804352/</guid><description>Description A change.org petition for truck driver Rogel Lazaro Aguilera-Mederos, sentenced to 110 years in a deadly Colorado pileup, has 4 million+ signatures.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos &amp;ldquo;Your honor, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I&amp;rsquo;m alive.&amp;rdquo; The Houston truck driver spoke emotionally in court as he was sentenced for a fiery crash that killed four people. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not related to Rogel, or any of his family, I simply believe that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t deserve his sentence or these charges.</description></item><item><title>Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of US COVID-19 cases</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</guid><description>Description NEW YORK (AP) — Omicron has raced ahead of other variants and is now the dominant version of the coronavirus in the U.S., accounting for 73% of new infections last week, federal health officials said Monday.
Summary Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of new US COVID casesTravelers wait for a shuttle but to arrive at the Los Angeles International Airport in Los Angeles, Monday, Dec. 20, 2021. (AP Photo/Jae C.</description></item><item><title>Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</guid><description>Description WASHINGTON (AP) — More than 12,000 military service members refusing the COVID-19 vaccine are seeking religious exemptions, and so far they are having zero success. That total lack of approvals is creating new tensions within the military, even as the vast majority of the armed forces have gotten vaccinated.
Summary The services, urgently trying to keep the coronavirus pandemic in check by getting troops vaccinated, are now besieged with exemption requests they are unlikely to approve.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/about/</guid><description>Enrich news from https://www.reddit.com/r/news/</description></item><item><title>A professor hid a cash prize on campus. All students had to do was read the syllabus.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</guid><description>Description With every new college semester, students are faced with multiple syllabuses outlining the subjects in their classes. But do students read them thoroughly? One Tennessee professor put it to the test.
Summary But do students read them thoroughly? &amp;ldquo;It an academic trope that no one reads the syllabus,&amp;rdquo; Wilson told CNN. Wilson told CNN that his syllabus typically doesn&amp;rsquo;t change much, but with Covid protocols there was some new information this time around.</description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>