<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russians on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russians/</link><description>Recent content in russians on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian troops fought street by street with Kyiv's forces in battle for key Ukrainian city</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296301289ec1178364093fc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296301289ec1178364093fc/</guid><description>Russian troops pushed deeper into a key eastern Ukrainian city Monday, fighting street by street with Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s forces in a battle that has left Sievierodonetsk in ruins.
Highlights Russian troops advance into Sievierodonetsk, fighting street by street with Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s forces. Russian forces also shelled parts of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northeast, and struggle continues for control of southern region. EU agrees to a partial oil embargo to pressure Moscow to end the war. Six civilians, including a French journalist, killed in fighting in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second-largest city, also reported in Kharkarkarkiv.</description></item><item><title>Swiss have frozen $8 billion in assets under Russia sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fb6fd004d76867b4e450c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 04:16:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fb6fd004d76867b4e450c/</guid><description>Switzerland has so far frozen some 7.5 billion Swiss francs ($8.03 billion) in funds and assets under sanctions against Russians to punish Moscow&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine, government official Erwin Bollinger said on Thursday.
Highlights Switzerland has so far frozen some 7.5 billion Swiss francs ($8.03 billion) in funds and assets under sanctions against Russians. Assets included money in frozen bank accounts and properties in four Swiss cantons, official says. Switzerland adopted European Union sanctions against Russian involved in Moscow&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine on Feb.</description></item><item><title>Red is dead: Russian anti-war protesters fly a new flag for peace</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ab6d3694adbf4ade88e50/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 09:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ab6d3694adbf4ade88e50/</guid><description>Seeing the tricolour as tainted, they took the ‘blood’ out to leave blue and white, then found others had done so too
Highlights When Putin’s forces invaded Ukraine, anti-war Russians joined protests around the world. Kai Katonina and his friends came up with a white, blue and white striped flag. It has since been embraced on social media as well as by Russian protesters on the streets. The new Russian flag has also drawn the ire of the Kremlin, and officials last week proposed banning it as an “extremist” symbol.</description></item><item><title>Arnold Schwarzenegger speaks to Russians in emotional plea against war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623414f1e147874adf6bc92c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 05:13:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623414f1e147874adf6bc92c/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I&amp;rsquo;m speaking to you today because there are things that are being kept from you,&amp;quot; he said. &amp;quot;Terrible things that you should know about.&amp;quot;
Highlights Arnold Schwarzenegger posted a heartfelt nine-minute video message on Twitter. He spoke of his admiration for the Russian people and his father&amp;rsquo;s experience in World War II. Schwarzenegger: &amp;ldquo;To President Putin, I say: You started this war. You are leading this war&amp;rdquo; He said the Russian government&amp;rsquo;s claim that it&amp;rsquo;s attempting to &amp;ldquo;de-Nazify&amp;rdquo; Ukraine was completely untrue, pointing out that Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president, Volodymir Zelenskyy, is Jewish and lost relatives in the Holocaust.</description></item><item><title>Blinken to Kazakhstan government: It's hard to get Russians to leave once they're in your home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</guid><description>As Kazakh authorities invite Russian-dominated alliance to quell protests, US secretary of state says &amp;rsquo;not clear why they feel the need for any outside assistance'
Summary WASHINGTON — US Secretary of State Antony Blinken warned Friday that Kazakhstan will find it difficult to lower Russian influence after inviting in troops to quell unrest. “I think one lesson in recent history is that once Russians are in your house, it’s sometimes very difficult to get them to leave,” Blinken told reporters.</description></item></channel></rss>