<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>charges on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/charges/</link><description>Recent content in charges on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:08:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/charges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NC 'Boogaloo Boi' sentenced on terrorism charges in Minneapolis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299eb7133f9a754ae6abb12/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299eb7133f9a754ae6abb12/</guid><description>The second of two self-described members of an anti-government extremist group accused in Minnesota of dealing firearm components to informants acting as members of Hamas is headed to prison. A federal judge on Wednesday sentenced Benjamin Ryan Teeter, of Hampstead, North Carolina, to four years behind bars.
Highlights Benjamin Ryan Teeter, 24, of Hampstead, North Carolina, got on the FBI&amp;rsquo;s radar after he and Michael Robert Solomon, 32, showed up with guns at protests in Minneapolis two years ago that followed the police murder of George Floyd.</description></item><item><title>UK seeking return of Kevin Spacey from US to face sexual assault charges | UK news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62945427b648600d43992caf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62945427b648600d43992caf/</guid><description>Exclusive: Formal extradition is to be pursued if actor fails to come back to the country voluntarily
Highlights UK would seek formal extradition unless Spacey decides to come back voluntarily. US officials would have to be satisfied there is &amp;lsquo;probable cause&amp;rsquo; to detain Spacey. Spacey faces four charges of sexual assault relating to alleged attacks against three males between 2005 and 2013. Former head of extradition at the CPS says Spacey could be extradited in weeks if he does not contest extradition.</description></item><item><title>Hate crime charges announced against man accused of plotting shooting in Georgia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628695f3db7aa6f15f283355/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628695f3db7aa6f15f283355/</guid><description>Federal hate crime charges have been announced against a Georgia man after he allegedly shot into two grocery stores. He is accused of being motivated by race.
Highlights Larry Edward Foxworth allegedly fired a gun repeatedly into two convenience stores at 2:30 a.m. on July 30, 2021. The indictment alleges that Foxworth, who is white, was motivated to shoot into the stores because of the perceived race, color or national origin of the people inside the stores.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: NJ police chief was passed out, pants down, on roadway in DWI arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281bdf69651b43e5ed45b0b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 02:59:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281bdf69651b43e5ed45b0b/</guid><description>Body cam footage from the April encounter involving Bordentown Police Chief Brian Pesce in Hamilton Township shows that he was sleeping on the street behind his pickup truck when officers arrived.
Highlights Police Chief Brian Pesce was arrested April 22 in Hamilton Township, Mercer County. He was charged with DWI, leaving the scene of an accident involving property damage, failing to report an accident, reckless driving and careless driving. Pesce has been on restricted duty until further notice pending investigation results as he faces charges for five traffic offenses.</description></item><item><title>'Freedom Convoy' leader Pat King charged with perjury, obstruction of justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fa55b9246872611c71b20/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 06:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fa55b9246872611c71b20/</guid><description>Ottawa convoy protest organizer Pat King is now facing perjury and obstruction of justice charges related to testimony he gave at his bail review hearing last week.
Highlights Ottawa convoy protest organizer Pat King is now facing perjury and obstruction of justice charges related to testimony he gave at his bail review hearing last week. King was arrested on Feb. 18 on charges relating to his involvement in the three-week protest against COVID-19 restrictions that overran the streets of Ottawa.</description></item><item><title>New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin arrested on campaign finance fraud charges, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255eb63d4023367746611bb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255eb63d4023367746611bb/</guid><description>New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin was arrested on charges related to a campaign finance fraud investigation, two people familiar with the matter told NBC New York.
Highlights Brian Benjamin surrendered to authorities and appeared before a federal judge in New York City on Tuesday. An indictment alleges that Benjamin was given campaign contributions from a Harlem real estate developer. In exchange, Benjamin obtained a $50,000 state grant for the developer&amp;rsquo;s business, the indictment states.</description></item><item><title>3 California police officers who restrained a man who died in their custody will not face criminal charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254b63c139fa4c840d39694/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 23:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254b63c139fa4c840d39694/</guid><description>The Alameda County district attorney will not file criminal charges against three police officers who restrained a Northern California man who died in their custody last year.
Highlights Mario Gonzalez Arenales, 26, died on April 19, 2021, following an encounter with three Alameda police officers. The county coroner&amp;rsquo;s office had classified the death as a homicide and pointed to the toxic effects of methamphetamine as the leading cause. Two wrongful death suits have been filed against the City of Alameda alleging the officers detained Gonzalez without reasonable suspicion and caused him to die of asphyxia.</description></item><item><title>Florida man strangles parents, kisses underage stepsister, and attacks deputy. All on his birthday.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246a614bb3e080633937696/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246a614bb3e080633937696/</guid><description>A 22-year-old Deltona man is facing eight felony charges after tackling a deputy during a violent fight, according to the Volusia County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.
Highlights The alleged fight started when the suspect’s girlfriend said she saw him forcibly kiss his 16-year-old stepsister. The incident happened on March 29, which also happened to be the birthday of the suspect, Russell Slimon. Russell is facing 10 charges including eight felonies including battery, child abuse and resisting arrest.</description></item><item><title>Capitol riot suspect is granted refugee status in Belarus after fleeing US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623a9ee5e4d5a4a090544e83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 04:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623a9ee5e4d5a4a090544e83/</guid><description>A US Capitol riot suspect who fled the United States has been granted refugee status in Belarus, according to Belarusian state-owned television BelTA.
Highlights A US Capitol riot suspect who fled the United States has been granted refugee status in Belarus. The California man, Evan Neumann, went to Europe after being charged in connection with the January 6, 2021, attack on the US Capitol. Neumann is accused of punching two officers at the Capitol on January 6 and using a metal barricade as a &amp;ldquo;battering ram&amp;rdquo; to strike officers trying to stop the attack.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin kicks off new trial against opposition leader Navalny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621de38684d1b6badecfa96e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621de38684d1b6badecfa96e/</guid><description>Investigators accuse Navalny of stealing more than $4.8m of public donations from the organisations he founded.
Highlights Russian opposition leader Alexey Navalny is accused of stealing more than $4.8m of public donations. He is currently serving a two and a half year sentence on old fraud charges. If found guilty, his sentence could extend up to 10 years. Amnesty International described the hearing as a “sham trial, attended by prison guards rather than the media’s.</description></item><item><title>Grand jury indicts 19 Austin police officers on aggravated assault charges over 2020 protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f1d67a5e04faca0cee4ea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 04:17:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f1d67a5e04faca0cee4ea/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — AP sources: Grand jury indicts 19 Austin police officers on aggravated assault charges over 2020 protests.
Highlights AP sources: Grand jury indicts 19 Austin police officers on aggravated assault charges over 2020 protests. 19 officers charged with aggravated assault, aggravated assault in Austin, Texas. AP sources say 19 officers were involved in the 2020 protests against the city&amp;rsquo;s Republican-led city council. Austin police have been criticized for their handling of the protests in advance of 2020 elections.</description></item><item><title>Pullman Elementary third grader faces assault charges for bullying</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209a4ba5930f3cb00406472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:39:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209a4ba5930f3cb00406472/</guid><description>A 3rd grade student is facing assault charges after an Allegan County mother said he beat up her 2nd grade son. Jada Paulin said her 8-year-old son Gavin, who has autism, has been experiencing ongoing abuse from this third grader, and it has turned violent. The two kids attend Pullman Elementary, which is part of the Bloomingdale Public Schools district. Bullying: Parent speaks out about bullying after son beat up at Portage middle school.</description></item></channel></rss>