<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>charges on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/charges/</link><description>Recent content in charges on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 09:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/charges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kremlin kicks off new trial against opposition leader Navalny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621de38684d1b6badecfa96e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621de38684d1b6badecfa96e/</guid><description>Investigators accuse Navalny of stealing more than $4.8m of public donations from the organisations he founded.
Highlights Russian opposition leader Alexey Navalny is accused of stealing more than $4.8m of public donations. He is currently serving a two and a half year sentence on old fraud charges. If found guilty, his sentence could extend up to 10 years. Amnesty International described the hearing as a “sham trial, attended by prison guards rather than the media’s.</description></item><item><title>Grand jury indicts 19 Austin police officers on aggravated assault charges over 2020 protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f1d67a5e04faca0cee4ea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 04:17:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f1d67a5e04faca0cee4ea/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — AP sources: Grand jury indicts 19 Austin police officers on aggravated assault charges over 2020 protests.
Highlights AP sources: Grand jury indicts 19 Austin police officers on aggravated assault charges over 2020 protests. 19 officers charged with aggravated assault, aggravated assault in Austin, Texas. AP sources say 19 officers were involved in the 2020 protests against the city&amp;rsquo;s Republican-led city council. Austin police have been criticized for their handling of the protests in advance of 2020 elections.</description></item><item><title>Pullman Elementary third grader faces assault charges for bullying</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209a4ba5930f3cb00406472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:39:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209a4ba5930f3cb00406472/</guid><description>A 3rd grade student is facing assault charges after an Allegan County mother said he beat up her 2nd grade son. Jada Paulin said her 8-year-old son Gavin, who has autism, has been experiencing ongoing abuse from this third grader, and it has turned violent. The two kids attend Pullman Elementary, which is part of the Bloomingdale Public Schools district. Bullying: Parent speaks out about bullying after son beat up at Portage middle school.</description></item></channel></rss>