<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>size on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/size/</link><description>Recent content in size on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 11:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/size/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nearing Earth is an asteroid the size of two Empire State Buildings.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265306e6cf02ffd3d91548e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 11:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265306e6cf02ffd3d91548e/</guid><description>On Thursday, April 28, a massive asteroid the size of the Empire State Building will speed past the Earth.
Highlights On Thursday, April 28, a massive asteroid the size of the Empire State Building will speed past the Earth. The asteroid, known as 418135 (2008 AG33), will be traveling at speeds of up to 23,264 miles per hour. Its width is estimated to be between 1,150 and 2,560 feet. That speed is 11 times faster than a rifle bullet, which travels at around 2,050 mph.</description></item><item><title>Holes the size of city blocks are forming in the Arctic seafloor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62311d9747bc33b77d62c8c3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 23:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62311d9747bc33b77d62c8c3/</guid><description>Marine scientists have discovered deep sinkholes &amp;ndash; including one larger than a city block of six-story buildings &amp;ndash; and ice-filled hills that have formed &amp;quot;extraordinarily&amp;quot; rapidly on a remote part of the Arctic seafloor.
Highlights Scientists find sinkholes and ice-filled hills that have formed &amp;ldquo;extraordinarily&amp;rdquo; rapidly on a remote part of the Arctic seafloor. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time an area of submerged permafrost, a frozen layer of Earth&amp;rsquo;s surface, has been surveyed in this way.</description></item></channel></rss>