<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>law on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/law/</link><description>Recent content in law on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 injured, 3 law enforcement officials hurt after gunfire erupts in Charleston, S.C.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296b67248eaf29125585fc3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296b67248eaf29125585fc3/</guid><description>Ten people were injured and three law enforcement officials were hurt Monday night after gunfire erupted in downtown Charleston, South Carolina, according to police.
Highlights Four of the 10 people injured were in critical condition in hospitals. A 17-year-old was among the injured, the rest were adults, police said. Two Charleston County Sheriff’s Office deputies were assaulted while trying to control the crowd, resulting in minor injuries. The shooting occurred during a violent Memorial Day weekend, a preliminary count found that gun violence left at least 156 people dead and 412 injured from 5 p.</description></item><item><title>Canada's Trudeau announces plan for national freeze on handguns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629563c4166e08fef4f508a9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629563c4166e08fef4f508a9/</guid><description>Canada&amp;rsquo;s government introduced legislation Monday to implement a &amp;quot;national freeze&amp;quot; on the sale and purchase of handguns as part of a gun control package that would also limit magazine capacities and ban some toys that look like guns.
Highlights Canada&amp;rsquo;s government introduces legislation to implement a &amp;ldquo;national freeze&amp;rdquo; on the sale and purchase of handguns as part of a gun control package. The new legislation would also limit magazine capacities and ban some toys that look like guns.</description></item><item><title>Gun makers lose challenge to New York law allowing lawsuits against industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293e0d4532a6e812a4117f8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293e0d4532a6e812a4117f8/</guid><description>A federal judge threw out a lawsuit by a group of gun manufacturers, distributors and retailers challenging the constitutionality of a New York law.
Highlights A federal judge threw out a lawsuit by a group of gun manufacturers, distributors and retailers challenging the constitutionality of a New York law. The law allows the state and people affected by gun violence to sue the industry. The National Shooting Sports Foundation argued the law wrongly imposes liability on companies operating anywhere in the country that make, sell or market guns or ammunition that are misused by criminals in New York.</description></item><item><title>A 17-year-old boy died by suicide hours after being scammed. The FBI says it's part of a troubling increase in 'sextortion' cases.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ac448f30216d66222fa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ac448f30216d66222fa9/</guid><description>Ryan Last received a message on a school night in February from someone he believed to be a girl.
Highlights A 17-year-old California teen was targeted by a cybercriminal posing as a young girl. The FBI says there were over 18,000 sextortion-related complaints in 2021, with losses in excess of $13 million. Experts say young males are especially vulnerable to the scams. Parents should be aware of the scams and talk to their kids about what they&amp;rsquo;re doing online, experts say.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court sides with Ted Cruz, striking down cap on use of campaign funds to repay personal campaign loans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282956286f0c83e21eb00c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282956286f0c83e21eb00c8/</guid><description>The Supreme Court on Monday ruled in favor of Republican Sen. Ted Cruz of Texas in a case involving the use of campaign funds to repay personal campaign loans, dealing the latest blow to campaign finance regulations.
Highlights The Supreme Court rules in favor of Ted Cruz in a case involving the use of campaign funds to repay personal campaign loans. Chief Justice John Roberts wrote the 6-3 decision; Justice Elena Kagan wrote the dissent for her liberal colleagues, Justice Stephen Breyer and Justice Sonia Sotomayor.</description></item><item><title>Texts show Marjorie Taylor Greene asked Meadows about martial law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267fdcfd39fdcaa74f67c27/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267fdcfd39fdcaa74f67c27/</guid><description>The Georgia congresswoman has testified she doesn&amp;rsquo;t recall whether she encouraged Trump to impose martial law.
Highlights Georgia Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene texted then-White House chief of staff Mark Meadows to tell him some GOP members of Congress had privately suggested former President Trump should declare martial law. She testified last week she doesn&amp;rsquo;t recall whether she encouraged the president to impose martial law as a way to remain in power.</description></item><item><title>Disney is refusing to cut LGBTQ scene in Doctor Strange 2, Saudi Arabia says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267803f84481d7044faa168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 05:17:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267803f84481d7044faa168/</guid><description>Official denies Marvel film is banned but says kingdom ‘still trying’ to get Disney to cut 12 seconds referring to lesbian character with two mothers
Highlights Official denies film has been banned but says kingdom&amp;rsquo;still trying&amp;rsquo; to get Disney to cut &amp;lsquo;LGBTQ references&amp;rsquo; The cuts amount to &amp;lsquo;barely 12 seconds&amp;rsquo; in which a lesbian character, America Chavez, refers to her ‘two moms’ Saudi Arabia’s general supervisor of cinema classification said the film will not be banned.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky lawmakers block abortion access with new law, effective immediately</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62581265ec7547ece70cf0aa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 12:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62581265ec7547ece70cf0aa/</guid><description>Kentucky effectively suspended legal abortion access on Wednesday as the legislature enacted a sweeping anti-abortion law that took effect right away and forces providers to stop offering abortions until they can meet certain requirements.
Highlights Kentucky legislature enacted a sweeping anti-abortion law that took effect right away. It forces providers to stop offering abortions until they can meet certain requirements. The law imposes requirements that the state&amp;rsquo;s clinics say make it too logistically difficult and expensive to operate.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs bill to make abortion illegal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255c1c90633f18697e04265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 18:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255c1c90633f18697e04265/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt signed a bill into law on Tuesday that makes it a felony to perform an abortion, punishable by up to 10 years in prison, as part of an aggressive push in Republican-led states across the country to scale back abortion rights.
Highlights Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt signed a bill into law that makes it a felony to perform an abortion, punishable by up to 10 years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn Subway Shooting: Multiple Shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255974d1ff65f9627ad4b56/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 15:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255974d1ff65f9627ad4b56/</guid><description>It happened in Sunset Park, near 4th Avenue and 36th Street. The suspect is said to be a man in a gas mask.
Highlights At least five people were shot Tuesday on a moving Brooklyn subway by a man in a gas mask and orange construction vest who may have tossed a smoke canister on the platform to distract the rush hour crowd, according to NYPD officials and senior law enforcement officials.</description></item><item><title>California cities spent huge share of federal Covid relief funds on police | US policing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625028e6189cd888fbe69a79/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 12:22:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625028e6189cd888fbe69a79/</guid><description>Records reveal that some cities gave more stimulus money to law enforcement than to health, housing and food initiatives
Highlights San Francisco allocated 49% ($153m) of federal funds on police, 13% ($41m) to the sheriff’s department, and the remainder to the fire department. Long Beach allocated the majority of its $135.8 million Arpa funds to police. Fresno allocated $36.6m of its Cares funds on the police, making up 67% of Cares spending on city salaries.</description></item><item><title>Postal workers hope new law will 'stop the bleeding' at U.S. Postal Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eb95f2dc254370c322023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 10:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eb95f2dc254370c322023/</guid><description>Postal workers in Wisconsin are optimistic that a new law overhauling the U.S. Postal Service and injecting more than $100 billion into the service will help put an end to years of instability in the service.
Highlights Postal Service Reform Act will save money by reducing USPS’s health care costs and eliminating a burdensome federal requirement that the service pre-fund retirees&amp;rsquo; expenses. The bill also makes six-day delivery a matter of law, after some cost-cutting plans could have ended Saturday service.</description></item><item><title>Security Guard At Columbus Jewish School Arrested After Threatening To 'Shoot Parents Picking Up Children'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249e4090bccf2a4d90f720a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 18:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249e4090bccf2a4d90f720a/</guid><description>Thomas Develin, 24, of the Northwest Side, was arrested Wednesday. He posted a photo of himself on social media site Discord holding a gun with the message “I’m at a Jewish school and about to make
Highlights Thomas Develin, 24, of the Northwest Side, was arrested Wednesday. He posted a photo of himself on social media site Discord holding a gun with the message “I’m at a Jewish school and about to make it everyone’s problem” He also posted about wanting to shoot the parents picking up their children from school.</description></item><item><title>First federal lawsuit filed against Florida's "Don't Say Gay" law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624716dc86f17a330bcad78e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624716dc86f17a330bcad78e/</guid><description>The law &amp;quot;is an unlawful attempt to stigmatize, silence, and erase LGBTQ people in Florida’s public schools.&amp;quot;
Highlights The law bans classroom instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity from kindergarten through 3rd grade. It is the first federal challenge to the law. The law &amp;ldquo;is an unlawful attempt to stigmatize, silence, and erase LGBTQ people in Florida&amp;rsquo;s schools,&amp;rdquo; the group says. The bill was signed by Florida lawmakers on Monday, and is set to be debated by the U.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles County is investigating sheriff's department's 'deputy gangs'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e13e3fb821f84cdff1470/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e13e3fb821f84cdff1470/</guid><description>The Los Angeles County Civilian Oversight Commission (COC) is launching an investigation into &amp;quot;deputy gangs&amp;quot; or groups participating in gang-like activity at the Los Angeles County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department, the Commission said Thursday.
Highlights The Commission was created by the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors to &amp;ldquo;improve public transparency and accountability&amp;rdquo; in the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department. The Commission will look at how many gangs are currently in operation and their effects on the community.</description></item><item><title>Citi's response to abortion bans: We'll pay for workers to travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623299d241630a7aa830e455/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 02:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623299d241630a7aa830e455/</guid><description>After a number of US states passed laws severely restricting access to abortions, Citigroup this week said it is providing employees with travel benefits to facilitate access to abortion clinics.
Highlights Citigroup&amp;rsquo;s new policy covers employees&amp;rsquo; expenses when traveling to seek an abortion, according to a person with knowledge of the matter. The company declined to comment beyond what it published in its proxy statement. Several states have recently passed laws that make many abortions illegal.</description></item><item><title>Petito family sues Brian Laundrie's parents, allege they knew Gabby 'had been murdered by their son'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ca9ef5c2f1167bdc58734/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 14:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ca9ef5c2f1167bdc58734/</guid><description>Gabby Petito&amp;rsquo;s parents accused the mother and father of presumed killer Brian Laundrie of hindering the search for their murdered daughter in a lawsuit.
Highlights Gabby Petito&amp;rsquo;s parents accuse the mother and father of presumed killer Brian Laundrie of hindering the search for their murdered daughter. The civil action by Joseph Petito and Nichole Schmidt was taken in Sarasota County, Florida, where Christopher and Roberta Laundries live. Petito’s body was found on Sept.</description></item><item><title>Curtis Reeves, retired police captain who fatally shot man in movie theater, acquitted</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a35418f0f606d551f953d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 14:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a35418f0f606d551f953d/</guid><description>A Florida jury acquitted retired Florida police captain Curtis Reeves in the shooting death of a man in a movie theater eight years ago.
Highlights Curtis Reeves was accused of second-degree murder and aggravated battery in the 2014 killing of Chad Oulson. Reeves pleaded not guilty and claimed self-defense, saying he feared he would be attacked. The case garnered widespread attention at the time of the killing, partly because of Reeves&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;stand your ground&amp;rdquo; claim.</description></item><item><title>Justice Department sues Missouri over new gun law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e9e653ba01b42eabb3110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e9e653ba01b42eabb3110/</guid><description>JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. (AP) — The Department of Justice on Wednesday sued Missouri over a contested new law banning local police from enforcing federal gun laws just days after pulling out of a state crime-fighting partnership.
Highlights Missouri law declares ‘invalid’ federal gun regulations that don’t have an equivalent in Missouri law. Agencies risk being sued for $50,000 by private citizens who believe their Second Amendment rights have been violated. Law also wrecked the crime-fighting partnership with U.</description></item><item><title>High numbers of mail ballots are being rejected in Texas under a new state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c6bda24612d02cb48af8e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 03:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c6bda24612d02cb48af8e/</guid><description>In Harris County — home to Houston — election officials so far have sent back to voters nearly 38% of mail-in ballots, citing issues with new state ID requirements.
Highlights Local election officials in Texas are sending mail-in ballots back to voters with incorrect IDs. The state&amp;rsquo;s controversial new voting law includes new restrictions on vote-by-mail ballots. The law requires that the ID voters use when they vote by mail matches what&amp;rsquo;s on their voter registration record.</description></item><item><title>Amazon deforestation: Record high destruction of trees in January</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a1ccc7edfcfd4606d4719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a1ccc7edfcfd4606d4719/</guid><description>An area of trees more than seven times the size of Manhattan, New York was destroyed.
Highlights Strong global demand for agricultural commodities is fuelling some of these illegal clearances. Another is the expectation that a new law will soon be passed in Brazil to legitimise and forgive land grabbing. New law is expected to be passed soon in the hope of legitimising and forgiving land grabbing in Brazil. An area of trees more than seven times the size of Manhattan, New York was destroyed in one of the worst clearances in Brazil&amp;rsquo;s history in 60 years by clearinghouses.</description></item><item><title>U.S. truckers planning protest convoy, perhaps starting in L.A. for Super Bowl, DHS warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62059bdb633558b3b095dc33/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 23:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62059bdb633558b3b095dc33/</guid><description>The convoy, similar to the one in Canada, would then head east and might get to Washington in time for President Biden&amp;rsquo;s State of the Union address on March 1, the bulletin says.
Highlights Department of Homeland Security is warning U.S. law enforcement agencies that a group of truckers is planning a protest of COVID-19 vaccine mandates that could start as soon as this weekend in Los Angeles. The bulletin warns that the convoy &amp;ldquo;could severely disrupt transportation, federal government, and law enforcement operations through gridlock and potential counterprotests&amp;rdquo; The warning was circulated to law enforcement nationwide on Tuesday and was first reported by Yahoo News.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated to be banned from restaurants and other venues in France under new Covid law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5aecda93cd027ca6e0c48/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 09:52:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5aecda93cd027ca6e0c48/</guid><description>The new law requires full vaccination for such venues, including tourist sites, many trains and all domestic flights, and applies to everyone aged 16 and over
Summary The National Assembly adopted the law by a vote of 215-58. The new law requires full vaccination for such venues, including tourist sites, many trains and all domestic flights, and applies to everyone aged 16 and over. The law also imposes tougher fines for fake passes and allows ID checks to avoid fraud.</description></item><item><title>That’s a wrap: French plastic packaging ban for fruit and veg begins</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf99a95a79d35167885f01/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf99a95a79d35167885f01/</guid><description>Law bans sale of carrots, bananas and other items in plastic as environment groups urge other countries to follow
Summary Spain will introduce a ban on plastic packaging of fruit and vegetables from 2023. For years, international campaigners have said unnecessary plastic packaging is causing environmental damage and pollution at sea. From New Year’s Day, France will ban supermarkets and other shops from selling cucumbers wrapped in plastic, and peppers, courgettes, aubergines and leeks in plastic packaging.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Weddington, attorney who won Roe v Wade abortion case, dies aged 76</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</guid><description>Texan lawyer and Linda Coffee won landmark 1973 case, safeguarding right now under threat from US supreme court
Summary Sarah Weddington, an attorney who argued and won the Roe v Wade supreme court case which established the right to abortion in the US, has died. “With Linda Coffee, she filed the first case of her legal career, Roe v Wade, fresh out of law school. Sarah Weddington poses with a signed copy of the Roe v Wade decision in front of the US supreme court in 2005.</description></item><item><title>US Marines among 12 apprehended in Okinawa for drug smuggling - The Mainichi</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6ebbd2a23f8e4a6578219/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6ebbd2a23f8e4a6578219/</guid><description>NAHA &amp;ndash; Okinawa Prefectural Police and other authorities apprehended 12 people including three members and a civilian employee of the U.S. Marines in
Summary Okinawa Prefectural Police headquarters (Mainichi/Takayasu Endo)NAHA &amp;ndash; Okinawa Prefectural Police and other authorities apprehended 12 people including three members and a civilian employee of the U.S. Marines in Okinawa on suspicion of smuggling cannabis and cocaine into Japan from the United States through military postal services that delivered items to U.</description></item><item><title>US Marines among 12 apprehended in Okinawa for drug smuggling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5b66c6db7c263d4a7aa08/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5b66c6db7c263d4a7aa08/</guid><description>NAHA &amp;ndash; Okinawa Prefectural Police and other authorities apprehended 12 people including three members and a civilian employee of the U.S. Marines in
Summary Okinawa Prefectural Police headquarters (Mainichi/Takayasu Endo)NAHA &amp;ndash; Okinawa Prefectural Police and other authorities apprehended 12 people including three members and a civilian employee of the U.S. Marines in Okinawa on suspicion of smuggling cannabis and cocaine into Japan from the United States through military postal services that delivered items to U.</description></item><item><title>He wore a wire, risked his life to expose who was in the KKK</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c383d63b857dd3cfa695d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 20:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c383d63b857dd3cfa695d5/</guid><description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — For nearly 10 years, Joseph Moore lived a secret double life. At times the U.S. Army veteran donned a white robe and hood as a hit man for the Ku Klux Klan in North Florida.
Summary He wore a wire, risked his life to expose who was in the KKKJoseph Moore looks out of a window at his home in Jacksonville, Fla., on Tuesday, Dec. 7, 2021.</description></item></channel></rss>