<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>touts on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/touts/</link><description>Recent content in touts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 19:10:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/touts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biden touts 'total unanimity' with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</guid><description>President Biden said Monday he and European leaders are in agreement following a call to discuss strategy in response to Russia’s military build-up along the Ukrainian border.
Summary Total unanimity with all the European leaders. We’ll talk about it later,” Biden said after a previously planned meeting with administration officials to discuss lowering prices. Biden met for 80 minutes earlier Monday with European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, European Council President Charles Michel, French President Emmanuel Macron Emmanuel Jean-Michel MacronDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;lsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine Biden huddling with European leaders on Russia&amp;rsquo;s military buildup near Ukraine MORE, British Prime Minister Boris Johnson Boris JohnsonDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;lsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine UK scrapping testing requirements for vaccinated arrivals MORE, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz, Italian Prime Minister Mario Draghi, NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg and Polish President Andrzej Duda.</description></item></channel></rss>