<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>linked on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/linked/</link><description>Recent content in linked on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:08:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/linked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hepatitis A outbreak may be linked to organic strawberries, FDA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295160b609bd9423ba95f36/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295160b609bd9423ba95f36/</guid><description>Organic strawberries sold at major chains including H-E-B, Kroger, Walmart, Sprouts Farmers Market, and Trader Joe’s may be linked to an outbreak of hepatitis A, the Food and Drug Administration said.
Highlights Organic strawberries sold at major chains including H-E-B, Kroger, Walmart, Sprouts Farmers Market, and Trader Joe’s may be linked to an outbreak of hepatitis A, the Food and Drug Administration said. People who purchased fresh organic strawberries between March 5, 2022, and April 25, 2022 should not eat them.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco DA drops charges against woman whose rape kit DNA linked her to a property crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eba52c21a59f1063e6f8d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 21:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eba52c21a59f1063e6f8d/</guid><description>District attorney Chesa Boudin said the charges violated constitutional protections against unreasonable searches and seizures
Highlights District attorney Chesa Boudin drops charges against a woman whose DNA collected from a rape kit was used to link her to a property crime. Officials said the practice violated the defendants’ fourth amendment protections against unreasonable searches and seizures by the government, and runs afoul of California’s Victims’ Bill of Rights. The district attorney also expressed concerns the practice would deter victims of sexual assault, which is widely underreported in the US, from coming forward.</description></item></channel></rss>