<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arrested on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arrested/</link><description>Recent content in arrested on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arrested/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man arrested in connection with "school shooter" signs found in 3 New Hampshire communities</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62926578dab7dc116d22fab7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62926578dab7dc116d22fab7/</guid><description>Multiple signs saying &amp;quot;school shooter&amp;quot; have been found in New Hampshire.
Highlights Man arrested after signs saying &amp;ldquo;school shooter&amp;rdquo; found in three communities. Guy Hanson, 61, of Pittsfield, New Hampshire, faces multiple charges. Department of Safety determined there is no credible threat at this time. Hanson is being held in Merrimack County Jail pending a hearing scheduled for Tuesday. No other suspects have been charged in relation to signs found in Barnstead, Epsom, and Pittsfields, N.</description></item><item><title>Arrest Made in Balloon Littering Investigation at Coconut Grove Marina</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d9501153c50bbffbde2a5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d9501153c50bbffbde2a5/</guid><description>Several boaters were caught on camera popping balloons and letting the trash fall into the water near a Coconut Grove marina in Miami-Dade County.
Highlights Cellphone video shows boaters popping balloons and letting the trash fall into the water near a Coconut Grove marina in Miami-Dade County. The man was identified as 29-year-old David Torres-Bocanegra. Balloon releases have been illegal in Florida since 1989. Balloons can be mistaken for food by sea turtles and other marine animals, and if eaten, can lead to internal injury, starvation, and death.</description></item><item><title>Veterinarian in Elmsford Arrested for Six Counts of Animal Cruelty, Assault and Forgery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f77700850980790ec79cb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 06:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f77700850980790ec79cb/</guid><description>Javier Diaz, DMV, 46, the owner of Main Street Animal Hospital, was arrested. Diaz was charged with Forgery 2nd degree, Six counts of animal cruelty and assault 3rd degree. Diaz will be arraigned in Elms
Highlights Javier Diaz, DMV, 46, the owner of Main Street Animal Hospital, charged with Forgery 2nd degree, Six counts of animal cruelty and assault 3rd degree. Diaz gave a certificate of a rabies vaccination and charged a pet owner without actually administering the NYS required vaccination.</description></item><item><title>Teen arrested after mother noticed son had gun at Texas school drop-off</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d7cecd1b05fa739cedfe4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d7cecd1b05fa739cedfe4/</guid><description>A teenager was arrested after police said his own mother noticed he had a gun at a school drop-off.
Highlights A mother was dropping off her 15-year-old son at O.L. Slaton Middle School around 9 a.m. when she noticed the firearm. The teen never made it inside the building, and he ran from the school. The Lubbock Police Department responded to the area along with several other agencies in an attempt to find him.</description></item><item><title>‘The Flash’ star Ezra Miller arrested again on Hawaii Island</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f5ca579f3445c74c2f76a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 01:07:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f5ca579f3445c74c2f76a/</guid><description>The star was taken into custody on assault charges.
Highlights Ezra Miller, known for playing “The Flash,” was arrested early Tuesday in Hawaii after allegedly throwing a chair at a woman. Police said Miller allegedly “became irate’ when asked to leave an acquaintance’s home. The 26-year-old victim reported a half-inch cut to her forehead. Miller was arrested following a traffic stop at the intersection of Highway 130 and Kukula Street. Miller appeared via Zoom in a Hilo courtroom to plead no contest to disorderly conduct stemming from an incident at a karaoke bar last month.</description></item><item><title>New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin arrested on campaign finance fraud charges, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255eb63d4023367746611bb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255eb63d4023367746611bb/</guid><description>New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin was arrested on charges related to a campaign finance fraud investigation, two people familiar with the matter told NBC New York.
Highlights Brian Benjamin surrendered to authorities and appeared before a federal judge in New York City on Tuesday. An indictment alleges that Benjamin was given campaign contributions from a Harlem real estate developer. In exchange, Benjamin obtained a $50,000 state grant for the developer&amp;rsquo;s business, the indictment states.</description></item><item><title>Florida man arrested for allegedly masturbating on a flight to Boston</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62540cf59b01a6b56a6b4813/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 11:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62540cf59b01a6b56a6b4813/</guid><description>A Florida man was arrested for allegedly masturbating and exposing his penis to a woman next to him on a flight from Newark to Boston.
Highlights Donald Edward Robinson, 76, of Bonita Springs, Florida, was charged with one count of lewd, indecent, and obscene acts while in the special aircraft jurisdiction of the U.S. He was arrested Sunday morning at Boston Logan International Airport and will appear in a federal court in Boston at a later date.</description></item><item><title>Survivalist who faked death to avoid child sex abuse image trial arrested after years on the run</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e72c2f84b57d1dc319d2c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 05:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e72c2f84b57d1dc319d2c/</guid><description>Jacob Greer, 28, a survivalist who faked his own death in 2016 to avoid child sex abuse image trial was arrested Monday in Washington.
Highlights Jacob Greer, 28, of Des Moines, was arrested Monday in Spanaway, the U.S. Marshals Service said. Greer faked his own death before fleeing Iowa in 2016 to avoid a child sex abuse image trial. He was arrested in April 2016 on charges of &amp;ldquo;receipt and possession of child pornography&amp;rdquo; Greer was released on bond the next day under pre-trial supervision and an ankle monitor was placed on him.</description></item><item><title>Michigan rep who pushed drunk-driving expungement arrested on 2nd OWI charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e65a5632ccc9865ff4b2a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 04:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e65a5632ccc9865ff4b2a/</guid><description>Mary Cavanagh, 30, was arrested on drunken driving allegations for a second time. The first-term Democrat from Redford was pulled over in Livonia and charged with operating while intoxicated, second offense. Her father, Phil C
Highlights Mary Cavanagh, 30, was arrested on drunken driving allegations for a second time in February. The first-term Democrat from Redford was pulled over in Livonia and charged with operating while intoxicated, second offense. In 2015, after another traffic stop for alleged drunken driving, Cavangh reportedly pleaded guilty to an ordinance violation of operating while impaired and served a year of probation.</description></item><item><title>Former Proud Boys chairman charged with conspiracy.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227e2fe7f2085b56befe6c7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 23:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227e2fe7f2085b56befe6c7/</guid><description>Enrique Tarrio, 38, is one of the most high-profile of more than 775 people criminally charged for their roles in the 2021 attack on the Capitol.
Highlights Enrique Tarrio is one of the most high-profile of more than 775 people criminally charged for their roles in the attack on the Capitol by supporters of then-President Donald Trump. Tarrio, 38, appeared in a virtual Miami-based federal court hearing from a cellblock in a nearby local jail, and prosecutors said they were seeking to have him detained pending trial because they believe he is a danger to the community and poses a risk of flight.</description></item><item><title>Memphis man arrested in Jan. 6 Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a6dd7036de9c6163e63d4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a6dd7036de9c6163e63d4/</guid><description>28-year-old Joshua Hernandez is facing multiple charges.
Highlights Joshua Hernandez, 28, is charged with multiple charges related to the breach of the U.S. Capitol. He was arrested in Memphis and made his initial appearance in the Western District of Tennessee. Court documents reveal Hernandez was among rioters who assaulted law enforcement and who entered the Capitol building. The Department of Justice says court documents reveal that Hernandez was part of a group who assaulted police and entered the building.</description></item><item><title>Tina Peters arrested for allegedly recording court proceeding</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62063690260f4b0a138baf56/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62063690260f4b0a138baf56/</guid><description>Mesa County Clerk and Recorder Tina Peters was arrested in Grand Junction Tuesday, and a judge signed a search warrant to obtain a video recording from her iPad that was allegedly taken by Peters during a court hearing Monday involving her deputy clerk’s burglary and cybercrime charges.
Highlights Mesa County Clerk and Recorder Tina Peters was arrested in Grand Junction Tuesday. A judge signed a search warrant to obtain a video recording from her iPad that was allegedly taken by Peters during a court hearing Monday.</description></item></channel></rss>