<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>board on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/board/</link><description>Recent content in board on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 19:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hundreds of US geographic sites to be renamed to eliminate offensive words</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</guid><description>A task force will prioritize a list of replacement names and present them to the federal Board on Geographic Names later this year
Highlights US officials have come up with a list of potential replacement names for hundreds of geographic sites in three dozen states. The list includes more than 660 sites in New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada, California, Idaho and many other states. US Interior secretary Deb Haaland in November formally declared the term “squaw’s derogatory and initiated a process to remove the word from use by the federal government and to replace other derogatory place names.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco recalls 3 members of city's school board</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620de7f08a75b38064560dba/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 06:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620de7f08a75b38064560dba/</guid><description>SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco residents recalled three members of the city’s school board Tuesday for what critics called misplaced priorities and putting progressive politics over the needs of children during the pandemic.
Highlights A special election on Feb. 15, 2022, will decide the fate of three school board members, all Democrats, including Commissioner Alison Collins. The election was the first recall in San Francisco since 1983, since a failed attempt to remove then-Mayor Dianne Feinstein.</description></item><item><title>Peter Thiel to step down from board of Facebook parent Meta</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201fb6834cae426c8687cb7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 05:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201fb6834cae426c8687cb7/</guid><description>Thiel, an early Facebook investor, will not stand for re-election to the board at the company&amp;rsquo;s 2022 annual stockholders&amp;rsquo; meeting.
Highlights Peter Thiel will step down from the board of Facebook owner Meta. Thiel will not stand for re-election to the board at the company&amp;rsquo;s 2022 annual stockholders&amp;rsquo; meeting. Thiel invested $500,000 in thefacebook.com in 2004, becoming the first significant outside investor in the fast-growing social networking site. Thiel has been on the Facebook board since 2005, but his tenure with the company has been fraught with controversy.</description></item></channel></rss>