<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>board on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/board/</link><description>Recent content in board on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/board/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>' I felt like crying.' River Valley alumni's anti-gay commencement speech sparks outrage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62988cb9e91d96d6809f503d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62988cb9e91d96d6809f503d/</guid><description>At River Valley&amp;rsquo;s graduation, alumni speaker Jim McGuire told grads to pursue relationships only between a man and a woman, sparking public outcry.
Highlights Alumni speaker Jim McGuire condemned homosexual relationships in graduation speech. Marion County Board of Developmental Disabilities says it will meet with county commissioners to discuss his position as a board member. Marion community members plan to speak out at board meeting Monday. River Valley School District says McGuire was speaking on his own accord and not on behalf of the district.</description></item><item><title>Florida students win yearbook flap over "Don't Say Gay" bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c0aad3e9eff1fa90caf41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c0aad3e9eff1fa90caf41/</guid><description>Students at a central Florida high school are declaring victory after taking their protest to their school board over plans to censor a yearbook page showing a student walkout against the state&amp;rsquo;s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law
Highlights Florida school board overruled superintendent&amp;rsquo;s plan to cover up a yearbook page showing a student walkout. Page showed students waving rainbow flags and a “love is love” sign during a walkout against the state&amp;rsquo;s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law.</description></item><item><title>Amazon to get hearing that could overturn NY union vote, labor board official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fa0e8be124451a2134990/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fa0e8be124451a2134990/</guid><description>Amazon.com Inc&amp;rsquo;s objections to a landmark union election at a company warehouse in New York City justify a hearing that could overturn the result, a U.S. National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) official said.
Highlights Amazon.com&amp;rsquo;s objections to a landmark union election at a company warehouse in New York City justify a hearing that could overturn the result, a U.S. National Labor Relations Board official said. The online retailer has accused the NLRB&amp;rsquo;s Brooklyn office of appearing to support the union drive and alleged that labor organizers intimidated workers to vote in their favor.</description></item><item><title>Texas residents sue county for removing books on race, sex education</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268c90e9854b60cb8aac444/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 04:40:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268c90e9854b60cb8aac444/</guid><description>Llano County residents are suing the county and local officials for restricting the content allowed in libraries, including topics on race and sex education.
Highlights Lawsuit claims Llano County, Texas, officials have removed 17,000 books from library shelves. The books include &amp;ldquo;Caste: The Origins of Our Discontents,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;In the Night Kitchen&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;It’s Perfectly Normal: Changing Bodies, Growing Up, Sex, and Sexual Health&amp;rdquo; The lawsuit claims the county is violating the first amendment rights of its residents.</description></item><item><title>Southwest Missouri high school teacher accused of using critical race theory loses job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624facdfaf23aa865b75cf7d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 03:33:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624facdfaf23aa865b75cf7d/</guid><description>Kim Morrison, a high school English teacher in Greenfield, was notified mid-March that her contract was not renewed for the next year.
Highlights Southwest Missouri high school teacher accused of using critical race theory loses job. English teacher at Greenfield High School said the vote in mid-March came shortly after allegations surfaced about a worksheet she used as part of teaching the book &amp;ldquo;Dear Martin&amp;rdquo; Critical race theory argues race is a social construct and racism has been embedded in policies and legal systems in the U.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds of US geographic sites to be renamed to eliminate offensive words</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 19:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217d841da3b12766bd8a4da/</guid><description>A task force will prioritize a list of replacement names and present them to the federal Board on Geographic Names later this year
Highlights US officials have come up with a list of potential replacement names for hundreds of geographic sites in three dozen states. The list includes more than 660 sites in New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada, California, Idaho and many other states. US Interior secretary Deb Haaland in November formally declared the term “squaw’s derogatory and initiated a process to remove the word from use by the federal government and to replace other derogatory place names.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco recalls 3 members of city's school board</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620de7f08a75b38064560dba/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 06:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620de7f08a75b38064560dba/</guid><description>SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco residents recalled three members of the city’s school board Tuesday for what critics called misplaced priorities and putting progressive politics over the needs of children during the pandemic.
Highlights A special election on Feb. 15, 2022, will decide the fate of three school board members, all Democrats, including Commissioner Alison Collins. The election was the first recall in San Francisco since 1983, since a failed attempt to remove then-Mayor Dianne Feinstein.</description></item><item><title>Peter Thiel to step down from board of Facebook parent Meta</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201fb6834cae426c8687cb7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 05:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201fb6834cae426c8687cb7/</guid><description>Thiel, an early Facebook investor, will not stand for re-election to the board at the company&amp;rsquo;s 2022 annual stockholders&amp;rsquo; meeting.
Highlights Peter Thiel will step down from the board of Facebook owner Meta. Thiel will not stand for re-election to the board at the company&amp;rsquo;s 2022 annual stockholders&amp;rsquo; meeting. Thiel invested $500,000 in thefacebook.com in 2004, becoming the first significant outside investor in the fast-growing social networking site. Thiel has been on the Facebook board since 2005, but his tenure with the company has been fraught with controversy.</description></item></channel></rss>