<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vote on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vote/</link><description>Recent content in vote on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finland's Parliament approves Nato application | News | Yle Uutiset</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283ae30a12a2b223feafe78/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:21:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283ae30a12a2b223feafe78/</guid><description>Following a 14-hour debate, the motion was passed by 188 votes to 8.
Highlights Finland will seek to join the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation (Nato) President Sauli Niinistö and Prime Minister Sanna Marin (SDP) announced the move on Sunday. Following a 14-hour debate, the motion was passed by 188 votes to 8. A total of 212 speeches were made to Parliament during the debate that preceded the vote. The president and government are now able to put the official application process into motion, possibly as soon as later on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>LA Resident Physicians Threaten To Strike Over Low Wages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e056235155fea195e0af4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e056235155fea195e0af4/</guid><description>The unionized health workers have until the end of May to vote on a strike.
Highlights Unionized resident physicians at three L.A. hospitals will hold a strike vote next week. They want a 7% raise in pay and housing stipends. The voting period for the strike will end May 30. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear when a strike and walkout could take place over the summer if approved by members. The last contract with the hospitals expired Sept.</description></item><item><title>Leaked U.S. Supreme Court decision suggests majority set to overturn Roe v. Wade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270af6417eb586e1237bcc2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 04:28:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270af6417eb586e1237bcc2/</guid><description>The U.S. Supreme Court looks set to vote to overturn the Roe v. Wade decision that legalized abortion nationwide, according to a leaked initial draft majority opinion published by Politico on Monday.
Highlights Leaked report says Roe v Wade ruling was wrong, says U.S. Supreme Court. Leaked opinion written by Justice Samuel Alito preparing for a majority of the court to overturn the landmark Roe v. Wade abortion rights decision later this year.</description></item><item><title>Slovenia's populist PM loses election to environmentalist party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266d845fc191c9b64f0130e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266d845fc191c9b64f0130e/</guid><description>Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist Prime Minister, Janez Janša, lost a national election on Sunday. The environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities. Preliminary figures showed the
Highlights Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist PM, Janez Janša, loses a national election on Sunday. The environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities. The election had been expected to be tight but preliminary figures showed the Freedom Movement, a newcomer in the election, leading with 34.</description></item><item><title>Police teargas Paris protestors after Macron re-elected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62663d2d06fe5ea2ed6e776a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 06:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62663d2d06fe5ea2ed6e776a/</guid><description>Riot police charged and sprayed teargas on demonstrators in central Paris protesting after President Emmanuel Macron was re-elected on Sunday, footage from social media showed.
Highlights Police charged and sprayed teargas on demonstrators in central Paris protesting after President Emmanuel Macron was re-elected on Sunday. Police sought to break up a crowd of mostly young people who had gathered in the central neighborhood of Chatelet to protest, images on Twitter showed.</description></item><item><title>Pakistan president dissolves Parliament at PM's request</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a9aa39c99c4e1fe2338fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:14:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a9aa39c99c4e1fe2338fa/</guid><description>ISLAMABAD (AP) — Pakistan’s prime minister threw the country into political limbo on Sunday, accusing the United States of attempting to oust him and cancelling a no-confidence vote he was poised to lose.
Highlights Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s embattled prime minister faces a no-confidence vote in Parliament on Sunday and the opposition said it has the numbers to win after Imran Khan&amp;rsquo;s allies and partners in a fragile coalition abandoned him. Imran Khan accuses the opposition of being in cahoots with the United States to unseat him, saying America wants him gone over his foreign policy choices that often favor China and Russia.</description></item><item><title>Debra Meadows appears to have filed three false voter forms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c0ca7e358639258f7c5d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 06:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c0ca7e358639258f7c5d3/</guid><description>&amp;quot;What we do know is a number of times as we have mail-in ballots, if there is not a chain&amp;hellip;
Highlights Mark Meadows, then White House chief of staff, is under investigation for potential voter fraud in 2020. Mark and Debra Meadows submitted voter registration forms that listed as their home a mobile home with a rusted metal roof that sold for $105,000 in 2021, even though they had never lived there.</description></item></channel></rss>