<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>equipment on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/equipment/</link><description>Recent content in equipment on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:15:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Patreon suspends donation page for nonprofit giving body armor to Ukrainian army</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218900507807c94a24b695c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218900507807c94a24b695c/</guid><description>Come Back Alive is looking to use money it has collected through Patreon to distribute armor and helmets to soldiers. Now it&amp;rsquo;s abilities are limited.
Highlights Russia invaded Ukraine late Wednesday, and over $300,000 rolled in, including many donations of less than $1,000. A nonprofit organization collecting donations to distribute body armor, medical kits, and helmets to Ukrainian soldiers. The organization last received money from its Patreon page in August, its director, Taras Chmut, told CNBC in an interview.</description></item><item><title>U.S. helps Ukraine to strengthen its border with Russia, Belarus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc31bcaf0f4952afc140b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 10:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc31bcaf0f4952afc140b5/</guid><description>The United States will finance projects including surveillance and monitoring equipment to strengthen Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s borders with Russia and Belarus, amid continuing escalation with Moscow, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border service said on Tuesday.
Summary Members of the Ukrainian State Border Guard Service patrol along the Ukraine-Belarus border, near the border with Poland, in Volyn region, Ukraine November 16, 2021. REUTERS/Gleb GaranichKYIV, Dec 28 (Reuters) - The United States will finance projects including surveillance and monitoring equipment to strengthen Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s borders with Russia and Belarus, amid continuing escalation with Moscow, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border service said on Tuesday.</description></item></channel></rss>