<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>strong on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/strong/</link><description>Recent content in strong on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/strong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York governor signs law raising age to own semiautomatic rifle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e7b1ced6b1d1a1926114c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e7b1ced6b1d1a1926114c/</guid><description>New Yorkers under age 21 will be prohibited from buying semiautomatic rifles under a new law signed Monday by Gov. Kathy Hochul.
Highlights New Yorkers under age 21 will be prohibited from buying semiautomatic rifles under a new law signed by Gov. Kathy Hochul. New York&amp;rsquo;s Legislature passed the bills last week, pushing the changes through after a pair of mass shootings involving 18-year-old gunmen using guns. One bill will require microstamping in new firearms, which could help law enforcement solve gun-related crimes.</description></item><item><title>Amazon union vote has strong lead in NY vote count; losing in Alabama</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62476ab643548491a47eea1d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 21:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62476ab643548491a47eea1d/</guid><description>Amazon.com Inc workers at a warehouse in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island have so far voted 57% in favor of unionizing with a final tally due on Friday, a potential landmark victory for organized labor at the second-largest U.S. private employer.
Highlights Amazon workers at a warehouse in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island have so far voted 57% in favor of unionizing with a final tally due on Friday. That win contrasted with 53% of Amazon workers in Alabama rejecting unionization, in a still-not final outcome.</description></item><item><title>Powell says 'inflation is much too high' and the Fed will take 'necessary steps' to address</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238e9c7f6ed779fe160c797/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 21:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238e9c7f6ed779fe160c797/</guid><description>Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell vowed tough action on inflation, which he said jeopardizes an otherwise strong recovery.
Highlights Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell vowed tough action on inflation, which he said jeopardizes an otherwise strong economic recovery. Powell said interest rate hikes would continue until inflation is under control. The Fed raised interest rates for the first time in more than three years in an attempt to battle inflation that is running at its highest level in 40 years.</description></item><item><title>Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher pledge to match up to $3 million in aid for Ukrainian refugees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222f0feb7170ee61678538f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 05:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222f0feb7170ee61678538f/</guid><description>Actors Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher have pledged to match up to $3 million in aid to displaced Ukrainians.
Highlights Actors Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher have pledged to match up to $3 million in aid to displaced Ukrainians. More than 1 million people have already fled Ukraine in a rapid exodus more than a week after Russia invaded and bombarded key cities across the country. Kunis: &amp;ldquo;The events that have unfolded in Ukraine are devastating.</description></item></channel></rss>