<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>order on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/order/</link><description>Recent content in order on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 14:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/order/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘This can’t be real’: Grubhub promotion turns New York City restaurants into a ‘war zone’ | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628651ec068a4f4a3f2dfba6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 14:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628651ec068a4f4a3f2dfba6/</guid><description>The deal resulted in 6,000 New Yorkers placing an order every minute, overwhelming kitchens and delivery workers
Highlights Grubhub&amp;rsquo;s free lunch promotion went badly awry on Tuesday in New York City. The app was offering $15 off of any order made in the city between 11am and 2pm. The platform said 69% of working New Yorkers said they had skipped lunch. But many users never saw their food after spending money, with some kept hungry and waiting for hours by the app’s promises that the food would arrive.</description></item><item><title>Texas loses appeal over investigation of transgender teen’s family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a77fa0142694bc51b6806/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a77fa0142694bc51b6806/</guid><description>The Texas 3rd Court of Appeals dismissed Republican Attorney General Ken Paxton’s appeal of the temporary order a judge issued last week halting the investigation by the Department of Family and Protective Services into the parents of the 16-year-old girl.
Highlights Court of Appeals rules ruling against ruling on gender-confirming parents&amp;rsquo; rights. Court also throws out order to stop state of Texas law requiring parents to report child sex abuse. The order was issued last week in response to the judge’s decision to halt the order.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s Foreign Affairs Minister: Russian troops will launch missiles on Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62223b774fe8e8b6d8a1da28/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62223b774fe8e8b6d8a1da28/</guid><description>Ukrainian Minister of Foreign Affairs Dmytro Kuleba stated that in order to execute its information attack on Ukraine, Russia intends to strike its own territory.
Highlights Minister of Foreign Affairs Dmytro Kuleba said Russia will lose the information war with Ukraine. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s tactic has been to &amp;ldquo;uncover these provocations before they are committed,&amp;rdquo; he said. Russia is preparing provocations to improve its position in the information field, he said. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defence publishes this information to block misinformation along the lines of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s attack on Russian territory, he added.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families who won defamation suit against Alex Jones subpoena Facebook as trial nears</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1903629059753f4d85456/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1903629059753f4d85456/</guid><description>The Sandy Hook families who won a defamation suit against extremist Alex Jones in&amp;hellip;
Summary NEWTOWN — The Sandy Hook families who won a defamation suit against extremist Alex Jones in Connecticut want to know whether the “Infowars” host used Facebook to amplify conspiracy theories as both sides prepare for a trial to establish damages. But since Facebook deactivated Jones’ accounts in 2018, his lawyers said they had no access to the social media data the families seek, according to court records.</description></item><item><title>Biden doubles U.S. order of Pfizer Covid treatment pills, speeds delivery as omicron rages across nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5502ab5446ea510871a64/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5502ab5446ea510871a64/</guid><description>With the new order, the U.S. has committed to purchase 20 million courses total from Pfizer.
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said another batch of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 treatment pills is shipping this week as the U.S. government doubles its order of the medication amid an unprecedented wave of infections driven by the highly contagious omicron variant. Biden on Tuesday directed the government to buy an additional 10 million courses of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s oral antiviral treatment, Paxlovid.</description></item></channel></rss>