<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bank on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bank/</link><description>Recent content in bank on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 20:15:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bank/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israel set to approve 4,000 settler units in occupied West Bank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276d3224cba3f86acc5f5f3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276d3224cba3f86acc5f5f3/</guid><description>If approved, it would be the biggest advancement of illegal settlement plans since US President Joe Biden took office.
Highlights Interior minister Ayelet Shaked says a planning committee will convene next week to approve 4,000 homes. If approved, it would be the biggest advancement of illegal settlement plans since US President Joe Biden took office. Between 600,000 and 750,000 Israeli settlers live in at least 250 illegal settlements in the West Bank and occupied East Jerusalem.</description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse sued in U.S. over alleged business related to oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d60f36784b3688d74faa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d60f36784b3688d74faa9/</guid><description>A group of people and entities have filed a class action lawsuit against Credit Suisse , alleging that the Swiss bank misled investors over business dealings related to Russian oligarchs, law firm Pomerantz LLP said.
Highlights Law firm Pomerantz LLP says Credit Suisse misled investors over dealings related to Russian oligarchs. Lawsuit filed in New York district court is on behalf of people and entities who acquired credit Suisse securities between March 19, 2021 and March 25, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Ford shuts down orders for 2022 Mustang Mach-E due to overwhelming demand</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fc1e1a26e381bd3c770e5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 08:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fc1e1a26e381bd3c770e5/</guid><description>Ford ramps up production at its plant in Mexico to build 2023 Mustang Mach-E, as 2022 order bank closes.
Highlights Ford shuts down orders for 2022 Mustang Mach-E due to overwhelming demand. An ongoing parts shortage has disrupted manufacturing and sales. In March, Ford stopped taking orders for the Premium and California Route 1 versions. Ford plans to use the entire Cuautitlan Stamping and Assembly Plant in Mexico for production starting this year.</description></item><item><title>$1 million bounty on Putin offered by Russian businessman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fa5e271132ab2a2f4f4d4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fa5e271132ab2a2f4f4d4/</guid><description>The Russian entrepreneur said the Russian president came to power by &amp;quot;blowing up apartment buildings in Russia.&amp;quot;
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin was offered to military officers by Russian entrepreneur Alex Konanykhin in a post he published on social media this week. &amp;ldquo;Putin is not the Russian president as he came to power as the result of a special operation of a. special operation in Russia, then violated the Constitution by.</description></item><item><title>EU announces new Russia sanctions with U.S. and others, including SWIFT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621afad5d9bb3d9ced374cce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 04:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621afad5d9bb3d9ced374cce/</guid><description>The United States and its allies on Saturday moved to block certain Russian banks&amp;rsquo; access to the SWIFT international payment system in further punishment of Moscow as it continues its military assault against Ukraine.
Highlights U.S. and its allies move to block certain Russian banks&amp;rsquo; access to the SWIFT international payment system in further punishment of Moscow. Measures will include restrictions on the Russian central bank&amp;rsquo;s international reserves, the nations said in a joint statement.</description></item><item><title>UK inflation rises at fastest rate in almost 30 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e2d0d27149367a95e2356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 11:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e2d0d27149367a95e2356/</guid><description>Inflation in the United Kingdom has risen at the fastest rate in almost 30 years as increased costs for energy, housing and transportation squeezed household budgets
Highlights Consumer price index ticked up to 5.5% in the 12 months through January. Latest figure is the highest since March 1992, when inflation reached 7.2%. U.K. consumers are reeling from a surge in utility bills fueled by increased demand for energy worldwide. By comparison, U.</description></item><item><title>Justin Trudeau invokes Emergencies Act for the first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b28b3ecb531b6cb0c80ee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b28b3ecb531b6cb0c80ee/</guid><description>Canada&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says police will also be given &amp;quot;more tools&amp;quot; to imprison or fine demonstrators.
Highlights Canada&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says police will also be given &amp;ldquo;more tools&amp;rdquo; to imprison or fine demonstrators. Critics have noted that the prime minister voiced support for farmers in India who blocked major highways to New Delhi for a year in 2021. Canada will always be there to defend the right of peaceful protest, he said at the time, saying: Canada will always defend the rights to peaceful protest.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin value tumbles almost 50% since record November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef137208dd6c94540b2f7f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef137208dd6c94540b2f7f/</guid><description>Bitcoin has lost almost half its value since its November high, with cryptocurrency prices continuing to plunge as major economies look to curb their growing popularity.
Summary And it&amp;rsquo;s not just Bitcoin, as cryptocurrencies in general have had a dismal start to the year. Bitcoin has fallen over 8% in the last 24 hours, and was trading at $35,479 as of 9:30 am ET, according to CoinDesk . On Thursday, Reuters reported that Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank has Governmentsare cracking down as well.</description></item><item><title>Bank of America reducing overdraft fees from $35 to $10, eliminating insufficient funds fees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61defb435bcaeeef1572b72d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 16:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61defb435bcaeeef1572b72d/</guid><description>Bank of America is reducing its overdraft fees from $35 to $10 and eliminating insufficient funds fees.
Summary Bank of America, the nation&amp;rsquo;s second-largest bank, says roughly 25% of its overdraft/NSF fee revenue each year came from NSF fees. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to reduce or eliminate overdraft fees for 20 years and to give them credit, they really did listen,&amp;rdquo; said Martin Eakes, CEO of the Center for Responsible Lending. After the financial crisis, Democrats put the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau and other regulators in charge of reining in overdraft fee revenue.</description></item></channel></rss>