<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>covid on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/covid/</link><description>Recent content in covid on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 09:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/covid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>German police under fire for misuse of COVID contact tracing app: German police used a contact tracing app to track down witnesses in a local crime case. The scandal has data protection advocates up in arms, with politicians warning that abuse of the app could undermine public trust</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de98c48408823222a66af7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 09:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de98c48408823222a66af7/</guid><description>German police used a contact tracing app to track down witnesses in a local crime case. The scandal has data protection advocates up in arms, with politicians warning that abuse of the app could undermine public trust.
Summary Authorities in Germany faced increasing criticism on Tuesday over their misuse of a COVID contact tracing app to investigate a case. While trying to track down witnesses, police and prosecutors managed to successfully petition local health authorities to release data from the Luca app, which logs how long people stayed at an establishment.</description></item><item><title>Covid vaccines prevented nearly a quarter-million deaths last spring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de8abb8c9e52312a0f774b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de8abb8c9e52312a0f774b/</guid><description>The Covid vaccine campaign in the U.S. helped prevent nearly a quarter-million deaths and more than 14 million cases of Covid, according to a modeling study.
Summary The Covid vaccination campaign in the United States cut hospitalizations and deaths by nearly half in the first six months of 2021, new research suggests. The shots saved nearly 241,000 lives and prevented almost 1.2 million hospitalizations, according to a model published Tuesday in the journal JAMA Network Open.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak reported at Rhode Island hospital after Covid-positive, asymptomatic staff asked to work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</guid><description>A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due
Summary A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due to a staffing shortage. On Saturday, the hospital had two Covid-positive staff members come into work and three on Monday, according to a memo posted on the official Rhode Island state website.</description></item><item><title>96% patients on oxygen support in Mumbai hospitals are unvaccinated: BMC chief</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da6bf82bb54b5831d9d074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da6bf82bb54b5831d9d074/</guid><description>Doctors at city officials separately said the trends were largely being reflected at their facilities, and that most of those requiring additional support were unvaccinated people above the age of 50 | Latest News India
Summary “Out of the around 1,900 Covid patients who were on oxygenated beds, around 96% are unvaccinated and only 4% are vaccinated,” Brihanmumbai Corporation (BMC) municipal commissioner Iqbal Chahal, citing data till January 6. Dr Gautam Bhansali of the Bombay Hospital, who is also coordinator of all private hospitals in the city, said, “In case of hospital beds, both vaccinated and unvaccinated citizens are occupants, but on oxygen beds, the majority of patients are unvaccinated.</description></item><item><title>U.S. reports over 1 million new daily Covid cases as omicron surges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d47d2fef87438ece772a0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d47d2fef87438ece772a0d/</guid><description>The U.S. also has the highest seven-day average of daily new cases in any country tracked by Johns Hopkins.
Summary Jeff Kowalsky | AFP | Getty ImagesThe U.S. has reported a record single-day number of daily Covid cases, with more than 1 million new infections. The new daily tally brings the total number of cases confirmed in the U.S. since the start of the pandemic to 56,189,547. Nonetheless, as of Jan.</description></item><item><title>Florida governor calls on feds for more COVID antibody doses</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d46f24cc876a1c26fe9c0e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d46f24cc876a1c26fe9c0e/</guid><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis called on the federal government Monday to allow states to directly purchase monoclonal antibody treatments from companies, saying the state is ready to open new monoclonal antibody treatment sites but is waiting on treatments.
Summary The governor said during a news conference that additional sites would open in South and Central Florida when the state receives more treatments, which he said could be between 30,000-40,000 additional doses.</description></item><item><title>Covid hospitalizations are rising across the country, even in high-vaccination states</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</guid><description>Hospitalization rates have increased in 29 states and territories since Nov. 1, according to an NBC News analysis of data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary The latest surge that is driving up the number of Covid cases across the country is also putting more people in hospitals, even in highly vaccinated states. Hospitalizations around the nation have risen 39 percent from Nov.</description></item></channel></rss>