<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>covid on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/covid/</link><description>Recent content in covid on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:13:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/covid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vice President Kamala Harris tests positive for Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268606c938e436982988a0c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268606c938e436982988a0c/</guid><description>Vice President Kamala Harris tested positive for Covid-19 on Tuesday after returning from a weeklong trip to California.
Highlights Vice President Joe Biden last tested negative for Covid-19 on Monday, White House says. Vice President Harris tested positive for the disease on both rapid and rapid tests, official says. Democratic Sens. Chris Murphy and Ron Wyden also tested positive on Tuesday. Senate Democrats had hoped to confirm Lisa Cook and Alvaro Bedoya to the Federal Reserve Board.</description></item><item><title>Attorney General Merrick Garland tests positive for Covid hours after event with FBI director, other top officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e59edea6cf40ede83dd03/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 03:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e59edea6cf40ede83dd03/</guid><description>Garland attended an event with FBI Director Christopher Wray hours before the positive result. He was at a D.C. dinner with hundreds of VIPs on Saturday.
Highlights Attorney General Merrick Garland tested positive for Covid just hours after speaking in person at a news conference with FBI Director Christopher Wray and other top Biden administration officials. Biden&amp;rsquo;s most recent Covid test, taken on Monday, came back negative, the White House said Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Tesla CEO Elon Musk says he has Covid again</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242b1c8e17290548a4f1097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 07:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242b1c8e17290548a4f1097/</guid><description>Tesla CEO Elon Musk said he has Covid again, following an earlier bout in November 2020.
Highlights SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk tested positive for Covid-19 on Monday. He has a history of under-estimating the novel coronavirus and balking at health officials. The announcement comes after Tesla&amp;rsquo;s factory in Shanghai faced Covid restrictions that reportedly require it to suspend production for four days until around April 1. Tesla also suspended production in Shanghai for two days earlier in March after officials implemented Covid health orders.</description></item><item><title>U.S. extends airplane mask mandate through April 18</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ae92477be6e27e210f239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 06:16:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ae92477be6e27e210f239/</guid><description>The U.S. is extending a requirement that masks are worn on planes, trains and other forms of transportation until the middle of next month.
Highlights The CDC says it will work with government agencies over the next month to &amp;ldquo;help inform a revised policy framework&amp;rdquo; Travel industry groups urge Biden administration to lift Covid testing requirements for inbound international travelers. The new rules will be based on Covid cases, new variant risk &amp;ldquo;and the latest science,&amp;rdquo; CDC says.</description></item><item><title>Norway lifts almost all remaining COVID restrictions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a38b3d896d20f43191976/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a38b3d896d20f43191976/</guid><description>Norway is lifting almost all remaining COVID restrictions even though Omicron is still spreading in the Nordic nation.
Highlights Norway lifts almost all remaining remaining COVID restrictions even though Omicron is still spreading in the Nordic nation. Prime Minister Jonas Gahr Stoere justified the move by saying that Norwegians are well protected by vaccines against the COVID-19 pandemic. The proportion of citizens who end in up in hospital has remained low despite the spread of the omicron variant.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer accused of pandemic profiteering as profits double</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620411a27dc2ee05167d53a8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 19:11:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620411a27dc2ee05167d53a8/</guid><description>Drugmaker makes $37bn in vaccine sales and predicts bumper year ahead from Covid jabs and pill
Highlights Pfizer forecast another bumper year in 2022, with a big boost coming from its Covid-19 pill Paxlovid. The US drugmaker&amp;rsquo;s overall revenues in 2021 doubled to $81.3bn. The bumper sales prompted accusations from campaigners of ‘pandemic profiteering’ The group Global Justice Now said the annual revenue of $81bn was more than the GDP of most countries.</description></item><item><title>Spotify Agrees to Pull Neil Young’s Music After His Criticism of Joe Rogan’s Podcast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1fcbc90c7cdece1b33f4a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1fcbc90c7cdece1b33f4a/</guid><description>Young accused Spotify of “spreading fake information about vaccines” by hosting The Joe Rogan Experience
Summary Now, Spotify has agreed to pull Young’s work from streaming, according to a statement from a Spotify spokesperson. “Spotify has recently become a very damaging force via its public misinformation and lies about COVID,” Young wrote. These young people believe Spotify would never present grossly unfactual information. In his original letter, Young accused Spotify of “potentially causing death to those who believe the disinformation being spread by them.</description></item><item><title>The next Covid variant will be more contagious than omicron, but the question is whether it will be more deadly, WHO says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</guid><description>A top WHO official warned against theories that the virus will continue to mutate into milder strains that make people less sick than earlier variants.
Summary RT: Maria Van Kerkhove, Head a.i. Emerging Diseases and Zoonosis at the World Health Organization (WHO), speaks during a news conference on the situation of the coronavirus at the United Nations in Geneva, Switzerland, January 29, 2020. The next Covid-19 variant that will rise to world attention will be more contagious than omicron, but the real question scientists need to answer is whether or not it will be more deadly, World Health Organization officials said Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Covid ‘denialist’ and Bolsonaro ally Olavo de Carvalho died of virus, says daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f08f2a2016ec4c10350c28/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f08f2a2016ec4c10350c28/</guid><description>Rightwing radical was a towering figure in Brazil who was adored and abhorred in equal measure by millions of followers and foes
Summary Olavo de Carvalho, the coronavirus-denying mentor of Jair Bolsonaro and Brazil’s radical right, has died in the United States, with one of his children citing Covid-19 as the cause. The statement did not say how Carvalho – a former astrologer who repeatedly trivialized Covid as the “moronavirus” – had died.</description></item><item><title>German police under fire for misuse of COVID contact tracing app: German police used a contact tracing app to track down witnesses in a local crime case. The scandal has data protection advocates up in arms, with politicians warning that abuse of the app could undermine public trust</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de98c48408823222a66af7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 09:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de98c48408823222a66af7/</guid><description>German police used a contact tracing app to track down witnesses in a local crime case. The scandal has data protection advocates up in arms, with politicians warning that abuse of the app could undermine public trust.
Summary Authorities in Germany faced increasing criticism on Tuesday over their misuse of a COVID contact tracing app to investigate a case. While trying to track down witnesses, police and prosecutors managed to successfully petition local health authorities to release data from the Luca app, which logs how long people stayed at an establishment.</description></item><item><title>Covid vaccines prevented nearly a quarter-million deaths last spring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de8abb8c9e52312a0f774b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de8abb8c9e52312a0f774b/</guid><description>The Covid vaccine campaign in the U.S. helped prevent nearly a quarter-million deaths and more than 14 million cases of Covid, according to a modeling study.
Summary The Covid vaccination campaign in the United States cut hospitalizations and deaths by nearly half in the first six months of 2021, new research suggests. The shots saved nearly 241,000 lives and prevented almost 1.2 million hospitalizations, according to a model published Tuesday in the journal JAMA Network Open.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak reported at Rhode Island hospital after Covid-positive, asymptomatic staff asked to work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</guid><description>A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due
Summary A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due to a staffing shortage. On Saturday, the hospital had two Covid-positive staff members come into work and three on Monday, according to a memo posted on the official Rhode Island state website.</description></item><item><title>96% patients on oxygen support in Mumbai hospitals are unvaccinated: BMC chief</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da6bf82bb54b5831d9d074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da6bf82bb54b5831d9d074/</guid><description>Doctors at city officials separately said the trends were largely being reflected at their facilities, and that most of those requiring additional support were unvaccinated people above the age of 50 | Latest News India
Summary “Out of the around 1,900 Covid patients who were on oxygenated beds, around 96% are unvaccinated and only 4% are vaccinated,” Brihanmumbai Corporation (BMC) municipal commissioner Iqbal Chahal, citing data till January 6. Dr Gautam Bhansali of the Bombay Hospital, who is also coordinator of all private hospitals in the city, said, “In case of hospital beds, both vaccinated and unvaccinated citizens are occupants, but on oxygen beds, the majority of patients are unvaccinated.</description></item><item><title>U.S. reports over 1 million new daily Covid cases as omicron surges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d47d2fef87438ece772a0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d47d2fef87438ece772a0d/</guid><description>The U.S. also has the highest seven-day average of daily new cases in any country tracked by Johns Hopkins.
Summary Jeff Kowalsky | AFP | Getty ImagesThe U.S. has reported a record single-day number of daily Covid cases, with more than 1 million new infections. The new daily tally brings the total number of cases confirmed in the U.S. since the start of the pandemic to 56,189,547. Nonetheless, as of Jan.</description></item><item><title>Florida governor calls on feds for more COVID antibody doses</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d46f24cc876a1c26fe9c0e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d46f24cc876a1c26fe9c0e/</guid><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis called on the federal government Monday to allow states to directly purchase monoclonal antibody treatments from companies, saying the state is ready to open new monoclonal antibody treatment sites but is waiting on treatments.
Summary The governor said during a news conference that additional sites would open in South and Central Florida when the state receives more treatments, which he said could be between 30,000-40,000 additional doses. [TRENDING: Cooler weather comes to Central Florida | WATCH: Snow falls in Florida.</description></item><item><title>Covid hospitalizations are rising across the country, even in high-vaccination states</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</guid><description>Hospitalization rates have increased in 29 states and territories since Nov. 1, according to an NBC News analysis of data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary The latest surge that is driving up the number of Covid cases across the country is also putting more people in hospitals, even in highly vaccinated states. Hospitalizations around the nation have risen 39 percent from Nov.</description></item></channel></rss>