<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>swift on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/swift/</link><description>Recent content in swift on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/swift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine crisis: US rejects Russian demand to bar Ukraine from Nato</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2d1063e8c11bfc2e9fbe2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2d1063e8c11bfc2e9fbe2/</guid><description>Russia says the response does not address its concerns about Nato, but &amp;quot;gives hope&amp;quot; over other issues.
Highlights &amp;ldquo;There should be no doubt about our seriousness of purpose when it comes to diplomacy, and we&amp;rsquo;re acting with equal focus and force to bolster Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defences and prepare a swift united response to further Russian aggression,&amp;rdquo; he said. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>No amount of alcohol is good for the heart, new report says, but critics disagree on science</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee95261e32d5dbcf7bdef2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 12:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee95261e32d5dbcf7bdef2/</guid><description>No amount of alcohol is good for the heart according to a new policy report by the World Health Federation, fueling an ongoing debate on what role drinking might play in heart heatlh.
Summary (CNN) In a bold move, the World Heart Federation released a policy brief Thursday saying that no amount of alcohol is good for the heart. &amp;ldquo;At the World Heart Federation, we decided that it was imperative that we speak up about alcohol and the damages to health, as well as the social and economic harms, because there is an impression in the population in general, and even among health care professionals, that it is good for the heart,&amp;rdquo; said Beatriz Champagne, chair of the advocacy committee that produced the report.</description></item></channel></rss>