<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>carolina on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/carolina/</link><description>Recent content in carolina on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 12:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/carolina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boy, 8, on vacation in S. Carolina killed by man shooting at random cars, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298aa1586b0582da10c7b0b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 12:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298aa1586b0582da10c7b0b/</guid><description>An 8-year-old boy vacationing in South Carolina was fatally shot when a man shooting randomly at passing cars struck his family’s vehicle, authorities said Tues
Highlights Quarius Naqua Dunham, a third grader from Portsmouth, New Hampshire, was fatally injured in the shooting Saturday near Florence, the Florence County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said. Quarius’ father, who was driving the car, was struck in the leg, the release said. Charles Montgomery Allen, 40, was arrested on suspicion of murder, attempted murder and other crimes, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina inmate convicted of killing toddler dies in prison attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d08b2d315fdb6375c1bac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 03:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d08b2d315fdb6375c1bac/</guid><description>Semajs Short, 24, was attacked in a housing area at Bertie Correctional Institution. He was convicted in the 2014 murder of 2-year-old Dy’Unanna Anderson. Short pleaded guilty to second-degree murder
Highlights Semajs Short, 24, was attacked in a housing area at Bertie Correctional Institution. He was convicted of second-degree murder in the 2014 murder of 2-year-old Dy&amp;rsquo;Unanna Anderson. Short was serving a 31-year prison sentence. Three other prisoners were injured in Tuesday’s assault, WCTI-TV reports.</description></item><item><title>QAnon follower from South Carolina who admitted he assaulted officers on January 6 sentenced to 44 months in prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2608cbd7ccb02088847be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2608cbd7ccb02088847be/</guid><description>Nicholas Languerand, an avowed follower of the QAnon conspiracy, pleaded guilty in November to assaulting law enforcement officers at the Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021.
Highlights Washington – A South Carolina man who traveled to Washington, D.C., on January 6, 2021 and later assaulted officers outside the U.S. Capitol was sentenced to 44 months in jail on Wednesday. Nicholas Languerand, an avowed follower of the QAnon conspiracy, pleaded guilty in November to assaulting officers and faced a maximum of 20-years prison sentence.</description></item><item><title>Son of North Carolina police officer shot by father has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</guid><description>The son of a Jacksonville police officer has died following an accidental shooting that occurred Dec. 27, involving his father.
Summary ONSLOW COUNTY, N.C. (WITN/Gray Media) - The 15-year-old son of a Jacksonville, North Carolina police officer has died after being shot last Monday at a home in Onslow County. Information released last week by authorities said the police officer accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head. Thursday afternoon, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said the teen has died.</description></item></channel></rss>