<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>services on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/services/</link><description>Recent content in services on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:14:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla will pay travel costs for staff seeking abortion services</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62768cd15e97503a68e64e08/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62768cd15e97503a68e64e08/</guid><description>Tesla is covering travel costs for employees seeking out-of-state abortions, joining the ranks of major companies who’ve introduced a similar policy to benefit
Highlights Tesla is covering travel costs for employees seeking out-of-state abortions. The car maker expanded its Safety Net program and health insurance offerings last year to include “travel and lodging support for those who may need to seek healthcare services that are unavailable in their home state” The company moved its corporate headquarters last year from Silicon Valley to Texas, which passed a law banning abortions at roughly six weeks of pregnancy.</description></item><item><title>Donations to U.S. abortion rights groups, clinics surge after Supreme Court leak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62736c451230aa3c1bfed51b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 06:19:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62736c451230aa3c1bfed51b/</guid><description>Donations have flooded into abortion clinics and abortion-rights advocacy groups since the leak of a U.S. Supreme Court draft ruling that showed the justices apparently poised to overturn the 1973 landmark Roe v. Wade decision.
Highlights Donations have flooded into abortion clinics and abortion-rights advocacy groups since the leak of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling. The ruling showed the justices apparently planned to overturn the 1973 landmark Roe v. Wade decision.</description></item><item><title>EU deal will push Google, Facebook, others to police platforms against hate speech, disinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264cf41f8f06fb43bfff2e1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264cf41f8f06fb43bfff2e1/</guid><description>European Union officials clinched the agreement in principle on the Digital Services Act after lengthy final negotiations that began Friday. The law will also force tech companies to make it easier for users to flag problems, ban online ads aimed at kids and empower regulators to punish noncompliance with billions in fines.
Highlights NEW: The Digital Services Act is one half of an overhaul for the 27-nation bloc’s digital rulebook. Big tech companies like Google and Facebook parent Meta will have to police their platforms more strictly to better protect European users from hate speech, disinformation and other harmful online content.</description></item><item><title>Canada reaches agreement to compensate indigenous children taken from families</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db772d15b46499f71f75fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db772d15b46499f71f75fc/</guid><description>Canada announced on Tuesday two agreements totaling $31.5 billion (40 billion Canadian dollars) to compensate First Nations children who were taken from their families and put into the child welfare system and to reform the system that removed them and deprived them of services they needed.
Summary Toronto, Canada Canada announced on Tuesday two agreements totaling $31.5 billion (40 billion Canadian dollars) to compensate First Nations children who were taken from their families and put into the child welfare system and to reform the system that removed them and deprived them of services they needed.</description></item></channel></rss>