<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>index on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/index/</link><description>Recent content in index on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla removed from S&amp;amp;P 500 ESG Index, prompting Musk fury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628617a4ddfd2c410d9c0440/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628617a4ddfd2c410d9c0440/</guid><description>An S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones Indices executive said it had removed Tesla from the S&amp;amp;P 500 ESG Index because of issues including claims of racial discrimination and crashes linked to its autopilot vehicles.
Highlights S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones Indices says it has removed electric carmaker Tesla from the widely followed index. Tesla CEO Elon Musk responded with harsh tweets including that &amp;ldquo;ESG is a scam&amp;rdquo; The back-and-forth over the index changes reflects a wider debate about the metrics used to judge corporate performance on environmental, social and governance (ESG) issues.</description></item><item><title>Small-business owners say inflation has become a bigger problem than the labor shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255a5db4c0c72b2e2473455/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255a5db4c0c72b2e2473455/</guid><description>Small businesses say inflation has become their biggest problem, and they don&amp;rsquo;t expect business conditions to improve over the next six months
Highlights The Small Business Optimism Index is down by 2.4 points in March, the third monthly drop in a row. The index is the lowest in the survey&amp;rsquo;s 48-year history. One-inflation is now the biggest problem facing small business owners, up 5 points from February. The Consumer Price Index, a key measure of inflation rate, rose to 8.</description></item></channel></rss>