<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mercenaries on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mercenaries/</link><description>Recent content in mercenaries on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:16:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mercenaries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian mercenaries and Mali army accused of killing 300 civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d4c3a8940161e34f54ad7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d4c3a8940161e34f54ad7/</guid><description>Human Rights Watch says deaths during anti-jihadist operation in Moura ‘the worst atrocity in Mali in a decade’
Highlights Human Rights Watch says 300 civilian men were allegedly executed over five days in March. HRW says it is the worst single atrocity reported in Mali’s decade-long armed conflict. Mali&amp;rsquo;s army has long been accused of rights abuses during counter-insurgency operations. It has forged closer links with Russia after its relations soured with the west – its former ally France – which has committed to scaling down its forces in the Sahel region.</description></item><item><title>Russian mercenaries deploy to eastern Ukraine – sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c51baa07a8b73cad605b98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c51baa07a8b73cad605b98/</guid><description>By Maria Tsvetkova and Anton Zverev MOSCOW (Reuters) - Russian mercenaries have deployed to separatist-controlled eastern Ukraine in recent weeks to b&amp;hellip;
Summary The fighter said he was planning to join up with fellow mercenaries on the Russian side of the border with the separatist-held Luhansk region in eastern Ukraine. One of the sources, a contractor who has taken part in Russian operations abroad and had already arrived in eastern Ukraine, said the deployment was for defensive purposes.</description></item></channel></rss>