<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>units on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/units/</link><description>Recent content in units on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 20:13:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/units/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida Guardsmen heading to Germany to resume training Ukrainian troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62703b4bbbf1512927815d17/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62703b4bbbf1512927815d17/</guid><description>The 160 soldiers left Ukraine in February, but have stayed in Europe.
Highlights The Florida National Guard is continuing to train Ukrainian troops outside of Ukraine. The 53rd Infantry Brigade Combat Team evacuated Ukraine in February. Canada is leading training on M777 howitzer systems that the U.S. and Canada have sent to Eastern Europe. The Guardsmen will train on equipment sent in two recent aid packages, including radars and tactical vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Chechen general Magomed Tushayev, the president’s right-hand man, killed near Kiev</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aec7f937630f9e06c606d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aec7f937630f9e06c606d/</guid><description>Magomed Tushayev was in charge of the so-called Kadyrov guard in Chechnya. He was known as one of the Lords of war and his loss is a severe blow to the Chechen contingent that was
Highlights Tushyen is one of the most elite military units in the world. He was known as one of those who lost his life in the Ukraine. The loss of his troops is a blow to his reputation as a leader in the country&amp;rsquo;s armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Ford beats out Tesla to become the auto industry’s top growth stock in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3f08f7a56bd392cbecb87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3f08f7a56bd392cbecb87/</guid><description>Ford accomplished this largely thanks to a leadership change in October 2020 from industry outsider Jim Hackett to auto veteran Jim Farley.
Summary In this article FThe all-electric Ford F-150 Lightning truck during an augmented reality presentation at the Motor Bella Auto Show in Pontiac, Michigan, on Tuesday, Sept. 21, 2021. He told CNBC the day before that the company halted reservations of the F-150 Lightning after they hit 200,000 units.</description></item></channel></rss>