<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cause on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cause/</link><description>Recent content in cause on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 03:33:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cause/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Covid-19 was third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, CDC reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6263734f7a7e5d2e375dd940/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 03:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6263734f7a7e5d2e375dd940/</guid><description>Covid-19 was the third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, following heart disease and cancer, for the second year in a row, according to provisional data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Highlights Covid-19 was the third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, following heart disease and cancer. The data was published Friday in the CDC&amp;rsquo;s Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus can destroy the placenta and lead to stillbirths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6206611f5053c6d1f69827a9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 13:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6206611f5053c6d1f69827a9/</guid><description>New research suggests the coronavirus can invade and destroy the placenta and lead to stillbirths in infected women. It&amp;rsquo;s an uncommon outcome for any pregnancy but women with COVID-19 face an elevated risk.
Highlights Coronavirus can destroy the placenta and lead to stillbirths in infected pregnant women. Researchers in 12 countries analyzed placental and autopsy tissue from 64 stillbirth and four newborns who died shortly after birth. The cases all involved unvaccinated women who had COVID-19 during their pregnancy.</description></item><item><title>Ford recalls nearly 185,000 F-150s for defect that can cause drivers to lose control of the vehicle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</guid><description>A new recall affects close to 185,000 F-150 pickups from the 2021 and 2022 model years.
Summary Ford Motor Company is recalling nearly 185,000 F-150s from the 2021 and 2022 model years for a defect that can cause a fractured driveshaft. Ford reports that insulators on the underbody of the trucks can loosen and contact the aluminum driveshaft, rubbing and scoring it. Operators may observe a loose underbody insulator, or hear a rattling, clicking or clunking noise due to a loose underbody insulator contacting the driveshaft.</description></item></channel></rss>