<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>45 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/45/</link><description>Recent content in 45 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/45/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Companies leaving Russia cost 45% of national GDP - Investment Monitor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b41c19834196bf1dd8472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b41c19834196bf1dd8472/</guid><description>Research from Yale shows that companies exiting Russia are taking with them revenues equal to almost half of Russia&amp;rsquo;s GDP.
Highlights Yale research shows that companies withdrawing from Russia are taking with them revenues equal to 45% of Russia&amp;rsquo;s GDP. Foreign direct investment (FDI) only accounted for 0.63% of the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP in 2020. Russian exports of oil and oil products are equivalent to only approximately 12% of GDP. Imports into Russia, on balance, are a net exporter, even as it is forced to sell oil and gas at highly discounted prices.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</guid><description>A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.
Summary New York (CNN Business) A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics. This pushed the quits rate to 3%, matching the high from September. Workers were most likely to quit their jobs in the hospitality industry, which had by far the highest quits rate at 6.</description></item></channel></rss>