<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gun on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gun/</link><description>Recent content in gun on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 injured, 3 law enforcement officials hurt after gunfire erupts in Charleston, S.C.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296b67248eaf29125585fc3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296b67248eaf29125585fc3/</guid><description>Ten people were injured and three law enforcement officials were hurt Monday night after gunfire erupted in downtown Charleston, South Carolina, according to police.
Highlights Four of the 10 people injured were in critical condition in hospitals. A 17-year-old was among the injured, the rest were adults, police said. Two Charleston County Sheriff’s Office deputies were assaulted while trying to control the crowd, resulting in minor injuries. The shooting occurred during a violent Memorial Day weekend, a preliminary count found that gun violence left at least 156 people dead and 412 injured from 5 p.</description></item><item><title>Students walk out of schools in protest of gun violence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62915a41d6a6b29e547b124a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62915a41d6a6b29e547b124a/</guid><description>Days after 19 students and 2 teachers were killed in a mass shooting, students walked out of class protesting gun violence.
Highlights Days after 19 students and 2 teachers were killed in a mass shooting at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, students at schools around the country staged walkouts to protest gun violence. Students at Oxford High School in Michigan, where a school shooting occurred in November, staged a walkout at 12 p.</description></item><item><title>How to Murder Your Husband writer found guilty of murdering husband</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fcff95e196320db24e681/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fcff95e196320db24e681/</guid><description>Portland jury finds Nancy Crampton Brophy guilty of killing chef Daniel Brophy in June 2018
Highlights Nancy Crampton Brophy, 71, found guilty of second-degree murder of her husband. The self-published romance novelist wrote an essay titled How to Murder Your Husband. The essay detailed various options for committing an untraceable killing. It was written in the form of a brainstorming exercise for writers in 2011. Daniel Brophy was killed on 2 June 2018 as he prepared for work at the Oregon Culinary Institute in south-west Portland.</description></item><item><title>Annadale man who allegedly called for ‘extermination’ of Biden supporters gets 3 years on gun charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628680e11b0f18d6d51254ea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 17:40:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628680e11b0f18d6d51254ea/</guid><description>Brian Maiorana, 55, was arrested late last year after allegedly calling for the ‘extermination’ of Democrats and their families. Authorities at the time discovered at the house a semiautomatic Glock pistol, two magazines
Highlights Brian Maiorana, 55, pleaded guilty to being a felon in possession of a firearm in April 2021. Authorities at the time discovered at the house a semiautomatic Glock pistol, two magazines of.45-caliber ammunition, parts for a.22-caliber firearm and additional ammunition.</description></item><item><title>Woman charged after gun in son's backpack goes off at school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285be822b25508e3f9fff64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 03:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285be822b25508e3f9fff64/</guid><description>Chicago police say a mother has been charged with child endangerment after a gun in her second grader’s backpack accidentally discharged at school, injuring a 7-year-old classmate
Highlights Chicago police say a gun in a second grader’s backpack accidentally discharged at school. The 28-year-old woman appeared in court on Wednesday on three misdemeanor child endangerment counts. A judge ordered her release from Cook County Jail on $1,000 bond. The bullet ricocheted off the floor and grazed the child&amp;rsquo;s abdomen, police said.</description></item><item><title>Federal operation nabs nearly 43,000 illegal gun silencers shipped from China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f57d8adfa582f8c16d02a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:19:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f57d8adfa582f8c16d02a/</guid><description>Operation Silent Night has led to the arrest of felons and domestic extremists who were found with illegal firearm silencers bought from China, officials say.
Highlights Operation Silent Night has seized 42,888 illegal imported silencers and 4,868 firearms, ICE says. The operation has led to 204 arrests, including felons and domestic extremists, officials say. Chinese websites targeted by this operation don’t require buyers to go through the lengthy background check process.</description></item><item><title>Rep. Madison Cawthorn caught bringing loaded gun through airport security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626852ae85a87c0c9952ec2f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626852ae85a87c0c9952ec2f/</guid><description>Madison Cawthorn, a Republican congressman from North Carolina, was caught trying to go through security with a loaded gun at Charlotte Douglas International Airport.
Highlights Madison Cawthorn, a Republican congressman from North Carolina, was caught trying to go through security with a loaded gun at Charlotte Douglas International Airport Tuesday morning. He was issued a citation for possession of a dangerous weapon on city property by Charlotte Mecklenburg police. This was the second time the congressman has been stopped trying to bring a weapon through airport security.</description></item><item><title>Autopsy shows Patrick Lyoya shot in head by Michigan cop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f345da859788504e34923/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 22:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f345da859788504e34923/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A Michigan police officer who killed Patrick Lyoya after a traffic stop pressed the gun against his head when firing the fatal shot, an expert who performed an independent autopsy for the Black man&amp;rsquo;s family said Tuesday.
Highlights Forensic pathologist Dr. Werner Spitz performed the autopsy last weekend at a funeral home. The 95-year-old forensic pathologist participated in the assassination investigations of President John F. Kennedy and Martin Luther King Jr.</description></item><item><title>No charges for cop who fatally shot Amir Locke</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e8f139662a51d696712b6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 07:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e8f139662a51d696712b6/</guid><description>No criminal charges will be filed in the fatal police shooting of Amir Locke.
Highlights Amir Locke, a legal gun owner, was fatally shot by Minneapolis police officers in February. Locke was not a suspect in the crime for which the warrant was issued and was not named in the document. Locke&amp;rsquo;s mother: &amp;ldquo;Can you imagine knowing that you&amp;rsquo;ll never get to see your 22-year-old baby ever again?&amp;rdquo; Locke&amp;rsquo;s legal team says it is &amp;ldquo;deeply disappointed&amp;rdquo; by the decision.</description></item><item><title>Video contrasts police depiction of stun gun on Black man.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624990f66b065c5cad7d6f66/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 12:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624990f66b065c5cad7d6f66/</guid><description>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee police officer who used his stun gun on a DoorDash driver wrote an arrest report saying the man had become argumentative while denying he was speeding, refused to hand over identifying information, demanded to see a supervisor and stayed in his car when ordered to get out.
Highlights Driver, Delane Gordon, a food delivery driver, began recording his traffic stop for speeding and asked to see the officer&amp;rsquo;s supervisor.</description></item><item><title>San Jose police shot athlete trying to wrest gun away from suspect, attorney says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245b7003a19582482998396/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245b7003a19582482998396/</guid><description>A man who was shot and injured by a San Jose cop while holding a ghost gun during a fight at a downtown taqueria was not the person who brought the handgun to the restaurant, police officials said.
Highlights K&amp;rsquo;aun Green, 20, was shot multiple times in the abdomen, leg and arm, attorney says. Officer shot Green while holding a ghost gun during a fight at a downtown taqueria, police say.</description></item><item><title>Feds: Forced-reset triggers are machine guns under US law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal officials are notifying gun dealers that some forced-reset triggers, which allow guns to fire rapidly with a single continuous pull of the trigger, are considered machine guns under federal law and subject to strict regulation.
Highlights The notification was being made Thursday in an open letter from the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives to federally licensed firearms dealers. It spells out how investigators have determined the triggers to be “conversion devices,” making the weapons machine guns.</description></item><item><title>Germany to disarm far-right extremists, restricts gun access</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62310116e5f0358fb56fe369/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 21:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62310116e5f0358fb56fe369/</guid><description>BERLIN (AP) — Germany&amp;rsquo;s top security officials announced a 10-point plan Tuesday to combat far-right extremism in the country that includes disarming about 1,500 suspected extremists and tightening background checks for those wanting to acquire guns.
Highlights Germany&amp;rsquo;s top security officials announced a ten-point plan Tuesday to combat far-right extremism in the country. The plan includes disarming some 1,500 suspected extremists and tightening background checks for those wanting to acquire guns.</description></item><item><title>Alec Baldwin sued by family of cinematographer killed on set</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c33644edebc26dd437e49/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 23:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c33644edebc26dd437e49/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The family of a cinematographer shot and killed on the set of the film “Rust” sued Alec Baldwin and the movie&amp;rsquo;s producers Tuesday alleging their “callous” disregard in the face of safety complaints led directly to her death.
Highlights Halyna Hutchins was shot and killed on the set of the film “Rust’s” on Oct. 21 when a gun went off, killing her and wounding the director. At a news conference announcing the lawsuit, attorneys for the husband and 9-year-old son said Baldwin refused training for the type of “cross-draw” he was performing when he fired the shot that killed her.</description></item><item><title>13 states have backed the Mexican government's lawsuit against a group of US gun manufacturers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fff44eec5861ae80dfcf13/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:16:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fff44eec5861ae80dfcf13/</guid><description>The attorneys general of 13 states and Washington DC this week expressed support for a federal lawsuit by the Mexican government that accuses a group of American gun manufacturers of facilitating the trafficking of weapons to criminals in Mexico, fueling gun violence.
Highlights The AGs say a federal law protecting gun manufacturers does not apply in this case. The gunmakers, along with a distributor, use &amp;ldquo;reckless and corrupt gun dealers and dangerous and illegal sales practices that the cartels rely on to get their guns,&amp;rdquo; the lawsuit claims.</description></item><item><title>Mother shoots her 4-year-old child twice while attempting to clean gun, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</guid><description>A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said.
Summary A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said. The mother initially told officers someone opened fire outside an apartment after unsuccessfully trying to snatch her purse, hitting the child twice.</description></item><item><title>Illinois police officer pleaded for her life before she was fatally shot with her own gun, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5cec2ff5130dff294129b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5cec2ff5130dff294129b/</guid><description>Bradley Police Sgt. Marlene Rittmanic desperately pleaded for her life before she was fatally shot with her own gun in a tragic shooting at a northern Illinois hotel last week, according to prosecutors.
Summary A police officer in Bradley, Illinois, pleaded for her life before she was fatally shot with her own gun at a hotel last week, prosecutors said. Sullivan pointed the gun and shot Bailey in the head and then turned the gun on Rittmanic and shot her as she tried to run away, Rowe alleged.</description></item></channel></rss>