<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crimes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crimes/</link><description>Recent content in crimes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crimes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In Mariupol, the occupiers plan a war crime, a “parade of prisoners”. The Ukrainian serviceman remembers a similar “parade” in 2014 in Donetsk, and human rights activists explain how Russia will be punished for it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278b20bbde588aecb3df8d0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278b20bbde588aecb3df8d0/</guid><description>In Mariupol, the occupiers are planning to hold &amp;quot;parade of prisoners&amp;quot; on May 9. A similar one was held on August 24, 2014 in Donetsk. Vasyl Stasiev is planning the parad. Lawyers explain why it is a war crime.
Highlights Vasyl Stasiev was in captivity from August 13 to December 26, 2014. The only thing I remember from that &amp;ldquo;parade&amp;rdquo; is the beastly crowd. The feeling was that they were ready just to attack us and tear us apart.</description></item><item><title>Russian commanders 'will be hunted down for war crimes', justice secretary warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220790dbc5a66d5a8ea76c9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 08:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220790dbc5a66d5a8ea76c9/</guid><description>The UK and 37 others countries referred Russia to the International Criminal Court on Wednesday for its &amp;quot;barbaric&amp;quot; invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Justice Secretary Dominic Raab said the UK is already planning to help identify and find fugitives suspected of war crimes. The UK and 37 other countries referred Russia to the International Criminal Court on Wednesday for its &amp;ldquo;barbaric&amp;rdquo; invasion of Ukraine. Justice Secretary Johnson said all 38 countries are &amp;ldquo;crystal clear that Mr Putin cannot commit these horrific acts with impunity&amp;rdquo; Mr Raab revealed more details to The Daily Telegraph.</description></item><item><title>Ahmaud Arbery: White trio guilty of hate crimes in killing of black man while he was out running</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215848c68b57b186495b716/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215848c68b57b186495b716/</guid><description>Greg and Travis McMichael, and their neighbour William &amp;quot;Roddie&amp;quot; Bryan have already been convicted of the murder of Mr Arbery and sentenced to life in prison.
Highlights Ahmaud Arbery, 25, was chased and shot by Travis McMichael, 35; his father and former police officer Greg, 66, and their neighbour William &amp;ldquo;Roddie&amp;rdquo; Bryan, 52, on 23 February 2020 in Satilla Shores just outside the city of Brunswick, Georgia. The trio had denied federal hate crime charges but were convicted of violating Mr Arbery&amp;rsquo;s civil rights and targeting him because he was black.</description></item></channel></rss>