<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sent on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sent/</link><description>Recent content in sent on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 15:14:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>17 LA gangs have sent out crews to follow and rob city's wealthiest, LAPD says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256e8a879f4c951d21d114e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 15:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256e8a879f4c951d21d114e/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES — More than a dozen Los Angeles gangs are targeting some of the city&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
Highlights LAPD task force is trying to identify the cause of a sudden surge in &amp;ldquo;follow-home&amp;rdquo; robberies. Police say at least 17 gangs, most based out of South L.A. and operating independently, are involved. The gangs are sending crews in multiple cars to find, follow and rob people driving high-end vehicles or wearing expensive jewelry, police say.</description></item><item><title>Michigan State Police trooper suspended after video shows him punch handcuffed suspect</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eff743f01144fd5961b0a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 15:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eff743f01144fd5961b0a/</guid><description>Michigan State Police say they learned about what happened only after a video made it to social media. The Saginaw NAACP is praising the public for bringing these incidents out
Highlights Michigan State Police say they learned about what happened only after a video made it to social media. The Saginaw NAACP is praising the public for bringing these incidents out. Michigan State police say they only learned about the incident after the video was posted on social media and posted on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>Former Meta employee caught in paedophile sting video after allegedly sending sexual messages to 13 year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</guid><description>Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’
Highlights Alleged paedophile caught in anti-paedophile sting by &amp;lsquo;Predator Catchers Indianapolis&amp;rsquo; He allegedly sent sexually explicit messages to someone he believed to be a 13-year-old. The man was the ‘manager of community development’ at Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta. A Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’ The man is no longer employed with the company and is ‘actively investigating’ the allegations.</description></item><item><title>Woman takes legal action after Met officer who called her ‘hot’ keeps job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 04:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</guid><description>Kristina O’Connor says detective who was investigating after men tried to steal her phone asked her out
Highlights Kristina O&amp;rsquo;Connor said she was sent inappropriate messages by DCI James Mason. The officer asked her out to dinner while taking her statement about an attempted robbery. A panel at a police misconduct hearing last year found him guilty of gross misconduct. The Met has confirmed he remains a serving officer. O’Connor is seeking a judicial review of how the investigation was handled by the force.</description></item></channel></rss>