<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sent on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sent/</link><description>Recent content in sent on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:14:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former Meta employee caught in paedophile sting video after allegedly sending sexual messages to 13 year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</guid><description>Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’
Highlights Alleged paedophile caught in anti-paedophile sting by &amp;lsquo;Predator Catchers Indianapolis&amp;rsquo; He allegedly sent sexually explicit messages to someone he believed to be a 13-year-old. The man was the ‘manager of community development’ at Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta. A Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’ The man is no longer employed with the company and is ‘actively investigating’ the allegations.</description></item><item><title>Woman takes legal action after Met officer who called her ‘hot’ keeps job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 04:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</guid><description>Kristina O’Connor says detective who was investigating after men tried to steal her phone asked her out
Highlights Kristina O&amp;rsquo;Connor said she was sent inappropriate messages by DCI James Mason. The officer asked her out to dinner while taking her statement about an attempted robbery. A panel at a police misconduct hearing last year found him guilty of gross misconduct. The Met has confirmed he remains a serving officer. O’Connor is seeking a judicial review of how the investigation was handled by the force.</description></item></channel></rss>