<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>line on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/line/</link><description>Recent content in line on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 02:35:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Smith Apologizes To Chris Rock After Slapping Him At The Oscars: “I Was Out Of Line And I Was Wrong”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242705bb1aa29accb57e836/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 02:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242705bb1aa29accb57e836/</guid><description>Will Smith Apologizes To Chris Rock After Slapping Him At The Oscars: &amp;quot;I Was Out Of Line And I Was Wrong&amp;quot;
Highlights The best way to compete is to find the best and worst of the best of the year. The best ways to compete are to compete with the best, the worst and the best. CNN will try to find out what the best way possible to compete in the best forum to compete against each other on CNN.</description></item><item><title>‘Let’s Go Brandon’ merchandise at Alaska exchange crossed AAFES’ line on vulgarity</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5a47e017f3feafb2c7e8e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5a47e017f3feafb2c7e8e/</guid><description>The Army and Air Force Exchange Service is emphasizing a ban on the sale of lewd or profane products in its stores after a vendor in Alaska sold figurines carrying a crude catch phrase aimed at the commander in chief.
Summary Buy Photo “Let’s Go Brandon” serves as code for some who oppose Joe Biden’s presidency. Pro-Trump crowds routinely chant the phrase during rallies, and it now adorns T-shirts, hats, coffee mugs and a host of other merchandise popular with conservatives.</description></item></channel></rss>