<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>loved on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/loved/</link><description>Recent content in loved on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 08:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/loved/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legendary comic book artist George Pérez dies after cancer battle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62777c632694d1145f984b9e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 08:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62777c632694d1145f984b9e/</guid><description>George Pérez, whose work for DC and Marvel made him one of the most iconic comic book artists of his generation, died Friday after a battle with pancreatic
Highlights George Pérez died Friday after a battle with pancreatic cancer at the age of 67. He died peacefully at home with his wife of 490 months and family by his side, a statement says. The comic book artist&amp;rsquo;s death was announced on Free Comic Book Day, a day his team said he &amp;ldquo;absolutely loved&amp;rdquo; He worked on titles including The Avengers, Teen Titans, and the 1987 relaunch of Wonder Woman.</description></item><item><title>14-year old girl was accidentally shot by another child, says sheriff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e36603cf5629272aefb85/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e36603cf5629272aefb85/</guid><description>Alexis Sky Pierson, 14, died after being shot Tuesday when another child picked up what was believed to be an unloaded weapon and fired it towards her.
Highlights Alexis Sky Pierson, 14, died after being shot by another child in Hancock County, Mississippi. A 10-year-old picked up what appeared to be an unloaded weapon and fired it towards her. A bullet was discharged from the weapon, striking the girl just below her left eye.</description></item></channel></rss>