<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>accounts on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/accounts/</link><description>Recent content in accounts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 23:14:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/accounts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facebook, Twitter remove disinformation accounts targeting Ukrainians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d571721856a605d0bcc99/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 23:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d571721856a605d0bcc99/</guid><description>Facebook and Twitter removed two anti-Ukrainian “covert influence operations” over the weekend, one tied to Russia and another with connections to Belarus, the
Highlights Facebook and Twitter removed two anti-Ukrainian “covert influence operations” over the weekend. One of the operations was an offshoot of a known Russian disinformation operation. The other campaign used hacked accounts to push similar anti-Ukraine propaganda and was tied to a known Belarusian hacking group. Disinformation experts warned that Russia is expected to continue to try to manipulate narratives about Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>As U.S. ‘trucker convoy’ picks up momentum, foreign meddling adds to fray</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207bfcffd4958efa37613e6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207bfcffd4958efa37613e6/</guid><description>There is growing momentum in the U.S. anti-vaccination community to conduct rallies similar to the “Freedom Convoy” that has paralyzed Ottawa, Canada.
Highlights The majority of the people behind the content mills are not clear, but Joan Donovan, director of the Shorenstein Center, said the pattern fits existing efforts to make money off U.S. It’s normal political activity,” Donovan said. “In other ways, we have to look at how some of the.</description></item></channel></rss>