<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ordered on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ordered/</link><description>Recent content in ordered on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ordered/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UN court orders Russia to cease hostilities in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62326ef287617621e7642c05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62326ef287617621e7642c05/</guid><description>THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The United Nations’ highest court on Wednesday ordered Russia to stop hostilities in Ukraine, granting measures requested by Kyiv although many are skeptical that Russia will comply.
Highlights The International Court of Justice ordered Russia to stop hostilities in Ukraine, granting measures requested by Kyiv. Russia snubbed a hearing last week, when lawyers for Ukraine told the court that Russia had started an “unprovoked aggression” The court also told Moscow to ensure military units “take no steps” to further the conflict, which Russia refers to as a “special military operation’s.</description></item><item><title>US State Department issues 'do not travel' warning for Ukraine as embassy staff is told to leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee326a11fc5601404430b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee326a11fc5601404430b2/</guid><description>The U.S. State Department has ordered the evacuation of American citizens in Ukraine amid the threat of Russian military action.
Summary The U.S. State Department has ordered the evacuation of American citizens in Ukraine amid the threat of Russian military action. &amp;ldquo;U.S. citizens in Ukraine should be aware that Russian military action anywhere in Ukraine would severely impact the U.S. Embassy’s ability to provide consular services, including assistance to U.S. citizens in departing Ukraine,&amp;rdquo; the State Department said in a travel advisory.</description></item><item><title>Shkreli ordered to return $64M, is barred from drug industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Martin Shkreli must return $64.6 million in profits he and his former company reaped from jacking up the price and monopolizing the market for a lifesaving drug, a federal judge ruled Friday while also barring the provocative, imprisoned ex-CEO from the pharmaceutical industry for the rest of his life.
Summary FILE - Former Turing Pharmaceuticals CEO Martin Shkreli attends the House Committee on Oversight and Reform Committee hearing on Capitol Hill in Washington, Feb.</description></item></channel></rss>