<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vessels on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vessels/</link><description>Recent content in vessels on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 22:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vessels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Turkey defuses mine after Russia warns of strays from Ukraine ports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f8fc509f15f9d5ca3e169/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 22:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f8fc509f15f9d5ca3e169/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s military deactivated a mine on Saturday that had drifted in from the Black Sea, setting off a loud explosion north of Istanbul, days after Russia warned several of them had washed away from Ukrainian ports.
Highlights Turkey&amp;rsquo;s military deactivated a mine that had drifted in from the Black Sea, setting off a loud explosion north of Istanbul. The mine was first discovered by fishermen in the upper Bosphorus strait. Russia warned several of them had washed away from Ukrainian ports earlier this month.</description></item><item><title>Flotilla Of Russian Landing Ships Has Entered The English Channel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea3df018a6d262efb9a633/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 05:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea3df018a6d262efb9a633/</guid><description>Evidence mounts that the six landing ships are ultimately headed toward the Black Sea and possible action against Ukraine.
Summary A group of Russian amphibious warfare vessels — three of which left the Baltic Sea region yesterday, preceded by another three the day before — have started to enter the English Channel. Multiple reports confirm that all six of the Russian Navy warships have begun their passage through the English Channel, after which they will enter the Atlantic Ocean.</description></item><item><title>Russian Landing Ships Leave Baltic Sea Raising Concerns That Ukraine May Be Their Final Destination</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7fd791b14066e5e408120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7fd791b14066e5e408120/</guid><description>The destination of the three ships is unknown but if they head south, bolstering the Black Sea Fleet could be their mission.
Summary Russian Government The Russian Navy landing ship Pyotr Morgunov during the celebrations for Navy Day in 2020. Swedish Armed Forces A Swedish Air Force JAS 39C Gripen keeps watch on a Russian landing ship underway in the Baltic. Here, an influx of Russian troops and materiel have led to widespread concerns that Moscow is poised to launch a potential new invasion of its neighbor.</description></item></channel></rss>