<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>series on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/series/</link><description>Recent content in series on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 11:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Estelle Harris Dies: ‘Seinfeld’s Estelle Costanza, ‘Toy Story’ Franchise’s Mrs. Potato Head Was 93</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249811538ec16488999c4b9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249811538ec16488999c4b9/</guid><description>Estelle Harris, who played George Costanza&amp;rsquo;s mother Estelle on &amp;lsquo;Seinfeld,&amp;rsquo; died today, aged 93.
Highlights Estelle Harris, who played George Costanza&amp;rsquo;s mother Estelle on the iconic NBC sitcom Seinfeld, died Saturday evening of natural causes in Palm Desert, California. Born Estelle Nussbaum in New York City on April 22, 1928, Harris appeared on 27 episodes of Seinfeld between 1992 and 1998. Harris is also known for voicing Mrs. Potato Head in three installments of Pixar’s Toy Story franchise (2, 3 and 4) Other film credits include Promoted, CBGB, Playing Mona Lisa, Dancing in September, What&amp;rsquo;s Cooking?</description></item><item><title>Reuters wins Polk Award for series on intimidation of U.S. election workers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62149bd925ba5d1c613288b7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62149bd925ba5d1c613288b7/</guid><description>The staff of Reuters has received a George Polk Award for its coverage of widespread intimidation of U.S. election workers by supporters of former President Donald Trump.
Highlights The staff of Reuters has received a George Polk Award for its coverage of widespread intimidation of U.S. election workers by supporters of former President Donald Trump. The prestigious Polk Awards, presented by Long Island University in the United States, honor special achievement in journalism.</description></item></channel></rss>