<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>patients on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/patients/</link><description>Recent content in patients on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:28:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/patients/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VA hospital denied emergency care to dying vet because staff couldn’t verify his military service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629775211e4ba9dced5bb3f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629775211e4ba9dced5bb3f1/</guid><description>The 60-year-old had received treatment for a heart ailment just a few months earlier at the Florida VA hospital.
Highlights A Florida VA hospital refused treatment for a 60-year-old man dying of heart failure because first responders could not prove his military service. The incident occurred at the Malcom Randall VA Medical Center in Gainesville, Florida, in summer 2020. The VA Inspector General’s Office said without policy and staffing changes, it may not be the last.</description></item><item><title>Doctor who branded his initials on patients' livers no longer allowed to practice medicine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0065f7bb357ed32f5cada/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0065f7bb357ed32f5cada/</guid><description>Dr.\u00a0Simon Bramhall, a British surgeon who branded his initials on patients&amp;rsquo; livers, has been struck off the medical register as of Monday
Summary (Dec. 13) APDr. Simon Bramhall, a British surgeon who branded his initials on patients&amp;rsquo; livers, has been struck off the medical register as of Monday, according to a report by BBC News. According to the U.K. General Medical Council, that means he can no longer work as a doctor in the U.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak reported at Rhode Island hospital after Covid-positive, asymptomatic staff asked to work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</guid><description>A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due
Summary A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due to a staffing shortage. On Saturday, the hospital had two Covid-positive staff members come into work and three on Monday, according to a memo posted on the official Rhode Island state website.</description></item><item><title>CDC warns about rabies linked to bats after 3 Americans die in recent weeks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d944acd56484b74c1e5d86/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 08:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d944acd56484b74c1e5d86/</guid><description>The CDC issued a warning Thursday about the risk of rabies after three Americans &amp;ndash; including a child – died from the disease over a six-week period last year.
Summary It comes after no cases of rabies were reported in the U.S. in 2019 and 2020. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issued a warning Thursday about the risk of rabies after three Americans &amp;ndash; including a child &amp;ndash; died from the disease over a six-week period last year.</description></item><item><title>Nurse goes beyond duty and rescues a hospitalized patient's dog from the shelter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8130ecf5db8e901644e28/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8130ecf5db8e901644e28/</guid><description>It was right after Thanksgiving that registered nurse Jennifer Smith got an early morning phone call from John Burley, one of her favorite patients. He was distraught about his beloved dog, Boomer.
Summary (CNN) It was right after Thanksgiving that registered nurse Jennifer Smith got an early morning phone call from John Burley, one of her favorite patients. He was distraught about his beloved dog, Boomer. &amp;ldquo;I came into work the Monday after Thanksgiving to the phone ringing at 7 a.</description></item></channel></rss>