<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>care on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/care/</link><description>Recent content in care on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 23:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/care/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Toddler dies after being found in vehicle at Tenn. daycare</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62881fb49f1ac20bfdba7179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 23:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62881fb49f1ac20bfdba7179/</guid><description>Police say a 1-year-old child has died after being found in a hot vehicle outside a Tennessee day care center
Highlights Police say a 1-year-old child has died after being found in a hot vehicle outside a Tennessee day care center. The child was pronounced dead at Le Bonheur Children’s Hospital on Thursday afternoon. The daycare center has capacity to care for up to 111 children, news outlets say. News outlets report temperatures reached 91 degrees in Memphis, Tennessee, on Thursday, at 9:30 a.</description></item><item><title>Texas loses appeal over investigation of transgender teen’s family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a77fa0142694bc51b6806/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a77fa0142694bc51b6806/</guid><description>The Texas 3rd Court of Appeals dismissed Republican Attorney General Ken Paxton’s appeal of the temporary order a judge issued last week halting the investigation by the Department of Family and Protective Services into the parents of the 16-year-old girl.
Highlights Court of Appeals rules ruling against ruling on gender-confirming parents&amp;rsquo; rights. Court also throws out order to stop state of Texas law requiring parents to report child sex abuse. The order was issued last week in response to the judge’s decision to halt the order.</description></item><item><title>Ivermectin does not prevent severe COVID-19, study finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621117d3166debb3aa5e613b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 16:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621117d3166debb3aa5e613b/</guid><description>Treatment with the dewormer drug ivermectin failed to prevent patients with mild to moderate COVID-19 from progressing to serious illness, a study published Friday by JAMA Internal Medicine found.
Highlights Treatment with dewormer drug ivermectin failed to prevent patients with mild to moderate COVID-19 progressing to serious illness. 43 of 249 patients, or 17%, who received &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; treatment progressed to severe illness, researchers say. Study compared the safety and effectiveness of the drug to standard care in 480 Malaysian patients.</description></item><item><title>US has suffered more than 1m excess deaths during pandemic, CDC finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ec83d73f565cb456f3193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 22:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ec83d73f565cb456f3193/</guid><description>The latest statistic hints at the breadth of Covid-19’s impact on health in the United States
Highlights There have been more than 1m excess deaths in the US during the pandemic. The deaths are mainly attributable to Covid-19, as well as conditions that may have resulted from delayed medical care and overwhelmed health systems. At least 923,000 Americans have died from confirmed Covid cases, according to the CDC. Other causes of death above the normally expected number have included heart disease, hypertension and Alzheimer’s disease.</description></item><item><title>ThedaCare loses court fight to keep health care staff who resigned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef59c276143456b5f4314e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef59c276143456b5f4314e/</guid><description>A hospital in northeastern Wisconsin has lost a court battle to keep health care staff who want to work elsewhere.
Summary A hospital in northeastern Wisconsin has lost a court battle to keep health care staff who want to work elsewhere. The civil court case between ThedaCare and Ascension Wisconsin comes at a time when health professionals are in great demand across the U.S. Just days before, seven former employees of ThedaCare were to start new jobs at Ascension&amp;rsquo;s St.</description></item><item><title>Nurse goes beyond duty and rescues a hospitalized patient's dog from the shelter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8130ecf5db8e901644e28/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8130ecf5db8e901644e28/</guid><description>It was right after Thanksgiving that registered nurse Jennifer Smith got an early morning phone call from John Burley, one of her favorite patients. He was distraught about his beloved dog, Boomer.
Summary (CNN) It was right after Thanksgiving that registered nurse Jennifer Smith got an early morning phone call from John Burley, one of her favorite patients. He was distraught about his beloved dog, Boomer. &amp;ldquo;I came into work the Monday after Thanksgiving to the phone ringing at 7 a.</description></item></channel></rss>