<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>numbers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/numbers/</link><description>Recent content in numbers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 22:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/numbers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Hero' guard, church deacon among Buffalo shooting victims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62817afc61c4f5d0cb731dda/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 22:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62817afc61c4f5d0cb731dda/</guid><description>The victims of Saturday&amp;rsquo;s racially motivated shooting in Buffalo, New York, include retired police officer Aaron Salter
Highlights Aaron Salter, a community member and security guard, was shot and killed by a white gunman in Buffalo, New York. Salter fired multiple times at the attacker, striking his armor-plated vest at least once. The retired Buffalo police officer was one of 10 people killed in the racially motivated attack. The victims were a cross-section of life in the predominantly Black neighborhood in Buffalo.</description></item><item><title>New federal rule requires serial numbers, background checks for ‘ghost gun’ kits</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254a82e3e45f1f08639f5d8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 22:14:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254a82e3e45f1f08639f5d8/</guid><description>The aim is to rein in privately made firearms without serial numbers. They&amp;rsquo;re increasingly cropping up at crime scenes across the U.S. The new rule requires homemade gun kits to be treated like other guns made and sold in the U
Highlights The Biden administration is expected to come out within days with its long-awaited ghost gun rule. The aim is to rein in privately made firearms without serial numbers. The rule requires homemade gun kits to be treated like other guns made and sold in the U.</description></item><item><title>US children hospitalized with COVID in record numbers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</guid><description>The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers
Summary The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbersSEATTLE &amp;ndash; The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers, and experts lament that most of the youngsters are not vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Monarch population soars 4,900 percent since last year in thrilling 2021 western migration</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7dacc4298ae6769c89769/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7dacc4298ae6769c89769/</guid><description>From 2,000 to 100,000, Western monarch butterflies arrived in California for their 2021 winter migration in huge numbers.
Summary When just 200 Western monarch butterflies arrived in the Pismo Beach Butterfly Grove from their northerly migration last year, park rangers feared the treasured insect would soon be gone forever. It’s expected that the monarch butterfly will be placed on the Endangered Species List soon, due to declines in both western and eastern monarch butterfly numbers.</description></item></channel></rss>