<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>demand on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/demand/</link><description>Recent content in demand on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/demand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. seeks new lithium sources as demand for clean energy grows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62436874c68b093770803a5d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62436874c68b093770803a5d/</guid><description>The element is critical to the development of lithium-ion batteries, which are rechargeable batteries seen as critical to reducing the carbon emissions created by cars and other forms of transportation.
Highlights The U.S. will need far more lithium to achieve its clean energy goals. The element is critical to development of rechargeable lithium-ion batteries that are seen as key to reducing climate-changing carbon emissions created by cars and other forms of transportation.</description></item><item><title>Jamaicans shun UK royal visit, demand slavery reparations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62391d738d706f5e07e4a43d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62391d738d706f5e07e4a43d/</guid><description>SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — Dozens of well-known leaders in Jamaica including professors and politicians are demanding an apology and slavery reparations as the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge prepare for a trip to the former British colony.
Highlights Prince William and his wife Catherine are embarking on a tour to Central America and the Caribbean, even as some countries in the region mull cutting ties to the British monarchy.</description></item><item><title>Protesters enter southern Alberta school, demand end of mask rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</guid><description>School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday where the gathering called for an end to mask mandates.
Highlights School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday. The gathering called for an end to mask mandates. The protest was quickly de-escalated by school officials and protestors were peacefully escorted out of the building.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item></channel></rss>