<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>demand on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/demand/</link><description>Recent content in demand on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/demand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protesters enter southern Alberta school, demand end of mask rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</guid><description>School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday where the gathering called for an end to mask mandates.
Highlights School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday. The gathering called for an end to mask mandates. The protest was quickly de-escalated by school officials and protestors were peacefully escorted out of the building.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item></channel></rss>