<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>girls on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/girls/</link><description>Recent content in girls on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 09:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/girls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kentucky governor vetoes transgender girls sports ban</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eab435db537cde8b1d520/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 09:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eab435db537cde8b1d520/</guid><description>FRANKFORT, Ky. (AP) — Kentucky&amp;rsquo;s Democratic governor on Wednesday vetoed a bill that&amp;hellip;
Highlights Gov. Andy Beshear said the Republican-backed measure “most likely” violates the U.S. Constitution&amp;rsquo;s equal protection rights. The state&amp;rsquo;s GOP-dominated legislature will have a chance to override the veto when lawmakers reconvene April 13 for the last two days of this year&amp;rsquo;s session. The bill sparked emotional debate at times but cleared both chambers with support from large majorities.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana man is freed after new evidence uncovered in 1977 attempted rape conviction</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ba74d119ce1ce4a91404a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 13:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ba74d119ce1ce4a91404a/</guid><description>Vincent Simmons​ is a free man after decades in prison.
Highlights Vincent Simmons was convicted of attempted aggravated rape of twin sisters in 1977. He has been trying for years to get a new trial. A judge says he will not retry him, saying the time &amp;ldquo;has been overcome&amp;rdquo; by new evidence. Simmons&amp;rsquo; twin sisters, now 59, say they are the victims and that he is guilty. The girls&amp;rsquo; testimony to police initially told police they didn&amp;rsquo;t know who he was and that &amp;ldquo;all Black people look alike&amp;rdquo; and even used the N-word, defense lawyer says.</description></item></channel></rss>