<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>districts on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/districts/</link><description>Recent content in districts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 02:53:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/districts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beijing races to contain 'urgent and grim' Covid outbreak as Shanghai lockdown continues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62660ce5ce46c457e8275cd1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 02:53:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62660ce5ce46c457e8275cd1/</guid><description>Beijing is racing to track a Covid-19 outbreak that may have been spreading in the capital for a week, city authorities said over the weekend, raising the prospect more stringent restrictions could soon be implemented in line with other Chinese cities.
Highlights Beijing is racing to track a Covid-19 outbreak that may have been spreading in the capital for a week. The capital recorded 19 new local cases on Sunday, bringing the total in the city since April 22 to 60.</description></item><item><title>Florida governor: school districts that defied no-mask mandate to lose $200m</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62123e96962cd6013a8137e4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 13:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62123e96962cd6013a8137e4/</guid><description>Ron DeSantis is backing a bill that would strip education funding from Democratic counties that retained Covid precautions
Highlights Florida governor backs controversial plan to strip $200m in education funding from Democratic counties that defied his executive order banning mask mandates in schools. DeSantis, who is widely seen as a leading heir to Donald Trump in the Republican party, plans to send the money instead to mostly Republican counties that supported him.</description></item></channel></rss>