<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>raises on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/raises/</link><description>Recent content in raises on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 13:36:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/raises/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GoFundMe effort in honor of Uvalde couple raises more than $2.6 million in four days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294c821b0c124704150254f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 13:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294c821b0c124704150254f/</guid><description>A GoFundMe campaign started in honor of Irma Garcia, one of the two teachers killed in the Texas school shooting, and her husband, Joe, who died Thursday, has
Highlights A GoFundMe campaign started in honor of Irma Garcia, one of the two teachers killed in the Texas school shooting, and her husband, Joe, who died Thursday, has raised more than $2.6 million in just four days. Irma Garcia was a fourth grade teacher who had been teaching at Robb Elementary in Uvalde for 23 years.</description></item><item><title>China says Taiwan is 'not Ukraine' as island raises alert level</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62165ddf75705c798f8da656/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62165ddf75705c798f8da656/</guid><description>Taiwan is &amp;quot;not Ukraine&amp;quot; and has always been an inalienable part of China, China&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry said on Wednesday, as Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen called for the island to beef up vigilance.
Highlights Taiwan is &amp;ldquo;not Ukraine&amp;rdquo; and has always been an inalienable part of China, China&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry says. Comments come as Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen calls for the island to beef up vigilance on military activities in response to the crisis.</description></item></channel></rss>