<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lab on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lab/</link><description>Recent content in lab on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>COVID-19 Testing Lab Incorrectly Tells 400 People They Tested Negative</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8f40b03f5ec8a065b6b9a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8f40b03f5ec8a065b6b9a/</guid><description>St. Vincent&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Sydney said the mistake appeared to be due to &amp;quot;human error.&amp;quot; The impacted people were contacted immediately, it said.
Summary A testing lab in Sydney wrongly told 400 people that they had tested negative for COVID-19. St. Vincent&amp;rsquo;s Hospital published a statement on Sunday saying its pathology service, named SydPath, released the incorrect results due to a &amp;ldquo;human error.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;SydPath last night incorrectly messaged more than 400 people, advising them they had tested negative to COVID,&amp;rdquo; the lab said.</description></item><item><title>Polish opposition senator hacked with spyware Pegasus by the current ruling party during the parliamentary elections</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5ee9f45555e41135a749a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5ee9f45555e41135a749a/</guid><description>WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Polish Sen. Krzysztof Brejza’s mobile phone was hacked with sophisticated spyware nearly three dozen times in 2019 when he was running the opposition&amp;rsquo;s campaign against the right-wing populist government in parliamentary elections, an internet watchdog found.
Summary (AP Photo) Polish Senator Krzysztof Brejza on the night of parliamentary elections on Oct. 13, 2019. The ruling party won a slim majority and Brejza is convinced that the hacking of his phone gave it an unfair advantage.</description></item></channel></rss>