<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>theft on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/theft/</link><description>Recent content in theft on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 04:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/theft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The top elected official in Texas’ smallest county has been charged with cattle theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289b82c48c13617ffcd2c32/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 04:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289b82c48c13617ffcd2c32/</guid><description>Loving County Judge Skeet Jones, the scion of a powerful ranching family, was arrested after a yearlong investigation that is ongoing, authorities said.
Highlights Judge Skeet Jones, 71, is facing three felony counts of livestock theft and one count of engaging in criminal activity. He is accused of gathering up and selling stray cattle in Loving County, Texas. The county has no school, no church, no grocery store and no bank, population 57 as of the last U.</description></item><item><title>Meijer theft suspect was a white man in his 30s. Police detained 60-year-old Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</guid><description>The incident is yet another example, a lawsuit says, of a Black person being confronted by law enforcement merely for going about his daily life.
Highlights Police were looking for a shoplifter in a West Chester Meijer in 2021. Police detained a 60-year-old Black man, Eric Lindsay, who was wearing an orange down coat and a brown-and-tan scarf. Lindsay, a business professional, was questioned for several minutes in an aisle as other shoppers looked on.</description></item><item><title>Thieves Steal Gallery Owner’s Multimillion-Dollar NFT Collection: 'All my apes gone'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7ad676d0d55e9b2c21d31/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 03:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7ad676d0d55e9b2c21d31/</guid><description>Dealer Ross Kramer said thieves had stolen his $2.2 million NFT collection.
Summary This just sold please help me,” wrote gallery owner Todd Kramer, of New York’s Ross + Kramer Gallery, in a since-deleted tweet posted on December 30. A phishing scam had drained his Ethereum wallet of 15 NFTs valued at a total of $2.2 million, including four apes from the “Bored Ape Yacht Club” collection. With the help of the buyers and the NFT platform OpenSea, Kramer was able to get back several of his NFTs.</description></item></channel></rss>