<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shot on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shot/</link><description>Recent content in shot on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mother charged after Florida toddler fatally shoots father</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f23d4a496fbce80d7a5bd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f23d4a496fbce80d7a5bd/</guid><description>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — A 2-year old boy fatally shot his father in an accident after finding a gun, and the boy&amp;rsquo;s mother is now facing criminal charges, authorities in Florida said Monday. Reggie Mabry, 26, was fatally shot late last month while he was playing a video game.
Highlights Reggie Mabry, 26, was fatally shot late last month while he was playing a video game. The gun was fired by his 2-year-old son in the home he shared with his wife and their three children.</description></item><item><title>Multiple People Injured in Shooting at Wisconsin Cemetery During Funeral</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299825f123574c57d4870c3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299825f123574c57d4870c3/</guid><description>A shooting at a cemetery south of Milwaukee on Thursday afternoon resulted in multiple victims, police said.
Highlights Police say multiple shots were fired at Graceland Cemetery in Racine, about 30 miles (48 kilometers) south of Milwaukee. The shooting occurred at the interment for Da’Shontay L. King Sr. who was fatally shot by Racine police May 20, his sister says. Residents say they heard 20 to 30 shots fired at the cemetery.</description></item><item><title>6 people shot in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, on Saturday night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629433fb1e04b2a48468459b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629433fb1e04b2a48468459b/</guid><description>Six people were shot, and two of them suffered life-threatening injuries, following an altercation between two groups of people in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, on Saturday night, police said.
Highlights Police: &amp;ldquo;Multiple parties exchanging gunfire and numerous people fleeing the area&amp;rdquo; Four are expected to survive while two have life-threatening injuries, police say. Most of those shot were teenagers or in their early 20s, police Sgt. Jeremy Eames says. Investigators believe the shooting was not gang-related, police chief Celeste Murphy says.</description></item><item><title>Texas school district locked down on reports of shooter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d57b739d23392644d9c5e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 22:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d57b739d23392644d9c5e/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — An 18-year-old gunman opened fire Tuesday at a Texas elementary&amp;hellip;
Highlights An 18-year-old gunman opened fire Tuesday at a Texas elementary school, killing 14 children, one teacher and injuring others. It was the deadliest shooting at a U.S. grade school since the shocking attack in Sandy Hook, Connecticut, almost a decade ago. The gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde with a handgun and possibly a rifle, Abbott says.</description></item><item><title>45-year-old Yan Zhiwen shot to death delivering food on scooter in Forest Hills, Queens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f6bce45bb712a5072ec94/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 05:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f6bce45bb712a5072ec94/</guid><description>It happened hours after Mayor Adams met with NYPD officials to address surging crime.
Highlights Yan Zhiwen, a food delivery worker, was shot and killed while on his scooter Saturday night in Queens. It happened near 108th Street and 67th Drive in Forest Hills at around 9:30 p.m. It happened hours after Mayor Eric Adams met with NYPD officials to address surging crime. Police are asking for help finding the shooter, who they say drove off in a light gray or tan Lexus.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting suspect has been arrested, law enforcement officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</guid><description>Suspected Brooklyn subway shooter Frank James was arrested by patrol officers in the East Village in New York City on Wednesday, three law enforcement officials tell CNN.
Highlights Images captured by people at the scene of the shooting show chaos and chaos. People can be heard rushing off the train after it pulled into the 36th Street subway station. The bullet hit one man in the back of his knee and came out the other side, he says.</description></item><item><title>'We're not finding soldiers, just innocent people': The horror of Russian occupation revealed in Borodianka</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d300e5c25d567ed6164bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 06:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d300e5c25d567ed6164bc/</guid><description>Oksana Kostychenko walks down a narrow pathway, leading to her back garden in Borodianka. The flower beds on one side are surprisingly well arranged, contrasting with the wanton destruction all around.
Highlights Body of a man found face-down with a bag over his head and hands tied behind his back. Authorities on site say all indications show he was another civilian casualty of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s war. Russian forces occupied Borodianka, Kyiv, for more than a month, razed to ground by long-range attacks.</description></item><item><title>War in Ukraine: Russian helicopter shot down by missile in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223c41f88bf8831307278f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 20:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223c41f88bf8831307278f9/</guid><description>The video, shared by Ukrainian armed forces, shows the helicopter being hit by a missile.
Highlights &amp;lsquo;Kherson is Ukraine&amp;rsquo;: Protests in city taken by Russia. Video, shared by Ukrainian armed forces, shows helicopter being hit by missile. Helicopter hit by a missile in video shared by Ukraine armed forces. Protests take place in the city of Kherson, which has been seized by Russia since 2008. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>DA clears deputy who shot and killed homeless Black man in San Clemente</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209576aad8df3fdf4c17013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209576aad8df3fdf4c17013/</guid><description>DA says Deputy Eduardo Duran was justified in shooting and killing Kurt Andreas Reinhold. Reinhold, 42, was shot and killed in San Clemente, Orange County, in September 2020. DA: Deputies had no reason to
Highlights DA’s Office says Deputy Eduardo Duran was justified in shooting and killing Kurt Andreas Reinhold. Reinhold, 42, was stopped by deputies on suspicion of jaywalking in San Clemente, Orange County. He was struck twice in his upper torso in the Sept.</description></item><item><title>Man was shot by police after officer mistook his gun for a Taser, police in Florida say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 03:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</guid><description>A police officer in Florida shot a man after mistaking his gun for a Taser, an initial review of the case suggests, police said in a statement.
Highlights Michael Ortiz is paralyzed and requires round-the-clock care, the complaint alleges. The Hollywood Police Department says the officer mistakenly fired a gun instead of a Taser. Ortiz was naked and handcuffed when police shot him in the back, his attorney says. Ortiz &amp;ldquo;was having a mental health crisis&amp;rdquo; on the day of the shooting after losing his dog, the lawyer says.</description></item><item><title>Bus driver shot in the head while transporting kids in north Minneapolis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</guid><description>Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis.
Highlights Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot in the head Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis. Police say they have not apprehended any suspects. Three children younger than 10 were on board the bus at the time of the shooting. Minneapolis Public Schools released a statement in response to the school bus shooting as well as a separate shooting in which a student was shot, which read, in part: “… We recognize the deep impact this has on our students, staff and families.</description></item><item><title>George Floyd’s 4-year-old niece shot after someone fired several shots into Houston apartment, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</guid><description>A 4-year-old girl was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.
Summary The shooting happened on Houston&amp;rsquo;s southside when someone fire multiple shots into the apartmentHOUSTON – George Floyd’s four-year-old niece was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.</description></item><item><title>Illinois police officer pleaded for her life before she was fatally shot with her own gun, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5cec2ff5130dff294129b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5cec2ff5130dff294129b/</guid><description>Bradley Police Sgt. Marlene Rittmanic desperately pleaded for her life before she was fatally shot with her own gun in a tragic shooting at a northern Illinois hotel last week, according to prosecutors.
Summary A police officer in Bradley, Illinois, pleaded for her life before she was fatally shot with her own gun at a hotel last week, prosecutors said. Sullivan pointed the gun and shot Bailey in the head and then turned the gun on Rittmanic and shot her as she tried to run away, Rowe alleged.</description></item><item><title>Denver gunman who killed five in shooting rampage knew victims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdad6d6451d9c95470d98e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdad6d6451d9c95470d98e/</guid><description>Lyndon James McLeod, 47, who was killed at scene was ‘on radar of law enforcement’, say Denver police
Summary Denver police said that Lyndon James McLeod, 47, who was also killed in the deadly rampage on Monday night, knew most of the victims and was “on the radar of law enforcement”. A man was then shot and killed at a home near Cheesman Park, also in Denver. Shortly before 6pm, Lakewood police received a report of shots fired at the Lucky 13 tattoo shop.</description></item></channel></rss>