<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>waste on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/waste/</link><description>Recent content in waste on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:09:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/waste/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. to phase out single-use plastic on public lands, national parks by 2032</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a12c07580efa5cde5ba9ba/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a12c07580efa5cde5ba9ba/</guid><description>The U.S. Interior Department said on Wednesday it will phase out single-use plastic products on public lands by 2032, including in national parks, in a move aimed at tackling a major source of U.S. plastic waste as recycling efforts falter.
Highlights Interior Department to phase out single-use plastic products on public lands by 2032. Move aimed at tackling major source of U.S. plastic waste as recycling efforts falter. Announcement comes as part of a broader package of announcements from Biden administration to recognize World Ocean Day.</description></item><item><title>The U.S. has discarded over 82 million Covid vaccine doses, led by CVS and Walmart</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f529e064b5290d16a05cf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 13:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f529e064b5290d16a05cf/</guid><description>Covid vaccine providers discarded 82.1 million doses in the U.S. from December 2020 through mid-May — just over 11 percent of all doses distributed.
Highlights Pharmacies, states, U.S. territories and federal agencies discarded 82.1 million Covid vaccine doses from December 2020 through mid-May. Two retail pharmacy chains, CVS and Walmart, were responsible for over a quarter of the doses thrown away in the United States in that time period. Five other pharmacies or dialysis centers — Health Mart, DaVita, Rite Aid, Publix and Costco — wasted fewer overall doses, but a higher share of doses than any other pharmacy or state.</description></item><item><title>U.S. plastic recycling rate drops to close to 5% - report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273b10be042fe9f5187ce4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 11:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273b10be042fe9f5187ce4e/</guid><description>The rate of plastic waste recycling in the United States fell to between 5%-6% in 2021 as some countries stopped accepting U.S. waste exports and as plastic waste generation surged to new highs, according to a report released on Wednesday.
Highlights Report: U.S. plastic waste recycling rate fell to between 5-6% in 2021. Decline coincides with a sharp drop in plastic waste exports, which had counted as recycled plastic. China and Turkey have since implemented plastic import bans and other countries set plastic waste contamination limits.</description></item><item><title>Ca Attorney General subpoenas Exxon Mobil over global plastic waste</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c54df2ad9f0d9265eb2ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 21:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c54df2ad9f0d9265eb2ee/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California&amp;rsquo;s attorney general on Thursday subpoenaed ExxonMobil as part of what he called a first-of-its-kind broader investigation into the petroleum industry for its alleged role in causing a global plastic pollution crisis, allegations that the company called meritless.
Highlights California Attorney General Rob Bonta said ExxonMobil was subpoenaed as a major source of global plastics pollution. ExxonMobil said it is the first to have “commercial-scale advanced recycling technology” at a major facility to convert used plastic into material that can be used to make new plastic.</description></item></channel></rss>