<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>continue on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/continue/</link><description>Recent content in continue on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:18:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/continue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boris Johnson announces the end of Covid restrictions in England | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62150c994afe8a02703164b7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:18:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62150c994afe8a02703164b7/</guid><description>UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson has announced plans to end all legal coronavirus restrictions in England and start &amp;quot;living with Covid.&amp;quot;
Highlights UK PM Boris Johnson announces plans to end legal Covid-19 restrictions in England. Johnson hails the end of restrictions as a ‘moment of pride for our nation and a source of hope for all that we can achieve in the years to come’ Queen Elizabeth II has tested positive for the virus.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan president tells troops to 'shoot to kill without warning' as he vows to 'completely eliminate' protesters and gives 'special thanks' to Putin for his help</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da09976841fb5aefc2beaa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da09976841fb5aefc2beaa/</guid><description>Security forces appeared to be in control of the streets of Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s main city Almaty on Friday morning and the president claimed constitutional order had mostly been restored.
Summary Fresh gunshots could be heard in the morning near the city&amp;rsquo;s central square, where troops and protesters had battled through much of the previous day. Kazakh service members stand guard in a square following the protests triggered by fuel price increase in central Almaty, Kazakhstan January 7, 2022.</description></item></channel></rss>