<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shanghai on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shanghai/</link><description>Recent content in shanghai on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 10:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shanghai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shanghai: Green fences baffle locked down residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62666d02a8b4375e1c418ff5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62666d02a8b4375e1c418ff5/</guid><description>Two-metre barriers have appeared all over the city as officials battle to contain a Covid outbreak.
Highlights Two-metre barriers have appeared all over the city as officials battle to contain a Covid outbreak. &amp;ldquo;There is a long corridor in our compound, and within the long corridor they put up another green fence three days ago,&amp;rdquo; he said on the phone. &amp;ldquo;No one told us the reason it was installed,&amp;rdquo; he added of the fence being put up in the corridor.</description></item><item><title>Beijing races to contain 'urgent and grim' Covid outbreak as Shanghai lockdown continues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62660ce5ce46c457e8275cd1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 02:53:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62660ce5ce46c457e8275cd1/</guid><description>Beijing is racing to track a Covid-19 outbreak that may have been spreading in the capital for a week, city authorities said over the weekend, raising the prospect more stringent restrictions could soon be implemented in line with other Chinese cities.
Highlights Beijing is racing to track a Covid-19 outbreak that may have been spreading in the capital for a week. The capital recorded 19 new local cases on Sunday, bringing the total in the city since April 22 to 60.</description></item><item><title>Tesla CEO Elon Musk says he has Covid again</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242b1c8e17290548a4f1097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 07:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242b1c8e17290548a4f1097/</guid><description>Tesla CEO Elon Musk said he has Covid again, following an earlier bout in November 2020.
Highlights SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk tested positive for Covid-19 on Monday. He has a history of under-estimating the novel coronavirus and balking at health officials. The announcement comes after Tesla&amp;rsquo;s factory in Shanghai faced Covid restrictions that reportedly require it to suspend production for four days until around April 1. Tesla also suspended production in Shanghai for two days earlier in March after officials implemented Covid health orders.</description></item><item><title>China shuts down city of 17.5m people in bid to halt Covid outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ea45a8a6805f7263b5da3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ea45a8a6805f7263b5da3/</guid><description>Authorities adopt a zero tolerance policy in Shenzhen, imposing a lockdown and testing every resident three times
Highlights Everyone in Shenzhen, a finance and technology centre that abuts Hong Kong, will undergo three rounds of testing. The mainland government has reported 1,938 new cases, more than triple Saturday’s total. About three-quarters, or 1,412 cases, were in Jilin province in the north-east. China has reported a total of 4,636 deaths on the mainland out of 115,466 confirmed cases since the pandemic started.</description></item><item><title>Chinese dialects in decline as government enforces Mandarin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e568792ec87815cb2fd535/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e568792ec87815cb2fd535/</guid><description>Linguists concerned as regional languages dwindle amid push to strengthen uniform national identity
Summary When he tried to speak to his cousin’s children in the local dialect, Qi was surprised. The decline in local dialects among the younger generation has become more apparent in recent years as China’s president, Xi Jinping, has sought to strengthen a uniform Chinese identity. But the popularisation of a standard national language is often at the expense of regional languages, including dialects of the Han majority and ethnic languages such as Mongolian and Uyghur.</description></item></channel></rss>