<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>assets on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/assets/</link><description>Recent content in assets on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:17:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/assets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shell to exit joint ventures with Gazprom and pull out of Nord Stream 2</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e46ed2e1ac0f8f1fb805a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e46ed2e1ac0f8f1fb805a/</guid><description>British oil major to exit joint ventures with Gazprom after BP pledged to sell its 20% Rosneft stake
Highlights Shell said it would ‘exit its joint ventures with Gazprom and related entities’, which are worth about $3bn. The oil company said its staff in Ukraine and other countries have been working together to manage the company’s response to the crisis locally. Shell will also end its involvement in the Nord Stream 2 pipeline project, in which it holds a 10% stake worth $1bn.</description></item><item><title>U.S. plans to cut ties with targeted Russian banks if Ukraine is invaded - sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213bae4ea9ae74210f6c6e4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213bae4ea9ae74210f6c6e4/</guid><description>President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has prepared an initial package of sanctions against Russia that includes barring U.S. financial institutions from processing transactions for major Russian banks, three people familiar with the matter said.
Highlights President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration has prepared an initial package of sanctions against Russia that includes barring U.S. financial institutions from processing transactions for major Russian banks, three people familiar with the matter said. The measures aim to hurt the Russian economy by cutting the &amp;ldquo;correspondent&amp;rdquo; banking relationships between targeted targeted Russian banks and American banks that enable international payments.</description></item><item><title>Canadian authorities freeze financial assets for those involved in ongoing protests in Ottawa | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213ac8b47be889ab6ea7faa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213ac8b47be889ab6ea7faa/</guid><description>A weeks-long blockade in the Canadian capital has led to almost 200 arrests and prolonged suffering for businesses caught in the middle of protests against Covid-19 mandates.
Highlights Canadian authorities freeze the finances associated with certain individuals and companies believed to be involved in the ongoing protests in Ottawa. A weeks-long blockade in the Canadian capital has led to almost 200 arrests and prolonged suffering for businesses caught in the middle of protests against Covid-19 mandates.</description></item></channel></rss>