<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kills on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kills/</link><description>Recent content in kills on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:09:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Armed female bystander kills man firing at party in West Virginia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62938ca685f11d9d4d61462b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62938ca685f11d9d4d61462b/</guid><description>A woman at a birthday party drew her pistol and left the gunman with multiple wounds, police say.
Highlights A woman at a birthday party drew her pistol and left the gunman with multiple wounds, police say. &amp;ldquo;Instead of running from the threat she engaged with the threat and saved several lives,&amp;rdquo; police say. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s just a member of the community who was carrying her weapon lawfully,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;And instead of running&amp;hellip; she engaged&amp;hellip; in the threat,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description></item><item><title>Sheriff: Camel attacks, kills 2 at Tenn. petting zoo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c8fc7961edbc7b1a27ed0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 12:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c8fc7961edbc7b1a27ed0/</guid><description>According to a post on the sheriff’s office’s Facebook page, they received a call of a loose camel near Shirley Farms on South Bluff Road around 4:44 p.m. on Thursday, March 10.
Highlights A camel attacked and killed two people at a petting zoo, according to the Obion County Sheriff’s Office. Bobby Matheny, 42, and Tommy Gunn, 67, were pronounced dead at the scene. Matheny was a custodian at Lake County High School for six years.</description></item><item><title>Montana Gov. Gianforte hunts, kills National Park Service-tracked mountain lion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fdd391aa9b11f610f0c4c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fdd391aa9b11f610f0c4c/</guid><description>Montana Gov.
Highlights Montana Gov. Greg Gianforte shot and killed a mountain lion that was being tracked by the National Park Service. Federal law prohibits hunting and discharging of firearms in Yellowstone National Park. The hunt was legal, Montana Fish, Wildlife &amp;amp; Parks spokesperson Greg Lemon says. In 2021, he said he &amp;ldquo;made a mistake&amp;rdquo; after he killed a Montana black wolf that was also tagged in Yellowstone before he completed the required state certification.</description></item></channel></rss>