<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>threatens on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threatens/</link><description>Recent content in threatens on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:18:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threatens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Musk threatens to walk away from Twitter deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ed188f0b9e51e26078786/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ed188f0b9e51e26078786/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — Elon Musk is threatening to walk away from his $44 billion bid to buy Twitter, accusing the company of refusing to give him information about its spam bot and fake accounts .
Highlights Elon Musk is threatening to end his $44 billion agreement to buy Twitter. Lawyers for the Tesla and SpaceX CEO made the threat in a letter to Twitter dated Monday, June 6, 2022 that the social platform included in a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission.</description></item><item><title>Ohio village scraps plan with affordable housing after Dave Chappelle threatens to pull his businesses</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204d6da056d4f6d744efc22/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204d6da056d4f6d744efc22/</guid><description>Yellow Springs, Ohio, failed to approve a zoning ordinance that included dozens of affordable housing units after opposition from comedian Dave Chappelle.
Highlights Yellow Springs, Ohio, failed to approve a zoning ordinance that included dozens of affordable housing units. Comedian Dave Chappelle called the Village Council &amp;ldquo;clowns&amp;rdquo; and threatened that his business ventures would be &amp;ldquo;off the table&amp;rdquo; The vote deadlocked at 2-2, ensuring that the new housing development cannot proceed.</description></item></channel></rss>