<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>middle on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/middle/</link><description>Recent content in middle on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 05:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/middle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gun stolen during 1970s found in middle school student's backpack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289c59b8f2f57f81f86ca12/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 05:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289c59b8f2f57f81f86ca12/</guid><description>BERKELEY COUNTY, S. C. (WCIV) — A handgun stolen from a state trooper during the 1970s was recently found in a middle school student’s backpack. Caption: A gun that was stolen from an Alaskan state trooper during the 1970s has been found in the backpack of a middle school student in South Carolina. (WCIV) Now, Berkeley County Sheriff Duane Lewis said he is determined to find out how the gun traveled 4,600 miles from South Carolina to Alaska.</description></item><item><title>Teen arrested after mother noticed son had gun at Texas school drop-off</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d7cecd1b05fa739cedfe4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d7cecd1b05fa739cedfe4/</guid><description>A teenager was arrested after police said his own mother noticed he had a gun at a school drop-off.
Highlights A mother was dropping off her 15-year-old son at O.L. Slaton Middle School around 9 a.m. when she noticed the firearm. The teen never made it inside the building, and he ran from the school. The Lubbock Police Department responded to the area along with several other agencies in an attempt to find him.</description></item><item><title>Israel settler opens fire at Palestine primary school in West Bank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230747b0743f306954a0180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 11:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230747b0743f306954a0180/</guid><description>An armed Israeli Jewish settler opened gunfire at a Palestinian girls&amp;rsquo; primary school in the occupied West Bank city of Bethlehem. Hundreds of students were evacuated and classes were cancelled following the attack. Violence and vandalism by Israeli settlers is commonplace in the
Highlights An armed Israeli Jewish settler opened gunfire at a Palestinian girls&amp;rsquo; primary school in the occupied West Bank city of Bethlehem. Hundreds of students were evacuated and classes were cancelled in the aftermath of the attack.</description></item></channel></rss>