<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lost on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lost/</link><description>Recent content in lost on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 04:16:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Non-verbal teen lost in L.A. area woods found after clinking rocks together, alerting rescuers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d14026dac76a05bbb067f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 04:16:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d14026dac76a05bbb067f/</guid><description>A non-verbal teen who was lost in a heavily wooded area near Los Angeles was after rescuers followed the sound made by his favorite objects — rocks.
Highlights The 16-year-old was found in a canyon near Los Angeles after he ran off into trees. Rescuers heard him clinking rocks as he threw them together. He was treated by paramedics and released to his family, authorities said. The sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department said it was &amp;ldquo;thrilled this incident had a happy ending,&amp;rdquo; adding: &amp;ldquo;Our Department was thrilled this incident has a good ending&amp;rdquo; The boy, 16, was found &amp;ldquo;sitting under an oak tree,&amp;rdquo; a sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputy said at a news conference in Los Angeles County, California, said he was &amp;ldquo;lucky&amp;rdquo; to find him after six hours of searching for him.</description></item><item><title>Mt. Everest's highest glacier lost 2,000 years worth of ice since the 1990s</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62049e916292795fa96f27cf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62049e916292795fa96f27cf/</guid><description>Even the world&amp;rsquo;s tallest mountain is not safe from climate change.
Highlights Scientists found that the South Col Glacier is losing ice 80 times faster than it took for ice to accumulate on the glacier&amp;rsquo;s surface. The glacier is currently losing several decades worth of ice accumulation every year. The melt could have serious impacts on the mountain, and those who live near it. Future research must focus on how widely these melting trends apply to other glaciers at the top of the world, the researchers concluded.</description></item><item><title>California redwood forest returned to native tribal group</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f08114de0cf40e72beb7a0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 23:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f08114de0cf40e72beb7a0/</guid><description>A conservation group is turning over a historic redwood grove on the Northern California coast to descendants of the original Native American inhabitants
Summary Save the Redwoods League planned to announce Tuesday that it is transferring more than 500 acres (202 hectares) on the Lost Coast to the InterTribal Sinkyone Wilderness Council. The league first worked with the Sinkyone council when it transferred a 164-acre (66-hectare) plot nearby to the group in 2012.</description></item></channel></rss>