<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>targets on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/targets/</link><description>Recent content in targets on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 05:10:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/targets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oklahoma gunman was targeting his surgeon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629997c0006d6b0a8585d073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 05:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629997c0006d6b0a8585d073/</guid><description>Police say the man blamed the doctor for his back pain and had purchased a rifle only hours earlier.
Highlights Police say the man blamed the doctor for his back pain and had purchased a rifle only hours earlier. &amp;ldquo;We are supposed to be the ones that are caring for others during tragedies like this,&amp;rdquo; says the doctor. &amp;ldquo;All of my colleagues went into medicine to help people,&amp;rdquo; he says. The man had purchased the rifle just hours earlier, police say.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: No Russia regime change plans, says Blinken</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62408debffa723f107fcddc3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 16:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62408debffa723f107fcddc3/</guid><description>The US secretary of state spoke after President Biden said Vladimir Putin should not remain in power.
Highlights Lviv was one of several targets in the west to be struck despite Russia saying it would focus on the east. In Ukraine itself, the western city of Lviv came under heavy rocket fire on Saturday. The western city had been spared the worst of the fighting, but was hit by heavy fire.</description></item><item><title>U.S. targets Abramovich plane, 99 others over Russia export violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623601c7d52d8c7bf2d0f4b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 16:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623601c7d52d8c7bf2d0f4b6/</guid><description>The U.S. Commerce Department on Friday moved to effectively ground 100 airplanes that have recently flown to Russia and are believed to violate U.S. export controls, including a plane used by Russian businessman Roman Abramovich.
Highlights The U.S. Commerce Department on Friday moved to effectively ground 100 airplanes that have recently flown to Russia. The list includes 99 Boeing airplanes operated by Russian passenger and cargo carriers including Aeroflot, AirBridge Cargo, Utair, Nordwind, Azur Air and Aviastar-TU.</description></item></channel></rss>