<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tijuana on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tijuana/</link><description>Recent content in tijuana on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 18:17:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tijuana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Big cross-border tunnel found linking Tijuana, San Diego</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283e68e78436a3660084f0c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 18:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283e68e78436a3660084f0c/</guid><description>SAN DIEGO (AP) — U.S. authorities on Monday announced the discovery of a major drug smuggling tunnel — running about the length of a six football fields — from Mexico to a warehouse in an industrial area in the U.S.
Highlights Authorities announced Monday, May 16, 2022, the discovery of the underground smuggling tunnel on Mexico&amp;rsquo;s border, running the length of a football field on U.S. soil to a warehouse in an industrial area.</description></item><item><title>US allows Ukrainians fleeing war into the country through Mexico</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62343f956f77017bc65592e1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62343f956f77017bc65592e1/</guid><description>Mexican official says at least 310 Ukrainians have reached the northern border city of Tijuana by air this month.
Highlights Mexican official says at least 310 Ukrainians have reached the northern border city of Tijuana by air this month. The US-Mexico border has been closed to most asylum seekers under a pandemic-era policy known as Title 42. A US citizen who travelled to Ukraine to retrieve her cousin and her cousin’s child got them into the US after a trek that took them through Poland, Croatia, Hungary, Amsterdam, Mexico City and then Tijuana.</description></item><item><title>Mexican journalist who told president she feared for her life shot dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efd85c1236c67fb3adec2e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 11:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efd85c1236c67fb3adec2e/</guid><description>Journalist Lourdes Maldonado López was killed in the Mexican border city of Tijuana on Sunday, days after news photographer Margarito Martínez was gunned down at his home there.
Summary Journalist Lourdes Maldonado López was killed in the Mexican border city of Tijuana on Sunday, days after news photographer Margarito Martínez was gunned down at his home there. According to local news reports, Maldonado was found dead of one gunshot inside a car outside her home.</description></item></channel></rss>