<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>killed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/killed/</link><description>Recent content in killed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 14:13:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/killed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US hunter fined after trophy photo proves he shot sheep in Canada | Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235e4d90e454bb5cd8fbf05/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 14:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235e4d90e454bb5cd8fbf05/</guid><description>Donald Lee claimed he killed a Fannin bighorn sheep in Alaska but an online sleuth and Yukon conservation officers proved he didn’t
Highlights Donald Lee claimed he killed a bighorn sheep in Alaska but it was in Canada, not the U.S. He was fined C$8,500 and banned from hunting in Canada for five years. He posted pictures of the scene in the Yukon on social media, but officers found the sheep had been killed in Canada.</description></item><item><title>Tiananmen Square protester killed in his New York law office</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230670a0bf8bc2bbd6ae4c8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230670a0bf8bc2bbd6ae4c8/</guid><description>Police say a dissident legal scholar who was jailed for two years in China after participating in the 1989 Tiananmen Square pro-democracy movement has been killed in his law firm’s office in New York
Highlights Li Jinjin, 66, was stabbed to death in the city where he had long worked as an immigration lawyer. Xiaoning Zhang, 25, was taken into custody and faces a murder charge. Friend of Li says killing might have stemmed from Li&amp;rsquo;s refusal to take Zhang on as a client.</description></item><item><title>Chechen general Magomed Tushayev, the president’s right-hand man, killed near Kiev</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aec7f937630f9e06c606d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aec7f937630f9e06c606d/</guid><description>Magomed Tushayev was in charge of the so-called Kadyrov guard in Chechnya. He was known as one of the Lords of war and his loss is a severe blow to the Chechen contingent that was
Highlights Tushyen is one of the most elite military units in the world. He was known as one of those who lost his life in the Ukraine. The loss of his troops is a blow to his reputation as a leader in the country&amp;rsquo;s armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Parents of worker killed in tornado that hit Amazon facility are suing the company for wrongful death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</guid><description>The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.
Summary (CNN) The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.</description></item><item><title>Hunters kill 20 Yellowstone wolves that roamed out of park</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d84793dfc5d19c55c40337/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d84793dfc5d19c55c40337/</guid><description>Twenty of Yellowstone National Park’s renowned gray wolves roamed from the park and were shot by hunters in neighboring states in recent months
Summary Twenty of Yellowstone National Park’s renowned gray wolves roamed from the park and were shot by hunters in neighboring states in recent monthsBILLINGS, Mont. Park Superintendent Cam Sholly first raised concerns last September about wolves dying near the park border. “Allowances for trapping and especially baiting are a major concern, especially if these tactics lure wolves out of the park,” Yellowstone spokesperson Morgan Warthin said.</description></item><item><title>Man killed in front of his 3 kids, girlfriend in potential Christmas Eve road rage shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8e5fbdb916eb1f48dca84/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8e5fbdb916eb1f48dca84/</guid><description>A man was driving with his girlfriend and three kids, heading to a Christmas Eve gathering, when he was shot dead in a possible road rage incident.
Summary A man was driving with his girlfriend and three kids, heading to a Christmas Eve gathering, when he was shot dead in a possible road rage incident, police in Maryland said. The suspect&amp;rsquo;s car apparently pulled up next to Kelly&amp;rsquo;s SUV and someone in the suspect&amp;rsquo;s car fired, police said.</description></item><item><title>Christmas tree lights likely to blame for Christmas Day fire that killed father and 2 sons</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c84b51c356656ed1dc2920/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c84b51c356656ed1dc2920/</guid><description>Police believe lights on a tree are what started a fire in Quakertown that killed three people early Christmas morning.
Summary Allentown, PA (18103)TodayCloudy for a while followed by some clearing late. There might be some early lingering showers..TonightCloudy for a while followed by some clearing late. There might be some early lingering showers. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>'Tragic': Teen apparently killed by stray police bullet in LA Burlington dressing room identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7b0a09418a68b928e2273/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7b0a09418a68b928e2273/</guid><description>Two people were fatally shot, including a 14-year-old girl, after officers opened fire during a confrontation with a suspect at a Los Angeles clothing store.
Summary The 14-year-old girl believed to have been killed by a stray police bullet in a dressing room in Los Angeles was identified by the local coroner &amp;ndash; a death the city&amp;rsquo;s police chief called &amp;ldquo;tragic.&amp;rdquo; The 14-year-old girl was identified by the LA County Coroner on Friday as Valentina Orellana Peralta.</description></item></channel></rss>