<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>killed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/killed/</link><description>Recent content in killed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 22:10:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/killed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 people were killed and at least 19 injured when vehicles crashed into pedestrians in Lincoln, Nebraska</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629540be92eeb4df5f3f994a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 22:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629540be92eeb4df5f3f994a/</guid><description>Two people are dead and at least 19 others injured after a two-car crash struck multiple pedestrians in Lincoln, Nebraska, according to authorities.
Highlights At least one of the 19 injured is in critical condition. Two women who were in one vehicle were killed, while the driver of the other vehicle is receiving treatment at a hospital. A vehicle was traveling westbound near 52nd and O streets, Lincoln Police Captain Max Hubka says.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Dozens feared dead after bomb hits school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627808d1c5b3e534085a9c33/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627808d1c5b3e534085a9c33/</guid><description>A Ukrainian official says 60 people may be dead after an air strike on a village school in Luhansk.
Highlights UN has recorded at least 2,345 civilian deaths and 2,919 injured in Ukraine. Thousands of combatants are also believed to have been killed or injured on both sides. At least 60 people may be dead after an air strike on a village school in Luhansk, Ukraine, an official says. More than 2,000 people have died since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion began on 24 February, the UN said last month.</description></item><item><title>New evidence found in Madeleine McCann case as German prosecutor is 'sure' suspect killed British girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627672c97457334a1bf84a68/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627672c97457334a1bf84a68/</guid><description>A German prosecutor has said he is &amp;quot;sure&amp;quot; that Madeleine McCann &amp;ndash; the British girl who disappeared from a resort in Portugal in 2007 at the age of three &amp;ndash; was killed by suspect Christian Brückner.
Highlights Prosecutor says he is &amp;ldquo;sure&amp;rdquo; Madeleine McCann was killed by suspect Christian Brückner. Prosecutor says investigators have found &amp;ldquo;new evidence&amp;rdquo; that links the convicted rapist and child sex abuser to the child&amp;rsquo;s disappearance. The British girl disappeared from a holiday resort in Portugal in 2007 at the age of three.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in crash that killed Seattle pedestrian identified as Auburn police officer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267aa6a7260c8123f398933/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 08:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267aa6a7260c8123f398933/</guid><description>Michael Smith, 33, was arrested Saturday night after he struck and killed a pedestrian in Seattle’s Interbay neighborhood. Police responded to the intersection of 15th Avenue West and Gilman Drive West just before 11 p.m.
Highlights A man was arrested Saturday night after he struck and killed a pedestrian in Seattle’s Interbay neighborhood. The 33-year-old suspect was identified as off-duty Auburn police officer Michael Smith. Smith was immediately placed on administrative leave while an internal investigation is conducted.</description></item><item><title>Hitmen killed an FSU law professor nearly 8 years ago. Now, his former brother-in-law has been arrested in the case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264c3463fc04d20f8091c5b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 03:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264c3463fc04d20f8091c5b/</guid><description>A Fort Lauderdale dentist has been charged in connection with the 2014 death of his former brother-in-law, a renowned Florida State University Law School professor.
Highlights Charles Adelson, Daniel Markel&amp;rsquo;s former brother-in-law, has been charged in connection with the 2014 death of Markel. Adelson was arrested at his home in South Florida on Thursday, according to a statement from the 2nd judicial circuit court of Leon County, Florida. Markel was fatally shot in the head at his Florida State University Law School home on July 18, 2014, CNN has reported.</description></item><item><title>March breaks record for most tornados in a single month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62537c727be68abbd107b567/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62537c727be68abbd107b567/</guid><description>It was a chaotic meteorological transition into spring as March saw the highest number of tornadoes in a single month in U.S. history.
Highlights At least 218 tornadoes occurred in March, with many of the tornadoes happening toward the end of the month. More tornadoes and severe weather are expected in the coming days. More severe weather that could conjure up more tornadoes is expected over the next several days. On Sunday and Monday, tornadoes could pop up in eastern Oklahoma, northeast Texas, southern Missouri and much of Arkansas.</description></item><item><title>16-year-old killed when teens wearing body armor take turns shooting at each other in Florida, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250978f6d6c0ae440f105bb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 20:14:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250978f6d6c0ae440f105bb/</guid><description>A 16-year-old boy was killed when he and another teen took turns shooting at each other while wearing a form of body armor, according to police.
Highlights Joshua Vining and Colton Whitler, both 17, were arrested Thursday in connection with the fatal shooting of Christopher Leroy Broad Jr. Police said Vining fatally shot Broad as the two were taking turns shooting at each other while wearing a vest containing “a form of body armor” An 18-year-old who was with the group — identified as Evan Vowell — recorded the shooting on his cell phone and turned over the footage to be used as evidence.</description></item><item><title>Two cousins, 12 and 14, killed while playing with gun on Instagram Live, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242a44733c2f2f0a74a6761/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242a44733c2f2f0a74a6761/</guid><description>Two young cousins from Missouri were livestreaming when one fatally shot the other before killing herself, police and a relative of the victims said.
Highlights Paris Harvey, 12, and her cousin Kuaron Harvey, 14, were livestreaming when one fatally shot the other before she killed herself, police say. Police classified the incident as a murder-suicide, but family members say it was a tragic accident. Paris’ mother, Shinise Harvey, says she let her daughter go to the apartment for a family party celebrating March birthdays.</description></item><item><title>Russian general Yakov Rezantsev killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f3c46d43bc77f9d9ce7a0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f3c46d43bc77f9d9ce7a0/</guid><description>Western officials believe low morale among Russian troops is forcing generals to the battlefield.
Highlights Western officials believe low morale among Russian troops is forcing generals to the battlefield. It is unusual for such senior Russian officers to be so close to battlefield. Western officials say they have been forced to move towards the front lines to deal with low morale of Russian troops. Russia has been hit by a growing number of problems in recent years, including the threat posed by Russia&amp;rsquo;s anti-Russian forces in Ukraine and Russia’s annexation of Crimea in 2010.</description></item><item><title>Russian navy commander killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237a6cbdf7fd557a009c592/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237a6cbdf7fd557a009c592/</guid><description>A senior naval commander in Russia&amp;rsquo;s Black Sea Fleet has been killed in Ukraine, the governor of Sevastopol said on Sunday.
Highlights A senior naval commander in Russia&amp;rsquo;s Black Sea Fleet has been killed in Ukraine. The deputy commander of the fleet died during fighting in the eastern Ukrainian port city of Mariupol. The Russian navy did not respond to a request for comment. Russia annexed Crimea from Ukraine in 2014, which is located on the Crimean peninsula, which Moscow annexed from Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US hunter fined after trophy photo proves he shot sheep in Canada | Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235e4d90e454bb5cd8fbf05/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 14:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235e4d90e454bb5cd8fbf05/</guid><description>Donald Lee claimed he killed a Fannin bighorn sheep in Alaska but an online sleuth and Yukon conservation officers proved he didn’t
Highlights Donald Lee claimed he killed a bighorn sheep in Alaska but it was in Canada, not the U.S. He was fined C$8,500 and banned from hunting in Canada for five years. He posted pictures of the scene in the Yukon on social media, but officers found the sheep had been killed in Canada.</description></item><item><title>Tiananmen Square protester killed in his New York law office</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230670a0bf8bc2bbd6ae4c8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230670a0bf8bc2bbd6ae4c8/</guid><description>Police say a dissident legal scholar who was jailed for two years in China after participating in the 1989 Tiananmen Square pro-democracy movement has been killed in his law firm’s office in New York
Highlights Li Jinjin, 66, was stabbed to death in the city where he had long worked as an immigration lawyer. Xiaoning Zhang, 25, was taken into custody and faces a murder charge. Friend of Li says killing might have stemmed from Li&amp;rsquo;s refusal to take Zhang on as a client.</description></item><item><title>Chechen general Magomed Tushayev, the president’s right-hand man, killed near Kiev</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aec7f937630f9e06c606d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aec7f937630f9e06c606d/</guid><description>Magomed Tushayev was in charge of the so-called Kadyrov guard in Chechnya. He was known as one of the Lords of war and his loss is a severe blow to the Chechen contingent that was
Highlights Tushyen is one of the most elite military units in the world. He was known as one of those who lost his life in the Ukraine. The loss of his troops is a blow to his reputation as a leader in the country&amp;rsquo;s armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Parents of worker killed in tornado that hit Amazon facility are suing the company for wrongful death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</guid><description>The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.
Summary (CNN) The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.</description></item><item><title>Hunters kill 20 Yellowstone wolves that roamed out of park</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d84793dfc5d19c55c40337/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d84793dfc5d19c55c40337/</guid><description>Twenty of Yellowstone National Park’s renowned gray wolves roamed from the park and were shot by hunters in neighboring states in recent months
Summary Twenty of Yellowstone National Park’s renowned gray wolves roamed from the park and were shot by hunters in neighboring states in recent monthsBILLINGS, Mont. Park Superintendent Cam Sholly first raised concerns last September about wolves dying near the park border. “Allowances for trapping and especially baiting are a major concern, especially if these tactics lure wolves out of the park,” Yellowstone spokesperson Morgan Warthin said.</description></item><item><title>Man killed in front of his 3 kids, girlfriend in potential Christmas Eve road rage shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8e5fbdb916eb1f48dca84/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8e5fbdb916eb1f48dca84/</guid><description>A man was driving with his girlfriend and three kids, heading to a Christmas Eve gathering, when he was shot dead in a possible road rage incident.
Summary A man was driving with his girlfriend and three kids, heading to a Christmas Eve gathering, when he was shot dead in a possible road rage incident, police in Maryland said. The suspect&amp;rsquo;s car apparently pulled up next to Kelly&amp;rsquo;s SUV and someone in the suspect&amp;rsquo;s car fired, police said.</description></item><item><title>Christmas tree lights likely to blame for Christmas Day fire that killed father and 2 sons</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c84b51c356656ed1dc2920/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c84b51c356656ed1dc2920/</guid><description>Police believe lights on a tree are what started a fire in Quakertown that killed three people early Christmas morning.
Summary Allentown, PA (18103)TodayCloudy for a while followed by some clearing late. There might be some early lingering showers..TonightCloudy for a while followed by some clearing late. There might be some early lingering showers. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>'Tragic': Teen apparently killed by stray police bullet in LA Burlington dressing room identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7b0a09418a68b928e2273/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7b0a09418a68b928e2273/</guid><description>Two people were fatally shot, including a 14-year-old girl, after officers opened fire during a confrontation with a suspect at a Los Angeles clothing store.
Summary The 14-year-old girl believed to have been killed by a stray police bullet in a dressing room in Los Angeles was identified by the local coroner &amp;ndash; a death the city&amp;rsquo;s police chief called &amp;ldquo;tragic.&amp;rdquo; The 14-year-old girl was identified by the LA County Coroner on Friday as Valentina Orellana Peralta.</description></item></channel></rss>