<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>faces on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/faces/</link><description>Recent content in faces on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:14:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/faces/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alex Jones avoids jail, faces escalating $25K daily fine until he complies with Sandy Hook testimony order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244e418430dee843ab53bd3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244e418430dee843ab53bd3/</guid><description>The fine, which could accumulate into six figures in as quickly as four days, was imposed&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones faces escalating daily fine of $25,000 for &amp;ldquo;intentionally failing to comply with the orders of the court” Judge Barbara Bellis also held him in contempt of court. The fine, which could accumulate into six figures in as quickly as four days, was imposed Wednesday. Bellis could have issued an order for Jones’ arrest to compel him to testify.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s brain chip company, Neuralink, faces animal abuse claims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c876ee99a0e206c987ae1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 05:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c876ee99a0e206c987ae1/</guid><description>An animal welfare group alleges that monkey test subjects endured ‘crude surgeries’ and ‘extreme suffering’
Highlights Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s brain chip company Neuralink is defending itself against claims that monkeys were tortured and left to die in horrific experiments at its facilities. The group Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine (PCRM) said the research caused “extreme suffering” in monkeys. PCRM obtained hundreds of pages of health records, necropsy reports and other documents related to the $1.</description></item><item><title>Pullman Elementary third grader faces assault charges for bullying</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209a4ba5930f3cb00406472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:39:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209a4ba5930f3cb00406472/</guid><description>A 3rd grade student is facing assault charges after an Allegan County mother said he beat up her 2nd grade son. Jada Paulin said her 8-year-old son Gavin, who has autism, has been experiencing ongoing abuse from this third grader, and it has turned violent. The two kids attend Pullman Elementary, which is part of the Bloomingdale Public Schools district. Bullying: Parent speaks out about bullying after son beat up at Portage middle school.</description></item></channel></rss>