<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>risk on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/risk/</link><description>Recent content in risk on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 09:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/risk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Possible case of monkeypox reported in Broward County, FL</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b4f8204451c4136d6be53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b4f8204451c4136d6be53/</guid><description>A “presumptive” case of monkeypox is being investigated in South Florida, state health officials say. The case appears to be related to international travel, the Florida Department of Health in Broward County says. The person
Highlights A “presumptive” case of monkeypox is being investigated in South Florida, state health officials say. The case appears to be related to international travel, and the risk to the community is low, they say. As of Friday, there were 80 confirmed cases worldwide, including at least two in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Gay men still face hurdles to donate blood amid national shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0e753f686cffe716fcdac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0e753f686cffe716fcdac/</guid><description>Gay and bisexual men are still restricted from giving blood, in a move that LGBTQ activists call discriminatory.
Summary The U.S. is facing a national blood crisis, the &amp;ldquo;worst blood shortage in over a decade,&amp;rdquo; the American Red Cross warns. Despite this urgent need for donations, people who have sex with gay or bisexual men are still facing restrictions on their ability to give blood. The agency changed the deferral period from 12 months to three months in November 2020 as blood donations fell and hospitals faced critical shortages during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Alcohol should have cancer warning labels, say doctors and researchers pushing to raise awareness of risk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db4ceec450f920d000aba5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db4ceec450f920d000aba5/</guid><description>Advocates of warning labels want Canadians to understand that alcohol is classified as a Group 1 carcinogen and one of the top causes of preventable cancer.
Summary Stockwell wants to change that, and he and other health experts are advocating for cancer warning labels on alcohol containers. Tim Stockwell, a senior scientist with the Canadian Institute for Substance Use Research at the University of Victoria, is among the researchers and doctors pushing for cancer warning labels on alcohol.</description></item><item><title>France's Bogdanoff TV twins die of Covid six days apart</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4d18fc17fa09c819f36f2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4d18fc17fa09c819f36f2/</guid><description>Grichka and Igor Bogdanoff had hosted a TV science and science-fiction show in the 1980s.
Summary Family friend Pierre-Jean Chalençon said they had left it too late to seek hospital treatment, deciding it was similar to flu. &amp;ldquo;People have said they were anti-vaxxers but they absolutely weren&amp;rsquo;t,&amp;rdquo; he told BFMTV. &amp;ldquo;Several friends told them to get themselves vaccinated but they felt because of their lifestyle and their [lack of] comorbidity, they weren&amp;rsquo;t at risk of Covid.</description></item><item><title>'High risk' of armed conflict over Ukraine, Russian defense ministry warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb6cf7c10051328a2930df/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb6cf7c10051328a2930df/</guid><description>The Biden administration has repeatedly called for diplomacy with Russia to deescalate tensions and end the war in Ukraine’s eastern provinces.
Summary Russia has said it has no plans to invade but demanded the U.S., NATO, and Ukraine take seriously its concerns. His Deputy Defense Minister Alexander Fomin blamed NATO again Monday for provoking conflict by sending warships and reconnaissance planes to back Ukraine. The estimated number of Russian troops near Ukraine have ranged from 60,000 to over 100,000, with one leaked U.</description></item></channel></rss>