<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>missing on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missing/</link><description>Recent content in missing on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 10:13:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Actress Lindsey Pearlman found dead after going missing in LA</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62121417c05200d0928ec69f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62121417c05200d0928ec69f/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Actor Lindsey Erin Pearlman, who had roles in “General Hospital,” “American Housewife” and other shows, was found dead days after she was reported missing in Los Angeles, authorities said.
Highlights Lindsey Erin Pearlman, 43, was last seen around noon last Sunday, ABC 7 reported. Her body was found Friday morning, Feb. 18, 2022, when officers responded to a call for a death investigation in a residential neighborhood of Hollywood.</description></item><item><title>Son of Sinéad O’Connor dies at age of 17 after going missing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9d13e3fc8393448a6f76d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9d13e3fc8393448a6f76d/</guid><description>Irish musician says Shane O’Connor, last seen on Friday morning, ‘was the very light of my life’
Summary Sinéad O’Connor’s 17-year-old son has died, two days after he was reported missing. The musician shared the news on social media, writing that he “decided to end his earthly struggle” and asked that “no one follows his example”. In the early hours of Saturday morning, O’Connor tweeted: “My beautiful son, Nevi’im Nesta Ali Shane O’Connor, the very light of my life, decided to end his earthly struggle today and is now with God.</description></item></channel></rss>