<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dangerous on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dangerous/</link><description>Recent content in dangerous on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 22:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dangerous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mom suing TikTok after 10-year-old daughter dies from dangerous "Blackout Challenge"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ed839cc648bb44c345e3c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 22:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ed839cc648bb44c345e3c/</guid><description>Tawainna Anderson said in December 2021 that her daughter Nylah was rushed to the hospital after attempting the challenge, which encourages users to choke themselves.
Highlights Tawainna Anderson said in December 2021, her daughter Nylah was rushed to the hospital after attempting the challenge. She was in the intensive care unit for several days before she died. Anderson is suing TikTok for multiple counts including wrongful death, strict products liability and negligence.</description></item><item><title>Dangerous chemicals found in food wrappers at major fast-food restaurants and grocery chains, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e9370d01422623def6957/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 04:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e9370d01422623def6957/</guid><description>Alarming levels of dangerous chemicals known as PFAS were discovered in food packaging at a number of well-known fast-food and fast-casual restaurants and grocery store chains, a new report found.
Highlights Consumer Reports finds high levels of dangerous chemicals known as PFAS in food packaging. The chemicals are used to prevent grease and water from soaking through food wrappers and beverage cups. The CDC and Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry call exposure to PFAS a &amp;ldquo;public health concern&amp;rdquo; The report comes more than two years into the COVID-19 pandemic, when the public has relied heavily on takeout and grocery deliveries.</description></item></channel></rss>