<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>restaurants on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/restaurants/</link><description>Recent content in restaurants on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 04:16:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/restaurants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dangerous chemicals found in food wrappers at major fast-food restaurants and grocery chains, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e9370d01422623def6957/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 04:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e9370d01422623def6957/</guid><description>Alarming levels of dangerous chemicals known as PFAS were discovered in food packaging at a number of well-known fast-food and fast-casual restaurants and grocery store chains, a new report found.
Highlights Consumer Reports finds high levels of dangerous chemicals known as PFAS in food packaging. The chemicals are used to prevent grease and water from soaking through food wrappers and beverage cups. The CDC and Agency for Toxic Substances and Disease Registry call exposure to PFAS a &amp;ldquo;public health concern&amp;rdquo; The report comes more than two years into the COVID-19 pandemic, when the public has relied heavily on takeout and grocery deliveries.</description></item><item><title>Burger King franchise 'refuses' to close 800 Russian restaurants</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234be1618f3c7014b0e55ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 17:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234be1618f3c7014b0e55ee/</guid><description>Burger King is trying to suspend its operations in Russia, but that&amp;rsquo;s proving difficult. A business partner controlling 800 restaurants has &amp;quot;refused&amp;quot; to close them, the company said.
Highlights Burger King is trying to suspend its operations in Russia, but that&amp;rsquo;s proving difficult. A business partner controlling 800 restaurants has &amp;ldquo;refused&amp;rdquo; to close them, the company said. Burger King can&amp;rsquo;t just snap its fingers and close up shop. The burger chain, owned by, has a joint venture partnership with businessman Alexander Kolobov in Russia.</description></item><item><title>The Russian Tea Room in New York City suffers as Ukraine invasion escalates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226a70ec5adda755162de6a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226a70ec5adda755162de6a/</guid><description>The Russian Tea Room is a 100-year-old New York City icon that has long drawn in locals and tourists alike. It was opened in 1927 by, perhaps apocryphally, “White Russian expatriates who had
Highlights The Russian Tea Room is a 100-year-old New York City icon that has long drawn in locals and tourists alike. It was opened in 1927 by, perhaps apocryphally, “White Russian expatriates who had fled the Bolsheviks,” according to the restaurant’s website.</description></item></channel></rss>