<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>defense on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/defense/</link><description>Recent content in defense on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 23:13:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/defense/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. boosts missile defense readiness in response to North Korea's "serious escalation" with recent missile tests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d28e057bb9cd386f34c81/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 23:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d28e057bb9cd386f34c81/</guid><description>Pentagon enhancing intelligence gathering and missile defense readiness in the region after Kim Jong Un regime tests components for a huge new missile.
Highlights U.S. intelligence agencies believe North Korea is testing components of its gigantic &amp;ldquo;Hwasong-17&amp;rdquo; intercontinental ballistic missile (ICBM) The new weapon was rolled out in a military parade in 2020, but as far as anyone knows, it has never been fired. If the missile works the way it has been designed to, it could potentially reach anywhere in the continental United States.</description></item><item><title>Feds offer no plea deals to 3 former cops charged with violating George Floyd's rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df79b738ce923aef1fa166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 01:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df79b738ce923aef1fa166/</guid><description>No last-minute plea deals are in the works for three former police officers charged with civil rights violations in the death of George Floyd, a prosecutor said.
Summary Chauvin pleaded guilty last month to federal civil rights charges stemming from the May 25, 2020, death of the 46-year-old Black man during an attempted arrest. Multiple videos showed Kueng and Lane helping Chauvin hold down Floyd, while Thao kept witnesses at bay.</description></item><item><title>'High risk' of armed conflict over Ukraine, Russian defense ministry warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb6cf7c10051328a2930df/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb6cf7c10051328a2930df/</guid><description>The Biden administration has repeatedly called for diplomacy with Russia to deescalate tensions and end the war in Ukraine’s eastern provinces.
Summary Russia has said it has no plans to invade but demanded the U.S., NATO, and Ukraine take seriously its concerns. His Deputy Defense Minister Alexander Fomin blamed NATO again Monday for provoking conflict by sending warships and reconnaissance planes to back Ukraine. The estimated number of Russian troops near Ukraine have ranged from 60,000 to over 100,000, with one leaked U.</description></item><item><title>US, Japan draw up joint military plan for possible Taiwan emergency: report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c545e2cac5dd680c38bdf0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c545e2cac5dd680c38bdf0/</guid><description>The U.S.
Summary The U.S. and Japanese militaries have made a draft plan for a joint operation should an emergency with Taiwan arise, Japan&amp;rsquo;s Kyodo news agency reported Thursday. Under the draft plan, the U.S. Marine Corps would deploy troops to and set up temporary bases on the Nansei island chain, an archipelago of Japan that stretches toward Taiwan, at the first sign of a Taiwan emergency, Kyodo said. They would not speak to the specific topics planned for discussion in the 2+2 meetings with Japan.</description></item></channel></rss>