<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>event on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/event/</link><description>Recent content in event on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 03:52:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teen arrested in Ontario after mass shooting threats made toward Florida LGBTQ event: police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a01ccd0d4dc58e248fc4b1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 03:52:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a01ccd0d4dc58e248fc4b1/</guid><description>A teen has been arrested in Mississauga, Ont. after allegedly making online threats to commit a mass shooting at an LGBTQ pride event in West Palm Beach, Fla., authorities say.
Highlights Teen arrested in Mississauga, Ontario, after allegedly threatening to commit mass shooting at LGBTQ pride event. Police say teen made threats to kill, do bodily injury, or conduct a mass shooting. Miami police received a report on Sunday of a threat made against the Pride on the Block 2022 event in West Palm Beach, Fla.</description></item><item><title>2 face criminal charges over balloon pollution in Biscayne Bay; could face time in prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f4d6989591a32eb9e150c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 06:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f4d6989591a32eb9e150c/</guid><description>The decision to use dozens of balloons to decorate a yacht during a recent marriage proposal in Miami turned out to be really costly for a group of people. The lesson authorities want the public to learn: It’s a crime to dispose of balloons in Biscayne Bay.
Highlights A witness shared a video on Instagram and environmentalists were outraged. Marine animals often mistake the nonbiodegradable deflated balloons for jellyfish. Miami-Dade police officers also issued civil citations with more than $23,000 in fines for the illegal dumping at the Bayshore Landing Marina in Coconut Grove.</description></item><item><title>‘Potentially historic’ wildfire event threatens New Mexico, Southwest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277984aa8daed53f2b16f57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277984aa8daed53f2b16f57/</guid><description>The entire state of New Mexico is under a red flag warning for dangerous fire conditions
Highlights The National Weather Service is calling it a “dangerous, long duration and potentially historic critical fire weather event” Tinderbox conditions conducive to the rapid spread of blazes are expected to persist well into next week. New ignitions are also anticipated, which could rapidly grow out of control. The Calf Canyon fire became New Mexico’s second-largest on record this week, now the state&amp;rsquo;s second largest on record.</description></item><item><title>1 dead, several injured in shooting at Mississippi Mudbug Festival, sheriff says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f067a09b1d93aa6366652/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 22:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f067a09b1d93aa6366652/</guid><description>One person has died and five others have been injured at the Mississippi Mudbug Festival, Hinds County Sheriff Tyree Jones said on Twitter late Saturday.
Highlights One person died and five others were injured at the Mississippi Mudbug Festival in Jackson, authorities say. The person who died is suspected to have been one of the shooters, officials say. Two juveniles have been detained, but no charges have been filed in the incident.</description></item><item><title>In wake of Astroworld tragedy, Houston, Harris County officials launch joint special events task force</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620903d25bc9494c44a4c415/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 13:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620903d25bc9494c44a4c415/</guid><description>Mayor Turner said the group will avoid studying what went wrong at the deadly 2021&amp;hellip;
Highlights Houston-Harris Special Events Task Force formed by Houston Mayor Sylvester Turner and Precinct 2 Commissioner Adrian Garcia. Ten concert-goers were killed and hundreds injured following a massive crowd surge at the Nov. 5 NRG Stadium concert. The city&amp;rsquo;s office of special events manages annually nearly 1,000 events attended by more than 10 million people. Turner: &amp;ldquo;The line of demarcation between the city and county properties is invisible to the public&amp;rdquo; The task force will make recommendations to improve communication, protocols and permitting requirements in Houston and Harris County &amp;ldquo;to ensure consistent operation standards for future events,&amp;rdquo; officials said.</description></item><item><title>Croatia To Withdraw Its Forces From NATO In Event Of Russia - Ukraine Conflict - President</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ffb43ec2567a2b727bd3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 08:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ffb43ec2567a2b727bd3/</guid><description>Croatia will withdraw its military from the NATO forces deployed in the region in the event of a conflict between Russia and Ukraine, President Zoran Milanovic said on Tuesday.I follow reports, according to which, NATO, not a separate state, not the United States, is strengthening its presence, sen ..
Summary (@FahadShabbir)BELGRADE (UrduPoint News / Sputnik - 25th January, 2022) Croatia will withdraw its military from the NATO forces deployed in the region in the event of a conflict between Russia and Ukraine, President Zoran Milanovic said on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Prime Minister Boris Johnson admits he attended No.10 'BYOB' garden party during the height of the first lockdown, as Labour Leader Keir Starmer demands his resignation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df6ba987f7f85ca08ef90a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df6ba987f7f85ca08ef90a/</guid><description>Prime minister apologises and accepts the public feel &amp;quot;rage&amp;quot; at his actions, as Keir Starmer demands his resignation.
Summary House of Commons via PA Wire/PA ImagesBoris Johnson has admitted he attended the No.10 “bring your own booze” party during the height of the first lockdown. Speaking at the start of PMQs on Wednesday, the prime minister apologised for the gathering on May 20, 2020. AdvertisementBut defending his actions, Johnson said he believed at the time it was a “work event” permitted “technically”under the rules when he “went into that garden”.</description></item></channel></rss>