<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>saying on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/saying/</link><description>Recent content in saying on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 23:14:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/saying/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian warship Moskva has sunk - state media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258aaafe240e0a9da388990/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 23:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258aaafe240e0a9da388990/</guid><description>The warship sunk while being towed a day after it was reported damaged by fire or a Ukrainian missile strike.
Highlights The warship sunk while being towed a day after it was reported damaged by fire or a Ukrainian missile strike. Russia&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said the warship sank due to damage sustained in the hull as fire broke out after ammunition exploded. &amp;ldquo;Given the choppy seas, the vessel sank,&amp;rdquo; state news agency Tass quoted the Russian defence ministry as saying.</description></item><item><title>‘Everybody wants to get the hell off’: JetBlue passengers plead with crew after three aborted landings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255cf2a39785dd7ffa9fa8c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 19:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255cf2a39785dd7ffa9fa8c/</guid><description>‘Arrest me!’ multiple customers challeng flight attendants in extraordinary mutiny captured on camera
Highlights JetBlue flight 1852 from Cancun was diverted to Newark Liberty International in New York after three aborted landing attempts. Several passengers shouted &amp;lsquo;Arrest me!&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;I don’t want to go back up in the air&amp;rsquo; JetBlue said it remained on the tarmac for an hour while the weather cleared before taking off for JFK. One passenger claims people were &amp;lsquo;fainting&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;throwing up&amp;rsquo; and begged crew to have &amp;lsquo;a little respect for human beings&amp;rsquo; The plane sat at Newark airport for over an hour as the passengers debated with crew.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky refuses US offer to evacuate, saying 'I need ammunition, not a ride'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b08330e17b424031d49a1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b08330e17b424031d49a1/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has turned down an offer from the United States of evacuation from the capital city Kyiv, the Ukraine embassy in Britain said Saturday on Twitter.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has turned down an offer from the United States of evacuation from the capital city Kyiv, the Ukraine embassy in Britain said Saturday on Twitter. &amp;ldquo;The fight is here; I need ammunition, not a ride,&amp;rdquo; he told the US, according to the embassy.</description></item><item><title>Winter Olympics hit by deluge of complaints from athletes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202b2be763fe7b456db1023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202b2be763fe7b456db1023/</guid><description>Grievances range from having to compete in freezing temperatures to confusion over isolation rules.
Highlights China has gone to great lengths to keep virus out of the country. Media, athletes and observers are being kept in distinct &amp;ldquo;bubble areas&amp;rdquo; The rules say anyone entering these bubbles must be fully vaccinated or spend 21 days in quarantine. Foreign spectators are banned from selling tickets to the general public in China. Fans complain about having to compete in freezing temperatures to confusion over isolation rules.</description></item><item><title>Germany urges 'prudence' in potential sanctions against Russia over Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee78bf52b2999c47989444/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee78bf52b2999c47989444/</guid><description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s leader has urged Europe and the United States to think carefully when considering sanctions against Russia for any aggression against Ukraine in a crisis pitting Berlin&amp;rsquo;s main gas supplier against its biggest security allies. Among a range of possible Western sanctions against President Vladmir Putin&amp;rsquo;s government, Germany could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if it invades Ukraine.
Summary BERLIN (Reuters) - Germany&amp;rsquo;s leader has urged Europe and the United States to think carefully when considering sanctions against Russia for any aggression against Ukraine in a crisis pitting Berlin&amp;rsquo;s main gas supplier against its biggest security allies.</description></item><item><title>Ohio's high court overturns new congressional map saying it 'unduly favors' Republicans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e263310c9630cf76136ffc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e263310c9630cf76136ffc/</guid><description>Ohio&amp;rsquo;s state supreme court ruled Friday that the state&amp;rsquo;s newly-drawn congressional map, which was passed by the GOP-controlled legislature, violates the state constitution because it &amp;quot;unduly favors the Republican Party and disfavors the Democratic Party.&amp;quot;
Summary (CNN) Ohio&amp;rsquo;s state supreme court ruled Friday that the state&amp;rsquo;s newly-drawn congressional map, which was passed by the GOP-controlled legislature, violates the state constitution because it &amp;ldquo;unduly favors the Republican Party and disfavors the Democratic Party.</description></item></channel></rss>