<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>making on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/making/</link><description>Recent content in making on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 13:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/making/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laws restricting lessons on racism make it hard for teachers to discuss the massacre in Buffalo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288e730b5b9dd23d19a5a5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288e730b5b9dd23d19a5a5c/</guid><description>After a gunman killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, teachers are grappling with anti-critical race theory laws that limit what they can discuss with students.
Highlights Teachers fear for their jobs because of state laws limiting how they can discuss racism. Educators took to social media and wrote essays debating how to talk about the Buffalo shooting. Experts describe social studies and history courses as a potential antidote to extremist ideologies that appear to have motivated the suspect in Buffalo, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Meet the 100-year-old man who's worked at the same company for 84 years - CNN Video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280c46bb9b8d88818db4bc7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 09:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280c46bb9b8d88818db4bc7/</guid><description>Walter Orthmann holds the Guinness World Record for longest time spent at a single company. Just how long? 84 years. The 100-year-old Brazilian shares his advice for making your career a lifelong pursuit of happiness.
Highlights Walter Orthmann holds the Guinness World Record for longest time spent at a single company. The 100-year-old Brazilian shares his advice for making your career a lifelong pursuit of happiness. The World Record holder holds the world record for most time spent working at one company in 84 years.</description></item></channel></rss>