<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>health on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/health/</link><description>Recent content in health on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:10:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>78,000 pounds of infant formula arrives in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b5d77a2a6b703f4225660/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 10:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b5d77a2a6b703f4225660/</guid><description>The White House says enough specialty infant formula for more than half a million baby bottles is about to arrive in the United States from Europe.
Highlights NEW: White House announces two new Defense Production Act authorizations for infant formula. Air Force plane carrying enough infant formula for more than half a million bottles arrives in Indianapolis. The White House says 1.5 million 8-ounce bottles of the three formulas are expected to arrive this week.</description></item><item><title>Covid's toll in the U.S. reaches a once unfathomable number: 1 million deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627321eefe701f275e6b622f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 01:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627321eefe701f275e6b622f/</guid><description>The U.S. on Wednesday recorded its 1 millionth Covid death, a once unthinkable toll even for the country with the world&amp;rsquo;s highest recorded toll from the virus.
Highlights The U.S. has the world&amp;rsquo;s highest recorded death toll from the Covid-19 pandemic. The number is equivalent to the population of San Jose, California, the 10th largest city in the United States. Brazil has recorded just over 660,000 confirmed Covid deaths; Peru has the highest number.</description></item><item><title>The first human case of H5N1 Avian Flu in the US detected in Colorado</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c47470a5e99aa1dd82117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c47470a5e99aa1dd82117/</guid><description>The first identified human case in the United States of the H5N1 virus, known as the avian flu and typically transmitted among poultry and wild birds, has been found in a Colorado man who works on a Western Slope poultry farm.
Highlights The first identified human case in the United States of the H5N1 virus has been found in a Colorado man who works on a poultry farm. Repeat testing on the man, however, has been negative.</description></item><item><title>Queen tests positive for coronavirus, Buckingham Palace says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62124c1774b6d62330957ee3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62124c1774b6d62330957ee3/</guid><description>The monarch, 95, is experiencing mild cold-like symptoms and expects to continue light duties at Windsor this week, the palace says.
Highlights The Queen, 95, is experiencing mild cold-like symptoms and expects to continue light duties at Windsor this week. She is understood to be triple vaccinated and is &amp;lsquo;immensely practical&amp;rsquo; Her Majesty&amp;rsquo;s doctors will be on hand to take care of and monitor her health. Announcement made just weeks after Queen reached her historic Platinum Jubilee of 70 years on the throne.</description></item><item><title>Vancouver health authorities warn staff to shelter and hide medical credentials during anti-vaxx convoy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200838b5cb0a71ae8cc8c7a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 02:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200838b5cb0a71ae8cc8c7a/</guid><description>Vancouver’s two health authorities are urging health-care workers to take defensive measures to avoid clashes with a convoy of anti-vaccination and anti-restriction demonstrators heading toward the city on Saturday.
Highlights A convoy of anti-vaccination and anti-restriction demonstrators are heading to Vancouver on Saturday. The convoy is expected to pass Mount Saint Joseph and St. Paul’s hospitals in the city. A health-care memo sent to staff at both hospitals tells them not to engage in the convoy.</description></item><item><title>No amount of alcohol is good for the heart, new report says, but critics disagree on science</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee95261e32d5dbcf7bdef2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 12:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee95261e32d5dbcf7bdef2/</guid><description>No amount of alcohol is good for the heart according to a new policy report by the World Health Federation, fueling an ongoing debate on what role drinking might play in heart heatlh.
Summary (CNN) In a bold move, the World Heart Federation released a policy brief Thursday saying that no amount of alcohol is good for the heart. &amp;ldquo;At the World Heart Federation, we decided that it was imperative that we speak up about alcohol and the damages to health, as well as the social and economic harms, because there is an impression in the population in general, and even among health care professionals, that it is good for the heart,&amp;rdquo; said Beatriz Champagne, chair of the advocacy committee that produced the report.</description></item><item><title>New Virginia Governor Youngkin to Lift School Mask Mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 09:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</guid><description>New Virginia governor Glenn Youngkin says he’s against school mask and vaccine mandates, plus will change COVID-19 policies after his 2022 inauguration.
Summary What to Know Virginia&amp;rsquo;s incoming governor, Glenn Youngkin, said he will rescind the statewide K-12 mask mandate. The removal of the school mask mandate may disproportionately affect low-income residents and communities of color, a political science professor said. Glenn Youngkin said after he was sworn in that he signed an executive order lifting the statewide school mask mandate.</description></item><item><title>China reports 5 new human cases of H5N6 bird flu</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2c586e3fa09ff580a6391/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2c586e3fa09ff580a6391/</guid><description>Summary Five more people in mainland China have tested positive for H5N6 bird flu, leaving two dead and three others seriously ill, officials say. It adds to a growing number of human cases which has led to urgent calls for increased surveillance. Chinese officials are providing only limited information about human cases of H5N6 bird flu and it often takes weeks before cases are publicly reported to WHO. H5N6 bird flu is known to cause severe illness in humans of all ages and has killed nearly half of those infected, according to WHO.</description></item><item><title>Thousands sign up for 1st dose of COVID-19 vaccine as Quebec threatens to tax the unvaxxed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e068c0620422bb46a3d4d5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e068c0620422bb46a3d4d5/</guid><description>Thousands more people have registered for their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine, amid threats by Quebec officials to tax the unvaccinated.
Summary More than 7,000 people registered for their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine Tuesday, amid threats by Quebec officials to tax the unvaccinated. &amp;ldquo;Our highest in several days,&amp;rdquo; tweeted Quebec Health Minister Christian Dubé, noting that 5,000 appointments were also made on Monday. The tax would apply to all adults in Quebec who refuse to get their first dose of a vaccine &amp;ldquo;in the next few weeks.</description></item><item><title>Psychedelics approved for medical use in Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db30d86b3959fac1adeeb5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db30d86b3959fac1adeeb5/</guid><description>Watch Psychedelics approved for medical use in Canada Video Online, on GlobalNews.ca
Summary Health care advocates are calling it a major breakthrough in treating serious or life-threatening conditions. As Aaron McArthur reports, Health Canada has given the green light for psychedelic drugs such as MDMA and magic mushrooms to be used for medical purposes. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Covid: Deadly Omicron should not be called mild, warns WHO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da7a0b4b9ea6ba4d8b6e0f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 06:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da7a0b4b9ea6ba4d8b6e0f/</guid><description>The WHO cautions that just like previous variants, Omicron is hospitalising and killing people.
Summary The WHO - the UN&amp;rsquo;s health agency - said the number of global cases has increased by 71% in the last week, and in the Americas by 100%. It said that among severe cases worldwide, 90% were unvaccinated. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Planned Parenthood fire in Knoxville confirmed to be arson</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7c986f6f934ad10b277d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7c986f6f934ad10b277d9/</guid><description>Summary For immediate release: Jan. 6, 2022KNOXVILLE, TN — Following the announcement of an arson investigation into the Dec. 31 fire at the Planned Parenthood of Tennessee and North Mississippi health center in Knoxville, leaders from the health care provider condemned the attack and resolved to reconvene services as soon as possible. “Local and federal authorities have determined that the fire at our Knoxville health center on December 31 was an intentional, criminal act,” said Ashley Coffield, president and CEO of Planned Parenthood of Tennessee &amp;amp; North Mississippi.</description></item><item><title>Whistleblower warns baffling illness affects growing number of young adults in Canadian province | Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d23ca3e7988e93cac61132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d23ca3e7988e93cac61132/</guid><description>Several new cases in New Brunswick involve caretakers of those afflicted, suggesting a possible environmental trigger
Summary The official number of cases under investigation, 48, remains unchanged since it was first announced in early spring 2021. But multiple sources say the cluster could now be as many as 150 people, with a backlog of cases involving young people still requiring further assessment. Prospective cases have typically stumped doctors and resisted a battery of standardized neurological tests used to rule out certain conditions.</description></item></channel></rss>