<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>went on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/went/</link><description>Recent content in went on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 12:16:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/went/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mexico's number of 'disappeared' people rises above 100,000</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628634ffe396f76806f06f35/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 12:16:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628634ffe396f76806f06f35/</guid><description>There are now over 100,000 people in Mexico&amp;rsquo;s national register of the &amp;quot;disappeared.&amp;quot; The UN says organized crime is among the leading causes of missing people in the country.
Highlights Mexico&amp;rsquo;s official figure of missing people surpasses 100,000 for the first time. Families are calling on authorities to do more to find victims of violence linked to organized crime. The interior ministry compiles a national register of the &amp;ldquo;desaparecidos&amp;rdquo; — Spanish for missing people — which is periodically updated.</description></item><item><title>Boy, 4, punched in head in New York's Times Square, mother takes suspect down</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62125a847f3ef9601adb2148/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 15:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62125a847f3ef9601adb2148/</guid><description>A man was arrested after he allegedly punched a 4-year-old child in the head in a seemingly random attack in Manhattan Thursday.
Highlights Babacar Mbaye allegedly punched a 4-year-old boy in the head in a random attack in Times Square. Rafaela Rivera and her children were taking a walk to enjoy the weather when she heard a smack. The boy, Angel Rivera, said he was hit with a closed fist and screamed for help.</description></item><item><title>Norway lifts almost all remaining COVID restrictions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a38b3d896d20f43191976/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 11:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a38b3d896d20f43191976/</guid><description>Norway is lifting almost all remaining COVID restrictions even though Omicron is still spreading in the Nordic nation.
Highlights Norway lifts almost all remaining remaining COVID restrictions even though Omicron is still spreading in the Nordic nation. Prime Minister Jonas Gahr Stoere justified the move by saying that Norwegians are well protected by vaccines against the COVID-19 pandemic. The proportion of citizens who end in up in hospital has remained low despite the spread of the omicron variant.</description></item><item><title>America’s covid job-saving programme gave most of its cash to the rich</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc4502077c21d1e7db2a7d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 21:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc4502077c21d1e7db2a7d/</guid><description>But the country was ill-prepared to do better | Graphic detail
Highlights America had little experience with anything approaching that sort of drastic intervention. Its hastily designed scheme sent much of its relief money to people who didn’t need it. But the country was ill-prepared to do better: crafting a targeted policy would have been hard, expensive and slow. European countries did better: governments encouraged struggling employers to keep workers on their payrolls with reduced hours, and then made up some or all of the pay gap.</description></item><item><title>A 74-year-old woman spent 27 years in prison for a murder she didn't commit. This week she was exonerated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3ded572a871c2c5157005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3ded572a871c2c5157005/</guid><description>A Tennessee woman who was wrongfully convicted of murdering her great-niece and spent 27 years in prison, was exonerated this week.
Summary (CNN) A Tennessee woman who was wrongfully convicted of murdering her great-niece and spent 27 years in prison, was exonerated this week. On June 26, 1987, Joyce Watkins, now 74, and her boyfriend at the time, Charlie Dunn, went to pick up Watkins four-year-old great-niece, Brandi, in Kentucky, according to a report filed with the Davidson County Criminal Court.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6. The ruling Wednesday comes one day after he asked a federal judge in Florida for a temporary restraining order, and it&amp;rsquo;s the first quick response to a lawsuit from a House witness, after several went to court to try to invalidate the committee and block the House from pursuing their phone records.</description></item></channel></rss>