<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>went on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/went/</link><description>Recent content in went on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 21:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/went/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>America’s covid job-saving programme gave most of its cash to the rich</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc4502077c21d1e7db2a7d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 21:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc4502077c21d1e7db2a7d/</guid><description>But the country was ill-prepared to do better | Graphic detail
Highlights America had little experience with anything approaching that sort of drastic intervention. Its hastily designed scheme sent much of its relief money to people who didn’t need it. But the country was ill-prepared to do better: crafting a targeted policy would have been hard, expensive and slow. European countries did better: governments encouraged struggling employers to keep workers on their payrolls with reduced hours, and then made up some or all of the pay gap.</description></item><item><title>A 74-year-old woman spent 27 years in prison for a murder she didn't commit. This week she was exonerated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3ded572a871c2c5157005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3ded572a871c2c5157005/</guid><description>A Tennessee woman who was wrongfully convicted of murdering her great-niece and spent 27 years in prison, was exonerated this week.
Summary (CNN) A Tennessee woman who was wrongfully convicted of murdering her great-niece and spent 27 years in prison, was exonerated this week. On June 26, 1987, Joyce Watkins, now 74, and her boyfriend at the time, Charlie Dunn, went to pick up Watkins four-year-old great-niece, Brandi, in Kentucky, according to a report filed with the Davidson County Criminal Court.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.</description></item></channel></rss>