<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>species on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/species/</link><description>Recent content in species on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 06:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/species/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Looming mass extinction could be biggest 'since the dinosaurs,' says WWF: More plants and animals than ever before are on a global list of threatened species, with the World Wildlife Fund Germany warning that more than 1 million species could go extinct within the next 10 years.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cd4afc3037f0ebfb2eb72a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cd4afc3037f0ebfb2eb72a/</guid><description>More plants and animals than ever before are on a global list of threatened species, with the World Wildlife Fund Germany warning that more than 1 million species could go extinct within the next 10 years
Summary The stark warnings came as WWF Germany released its &amp;ldquo;Winners and Losers of 2021,&amp;rdquo; an annual list of animals whose existence is now acutely under threat — as well as conservation victories. Facing a mass extinction event &amp;lsquo;within the next decade&amp;rsquo;There are currently 142,500 animal and plant species on the Red List of the International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN) — 40,000 of which are &amp;ldquo;threatened with extinction.</description></item><item><title>Monarch population soars 4,900 percent since last year in thrilling 2021 western migration</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c7dacc4298ae6769c89769/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c7dacc4298ae6769c89769/</guid><description>From 2,000 to 100,000, Western monarch butterflies arrived in California for their 2021 winter migration in huge numbers.
Summary When just 200 Western monarch butterflies arrived in the Pismo Beach Butterfly Grove from their northerly migration last year, park rangers feared the treasured insect would soon be gone forever. It’s expected that the monarch butterfly will be placed on the Endangered Species List soon, due to declines in both western and eastern monarch butterfly numbers.</description></item></channel></rss>