<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>researchers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/researchers/</link><description>Recent content in researchers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/researchers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Covid Science: Virus leaves antibodies that may attack healthy tissues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5888054958750a828601c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5888054958750a828601c/</guid><description>The following is a summary of some recent studies on COVID-19. They include research that warrants further study to corroborate the findings and that has yet to be certified by peer review.
Summary Once the body learns to recognize SARS-CoV-2, either after infection or vaccination, B cells generate fresh antibodies against the virus if there are not already enough antibodies circulating in the blood that can neutralize it. Memory B cells' robust ability to proliferate and produce antibodies might compensate &amp;ldquo;in less than two days&amp;rdquo; for those antibodies' reduced effectiveness, they speculate.</description></item><item><title>Japan Is Working on a COVID-19 Vaccine That Offers Lifelong Immunity</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</guid><description>While pharma companies focus on developing variant-specific boosters, Japan is working on a vaccine that could offer lifelong immunity.
Summary Researchers at the Tokyo Metropolitan Institute of Medical Science are working on a COVID-19 vaccine that not only delivers lifelong immunity against the SARS-CoV-2 virus but could also be transported at room temperature to far-off corners of the world, The Japan Times reported. The vaccine that is being developed by Michinori Kohara and his team of researchers employs the most successful vaccine used in history, one against smallpox.</description></item></channel></rss>