<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>according on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/according/</link><description>Recent content in according on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/according/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas woman sought in fatal shooting of professional cyclist, US Marshals say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289fda745038516341b41ad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289fda745038516341b41ad/</guid><description>A manhunt is underway for a Texas woman wanted in connection with the fatal shooting of a professional cyclist.
Highlights Kaitlin Marie Armstrong, 35, is wanted in the killing of 25-year-old Anna Moriah Wilson. Wilson was found bleeding and unconscious with multiple gunshot wounds at a friend&amp;rsquo;s home the night of May 11. Authorities say she was once romantically linked to the suspect&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend. Armstrong&amp;rsquo;s Jeep was captured on surveillance footage from a neighboring residence stopping outside the residence the evening of the shooting, police say.</description></item><item><title>Just before Buffalo shooting, 15 users signed into suspect’s chatroom, says person familiar with review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62874d7bbc147e10b44fabc8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62874d7bbc147e10b44fabc8/</guid><description>The users were able to scroll through months of voluminous writings and racist screeds.
Highlights Alleged gunman Payton Gendron&amp;rsquo;s online chatroom invitation was accepted by 15 users, according to a person with knowledge of the messaging platform Discord’s investigation into the matter. When the 15 accepted the invite to that server, they were able to scroll back through months of his voluminous writings and racist screeds. The invitation, headed “Happening: This is not a drill,” also included a separate link to an account on the video streaming service Twitch, where he allegedly broadcast video of his attack from a camera mounted on his military-style helmet.</description></item><item><title>Report: Elon Musk exposed himself to SpaceX flight attendant, according to documents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870e2f0fa7953f0335d28d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 03:43:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870e2f0fa7953f0335d28d/</guid><description>The billionaire tech mogul allegedly offered a severance package worth $250,000 to a&amp;hellip;
Highlights Business Insider obtained documents from a flight attendant. They say Musk allegedly offered her $250,000 to pay for an erotic massage. Musk has yet to respond to the allegations. The publication reached out to the media for comment. The payment included non-disclosure clauses that barred the attendant from mentioning the incidents or disclosing information about SpaceX or Musk&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the alleged incident, the report says.</description></item><item><title>Florida man gets life in prison for traveling to Vietnam to sexually abuse minors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286e2f77d5186c91f46d440/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286e2f77d5186c91f46d440/</guid><description>Christopher Edwin Day, 52, traveled to Vietnam to have sexual encounters with Vietnamese boys. Court records say he flew back and forth disguising himself as an English teacher. Some of the boys, according to the DOJ, were lured with promises
Highlights Christopher Edwin Day, 52, traveled to Vietnam to have sexual encounters with minor Vietnamese boys. Court records say he flew back and forth disguising himself as an English teacher. Some of the boys, according to the DOJ, were lured with promises of money and gifts.</description></item><item><title>More than 200 sailors moved off aircraft carrier after multiple suicides</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271565d0e1aaf5bf3164ce9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 16:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271565d0e1aaf5bf3164ce9/</guid><description>More than 200 sailors have moved off the USS George Washington aircraft carrier after multiple deaths by suicide among the crew, including three in less than one week in April, according to the Navy.
Highlights More than 200 sailors have moved off the USS George Washington aircraft carrier after multiple deaths by suicide among the crew. The nuclear-powered aircraft carrier continues to go through a years-long refueling and overhaul process at the shipyard in Newport News, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>Netflix shares crater 20% after company reports it lost subscribers for the first time in more than 10 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f41f26abb2bb99f5e4761/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 23:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f41f26abb2bb99f5e4761/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first time the streamer has reported a subscriber loss in more than a decade.
Highlights Netflix reported a loss of 200,000 subscribers during the first quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s shares cratered more than 25% in extended hours after the report. Netflix is forecasting a global paid subscriber loss of 2 million for the second quarter. Co-CEO Reed Hastings said the company is exploring lower-priced, ad-supported tiers in a bid to bring in new subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Trafficking ring moved nearly 300 guns from Georgia to Pennsylvania, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555144638320951fd70caf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555144638320951fd70caf/</guid><description>Atlanta rapper Fredrick Norman, aka “Slowkey Fred,&amp;quot; is one of 11 people facing federal charges in connection with an alleged straw-purchasing scheme, according to records and interviews.
Highlights ATF agents traced nearly 300 firearms purchased in Georgia from dozens of gun retailers to the suspects. Some were found at crime scenes and in the possession of convicted felons in Philadelphia. 11 suspects in Georgia and Pennsylvania are accused of trafficking guns from Georgia to Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>Theater in Mariupol where hundreds were taking refuge has been bombed, according to city council</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623285a34b67a03263c69177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:50:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623285a34b67a03263c69177/</guid><description>The Mariupol City Council has posted an image of the Ukrainian city&amp;rsquo;s theater — where hundreds of people are said to have taken shelter — after it sustained heavy damage in a bombing Wednesday.
Highlights CNN video shows a burned-out theater in the heart of the city of Mariupol. Hundreds of people are said to have been killed in the attack. The Russian city is said to be the largest in number and size of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest city.</description></item><item><title>Man accused of hiding in woman's attic, secretly filming her after meeting on OnlyFans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622280bbfc3ec51580e8f23a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622280bbfc3ec51580e8f23a/</guid><description>A Pennsylvania man is accused of breaking into a New Hampshire woman&amp;rsquo;s home and hiding out in her attic after they met through her OnlyFans account, according
Highlights Mauricio Damian Guerrero, 20, from Bensalem, was arrested and charged with four counts of burglary. Guerrero allegedly broke into the woman&amp;rsquo;s Somersworth home early in the morning on Feb. The woman said she met Guerrero through her OnlyFans account and gave him her address because he said he wanted to buy her a television and fireplace.</description></item><item><title>The number of U.S. cities with an average home price of $1 million tripled last year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62173e7300a4427f77836404/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62173e7300a4427f77836404/</guid><description>With the average price of a home up 19.6% last year, 146 new &amp;quot;million-dollar cities&amp;quot; were added in 2021 — the most ever in one year.
Highlights 146 new million-dollar cities were added in 2021, bringing the total number to a new record of 481. California, Massachusetts and New York added the most new cities with average home values above $1 million. The median price of a home in the U.</description></item><item><title>After more than 1,000 years, this English pub is closing its doors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62026ce11f1760ad0d277f11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62026ce11f1760ad0d277f11/</guid><description>An English pub that claims to be the oldest in Britain is closing due to financial problems worsened by the pandemic.
Highlights Ye Olde Fighting Cocks in St. Albans, north of London, has been in business since 793 AD. The pub took its name from cock fights that were held there in the late 19th and early 20th centuries. Landlord Christo Tofalli said trading conditions were &amp;ldquo;extremely tough&amp;rdquo; before the pandemic, but the effects of Covid-19 were &amp;ldquo;devastating&amp;rdquo; and left the pub struggling to meet its financial obligations.</description></item><item><title>Argument leads to fatal shooting in checkout line of grocery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200f0870c2638ac3acadb69/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 10:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200f0870c2638ac3acadb69/</guid><description>An argument in the checkout line of a South Florida grocery store escalated into a fatal shooting
Highlights Argument started in checkout line of Publix in upscale neighborhood of Coral Gables. Four people were shot Saturday night at Player’s Sports Bar and Grill in North Lauderdale. In Orlando, police are searching for a suspect in a fatal shooting at a banquet hall early Sunday. One victim has injuries that are believed to be life-threatening, sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said in a news release.</description></item><item><title>Texas dog walker permanently disfigured in 'bloodthirsty' attack by 2 dogs, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f3868b58d56617a9035729/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 06:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f3868b58d56617a9035729/</guid><description>Jacqueline Claire Durand, 22, a dog walker, was permanently disfigured last month in an attack by two dogs she was hired to walk, according to lawsuit.
Highlights A Texas college student working as a dog walker was permanently disfigured last month when two dogs pounced on her in a “bloodthirsty” attack, a civil lawsuit alleges. The Dogs were so violent and bloodthirsty that they pulled all of Jacqueline’s clothes off, including her blue jeans,” the lawsuit said.</description></item><item><title>Video shows Florida police sergeant grabbing fellow officer by her throat</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e246f87c716e8014992abf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e246f87c716e8014992abf/</guid><description>A Florida police sergeant has been relieved of his supervisory responsibilities and is under investigation after he was filmed grabbing an officer by her throat, according to officials.
Summary A Florida police sergeant has been relieved of his supervisory responsibilities and is under investigation after he was filmed grabbing an officer by her throat, according to officials. Sunrise police shared body camera video of the Nov. 19 incident with NBC News, but the footage was muted with faces blurred, except for the sergeant&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>The great American sickout: Omicron is causing "hellacious" worker shortages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e200a16e8599152545f93e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e200a16e8599152545f93e/</guid><description>COVID-19 is tearing through the U.S. workforce, disrupting businesses from grocery stores to airlines.
Summary A record spike in COVID-19 cases due to the Omicron variant is causing a nationwide worker &amp;ldquo;sickout,&amp;rdquo; disrupting businesses ranging from grocery stores to airlines. The past few weeks have been &amp;ldquo;hellacious,&amp;rdquo; Delta Airlines CEO Ed Bastian said in a Thursday conference call with stock analysts and reporters. The latest worker shortages are compounding earlier pandemic problems, including supply-chain disruptions and shortages of some services.</description></item><item><title>Biden doubles U.S. order of Pfizer Covid treatment pills, speeds delivery as omicron rages across nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5502ab5446ea510871a64/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5502ab5446ea510871a64/</guid><description>With the new order, the U.S. has committed to purchase 20 million courses total from Pfizer.
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said another batch of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 treatment pills is shipping this week as the U.S. government doubles its order of the medication amid an unprecedented wave of infections driven by the highly contagious omicron variant. Biden on Tuesday directed the government to buy an additional 10 million courses of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s oral antiviral treatment, Paxlovid.</description></item><item><title>Kent Police assistant chief suspended for displaying Nazi insignia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfd1e5b6de86501de149fa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfd1e5b6de86501de149fa/</guid><description>Derek Kammerzell claimed he meant it as a joke because his co-workers called him “The German General.”
Summary Derek Kammerzell, an assistant chief with the Kent Police Department, received a two-week suspension in July 2021 after displaying a Nazi symbol on the office door above his name. That anonymous group emailed the documents Dec. 27 to the Kent Reporter and the Kent City Council. “The city took the allegations against Assistant Chief Kammerzell very seriously and stands by its independent investigation and discipline.</description></item><item><title>Japanese university finds drug effective in treating ALS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</guid><description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University says it has found a drug effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, also known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Summary KYODO NEWS - 5 hours ago - 13:43 | All, JapanJapan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University said Friday it has found that a drug being developed for the treatment of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s is also effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, more commonly known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease. The drug has been found capable of curbing the abnormal agglomeration of protein that causes the progressive neurodegenerative disease, the state-run university in northeastern Japan said.</description></item></channel></rss>