<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>according on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/according/</link><description>Recent content in according on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 06:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/according/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas dog walker permanently disfigured in 'bloodthirsty' attack by 2 dogs, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f3868b58d56617a9035729/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 06:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f3868b58d56617a9035729/</guid><description>Jacqueline Claire Durand, 22, a dog walker, was permanently disfigured last month in an attack by two dogs she was hired to walk, according to lawsuit.
Highlights A Texas college student working as a dog walker was permanently disfigured last month when two dogs pounced on her in a “bloodthirsty” attack, a civil lawsuit alleges. The Dogs were so violent and bloodthirsty that they pulled all of Jacqueline’s clothes off, including her blue jeans,” the lawsuit said.</description></item><item><title>Video shows Florida police sergeant grabbing fellow officer by her throat</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e246f87c716e8014992abf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e246f87c716e8014992abf/</guid><description>A Florida police sergeant has been relieved of his supervisory responsibilities and is under investigation after he was filmed grabbing an officer by her throat, according to officials.
Summary A Florida police sergeant has been relieved of his supervisory responsibilities and is under investigation after he was filmed grabbing an officer by her throat, according to officials. Sunrise police shared body camera video of the Nov. 19 incident with NBC News, but the footage was muted with faces blurred, except for the sergeant&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>The great American sickout: Omicron is causing "hellacious" worker shortages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e200a16e8599152545f93e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e200a16e8599152545f93e/</guid><description>COVID-19 is tearing through the U.S. workforce, disrupting businesses from grocery stores to airlines.
Summary A record spike in COVID-19 cases due to the Omicron variant is causing a nationwide worker &amp;ldquo;sickout,&amp;rdquo; disrupting businesses ranging from grocery stores to airlines. The past few weeks have been &amp;ldquo;hellacious,&amp;rdquo; Delta Airlines CEO Ed Bastian said in a Thursday conference call with stock analysts and reporters. The latest worker shortages are compounding earlier pandemic problems, including supply-chain disruptions and shortages of some services.</description></item><item><title>Biden doubles U.S. order of Pfizer Covid treatment pills, speeds delivery as omicron rages across nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5502ab5446ea510871a64/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5502ab5446ea510871a64/</guid><description>With the new order, the U.S. has committed to purchase 20 million courses total from Pfizer.
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said another batch of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 treatment pills is shipping this week as the U.S. government doubles its order of the medication amid an unprecedented wave of infections driven by the highly contagious omicron variant. Biden on Tuesday directed the government to buy an additional 10 million courses of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s oral antiviral treatment, Paxlovid.</description></item><item><title>Kent Police assistant chief suspended for displaying Nazi insignia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfd1e5b6de86501de149fa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfd1e5b6de86501de149fa/</guid><description>Derek Kammerzell claimed he meant it as a joke because his co-workers called him “The German General.”
Summary Derek Kammerzell, an assistant chief with the Kent Police Department, received a two-week suspension in July 2021 after displaying a Nazi symbol on the office door above his name. That anonymous group emailed the documents Dec. 27 to the Kent Reporter and the Kent City Council. “The city took the allegations against Assistant Chief Kammerzell very seriously and stands by its independent investigation and discipline.</description></item><item><title>Japanese university finds drug effective in treating ALS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</guid><description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University says it has found a drug effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, also known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Summary KYODO NEWS - 5 hours ago - 13:43 | All, JapanJapan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University said Friday it has found that a drug being developed for the treatment of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s is also effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, more commonly known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease. The drug has been found capable of curbing the abnormal agglomeration of protein that causes the progressive neurodegenerative disease, the state-run university in northeastern Japan said.</description></item></channel></rss>