<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>indictment on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/indictment/</link><description>Recent content in indictment on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 12:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/indictment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DOJ charges 3 Russians with running ‘foreign influence and disinformation network’ in U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259632051a2d4ad1a86250e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 12:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259632051a2d4ad1a86250e/</guid><description>The three Russians worked to undermine the U.S. and &amp;quot;promote Russia&amp;rsquo;s illicit actions designed to destroy the sovereignty of Ukraine,&amp;quot; an indictment alleged.
Highlights Three Russians accused of running a yearslong scheme to influence U.S. officials. The scheme included &amp;ldquo;staged events, paid propaganda, and the recruitment of at least one American citizen to do their bidding,&amp;rdquo; indictment alleges. Aleksandr Mikhaylovich Babakov, a former Russian senator and deputy chairman of the State Duma, is charged with conspiring to act as Russian agents in the United States without notifying the attorney general and conspiring to commit visa fraud.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Virginia police officer and West Virginia lawmaker plead guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</guid><description>Jacob Fracker, who has agreed to cooperate with federal prosecutors, was fired from his job as a police officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia while Derrick Evans resigned from the West Virginia state legislature before the session started.
Highlights Jacob Fracker pleads guilty to conspiring to obstruct an official proceeding, the joint session of Congress that convened on January 6, 2021, to certify President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s electoral victory. A former West Virginia state lawmaker pleaded guilty Friday to a civil disorder charge, punishable by up to five years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keepers leader and 10 others charged with 'seditious conspiracy' related to US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0af18e4592ec744bbf895/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 23:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0af18e4592ec744bbf895/</guid><description>The Justice Department escalated its January 6 investigation by bringing seditious conspiracy charges against 11 defendants, including the leader of the Oath Keepers, Stewart Rhodes.
Summary (CNN) The Justice Department escalated its January 6 investigation by bringing seditious conspiracy charges against 11 defendants, including the leader of the Oath Keepers, Stewart Rhodes. JUST WATCHED Inside America&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;militias&amp;rsquo; - from the KKK to the Oath Keepers Replay More Videos &amp;hellip; MUST WATCH Inside America&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;militias&amp;rsquo; - from the KKK to the Oath Keepers 11:47&amp;quot;We aren&amp;rsquo;t going through this without civil war.</description></item></channel></rss>