<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>books on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/books/</link><description>Recent content in books on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 05:19:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nashville Public Library debuts limited edition 'I read banned books' library cards</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62735e5c6daa06ff0bb8b4eb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 05:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62735e5c6daa06ff0bb8b4eb/</guid><description>The debate over banned books in school libraries and classrooms has taken place across the country, even putting Tennessee under the national spotlight. Now the Nashville Public Library wants to ensure everyone has the &amp;lsquo;Freedom to Read&amp;rsquo;.
Highlights The Nashville Public Library wants to ensure everyone has the &amp;lsquo;Freedom to Read&amp;rsquo; The goal is to get the 5,000 limited edition library cards in the hands of new sign-ups this month. The debate over banned books in school libraries and classrooms has taken place across the country, even putting Tennessee under the national spotlight.</description></item><item><title>Texas residents sue county for removing books on race, sex education</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268c90e9854b60cb8aac444/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 04:40:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268c90e9854b60cb8aac444/</guid><description>Llano County residents are suing the county and local officials for restricting the content allowed in libraries, including topics on race and sex education.
Highlights Lawsuit claims Llano County, Texas, officials have removed 17,000 books from library shelves. The books include &amp;ldquo;Caste: The Origins of Our Discontents,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;In the Night Kitchen&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;It’s Perfectly Normal: Changing Bodies, Growing Up, Sex, and Sexual Health&amp;rdquo; The lawsuit claims the county is violating the first amendment rights of its residents.</description></item><item><title>US conservatives linked to rich donors wage campaign to ban books from schools | US news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</guid><description>Experts warn trend is accelerating as groups push for bans of works that often address race, LGBTQ issues and marginalized people
Summary Conservative groups across the US, often linked to deep-pocketed rightwing donors, are carrying out a campaign to ban books from school libraries, often focused on works that address race, LGBTQ issues or marginalized communities. Groups purporting to be “grassroots” efforts have frequently led the charge, petitioning school boards or elected officials to remove certain books.</description></item></channel></rss>