<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jailed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jailed/</link><description>Recent content in jailed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 14:14:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jailed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine court jails Russian soldier for life in war crimes trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b959de21b1e4548374c15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 14:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b959de21b1e4548374c15/</guid><description>A Ukrainian court sentenced a Russian soldier to life in prison on Monday for killing an unarmed civilian in the first war crimes trial arising from Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion.
Highlights Ukrainian court sentences Russian tank commander Vadim Shishimarin to life in prison for killing unarmed civilian. 21-year-old tank commander pleaded guilty to killing Oleksandr Shelipov in the northeastern Ukrainian village of Chupakhivka on Feb. 28, four days after the invasion. Russia denies targeting civilians or involvement in war crimes while it carries out what it calls a &amp;ldquo;special military operation&amp;rdquo; in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Tiananmen Square protester killed in his New York law office</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230670a0bf8bc2bbd6ae4c8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230670a0bf8bc2bbd6ae4c8/</guid><description>Police say a dissident legal scholar who was jailed for two years in China after participating in the 1989 Tiananmen Square pro-democracy movement has been killed in his law firm’s office in New York
Highlights Li Jinjin, 66, was stabbed to death in the city where he had long worked as an immigration lawyer. Xiaoning Zhang, 25, was taken into custody and faces a murder charge. Friend of Li says killing might have stemmed from Li&amp;rsquo;s refusal to take Zhang on as a client.</description></item><item><title>El Salvador frees women jailed after miscarriages | The women had been jailed for terms ranging from 6 to 13 years under some of the region’s harshest anti-abortion laws</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c804fb31d174404881d81f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c804fb31d174404881d81f/</guid><description>The women had been jailed for terms ranging from six to 13 years under some of the region’s harshest anti-abortion laws.
Summary The women had lost their fetuses due to “health emergencies” during pregnancy, said the ACDATEE abortion rights group. El Salvador bans abortion in all cases, and terminating a pregnancy can send a woman to jail for up to eight years. “We continue fighting for the freedom of the rest of the women imprisoned,” said Herrera.</description></item></channel></rss>