<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>seek on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/seek/</link><description>Recent content in seek on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 14:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/seek/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Simone Biles, others seek $1B-plus from FBI over Nassar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0ad68c3814631b63d2096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 14:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0ad68c3814631b63d2096/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — Olympic gold medalist Simone Biles and dozens of other women who say they were sexually assaulted by Larry Nassar are seeking more than $1 billion from the FBI for failing to stop the sports doctor when the agency first received allegations against him, lawyers said Wednesday.
Highlights Olympic gold medalist Simone Biles and dozens of other women who say they were sexually assaulted by Larry Nassar are seeking more than $1 billion from the FBI for failing to stop the now convicted sports doctor when the agency first received allegations against him, lawyers said Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee makes camping on public land a felony.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f80e255deeb96c53c8fdc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f80e255deeb96c53c8fdc/</guid><description>COOKEVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Miranda Atnip lost her home during the coronavirus pandemic after her boyfriend moved out and she fell behind on bills. Living in a car, the 34-year-old worries every day about getting money for food, finding somewhere to shower, and saving up enough money for an apartment where her three children can live with her again.
Highlights Tennessee is about to become the first U.S. state to make it a felony to camp on local public property such as parks.</description></item></channel></rss>