<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rate/</link><description>Recent content in rate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fed Governor Christopher Waller says he’s prepared to take rates past ‘neutral’ to fight inflation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295b1c23b2b93906b7d7718/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295b1c23b2b93906b7d7718/</guid><description>Fed Governor Christopher Waller said he would support hikes that pass through exceed the &amp;quot;neutral&amp;quot; level.
Highlights Fed Governor Christopher Waller says he would support hikes that exceed the &amp;ldquo;neutral&amp;rdquo; level. Waller: &amp;ldquo;I am not taking 50 basis-point hikes off the table until I see inflation coming down closer to our 2 percent target&amp;rdquo; The central bank official said he thinks the Fed can raise rates and tamp down demand without causing a severe economic downturn.</description></item><item><title>Guns killed more youngsters than cars for the first time in 2020</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f989bf88db1e492adf3c4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f989bf88db1e492adf3c4/</guid><description>Guns killed more in 2021, too. The increase is driven by the number of Black youths killed by firearms.
Highlights The Washington Post analysis reviewed CDC death records for people ages 1 through 19 from 2011 through October 2021. The change was caused by a 30 percent increase in gun deaths for people 19 and younger in 2020. Non-Hispanic Black youths are the only group for whom guns are deadlier than cars.</description></item><item><title>Roofing scammers throw Florida’s property insurance market into chaos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62892b42093585a27c8b49c4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 18:11:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62892b42093585a27c8b49c4/</guid><description>Florida lawmakers are scrambling to fix a property insurance crisis that has has forced painful rate hikes and put several companies out of business.
Highlights Insurance industry&amp;rsquo;s net losses have risen in each of the past five years, surpassing $1 billion in 2021. Florida is the most volatile property insurance market in the country, an industry spokesman says. Lawmakers will begin a special session on Monday to address the state&amp;rsquo;s property insurance crisis.</description></item><item><title>Fed to fight inflation with fastest rate hikes in decades</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270491beb3c8e9ef6477017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270491beb3c8e9ef6477017/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve is poised this week to accelerate its most drastic steps in three decades to attack inflation by making it costlier to borrow — for a car, a home, a business deal, a credit card purchase — all of which will compound Americans&amp;rsquo; financial strains and likely weaken the economy.
Highlights The Federal Reserve is poised this week to begin unleashing its most drastic steps in three decades to attack inflation by making it costlier to borrow.</description></item><item><title>30-year fixed mortgage crosses 5%</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d94bc730e878ba9381295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d94bc730e878ba9381295/</guid><description>The average rate on the popular 30-year fixed mortgage just crossed 5%, for the first time 2011, save two days in 2018. It stood at 3.38% one year ago today.
Highlights The average rate on the popular 30-year fixed mortgage just crossed 5%, now standing at 5.02%. This is the first time it has crossed that threshold since 2011, save two days in 2018. It stood at 3.38% one year ago today.</description></item><item><title>Inflation rises 7.5% over the past year, even more than expected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620547a818dd4b36a4e08358/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 17:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620547a818dd4b36a4e08358/</guid><description>The consumer price index was expected to increase 7.2% from a year ago, according to a Dow Jones economist survey.
Highlights Consumer price index for January rose 7.5% compared with a year ago, the Labor Department says. That compared with Dow Jones estimates of 7.2%. Core inflation rose at its fastest level since August 1982. Stock market futures declined following the report, with rate-sensitive tech stocks hit especially hard. The chances of a 0.</description></item></channel></rss>