<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rate/</link><description>Recent content in rate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fed to fight inflation with fastest rate hikes in decades</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270491beb3c8e9ef6477017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270491beb3c8e9ef6477017/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve is poised this week to accelerate its most drastic steps in three decades to attack inflation by making it costlier to borrow — for a car, a home, a business deal, a credit card purchase — all of which will compound Americans&amp;rsquo; financial strains and likely weaken the economy.
Highlights The Federal Reserve is poised this week to begin unleashing its most drastic steps in three decades to attack inflation by making it costlier to borrow.</description></item><item><title>30-year fixed mortgage crosses 5%</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d94bc730e878ba9381295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 13:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d94bc730e878ba9381295/</guid><description>The average rate on the popular 30-year fixed mortgage just crossed 5%, for the first time 2011, save two days in 2018. It stood at 3.38% one year ago today.
Highlights The average rate on the popular 30-year fixed mortgage just crossed 5%, now standing at 5.02%. This is the first time it has crossed that threshold since 2011, save two days in 2018. It stood at 3.38% one year ago today.</description></item><item><title>Inflation rises 7.5% over the past year, even more than expected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620547a818dd4b36a4e08358/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 17:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620547a818dd4b36a4e08358/</guid><description>The consumer price index was expected to increase 7.2% from a year ago, according to a Dow Jones economist survey.
Highlights Consumer price index for January rose 7.5% compared with a year ago, the Labor Department says. That compared with Dow Jones estimates of 7.2%. Core inflation rose at its fastest level since August 1982. Stock market futures declined following the report, with rate-sensitive tech stocks hit especially hard. The chances of a 0.</description></item></channel></rss>