<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>staff on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/staff/</link><description>Recent content in staff on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/staff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas school district asks parents to become substitute teachers amid COVID surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</guid><description>According to Hays CISD, parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation to become substitute teachers.
Summary The Hays Consolidated Independent School District (Hays CISD) in Kyle is asking parents to consider applying to become a substitute teacher as coronavirus continues to surge across Texas. According to Hays CISD, the parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation.</description></item><item><title>62,000 Los Angeles students and staff test positive for Covid ahead of return to school Tuesday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</guid><description>As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show.
Summary (CNN) As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show. The Los Angeles Unified School District (LAUSD) is requiring all students and employees to show a negative test result before returning. It is the nation&amp;rsquo;s second largest district, with more than 640,000 students in grades K-12.</description></item><item><title>Outbreak reported at Rhode Island hospital after Covid-positive, asymptomatic staff asked to work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dace794f10c4f9701608db/</guid><description>A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due
Summary A Rhode Island hospital is dealing with a Covid-19 outbreak with patients after it asked staff who had tested positive, but were asymptomatic, to come in due to a staffing shortage. On Saturday, the hospital had two Covid-positive staff members come into work and three on Monday, according to a memo posted on the official Rhode Island state website.</description></item><item><title>Citigroup to enforce 'no-jab, no-job' policy starting Jan. 14 - source</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9a70cd8fece602047fcc7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9a70cd8fece602047fcc7/</guid><description>Citigroup Inc staff in the United States who have not been vaccinated against COVID-19 by Jan. 14 will be placed on unpaid leave and fired at the end of the month unless they are granted an exemption, according to a company memo seen by Reuters on Friday.
Summary When it announced its policy, Citigroup also said it would assess exemptions on religious or medical grounds, or any other accommodation by state or local law, on a case-by-case basis.</description></item><item><title>Autopsy: Death of Black Kansas teen in custody was homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb42b96bd7dae261c96a96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb42b96bd7dae261c96a96/</guid><description>An autopsy report says that a Black youth’s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicide
Summary An autopsy report says that a Black youth’s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicideTOPEKA, Kan. &amp;ndash; A Black youth&amp;rsquo;s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicide, according to an autopsy report released Monday that contradicts an earlier, preliminary finding that the teenager hadn&amp;rsquo;t suffered life-threatening injuries.</description></item></channel></rss>