<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>staff on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/staff/</link><description>Recent content in staff on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/staff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Citigroup to enforce 'no-jab, no-job' policy starting Jan. 14 - source</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9a70cd8fece602047fcc7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 15:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9a70cd8fece602047fcc7/</guid><description>Citigroup Inc staff in the United States who have not been vaccinated against COVID-19 by Jan. 14 will be placed on unpaid leave and fired at the end of the month unless they are granted an exemption, according to a company memo seen by Reuters on Friday.
Summary When it announced its policy, Citigroup also said it would assess exemptions on religious or medical grounds, or any other accommodation by state or local law, on a case-by-case basis.</description></item><item><title>Autopsy: Death of Black Kansas teen in custody was homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb42b96bd7dae261c96a96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb42b96bd7dae261c96a96/</guid><description>An autopsy report says that a Black youth’s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicide
Summary An autopsy report says that a Black youth’s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicideTOPEKA, Kan. &amp;ndash; A Black youth&amp;rsquo;s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicide, according to an autopsy report released Monday that contradicts an earlier, preliminary finding that the teenager hadn&amp;rsquo;t suffered life-threatening injuries.</description></item></channel></rss>