<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arbery on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arbery/</link><description>Recent content in arbery on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:49:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arbery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ahmaud Arbery: White trio guilty of hate crimes in killing of black man while he was out running</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215848c68b57b186495b716/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215848c68b57b186495b716/</guid><description>Greg and Travis McMichael, and their neighbour William &amp;quot;Roddie&amp;quot; Bryan have already been convicted of the murder of Mr Arbery and sentenced to life in prison.
Highlights Ahmaud Arbery, 25, was chased and shot by Travis McMichael, 35; his father and former police officer Greg, 66, and their neighbour William &amp;ldquo;Roddie&amp;rdquo; Bryan, 52, on 23 February 2020 in Satilla Shores just outside the city of Brunswick, Georgia. The trio had denied federal hate crime charges but were convicted of violating Mr Arbery&amp;rsquo;s civil rights and targeting him because he was black.</description></item><item><title>Three men convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery sentenced to life in prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8b805d451137bd8cc0f83/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8b805d451137bd8cc0f83/</guid><description>The three white men convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery, a Black man, in Georgia were sentenced Friday to life in prison.
Summary The three white men convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery, a Black man, in Georgia were sentenced Friday to life in prison. The sentences for Travis McMichael, who shot Arbery; and his father, Gregory McMichael, do not carry the possibility of parole. An attorney for Travis McMichael said he &amp;ldquo;should have the opportunity to show that he&amp;rsquo;s grown, to show that he&amp;rsquo;s changed.</description></item></channel></rss>