<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>systems on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/systems/</link><description>Recent content in systems on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 06:17:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Germany agrees to send heavy weapons to Ukraine after major policy U-turn | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268dfeea79ba879da7d314b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 06:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268dfeea79ba879da7d314b/</guid><description>Germany has agreed to deliver anti-aircraft tanks to Ukraine, the German Defense Ministry announced on Tuesday, a move that underscores a major shift in its approach to providing military help to Ukraine.
Highlights Germany has agreed to deliver anti-aircraft tanks to Ukraine, the German Defense Ministry announced on Tuesday. The move underscores a major shift in Germany&amp;rsquo;s approach to providing military help to Ukraine. Germany initially resisted calls to provide weaponry to Kyiv, agreeing only to provide humanitarian help and medical equipment.</description></item><item><title>US Secretary of State Antony Blinken will visit Kyiv on Sunday - Zelensky</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626540912723ebe1cce58c71/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 12:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626540912723ebe1cce58c71/</guid><description>The US secretary of state, and the defence secretary, are expected in Ukraine later, President Zelensky says.
Highlights Two residential blocks were hit, killing at least eight people, including a three-month-old, her mother and grandmother. The Ukrainian government has said the killing of baby Kira and the seven other victims is an act of terror, designed to break people’s will to fight. The Russians claim they hit legitimate military facilities. But, there could be another rationale for the strikes, one that is as effective as it is cynical.</description></item><item><title>Russia says it used hypersonic missiles in Ukraine for first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236fe2f5d0597f9286eeef5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 10:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236fe2f5d0597f9286eeef5/</guid><description>Aeroballistic missiles destroyed a large underground warehouse containing missiles and aviation ammunition, Moscow says.
Highlights Russia says it used its newest Kinzhal hypersonic missiles for the first time in Ukraine to destroy a weapons storage site in the country’s west. The aeroballistic missiles destroyed a large underground warehouse containing missiles and aviation ammunition, Moscow says. The region of Ivano-Frankivsk shares a 50km (30 miles) long border with NATO member Romania. President Vladimir Putin announced an array of new weapons in 2018 in one of his most bellicose speeches in years, saying they could hit almost any point in the world and evade a United States-built missile shield.</description></item><item><title>‘Irreversible’: No easy fix for water fouled by gas driller</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211f842bd9e17f404606f9b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 08:14:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211f842bd9e17f404606f9b/</guid><description>DIMOCK, Pa. (AP) — Meeting with a man whose well water has been polluted for years, officials in the Pennsylvania attorney general’s office asked him whether he’d consider accepting a treatment system from the gas driller charged with fouling his aquifer.
Highlights Dimock, Pennsylvania, is one of the best-known pollution cases ever to emerge from the U.S. drilling and fracking boom. Faulty gas wells drilled by Cabot Oil &amp;amp; Gas were blamed for leaking methane into the groundwater in Dimock.</description></item></channel></rss>