<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wages on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wages/</link><description>Recent content in wages on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LA Resident Physicians Threaten To Strike Over Low Wages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e056235155fea195e0af4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e056235155fea195e0af4/</guid><description>The unionized health workers have until the end of May to vote on a strike.
Highlights Unionized resident physicians at three L.A. hospitals will hold a strike vote next week. They want a 7% raise in pay and housing stipends. The voting period for the strike will end May 30. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear when a strike and walkout could take place over the summer if approved by members. The last contract with the hospitals expired Sept.</description></item><item><title>Target raises its minimum wage to as much as $24 an hour</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621efca21f2048a0356d87c0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 05:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621efca21f2048a0356d87c0/</guid><description>Worker shortages around the U.S. during the pandemic have forced retailers to boost their pay.
Highlights Target announced in 2017 it would increase hourly wages to $15 per hour by 2020. The Minneapolis-based discount retailer said Monday that it will adopt minimum wages that range from $15 to $24 an hour. Target&amp;rsquo;s CEO Brian Cornell: &amp;ldquo;We want to continue to have an industry-leading position&amp;rdquo; The new starting wage range is part of a company plan to spend an additional $300 million on its labor force this year that will also include broader, faster access to health care coverage for its hourly workers.</description></item><item><title>Workers at nearly 80 Kroger's King Soopers go on strike as talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03e92708b1033bb719187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03e92708b1033bb719187/</guid><description>More than 8,000 workers at nearly 80 King Soopers stores went on strike for better wages on Wednesday as negotiations stalled, but the stores stayed open as the Kroger Co-owned Colorado chain hired temporary staff and promoted online ordering.
Summary A union member raises a sign outside a Kroger&amp;rsquo;s King Soopers store during a protest as workers go on strike in Denver, Colorado, U.S., January 12, 2022. The striking workers are employed at King Soopers stores in the Denver metropolitan area, Boulder, Parker and Broomfield cities of Colorado, among others.</description></item></channel></rss>