<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ny on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ny/</link><description>Recent content in ny on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NY passes bill raising age to buy, own semi-automatic rifles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299c2088113d87ae45f8024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299c2088113d87ae45f8024/</guid><description>ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York&amp;rsquo;s legislature voted Thursday to ban anyone under age 21 from buying or possessing a semi-automatic rifle, a major change to state firearm laws pushed through less than three weeks after an 18-year-old used one of the guns to kill 10 people at a supermarket in Buffalo.
Highlights The age limit bill passed the Senate along party lines, 43-20, and in the Assembly 102-47, and will now head to Hochul’s desk for her signature.</description></item><item><title>Amazon union vote has strong lead in NY vote count; losing in Alabama</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62476ab643548491a47eea1d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 21:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62476ab643548491a47eea1d/</guid><description>Amazon.com Inc workers at a warehouse in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island have so far voted 57% in favor of unionizing with a final tally due on Friday, a potential landmark victory for organized labor at the second-largest U.S. private employer.
Highlights Amazon workers at a warehouse in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island have so far voted 57% in favor of unionizing with a final tally due on Friday. That win contrasted with 53% of Amazon workers in Alabama rejecting unionization, in a still-not final outcome.</description></item><item><title>N.Y. college student burned in suspected acid attack criticizes police investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236e260bdac757620e615d7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 08:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236e260bdac757620e615d7/</guid><description>A Hofstra University student who was badly burned in a suspected acid attack last year detailed the pain she still endures and questioned whether Long Island police are taking the investigation seriously.
Highlights Hofstra University student Nafiah Ikram, 22, was walking into her Elmont home last March around 8:30 p.m. when a person ran up to her and threw a liquid in her face. Ikram has spent the past year in and out of the hospital undergoing surgeries.</description></item></channel></rss>