<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>southern on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/southern/</link><description>Recent content in southern on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 13:36:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/southern/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Barrel containing human remains discovered in Lake Mead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62712fa09ae6ca62d0ec3444/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 13:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62712fa09ae6ca62d0ec3444/</guid><description>LAS VEGAS (AP) — A body inside a barrel was found over the weekend on the the newly exposed bottom of Nevada&amp;rsquo;s Lake Mead as drought depletes one of the largest U.S. reservoirs — and officials predicted the discovery could be just the first of more grim finds.
Highlights A body inside a barrel was found over the the the newly exposed bottom of Nevada’s Lake Mead as drought depletes one of the largest U.</description></item><item><title>Workers discover ‘unprecedented’ Phoenician necropolis in southern Spain</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d0be8d7bb1be7ad9d4308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 10:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d0be8d7bb1be7ad9d4308/</guid><description>Preliminary surveys in Osuna have turned up eight burial vaults as well as staircases
Highlights Archaeologists find Phoenician-Carthaginian cemetery in the town of Osuna, 55 miles (90km) east of Seville. Site dates back to the fourth or fifth century BC and is highly unusual as such sites are normally found in coastal areas rather than so far inland. The only similar finds have been made around the coast of Cádiz, which was founded by the Phoenicians in 1100BC and which is one of the oldest continuously inhabited cities in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Lukashenko promises to send "whole contingent of Belarusian army" to the border with Ukraine claiming that "the Ukrainians have started dragging troops there”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01eb5e0e2347fcede0d28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01eb5e0e2347fcede0d28/</guid><description>Summary Lukashenko explained this by the fact that &amp;ldquo;the Ukrainians have allegedly started dragging troops there”Alexander Lukashenko at &amp;ldquo;Big Conversation with the President&amp;rdquo; BeltaSelf-proclaimed President of Belarus Alexander Lukashenko said that he would take &amp;ldquo;a whole contingent of the Belarusian army&amp;rdquo; to the border with Ukraine. Lukashenko made this statement during a meeting with the chairman of the State Border Committee of Belarus. We just want to protect our southern border.</description></item></channel></rss>