<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>san on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/san/</link><description>Recent content in san on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 18:19:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/san/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>San Jose police officer faces charges for masturbating during disturbance call: D.A.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ea106b350a098a158bb22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 18:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ea106b350a098a158bb22/</guid><description>A San Jose police officer faces indecent exposure charges for allegedly masturbating at a family&amp;rsquo;s home while responding to a disturbance call last month, officials say.
Highlights Matthew Dominguez, 32, was arrested on Thursday, Santa Clara County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s office said. The incident took place April 21, when he and two other officers were sent to a home on a call that a family member, who is mentally ill, was being violent.</description></item><item><title>Marriott gives guest's luggage worth over $8K to alleged thief, only required to pay $500 in damages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62734bc4cfeef9259ce01b49/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62734bc4cfeef9259ce01b49/</guid><description>A tourist sued a San Francisco Marriott for giving luggage to an alleged criminal, but the hotel is only required to pay $500 in damages.
Highlights Bob Sabouni lost $8,390.88 of his belongings to an alleged criminal. He sued the San Francisco Marriott Marquis and won. Marriott successfully appealed the case, but a judge ruled that it was done so unfairly. The Inn Keeper&amp;rsquo;s statute limits a hotel&amp;rsquo;s liability for guests&amp;rsquo; belongings to $1,000.</description></item><item><title>San Jose Kidnapping: 3-Month-Old Baby Found, Suspects in Custody</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626909a0a183b6dd22a3843a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 09:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626909a0a183b6dd22a3843a/</guid><description>A 3-month-old baby who was taken from a San Jose home has been found safe.
Highlights 3-month-old Brandon Cuellar was taken to a hospital as a precaution. The baby was taken for a checkup before being reunited with his mother, sources tell NBC Bay Area. Police said a suspect entered an apartment in the 1000 block of Elm Street on Monday afternoon and took the baby as the child&amp;rsquo;s grandmother was unloading groceries.</description></item><item><title>Three gold medals stolen from Paralympian's car in Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e7d49f9ebd7728fa63ba9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 09:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e7d49f9ebd7728fa63ba9/</guid><description>Three gold medals stolen from a Paralympian&amp;rsquo;s car in Texas Saturday were recovered by the next day, according to police.
Highlights Three gold medals stolen from a man&amp;rsquo;s car found in Texas. Police say they were stolen from the back of the car. Police are still looking for the medals. The medals will be returned to the owner of the stolen car. The man had his left leg amputated above the knee after a motorcycle accident in 2009.</description></item><item><title>2 killed, 2 injured in shooting near San Francisco's Alice Chalmers Playground, police say.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ba8ece40d3391a6e38bd4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ba8ece40d3391a6e38bd4/</guid><description>Police are investigating a shooting that left two dead and two injured near the Alice Chalmers Playground in San Francisco Sunday afternoon.
Highlights Police are investigating a shooting that left two dead and two injured near the Alice Chalmers Playground in San Francisco Sunday afternoon. The incident happened at around 4:39 p.m. on the 600 block of Brunswick Avenue. Police say they located four adult male victims with gunshot wounds. One of the victims was grazed in the head with the bullet, before succumbing to their injuries.</description></item><item><title>Russians are blocked at US border, Ukrainians are admitted</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c363cac842f5f804c1f6a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c363cac842f5f804c1f6a/</guid><description>Sandra Schulman
Highlights About three dozen would-be asylum seekers from Russia found themselves blocked from entering the U.S. on Friday while a group of Ukrainians flashed passports and were escorted across the border. The Russians — 34 as of Friday — had been camped several days at the busiest US border crossing with Mexico, two days after the city of Tijuana officials gently urged them to leave. The number of Russian asylum seekers entering at US land crossings surpassed 8,600 from September through February, about 30 times the same time a year earlier were processed under laws that allow them to seek asylum under laws allowing them to do so.</description></item><item><title>Surfer killed in shark attack at California beach, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7867466d039d017d3c11a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 21:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7867466d039d017d3c11a/</guid><description>A male surfer was killed in a shark attack in Morro Bay, California, on Christmas Eve, the Morro Bay Harbor Department confirmed to CNN.
Summary (CNN) A male surfer was killed in a shark attack in Morro Bay, California, on Christmas Eve, the Morro Bay Harbor Department confirmed to CNN. &amp;ldquo;Harbor, Police and Fire Departments responded to a report of a male victim unresponsive on the beach after he was pulled from the water suffering from an apparent shark attack,&amp;rdquo; the Harbor Department said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest 76-year-old man in cold case of 1978 strangling death of teen in San Francisco</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</guid><description>Description Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City
Summary Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City teen who was found dead after visiting Golden Gate Park. Mark Stanley Personette, of Conifer, Colorado, was arrested Dec.</description></item></channel></rss>