<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stress on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stress/</link><description>Recent content in stress on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 13:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia attempts to trade civilians for military prisoners - Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d380bddfb5478d9520097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 13:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d380bddfb5478d9520097/</guid><description>Inconsistent air support has left Russia facing considerable challenges, the UK&amp;rsquo;s ministry of defence says.
Highlights Ukrainian soldiers are under siege on the territory of the Azovstal steel plant. The number of people holed up in Mariupol is unclear but it’s thought to be hundreds, including some children. The fighters’ relatives say the men are exhausted, dirty and hungry with food and water supplies running out. They say they’re even ready to act as a human shield if that helps evacuate the men to safety.</description></item><item><title>'Tsunami' of woes: U.S. school shootings spike amid pandemic stress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</guid><description>Signs are emerging that the challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers studying the phenomenon worry it will only grow.
Highlights Signs are emerging that the stresses and challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers who are studying the phenomenon worry it will only get worse. Already, campuses have been the site of 141 shootings so far during the 2021-22 school year - more than at any point in the previous decade.</description></item></channel></rss>