<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wrote on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wrote/</link><description>Recent content in wrote on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wrote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California bees can be fish and have the same protections, a court has ruled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f159efb36cf783ac93b07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:09:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f159efb36cf783ac93b07/</guid><description>A fishy ruling from California: A California court has ruled bees can legally be considered fish under specific circumstances.
Highlights The ruling reversed an earlier judgment which found bumblebees could not be considered &amp;ldquo;fish&amp;rdquo; under the California Endangered Species Act. Notably, invertebrates are absent from the list of protected species. California&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal ruled bees can legally be considered fish under specific circumstances. The ruling reverses an earlier ruling which found the bumblebee was not allowed to be classified as a fish under the endangered species Act of 2062 and 2067.</description></item><item><title>Texts show Marjorie Taylor Greene asked Meadows about martial law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267fdcfd39fdcaa74f67c27/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267fdcfd39fdcaa74f67c27/</guid><description>The Georgia congresswoman has testified she doesn&amp;rsquo;t recall whether she encouraged Trump to impose martial law.
Highlights Georgia Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene texted then-White House chief of staff Mark Meadows to tell him some GOP members of Congress had privately suggested former President Trump should declare martial law. She testified last week she doesn&amp;rsquo;t recall whether she encouraged the president to impose martial law as a way to remain in power.</description></item><item><title>Former Kentucky clerk Kim Davis violated rights of same-sex couples, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236f02da07076bc3a44fabb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236f02da07076bc3a44fabb/</guid><description>Former clerk Kim Davis refused to issue marriage licenses to two same-sex couples in 2015.
Highlights U.S. District Judge David Bunning in Ashland issued the ruling Friday in two longstanding lawsuits involving Kim Davis and two same-sex couples. With the decision, a jury trial will still need to take place to decide on damages the couples could be owed. Bunning reasoned that Davis &amp;ldquo;cannot use her own constitutional rights as a shield to violate the constitutional rights of others while performing her duties as an elected official&amp;rdquo; The case could return to the Supreme Court, which declined to take the case in October 2020.</description></item><item><title>A mother says her son was sold in a mock slave auction. School district votes unanimously on action plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</guid><description>A North Carolina school board voted unanimously Monday to approve an action plan after reported racial bullying in the district, including a student-organized mock auction of Black students.
Highlights A group of parents and community members had called on the Chatham County School District to make changes after several reported racial bullying instances at schools in the district. Ashley Palmer said her Black son told her that some of his classmates were sold in a mock slave auction at J.</description></item><item><title>Young Ukrainian volunteer killed delivering aid to dog shelter near Kyiv: ‘She was a hero’ - National</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245ec44c82d9f4715952c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245ec44c82d9f4715952c9/</guid><description>A young Ukrainian volunteer was shot and killed near Kyiv after delivering supplies to a dog shelter. Her friends say she was targeted at close-range by Russian troops.
Highlights Anastasiia Yalanskaya, a young volunteer in Ukraine, was shot and killed while delivering food to a dog shelter in Bucha, 30 kilometres outside Kyiv, on Friday. Friends and family say her car was deliberately targeted at close-range by Russian troops. Russian troops are increasingly killing civilians at random as a way to scare the population into submission, friends say.</description></item><item><title>EA Sports to remove Russian teams from FIFA, NHL video games</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ff9edef7727f2e5a706f7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ff9edef7727f2e5a706f7/</guid><description>EA sports wrote the move is &amp;quot;in line with our partners at FIFA and UEFA[.]&amp;quot;
Highlights Russian and Belarusian hockey teams have been removed from all international competitions. The International Ice Hockey Federation has also banned Russia and Belarus from international games. EA Sports said the move is &amp;ldquo;in line with the decision to remove the Russian national team from the latest FIFA video game franchise. The decision was made by the International Hockey Federation, the European Union and the Russian Federation of Hockey Hockey Federation.</description></item><item><title>Two top Russian billionaires speak out against invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</guid><description>Oleg Deripaska and Ukrainian-born Mikhail Fridman call for peace, as activities come under threat from sanctions
Highlights Russian billionaires Mikhail Fridman and Oleg Deripaska speak out against Moscow’s invasion of Ukraine. In a letter to his employees he called for an end to the “bloodshed” in an email to staff at LetterOne. He joins a small group of prominent Russians – including popular actors, musicians and television presenters – who have called on President Vladimir Putin stop the military operation in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Utah billionaire leaves Mormon church, donates $600K to LGBTQ group</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</guid><description>Description Jeff Green, a billionaire from Utah, resigned from the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and donated to LGBTQ group Equality Utah.
Summary “The church leadership is not honest about its history, its finances, and its advocacy,” he wrote, according to the Tribune. “We made this investment sizable and publicly to send a message that Equality Utah isn’t going anywhere,” Green wrote, adding that he hopes the donation is the first of many.</description></item></channel></rss>