<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>press on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/press/</link><description>Recent content in press on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:14:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/press/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>17 people shot on N. Water St. Friday night, Milwaukee police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628053c6389460d8cae0b735/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628053c6389460d8cae0b735/</guid><description>17 people were shot on Water St. in downtown Milwaukee Friday night, according to Milwaukee Police.
Highlights 17 people were shot on Water St. in downtown Milwaukee Friday night. Police say it happened just after 11:00 p.m. Friday in the 1100 block of N. Water St., near E. Highland Ave. The victims range from 15 to 47 years of age, police say. Police and Mayor Cavalier Johnson held a press conference Saturday afternoon to address Friday&amp;rsquo;s violence.</description></item><item><title>US accuses financial website Zero Hedge of spreading Russian propaganda</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c488b56e1c92fe7378875/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c488b56e1c92fe7378875/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. intelligence officials on Tuesday accused a conservative financial news website with a significant American readership of amplifying Kremlin propaganda and alleged five media outlets targeting Ukrainians have taken direction from Russian spies.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Ministry announced Tuesday that some units participating in military exercises would begin returning to their bases. In a response posted online Tuesday morning, the website said it “has never worked, collaborated or cooperated with Russia, nor are there any links to spy agencies” Zero Hedge has been sharply critical of Biden and posted stories about allegations of wrongdoing by his son Hunter.</description></item></channel></rss>