<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sue on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sue/</link><description>Recent content in sue on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Victims, parents of Oxford school shooting victims sue school employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628de4e0c5f62b4bdd93e509/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628de4e0c5f62b4bdd93e509/</guid><description>The lawsuit against Oxford Community School District and administrators
Highlights Plaintiffs and families of victims of November shooting in Michigan file lawsuit against school district, school administrators. Lawsuit accuses administrators of failing to notify law enforcement of the actions of the accused shooter leading up to the shooting. Justin Shilling and Tate Myre, who were killed in the shooting, and representatives for four minors who were injured in shooting. The lawsuit claims other students saw Ethan Crumbley with shell casings and live ammunition rounds one day before shooting.</description></item><item><title>Sixteen states sue the Postal Service over plan to buy gas-powered vehicles.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c2b68205659c4f6f868bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c2b68205659c4f6f868bf/</guid><description>The lawsuits allege the Postal Service&amp;rsquo;s environmental analysis to justify spending up to $11.3 billion on gas-powered delivery trucks was deeply flawed.
Highlights 16 states sue U.S. Postal Service over its plan to replace its aging fleet with thousands of gas-powered delivery vehicles over the next decade. The lawsuits allege the agency&amp;rsquo;s environmental analysis to justify spending up to $11.3 billion on the gas trucks was deeply flawed. The Postal Service has about 230,000 vehicles, making up about one-third of the country&amp;rsquo;s entire federal fleet.</description></item></channel></rss>