<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>actor on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/actor/</link><description>Recent content in actor on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 20:11:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/actor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Goodfellas’ Star Ray Liotta Dies at 67</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fdedda65cf001017e21b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 20:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fdedda65cf001017e21b1/</guid><description>Ray Liotta has died. The &amp;lsquo;Goodfellas&amp;rsquo; star and &amp;lsquo;Field Of Dreams&amp;rsquo; actor was 67.
Highlights Actor Ray Liotta dies in his sleep in the Dominican Republic, where he was shooting the film Dangerous Waters. Liotta, 67, was engaged to be married to Jacy Nittolo. His career breakout came in the 1990 Martin Scorsese crime classic Goodfellas. He also starred with Taron Egerton in the Apple TV+ series Black Bird, recurred on Prime Video’s Hanna and starred opposite Jennifer Lopez in the 2016-18 NBC police drama Shades of Blue.</description></item><item><title>Sky News: Kevin Spacey charged with four counts of sexual assault against three men, CPS says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fc3241bd5f202b4ef3752/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fc3241bd5f202b4ef3752/</guid><description>The alleged incidents took place in London between March 2005 and August 2008, and in Gloucestershire in April 2013.
Highlights Oscar-winning actor Kevin Spacey charged with four counts of sexual assault against three men. The 62-year-old has also been charged with causing a person to engage in penetrative sexual activity without consent. The alleged incidents took place in London between March 2005 and August 2008, and in Gloucestershire in April 2013.</description></item><item><title>Actor Will Smith banned from attending Oscars for 10 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250a51e3c436a46c45715d2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 21:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250a51e3c436a46c45715d2/</guid><description>Will Smith will not be allowed to attend the Academy Awards for the next 10 years, as a result of his slapping comedian Chris Rock on stage during this year&amp;rsquo;s Oscar ceremony, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts &amp;amp; Sciences announced in a statement obtained by CNN.
Highlights Will Smith will not be allowed to attend the Academy Awards for the next 10 years. The decision was made during a Board of Governors meeting held earlier in the day in Los Angeles.</description></item></channel></rss>