<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fired on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fired/</link><description>Recent content in fired on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 23:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fired/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>911 dispatcher fired after allegedly hanging up on store employee during Buffalo shooting call</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a946ffd4003af0917ad8f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 23:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a946ffd4003af0917ad8f/</guid><description>The 911 dispatcher accused of hanging up on an employee calling for help during the supermarket shooting that killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, last month has been fired, officials said.
Highlights The 911 dispatcher accused of hanging up on an employee calling for help during the supermarket shooting that killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, last month has been fired, officials said. The assistant office manager at Tops Friendly Market called 911 when a white gunman, 18, stormed the store on May 14 and opened fire.</description></item><item><title>Teens shot trying to break into man's car were 13 and 16-years-old, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bf246ad859237b7d3b81d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 14:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bf246ad859237b7d3b81d/</guid><description>According to investigators, the call first came in around 2 a.m. as a report of a car burglary with shots fired on Martinwood Drive.
Highlights Two teenagers were shot by a man after reportedly trying to break into his car, Orange County deputies said. The call first came in around 2 a.m. as a report of a car burglary with shots fired on Martinwood Drive in Pine Hills. The victim said the suspects made &amp;ldquo;threatening movements toward him&amp;rdquo; and so he fired several shots.</description></item><item><title>Gay substitute teacher says he was fired after handing out Pride bracelets to students</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247cdf457af244b34e32179/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 04:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247cdf457af244b34e32179/</guid><description>A gay Ohio substitute teacher was fired last week after handing out Pride bracelets to high school students, the latest example of LGBTQ discussion in schools sparking controversy amid heated debates in school boards and states around the country.
Highlights Jay Bowman said he was fired for handing out Pride bracelets to his students at Huntington High School in Chillicothe, Ohio. Bowman says he also answered questions from students about the LGBTQ advocacy group.</description></item><item><title>George Floyd’s 4-year-old niece shot after someone fired several shots into Houston apartment, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</guid><description>A 4-year-old girl was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.
Summary The shooting happened on Houston&amp;rsquo;s southside when someone fire multiple shots into the apartmentHOUSTON – George Floyd’s four-year-old niece was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.</description></item><item><title>Over 65 shots fired on busy Philadelphia street; 6 wounded</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0506c95d92b6a62854313/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 13:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0506c95d92b6a62854313/</guid><description>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Six gunmen fired more than 65 rounds on a Philadelphia street, sending nighttime pedestrians on a busy block teeming with markets and restaurants scrambling for cover and injuring six people, at least one of them critically, police said Friday.
Summary A man walks past a parked vehicle with a bullet holes in the rear window on Friday, Dec. 31, 2021, in Philadelphia. Two gunmen fired more than 65 rounds on a Philadelphia street last night, sending nighttime pedestrians on a busy block teeming with markets and restaurants scrambling for cover and injuring six people, at least one of them critically, police said Friday.</description></item></channel></rss>