<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fired on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fired/</link><description>Recent content in fired on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fired/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>George Floyd’s 4-year-old niece shot after someone fired several shots into Houston apartment, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5eacf520faacb3b29c012/</guid><description>A 4-year-old girl was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.
Summary The shooting happened on Houston&amp;rsquo;s southside when someone fire multiple shots into the apartmentHOUSTON – George Floyd’s four-year-old niece was shot on Saturday at her home on Houston’s south side, and authorities are trying to find the person or people who fired multiple times into the apartment.</description></item><item><title>Over 65 shots fired on busy Philadelphia street; 6 wounded</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0506c95d92b6a62854313/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 13:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0506c95d92b6a62854313/</guid><description>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Six gunmen fired more than 65 rounds on a Philadelphia street, sending nighttime pedestrians on a busy block teeming with markets and restaurants scrambling for cover and injuring six people, at least one of them critically, police said Friday.
Summary A man walks past a parked vehicle with a bullet holes in the rear window on Friday, Dec. 31, 2021, in Philadelphia. Two gunmen fired more than 65 rounds on a Philadelphia street last night, sending nighttime pedestrians on a busy block teeming with markets and restaurants scrambling for cover and injuring six people, at least one of them critically, police said Friday.</description></item></channel></rss>