<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>drivers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/drivers/</link><description>Recent content in drivers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/drivers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Walmart says it is raising truckers’ pay and starting a training program as it grapples with driver shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fe0bb488d355f55ec5200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fe0bb488d355f55ec5200/</guid><description>Walmart is trying to expand the pipeline of truck drivers amid a national shortage.
Highlights Walmart says truck drivers will now make between $95,000 and $110,000 in their first year with Walmart. The retailer is ramping up recruiting efforts for truck drivers amid a tight market for trucking labor. The shortage of truck drivers in the U.S. hit an all-time high of more than 80,000 workers last year, trade group says.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco drivers can now get a text before getting towed, the first of its kind in the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2e1a82f4d83c39bf84bd3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2e1a82f4d83c39bf84bd3/</guid><description>San Francisco is the first city in America to offer this service.
Summary San Francisco officials are now offering drivers a tiny bit of relief. The San Francisco Examiner reported Thursday that locals can now receive text messages warning them if their car is about to be impounded, making San Francisco the first city in the country with such a service. The program, naturally called Text Before Tow, will send San Francisco drivers who opt in a text when their car may be towed for 72-hour parking, blocking driveways or parking in construction zones or temporary no-parking zones.</description></item><item><title>Ford recalls nearly 185,000 F-150s for defect that can cause drivers to lose control of the vehicle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</guid><description>A new recall affects close to 185,000 F-150 pickups from the 2021 and 2022 model years.
Summary Ford Motor Company is recalling nearly 185,000 F-150s from the 2021 and 2022 model years for a defect that can cause a fractured driveshaft. Ford reports that insulators on the underbody of the trucks can loosen and contact the aluminum driveshaft, rubbing and scoring it. Operators may observe a loose underbody insulator, or hear a rattling, clicking or clunking noise due to a loose underbody insulator contacting the driveshaft.</description></item></channel></rss>