<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pandemic on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pandemic/</link><description>Recent content in pandemic on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 20:11:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pandemic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More than 6,000 flights canceled so far over Memorial Day weekend</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629524af5dec53e1844a13a9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 20:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629524af5dec53e1844a13a9/</guid><description>More than 1,500 flights were canceled on Monday alone, according to flight tracking website FlightAware.
Highlights More than 1,500 flights were canceled on Monday alone, according to flight tracking website FlightAware. Delta Air Lines canceled 133 flights on Monday, or 4% of its operations. Delta announced Thursday that from July 1 to Aug. 7, it would reduce service by about 100 daily departures, primarily in parts of the U.S. and Latin America that Delta frequently serves.</description></item><item><title>U.S. no longer in ‘full-blown’ pandemic phase, Fauci says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62696d122c40f39a1baff38a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 16:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62696d122c40f39a1baff38a/</guid><description>Anthony Fauci said the United States is no longer seeing “tens and tens and tens of thousands of hospitalizations and thousands of deaths&amp;quot; from covid-19.
Highlights Anthony S. Fauci, President Biden’s chief medical adviser, says the U.S. is finally “out of the full-blown explosive pandemic phase” that has led to nearly 1 million deaths from covid-19 and more than two years of suffering and hardship. “The world is still in a pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Death toll nears 6 million as pandemic enters its 3rd year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62252383ea2f3c96d25faf4b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 21:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62252383ea2f3c96d25faf4b/</guid><description>BANGKOK (AP) — The official global death toll from COVID-19 is on the verge of eclipsing 6 million — underscoring that the pandemic, now entering its third year, is far from over. The milestone is the latest tragic reminder of the unrelenting nature of the pandemic even as people are shedding masks, travel is resuming and businesses are reopening around the globe.
Highlights The official global death toll from COVID-19 is on the verge of eclipsing 6 million.</description></item><item><title>Ireland Will Soon Pay Arts and Culture Workers a Basic Income to Help the Sector Bounce Back From the Pandemic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</guid><description>Ireland announces a basic income plan for artists in an effort to counter the ongoing effects of the pandemic and lockdown.
Summary Artists and culture workers in Ireland will soon be eligible for some much-needed financial support as the government readies a new basic income program. Ireland will commit roughly €25 million ($28.3 million) to the program, which it expects to implement early this year. It will pay some 2,000 people a basic income for three years.</description></item><item><title>India has “substantially greater” COVID-19 deaths than official reports suggest—close to 3 million, which is more than six times higher than the government has acknowledged and the largest number of any country. The finding could prompt scrutiny of other countries with anomalously low death rates.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</guid><description>Summary India, from the earliest days of the pandemic, has reported far fewer COVID-19 deaths than expected given the toll elsewhere—an apparent death “paradox” that some believed was real and others thought would prove illusory. That’s 340 COVID-19 deaths per million—about one-seventh the per capita COVID-19 mortality tallied in the United States. “The Indian government very much is trying to suppress the numbers in the way that they coded the COVID deaths,” Jha says.</description></item><item><title>Overwhelmed by Omicron surge, U.S. hospitals delay surgeries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d871bcb893d622e77dd3ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d871bcb893d622e77dd3ed/</guid><description>Hospitals across the United States are postponing elective surgeries to free up staff and beds due to a surge in COVID-19 cases driven by the highly transmissible Omicron variant of the coronavirus.
Summary REUTERS/Shannon StapletonWASHINGTON, Jan 7 (Reuters) - Hospitals across the United States are postponing elective surgeries to free up staff and beds due to a surge in COVID-19 cases driven by the highly transmissible Omicron variant of the coronavirus.</description></item><item><title>U.S. hits record high with nearly 500,000 COVID-19 cases in a single day</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf0cfd470861cb7f09e997/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 14:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf0cfd470861cb7f09e997/</guid><description>The staggering number comes as the Omicron variant continues to spread across the nation.
Summary The U.S. reported nearly half a million new COVID infections in a single day, marking the largest daily total of any country during the pandemic. More than 486,000 new cases were reported in a 24-hour period, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Thursday. Puerto Rico and Washington, D.C., are also averaging more daily cases than ever.</description></item></channel></rss>