<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>body on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/body/</link><description>Recent content in body on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 07:13:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/body/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Missing hiker's body found in LA park with dog by his side</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624948e4e125d5c23b8798db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624948e4e125d5c23b8798db/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A hiker who went missing two weeks ago was found dead in Griffith&amp;hellip;
Highlights Oscar Alejandro Hernandez, 29, was reported missing on March 16. His body was found Thursday night in a remote area of the sprawling urban park. His dog, King, was alive but emaciated. Hernandez was found with his dog by his side, authorities said. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Hiker falls 700 feet to death while taking selfie on a peak in the Superstition Mountains near Phoenix</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f33237fcd3269c420c1e87/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f33237fcd3269c420c1e87/</guid><description>Richard Jacobson &amp;quot;went to go take a photograph with himself and the city skyline in the background&amp;quot; when he lost his footing, officials said.
Highlights A hiker camping on a peak in the Superstition Mountains east of metro Phoenix was found dead after apparently slipping while taking a selfie and falling hundreds of feet, authorities said Wednesday. The body of Richard Jacobson, 21, was recovered after a hiking companion called 911 at approximately 12:45 a.</description></item></channel></rss>