<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>uk on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uk/</link><description>Recent content in uk on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK seeking return of Kevin Spacey from US to face sexual assault charges | UK news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62945427b648600d43992caf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62945427b648600d43992caf/</guid><description>Exclusive: Formal extradition is to be pursued if actor fails to come back to the country voluntarily
Highlights UK would seek formal extradition unless Spacey decides to come back voluntarily. US officials would have to be satisfied there is &amp;lsquo;probable cause&amp;rsquo; to detain Spacey. Spacey faces four charges of sexual assault relating to alleged attacks against three males between 2005 and 2013. Former head of extradition at the CPS says Spacey could be extradited in weeks if he does not contest extradition.</description></item><item><title>Sky News: Kevin Spacey charged with four counts of sexual assault against three men, CPS says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fc3241bd5f202b4ef3752/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fc3241bd5f202b4ef3752/</guid><description>The alleged incidents took place in London between March 2005 and August 2008, and in Gloucestershire in April 2013.
Highlights Oscar-winning actor Kevin Spacey charged with four counts of sexual assault against three men. The 62-year-old has also been charged with causing a person to engage in penetrative sexual activity without consent. The alleged incidents took place in London between March 2005 and August 2008, and in Gloucestershire in April 2013.</description></item><item><title>UK says quarter of Russian battalion groups that invaded Ukraine are likely "ineffective"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62702cfbbe58e80ad7618a13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 19:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62702cfbbe58e80ad7618a13/</guid><description>A quarter of the Russian battalion groups that invaded Ukraine have likely now been rendered &amp;quot;ineffective,&amp;quot; according to the UK&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defence.
Highlights Russian forces are putting pressure on the front lines in Luhansk, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s easternmost region, as part of its renewed offensive. Head of military administration: Russian forces were laying waste to villages along front lines of the region and pressing forward. This scorched-earth strategy has forced Ukrainian military forces to pull back in some places, to avoid significant losses of life.</description></item><item><title>‘Troll factory’ spreading Russian pro-war lies online, says UK</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e89cec6b3aeae30d8a412/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e89cec6b3aeae30d8a412/</guid><description>St Petersburg outfit hijacks discussions on Twitter, TikTok, world leaders’ social accounts and media websites, as well as manipulating opinion polls
Highlights Research funded by the UK government found operatives were ordering followers to target western media outlets and politicians. The St Petersburg outfit hijacks discussions on Twitter, TikTok, world leaders’ social accounts and media websites. The research said TikTok influencers were being paid to amplify pro-Kremlin narratives. The troll farm is said to recruit and hire salaried workers openly, justifying the work as ‘patriotic activity’ in support of the “special military operation” in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>UK to fund 2 mln pounds of food supplies for encircled Ukrainian cities</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f581fa21c546d4f77c41f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 18:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f581fa21c546d4f77c41f/</guid><description>Britain said on Saturday it would fund 2 million pounds ($2.6 million) worth of vital food supplies for areas of Ukraine which are encircled by Russian forces following a direct request from the Ukrainian government.
Highlights Britain said on Saturday it would fund 2 million pounds ($2.6 million) worth of vital food supplies for areas of Ukraine encircled by Russian forces. Britain said around 25 truckloads of dried food, tinned goods and water will be transported by road and rail from warehouses in Poland and Slovakia to the most at-risk Ukrainian towns and cities.</description></item><item><title>Russia Today has its licence to broadcast in UK revoked with immediate effect by watchdog Ofcom</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623493343ff20adeff38c9bd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 14:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623493343ff20adeff38c9bd/</guid><description>The media regulator cited the fact the channel was funded by a state which has recently invaded a neighbouring country but RT said the decision showed Ofcom was &amp;quot;nothing more than a tool of government&amp;quot;.
Highlights Russia Today has had its licence to broadcast in the UK revoked with immediate effect. Ofcom said it did not consider the channel &amp;ldquo;fit and proper&amp;rdquo; or a &amp;ldquo;responsible broadcaster&amp;rdquo; It cited the fact that the news channel was funded by the Russian state which has recently invaded a neighbouring country.</description></item><item><title>UK inflation rises at fastest rate in almost 30 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e2d0d27149367a95e2356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 11:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e2d0d27149367a95e2356/</guid><description>Inflation in the United Kingdom has risen at the fastest rate in almost 30 years as increased costs for energy, housing and transportation squeezed household budgets
Highlights Consumer price index ticked up to 5.5% in the 12 months through January. Latest figure is the highest since March 1992, when inflation reached 7.2%. U.K. consumers are reeling from a surge in utility bills fueled by increased demand for energy worldwide. By comparison, U.</description></item><item><title>Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky claims Vladimir Putin is putting illegal pressure on Britain's political system</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 13:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</guid><description>Mikhail Khodorkovsky says Russian meddling is happening &amp;quot;directly and indirectly&amp;quot; in Britain - and it must be stopped.
Highlights Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky calls out &amp;lsquo;dangerous, illegal&amp;rsquo; pressure by Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;cronies&amp;rsquo; in the UK. Former head of oil giant Yukos was imprisoned for eight years by Putin&amp;rsquo;s government for tax evasion and theft in a controversial case. He says Putin is &amp;ldquo;capable of all sorts of actions, including ill-judged ones&amp;rdquo; Putin is &amp;lsquo;in fact afraid&amp;rsquo; of a war with Ukraine, says ex-Russian oligarch.</description></item><item><title>Russia told the US and West to stop supplying arms to Ukraine, saying it's threatening Russia..</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</guid><description>Russia is amassing troops on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border. The US and Ukraine warn of an imminent Russian invasion.
Summary The US and Ukraine have repeatedly warned that Russia appeared to be preparing to invade. The US has also given Ukraine military assistance, including arms and training. The US, Ukraine, and other allies have repeatedly warned that Russia appears to be preparing to invade Ukraine. And Ukraine warned that Russia was almost done gathering enough troops along its border for a possible offensive.</description></item></channel></rss>