<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>uk on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uk/</link><description>Recent content in uk on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 13:13:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky claims Vladimir Putin is putting illegal pressure on Britain's political system</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 13:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</guid><description>Mikhail Khodorkovsky says Russian meddling is happening &amp;quot;directly and indirectly&amp;quot; in Britain - and it must be stopped.
Highlights Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky calls out &amp;lsquo;dangerous, illegal&amp;rsquo; pressure by Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;cronies&amp;rsquo; in the UK. Former head of oil giant Yukos was imprisoned for eight years by Putin&amp;rsquo;s government for tax evasion and theft in a controversial case. He says Putin is &amp;ldquo;capable of all sorts of actions, including ill-judged ones&amp;rdquo; Putin is &amp;lsquo;in fact afraid&amp;rsquo; of a war with Ukraine, says ex-Russian oligarch.</description></item><item><title>Russia told the US and West to stop supplying arms to Ukraine, saying it's threatening Russia..</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</guid><description>Russia is amassing troops on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border. The US and Ukraine warn of an imminent Russian invasion.
Summary The US and Ukraine have repeatedly warned that Russia appeared to be preparing to invade. The US has also given Ukraine military assistance, including arms and training. The US, Ukraine, and other allies have repeatedly warned that Russia appears to be preparing to invade Ukraine. And Ukraine warned that Russia was almost done gathering enough troops along its border for a possible offensive.</description></item></channel></rss>