<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wont on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wont/</link><description>Recent content in wont on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:17:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wont/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Air Force cadets who refused Covid vaccine won’t be commissioned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bc15f2c70ed12b11701dd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bc15f2c70ed12b11701dd/</guid><description>Three cadets at the U.S. Air Force Academy who have refused the Covid-19 vaccine will not be commissioned as military officers, the academy said Saturday.
Highlights The Air Force is the only military academy, so far, where cadets are not being commissioned due to vaccine refusal. The Naval Academy in Annapolis, Maryland, said Saturday that none of the Navy or Marine Corps seniors there are being prevented from commissioning. A fourth cadet who had refused the vaccine until about a week ago, decided to be vaccinated and will graduate and become an Air Force officer.</description></item><item><title>Boston Hospital refuses heart transplant for man after he refuses to be vaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f02cc4f855ea5e54011307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f02cc4f855ea5e54011307/</guid><description>Brigham and Women&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Boston says its policy won&amp;rsquo;t allow DJ Ferguson to have the surgery since not being vaccinated seriously hurts its chances for success and his long-term outlook.
Summary A Boston hospital says it won&amp;rsquo;t consider performing a heart transplant on a patient who refuses to get vaccinated against COVID-19, CBS Boston reports. DJ Ferguson, 31, is fighting for his life at Brigham and Women&amp;rsquo;s Hospital and in desperate need of a heart transplant.</description></item><item><title>Michigan says it won't follow CDC's more relaxed COVID-19 quarantine recommendations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce2bfb7e28cc2bb7b6ae30/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce2bfb7e28cc2bb7b6ae30/</guid><description>Michigan health officials say they won&amp;rsquo;t adopt shorter federal COVID-19 isolation/quarantine guidelines until the review
Summary Michigan says it won&amp;rsquo;t follow CDC&amp;rsquo;s more relaxed COVID-19 quarantine recommendationsShow Caption Hide Caption CDC shortens COVID-19 isolation and quarantine guidelines CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the changes were made based on &amp;ldquo;two years of science&amp;rdquo; about the virus. Rather, Michigan health leaders say they will continue to recommend previous, longer quarantine and isolation guidelines, including those for K-12 schools and congregate care settings.</description></item><item><title>Michigan woman won’t be charged for outing anti-mask nurses on Twitter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd914e20fa07a434457363/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd914e20fa07a434457363/</guid><description>A conservative sheriff in Michigan who wanted charges to be filed against a Howell woman for calling out anti-maskers on Twitter won’t get his way&amp;hellip;.
Summary click to enlarge ShutterstockIn a series of tweets earlier this month, Kasey Helton took aim at anti-mask nurses who spread misinformation about COVID-19. This evening I was notified by my attorney that the Livingston County prosecutor’s office WILL NOT seek felony charges for a dubious criminal complaint brought against me by the @LCSOMI related to my tweets exposing nurses for publicly spreading COVID #misinfo at gov’t meetings.</description></item></channel></rss>