<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>water on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/water/</link><description>Recent content in water on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 13:22:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/water/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Drought prompts Nebraska to divert water from river it shares with Colorado</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62654f146b51ef6ed5a9217c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 13:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62654f146b51ef6ed5a9217c/</guid><description>With many Western states in severe drought and vying for their share of a diminishing amount of water, Nebraska is taking a new tact by trying to divert water
Highlights The Nebraska Legislature this week approved construction of a $53 million canal in Colorado that would solidify its share of water from the South Platte River. As climate change makes the West hotter and drier, cities and states will intensify efforts to find and secure water.</description></item><item><title>An unsent text message and desperate phone calls detail California family's last moments before they died while hiking</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62108af88c8a60f239d3b693/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 06:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62108af88c8a60f239d3b693/</guid><description>Family selfies, nature photos, an unanswered text and several calls that were never connected detail the final hours of a California couple and their child before they died on a hiking trail near Yosemite last August.
Highlights Jonathan Gerrish, Ellen Chung and their 1-year-old daughter, Miju, died from hyperthermia. Authorities were able to pull a text message from Gerrish&amp;rsquo;s phone at 11:56 a.m. asking for help. It was never received due to lack of cell service in the area.</description></item><item><title>China’s lunar probe finds first on-site evidence of water on moon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dadc8f3bf7b4ace045b892/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dadc8f3bf7b4ace045b892/</guid><description>The presence of water had been confirmed by remote observation but the lander has now detected signs of the H20 molecule in rocks and soil.
Summary The probe has previously collected and sent back lunar rocks. Photo: Xinhua READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>