<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>water on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/water/</link><description>Recent content in water on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/water/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-deputy gets 18 years after detainees drown in locked van</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287bde024ee89e50b7aecc7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287bde024ee89e50b7aecc7/</guid><description>A deputy in South Carolina whose police van was swept away by floodwaters in the aftermath of Hurricane Florence, drowning two women seeking mental health treatment trapped in a cage in the back has been sentenced to 18 years in prison
Highlights Former Horry County deputy Stephen Flood was found guilty of involuntary manslaughter and reckless homicide. Wendy Newton, 45, and Nicolette Green, 43, drowned in a police van after Hurricane Florence.</description></item><item><title>17 people shot on N. Water St. Friday night, Milwaukee police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628053c6389460d8cae0b735/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628053c6389460d8cae0b735/</guid><description>17 people were shot on Water St. in downtown Milwaukee Friday night, according to Milwaukee Police.
Highlights 17 people were shot on Water St. in downtown Milwaukee Friday night. Police say it happened just after 11:00 p.m. Friday in the 1100 block of N. Water St., near E. Highland Ave. The victims range from 15 to 47 years of age, police say. Police and Mayor Cavalier Johnson held a press conference Saturday afternoon to address Friday&amp;rsquo;s violence.</description></item><item><title>Sheriff's office releases video of shark-infested waters off Florida coast, warns of "dangers below the water"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1fa208dfd0c92b109c6e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 08:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1fa208dfd0c92b109c6e/</guid><description>&amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s important to be aware of the dangers below the water as well as above,&amp;quot; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office wrote.
Highlights The Pasco Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office in Florida released aerial video of shark-infested waters off the Gulf Coast, warning the public to &amp;ldquo;be aware of the dangers below the water as well as above&amp;rdquo; The sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office did not identify the type of sharks in the aerial video but they appear to resemble blacktip sharks, which were captured on drone video last year off Florida near Singer Island.</description></item><item><title>Barrel containing human remains discovered in Lake Mead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62712fa09ae6ca62d0ec3444/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 13:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62712fa09ae6ca62d0ec3444/</guid><description>LAS VEGAS (AP) — A body inside a barrel was found over the weekend on the the newly exposed bottom of Nevada&amp;rsquo;s Lake Mead as drought depletes one of the largest U.S. reservoirs — and officials predicted the discovery could be just the first of more grim finds.
Highlights A body inside a barrel was found over the the the newly exposed bottom of Nevada’s Lake Mead as drought depletes one of the largest U.</description></item><item><title>Coastal Panel Staff Advises Against Huntington Beach Desalination Plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fcd74951274a79e6720e9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:24:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fcd74951274a79e6720e9/</guid><description>A proposed California desalination plant that would produce 50 million gallons of drinking water per day failed a crucial regulatory hurdle on Monday, possibly dooming a project that had been promoted as a partial solution for sustained drought.
Highlights Staff of the California Coastal Commission recommended denying approval of the Huntington Beach plant proposed by Poseidon Water. The plant is expected to produce 50 million gallons of drinking water per day, enough for 16% of the homes in the Orange County Water District, where 2.</description></item><item><title>Lake Powell water officials face an impossible choice amid the West's megadrought - CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e185ce34e269f6de996c7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 05:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e185ce34e269f6de996c7/</guid><description>Lake Powell, the country&amp;rsquo;s second-largest reservoir, is drying up.
Highlights Glen Canyon Dam has lost about 16 percent of its capacity to generate power over the past several years. In a worst-case scenario, the Interior Department projects the dam could stop producing power by January. The agency is now weighing an emergency action that would buy the dam more time. Loss of power at the dam would also mean higher energy costs for customers as the price of fossil fuels skyrockets.</description></item><item><title>Drought prompts Nebraska to divert water from river it shares with Colorado</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62654f146b51ef6ed5a9217c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 13:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62654f146b51ef6ed5a9217c/</guid><description>With many Western states in severe drought and vying for their share of a diminishing amount of water, Nebraska is taking a new tact by trying to divert water
Highlights The Nebraska Legislature this week approved construction of a $53 million canal in Colorado that would solidify its share of water from the South Platte River. As climate change makes the West hotter and drier, cities and states will intensify efforts to find and secure water.</description></item><item><title>An unsent text message and desperate phone calls detail California family's last moments before they died while hiking</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62108af88c8a60f239d3b693/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 06:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62108af88c8a60f239d3b693/</guid><description>Family selfies, nature photos, an unanswered text and several calls that were never connected detail the final hours of a California couple and their child before they died on a hiking trail near Yosemite last August.
Highlights Jonathan Gerrish, Ellen Chung and their 1-year-old daughter, Miju, died from hyperthermia. Authorities were able to pull a text message from Gerrish&amp;rsquo;s phone at 11:56 a.m. asking for help. It was never received due to lack of cell service in the area.</description></item><item><title>China’s lunar probe finds first on-site evidence of water on moon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dadc8f3bf7b4ace045b892/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dadc8f3bf7b4ace045b892/</guid><description>The presence of water had been confirmed by remote observation but the lander has now detected signs of the H20 molecule in rocks and soil.
Summary The probe has previously collected and sent back lunar rocks. Photo: Xinhua READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>