<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>price on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/price/</link><description>Recent content in price on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:17:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/price/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small-business owners say inflation has become a bigger problem than the labor shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255a5db4c0c72b2e2473455/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 16:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255a5db4c0c72b2e2473455/</guid><description>Small businesses say inflation has become their biggest problem, and they don&amp;rsquo;t expect business conditions to improve over the next six months
Highlights The Small Business Optimism Index is down by 2.4 points in March, the third monthly drop in a row. The index is the lowest in the survey&amp;rsquo;s 48-year history. One-inflation is now the biggest problem facing small business owners, up 5 points from February. The Consumer Price Index, a key measure of inflation rate, rose to 8.</description></item><item><title>Federal Reserve warns of "brewing U.S. housing bubble"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624635d4866262bb2a9f5cc3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 23:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624635d4866262bb2a9f5cc3/</guid><description>Economists say the pandemic housing boom is showing &amp;quot;signs of exuberance&amp;quot; akin to the boom of the early 2000s.
Highlights Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas says housing market is showing &amp;ldquo;signs of a brewing U.S. housing bubble&amp;rdquo; Mortgage rates are at an average of 4.67% for a fixed 30-year loan for the week ended March 31. The national median listing price for a home has jumped to a record $405,000, Realtor.</description></item><item><title>Coca-Cola suspends business in Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227f9b555a9f4bdc7272911/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227f9b555a9f4bdc7272911/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president addresses the House of Commons as the UK and US announce bans on Russian oil imports.
Highlights Oil prices jumped more than 7% at one point on Tuesday, as the US and UK announced plans to ban Russian oil imports. The price of Brent crude, an international benchmark, is now hovering at around $130 (£99) a barrel. In the US, Americans are now paying an average of $4.17 per gallon – the highest on record.</description></item><item><title>California's average gas price hits new record high with $5.28 a gallon, AAA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227020bc87880fdf0b7dea2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 07:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227020bc87880fdf0b7dea2/</guid><description>California hit another record for the average price of regular unleaded gas this weekend, at $5.28 a gallon as of Sunday.
Highlights California hit another record for the average price of regular unleaded gas this weekend. Napa, Marin, and Sonoma counties are the most expensive for gas. California&amp;rsquo;s already record-high gas prices are expected to get even more expensive in the coming months, fueled by the crisis in Ukraine. Long lines could be seen at the Costco in South San Francisco where the price of gasoline continues to surge.</description></item><item><title>National average for a gallon of gas tops $4, the highest price at the pump since 2008</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224f9ee743e1aabb861a1c3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 18:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224f9ee743e1aabb861a1c3/</guid><description>Consumers are paying the most at the pump since 2008.
Highlights The national average for a gallon of gas hit $4.009 on Sunday, according to AAA, which is the highest since July 2008, not adjusted for inflation. The jump in prices follows a surge in the price of oil amid Russia&amp;rsquo;s war on Ukraine. The Biden administration has said for months that they are working to bring down prices at the pump, and in the fall tapped the Strategic Petroleum Reserve.</description></item><item><title>Average national gasoline price surges to $3.83 a gallon, the highest since 2012</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62236f911922aef59bcca8d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 14:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62236f911922aef59bcca8d6/</guid><description>Gas prices are surging, adding to inflationary concerns across the U.S. economy.
Highlights The national average for a gallon of regular gas stood at $3.83 on Friday, the highest since Sept. 21, 2012. Prices are rising at a fast clip, with Friday&amp;rsquo;s average nearly 11 cents a gallon above Thursday&amp;rsquo;s. Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine and the subsequent sanctions against the nation&amp;rsquo;s financial sector are prompting fears of supply shortages in what was already a tight market.</description></item><item><title>Canada should temporarily ban foreign home buyers, rezone cities - housing minister</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c464def47fd04f449d4106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c464def47fd04f449d4106/</guid><description>Municipalities should rezone broadly to allow more density and Canada should temporarily ban foreign buyers to help alleviate the housing affordability crunch faced by residents, the country&amp;rsquo;s housing minister said on Tuesday.
Summary Canada&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Housing, Diversity, and Inclusion Ahmed Hussen speaks during Question Period in the House of Commons on Parliament Hill in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada November 30, 2021. REUTERS/Blair Gable/OTTAWA, Dec 21 (Reuters) - Municipalities should rezone broadly to allow more density and Canada should temporarily ban foreign buyers to help alleviate the housing affordability crunch faced by residents, the country&amp;rsquo;s housing minister said on Tuesday.</description></item></channel></rss>