<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weather on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weather/</link><description>Recent content in weather on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 22:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>11-Year-Old Survivor of Uvalde Massacre Put Blood on Herself and Played Dead, Aunt Says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62914c1a3d3d46f2e3d4ba80/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 22:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62914c1a3d3d46f2e3d4ba80/</guid><description>The family of a girl who survived the school shooting in Uvalde, Texas says the 4th grader put blood on herself and played dead after the gunman entered her&amp;hellip;
Highlights Miah Cerrillo, 11, survived the massacre at Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, on Tuesday. Her aunt and godmother said the 4th grader is struggling to cope and telling them what she witnessed during the shooting. Blanca Rivera said Miah&amp;rsquo;s teacher, Irma Garcia, was one of the two teachers killed.</description></item><item><title>Historic heatwave poised to hit dozens of US states this weekend</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62894717b260a97c4eb58427/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 20:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62894717b260a97c4eb58427/</guid><description>Temperatures expected to be 20F to 30F above average for this time of year, breaking records and raising health fears
Highlights Temperatures between 20F and 30F above average in mid-Atlantic and north-east. More than 120 million Americans are expected to be affected by the punishing heat. Temperatures expected to break or tie roughly 130 heat records for this time of year. Fears of health risks for outdoor workers and those who do not have access to indoor cooling.</description></item><item><title>Over 40 million people are under severe storm threat this weekend .</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d989b2f32cf19522e1655/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 20:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d989b2f32cf19522e1655/</guid><description>Two separate weather systems will bring severe storms to more than a dozen states this weekend, some of the same ones that were hit Friday night.
Highlights Two separate weather systems will bring severe storms to more than a dozen states this weekend. The system that brought over 150 severe storm reports to the central Plains on Friday will now push east on Saturday. All severe weather hazards will be possible including damaging winds, hail, and tornadoes.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: Police Officer Kills Dog in Miami-Dade After Barking Complaint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</guid><description>A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing him while responding to&amp;hellip;
Summary A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing the 8-month-old. The incident happened in unincorporated Miami-Dade near Miami Gardens on Wednesday, January 12 around 7 p.m. as a police officer was responding to a call regarding dogs barking.</description></item></channel></rss>