<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weather on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weather/</link><description>Recent content in weather on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 20:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Over 40 million people are under severe storm threat this weekend .</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d989b2f32cf19522e1655/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 20:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d989b2f32cf19522e1655/</guid><description>Two separate weather systems will bring severe storms to more than a dozen states this weekend, some of the same ones that were hit Friday night.
Highlights Two separate weather systems will bring severe storms to more than a dozen states this weekend. The system that brought over 150 severe storm reports to the central Plains on Friday will now push east on Saturday. All severe weather hazards will be possible including damaging winds, hail, and tornadoes.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: Police Officer Kills Dog in Miami-Dade After Barking Complaint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</guid><description>A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing him while responding to&amp;hellip;
Summary A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing the 8-month-old. The incident happened in unincorporated Miami-Dade near Miami Gardens on Wednesday, January 12 around 7 p.m. as a police officer was responding to a call regarding dogs barking.</description></item></channel></rss>