<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dhs on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dhs/</link><description>Recent content in dhs on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:54:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dhs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>White House Secret Service personnel ‘compromised’ by men impersonating DHS agents, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250d91e4c5c73ccffae3c12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250d91e4c5c73ccffae3c12/</guid><description>A Secret Service agent assigned to protect first lady Jill Biden is a witness in the case of two men accused of impersonating Homeland Security agents.
Highlights Two men charged with impersonating DHS agents &amp;ldquo;compromised&amp;rdquo; Secret Service personnel assigned to protect first lady Jill Biden and the White House, prosecutors say. Federal prosecutors ask a judge to hold the duo without bail. Magistrate Judge G. Michael Harvey: &amp;ldquo;This is not just two people dressing up for Halloween, your honor.</description></item><item><title>Internal investigation of domestic violent extremism reveals four sympathizers inside DHS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c9d14f9612d11f1ce437e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 13:16:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c9d14f9612d11f1ce437e/</guid><description>Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas told CBS News in an exclusive interview, he finds &amp;quot;significant gaps&amp;quot; in DHS policy to be &amp;quot;troubling.&amp;quot;
Highlights DHS has &amp;ldquo;significant gaps&amp;rdquo; that impede its ability to &amp;ldquo;prevent, detect and respond&amp;rdquo; to potential DVE threats, report says. Four incidents of &amp;ldquo;active participation or support for domestic extremist activity&amp;rdquo; among DHS employees since 2019. DHS has not adopted an authoritative definition of &amp;ldquo;domestic violent extremist&amp;rdquo; that can be incorporated&amp;quot; into DHS policies and guidance, report finds.</description></item></channel></rss>