<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>insurance on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/insurance/</link><description>Recent content in insurance on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 18:11:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/insurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Roofing scammers throw Florida’s property insurance market into chaos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62892b42093585a27c8b49c4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 18:11:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62892b42093585a27c8b49c4/</guid><description>Florida lawmakers are scrambling to fix a property insurance crisis that has has forced painful rate hikes and put several companies out of business.
Highlights Insurance industry&amp;rsquo;s net losses have risen in each of the past five years, surpassing $1 billion in 2021. Florida is the most volatile property insurance market in the country, an industry spokesman says. Lawmakers will begin a special session on Monday to address the state&amp;rsquo;s property insurance crisis.</description></item><item><title>San Jose passes first U.S. law requiring gun owners to get liability insurance and pay annual fee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f18c40be2b21499173e8a2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 18:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f18c40be2b21499173e8a2/</guid><description>They&amp;rsquo;d also have to pay an annual fee. But opponents promised to fight the measure in court. People on both sides of the issue spoke at length before the vote was taken.
Summary The San Jose City Council overwhelmingly approved the measure despite opposition from gun owners who said it would violate their Second Amendment rights and promised to sue. Council members, including several who had lost friends to gun violence, said it was a step toward dealing with gun violence, which Councilman Sergio Jimenez called &amp;ldquo;a scourge on our society.</description></item></channel></rss>