<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mr on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mr/</link><description>Recent content in mr on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biden Considers Sending Thousands of Troops, Including Warships and Aircraft, to Eastern Europe and Baltics Amid Fears of Russian Attack on Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee5c9b135932fdb2bf832c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee5c9b135932fdb2bf832c/</guid><description>The president is also considering deploying warships and aircraft to NATO allies, in what would be a major shift from its restrained stance on Ukraine.
Summary Thinning out staff at American embassies is a common precaution when conflicts or other crises arise that could put American diplomats in harm’s way. In his news conference last week, Mr. Biden said he had cautioned Mr. Putin that a Russian invasion of Ukraine would prompt Washington to send more troops to the region.</description></item><item><title>Police probe clears Dayton, Ohio, officers who pulled paraplegic driver out of car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1741adfcb507831a3dba7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1741adfcb507831a3dba7/</guid><description>A Dayton, Ohio, police internal investigation of a traffic stop where officers pulled a paraplegic driver out of a car by his hair and arms cleared the officers of the most serious allegations against them.
Summary (CNN) A Dayton, Ohio, police internal investigation of a traffic stop where officers pulled a paraplegic driver out of a car by his hair and arms cleared the officers of the most serious allegations against them.</description></item><item><title>Finland says it could join NATO if it wants to, despite Russia's opposition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</guid><description>Finland’s President Sauli Niinistö on Saturday reiterated his country’s right to join Nato if it wants to, in a dismissal of Russian demands for no further expansion of the Western military alliance near its borders.
Summary Last month Russian President Vladimir Putin sought guarantees that Finland would not join Nato. In a statement released by the Kremlin, President Putin said Russian wants “international legal security guarantees” ruling out “Nato’s further movement eastward”.</description></item></channel></rss>