<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dying on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dying/</link><description>Recent content in dying on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:28:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dying/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VA hospital denied emergency care to dying vet because staff couldn’t verify his military service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629775211e4ba9dced5bb3f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629775211e4ba9dced5bb3f1/</guid><description>The 60-year-old had received treatment for a heart ailment just a few months earlier at the Florida VA hospital.
Highlights A Florida VA hospital refused treatment for a 60-year-old man dying of heart failure because first responders could not prove his military service. The incident occurred at the Malcom Randall VA Medical Center in Gainesville, Florida, in summer 2020. The VA Inspector General’s Office said without policy and staffing changes, it may not be the last.</description></item><item><title>Astronomers spot dying star just before it explodes and record supernova | Science &amp;amp; Tech News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d89bec6d2f6425886fb36c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d89bec6d2f6425886fb36c/</guid><description>The discovery reveals new details about how red supergiants evolve just before going supernova, potentially allowing astronomers to detect them in the future.
Summary Astronomers have for the first time imaged the last moments in the life of a red supergiant star. &amp;ldquo;This is a breakthrough in our understanding of what massive stars do moments before they die,&amp;rdquo; said Dr Wynn Jacobson-Galán, lead author of the study. &amp;ldquo;Direct detection of pre-supernova activity in a red supergiant star has never been observed before in an ordinary Type II supernova.</description></item></channel></rss>