<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>abortions on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abortions/</link><description>Recent content in abortions on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:14:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abortions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla will pay travel costs for staff seeking abortion services</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62768cd15e97503a68e64e08/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62768cd15e97503a68e64e08/</guid><description>Tesla is covering travel costs for employees seeking out-of-state abortions, joining the ranks of major companies who’ve introduced a similar policy to benefit
Highlights Tesla is covering travel costs for employees seeking out-of-state abortions. The car maker expanded its Safety Net program and health insurance offerings last year to include “travel and lodging support for those who may need to seek healthcare services that are unavailable in their home state” The company moved its corporate headquarters last year from Silicon Valley to Texas, which passed a law banning abortions at roughly six weeks of pregnancy.</description></item><item><title>Donations to U.S. abortion rights groups, clinics surge after Supreme Court leak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62736c451230aa3c1bfed51b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 06:19:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62736c451230aa3c1bfed51b/</guid><description>Donations have flooded into abortion clinics and abortion-rights advocacy groups since the leak of a U.S. Supreme Court draft ruling that showed the justices apparently poised to overturn the 1973 landmark Roe v. Wade decision.
Highlights Donations have flooded into abortion clinics and abortion-rights advocacy groups since the leak of a U.S. Supreme Court ruling. The ruling showed the justices apparently planned to overturn the 1973 landmark Roe v. Wade decision.</description></item><item><title>MacKenzie Scott donates a record $275 million to Planned Parenthood</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623be381d1822640d19d4e72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 03:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623be381d1822640d19d4e72/</guid><description>Billionaire philanthropist MacKenzie Scott donated $275 million to women&amp;rsquo;s healthcare provider Planned Parenthood, the largest gift from a single donor in the organization&amp;rsquo;s more than 100-year history, Planned Parenthood said on Wednesday.
Highlights Billionaire philanthropist MacKenzie Scott donated $275 million to women&amp;rsquo;s healthcare provider Planned Parenthood. The donation is part of Scott&amp;rsquo;s pledge to give away the majority of her wealth. Scott received a 4% stake in Amazon.com Inc as part of her divorce from Jeff Bezos.</description></item><item><title>California governor signs law that makes abortions cheaper</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b9b74082bf978c99c9e4d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b9b74082bf978c99c9e4d/</guid><description>Gov. Gavin Newsom has signed a new law to make abortions cheaper for people on private insurance plans.
Highlights Gov. Gavin Newsom signed a new law to make abortions cheaper for people on private insurance plans. Newsom has signed a law that makes it easier to get an abortion cheaper for those on private plans. The law was signed by California&amp;rsquo;s new governor last week. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>