<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>training on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/training/</link><description>Recent content in training on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 07:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde school district police chief declines to answer CNN questions in first public comments in a week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629862835ceef11ad1cd8df8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 07:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629862835ceef11ad1cd8df8/</guid><description>Pedro &amp;quot;Pete&amp;quot; Arredondo, the embattled Uvalde school police chief who led the flawed law enforcement response to last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting and has remained out of the public eye since, spoke exclusively to CNN on Wednesday and declined to answer substantive questions about the massacre.
Highlights Pedro &amp;ldquo;Pete&amp;rdquo; Arredondo spoke exclusively to CNN about the school shooting last week. He declined to answer substantive questions about the massacre. 19 children and two teachers were killed in the shooting at Robb Elementary in Uvalde, Texas, last Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde school police chief identified as commander who decided not to breach classroom</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62918b67c7239b3eba9f1372/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62918b67c7239b3eba9f1372/</guid><description>At a news conference Friday, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Col. Steven McCraw said the person who made the decision not to breach the Uvalde elementary school classroom where a gunman was shooting children and teachers was the school district police chief, calling it the “wrong decision” to not engage the gunman sooner.
Highlights Pedro “Pete” Arredondo is identified on the Uvalde School District website as the police chief. At a news conference Friday, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Col.</description></item><item><title>LA Resident Physicians Threaten To Strike Over Low Wages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e056235155fea195e0af4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e056235155fea195e0af4/</guid><description>The unionized health workers have until the end of May to vote on a strike.
Highlights Unionized resident physicians at three L.A. hospitals will hold a strike vote next week. They want a 7% raise in pay and housing stipends. The voting period for the strike will end May 30. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear when a strike and walkout could take place over the summer if approved by members. The last contract with the hospitals expired Sept.</description></item><item><title>Florida Guardsmen heading to Germany to resume training Ukrainian troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62703b4bbbf1512927815d17/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62703b4bbbf1512927815d17/</guid><description>The 160 soldiers left Ukraine in February, but have stayed in Europe.
Highlights The Florida National Guard is continuing to train Ukrainian troops outside of Ukraine. The 53rd Infantry Brigade Combat Team evacuated Ukraine in February. Canada is leading training on M777 howitzer systems that the U.S. and Canada have sent to Eastern Europe. The Guardsmen will train on equipment sent in two recent aid packages, including radars and tactical vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Germany will provide training and maintenance to Ukrainian military, foreign minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260771f926d2271050d0132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260771f926d2271050d0132/</guid><description>Germany will provide training and maintenance to the Ukrainian military, German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock said in Latvia Wednesday.
Highlights Germany will provide training and maintenance to the Ukrainian military, German foreign minister says. Annalena Baerbock said that Germany could not provide further weaponry as the country had no weapons it could “deliver quickly and without delay right now. Germany has chosen not to make public all the weapons it has previously sent to Ukraine, she said.</description></item><item><title>Police trainer testifies against officers in Floyd's death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202dc604d4ac3d9ae76a1d9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202dc604d4ac3d9ae76a1d9/</guid><description>ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — A Minneapolis police officer who oversaw medical training for two of the three former officers charged with violating George Floyd&amp;rsquo;s civil rights testified Tuesday that the officers were trained to give CPR as soon as they fail to find a pulse on someone.
Highlights Officer Derek Chauvin knelt on George Floyd’s neck for 9 1/2 minutes as he was handcuffed, facedown. Officer J. Alexander Kueng, Thomas Lane and Tou Thao are accused of depriving Floyd, 46, of his rights.</description></item><item><title>UK sends 30 elite troops and 2,000 anti-tank weapons to Ukraine amid fears of Russian invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 04:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</guid><description>British surveillance aircraft have also been spotted as part of a quiet but notable build-up of support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s military by the UK.
Summary A group of around 30 elite British troops has arrived in Ukraine to help train the Ukrainian armed forces on new anti-tank weapons gifted by the UK amid fears of an imminent, new Russian invasion, Sky News understands. Open source flight-tracking software has plotted Royal Air Force C-17 transport aircraft flying back and forth between the UK and Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>