<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sentence on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sentence/</link><description>Recent content in sentence on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sentence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-cop pleads guilty to manslaughter in George Floyd killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285604b04b797a582783e3e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285604b04b797a582783e3e/</guid><description>A former Minneapolis police officer has pleaded guilty to a state charge of aiding and abetting second-degree manslaughter in the death of George Floyd
Highlights Thomas Lane pleads guilty to aiding and abetting second-degree manslaughter. He will avoid what could have been a lengthy state sentence if he was convicted of murder. Lane and two other officers have already been convicted on federal counts of willfully violating Floyd&amp;rsquo;s rights. The guilty plea comes a week before the two-year anniversary of Floyd’s May 25, 2020, killing.</description></item><item><title>Patient claims a Christian rehab facility kicked her out for kissing another woman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62711f81c97c1ee2c8a84ae6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62711f81c97c1ee2c8a84ae6/</guid><description>A Florida woman claims she was forced to go to jail after being kicked out of a court-ordered, Christian-based drug rehab center for kissing another woman.
Highlights Kaylia Hevia, 29, was sentenced to 120 days in jail for violating probation at Teen Challenge, a &amp;ldquo;Christ-centered&amp;rdquo; drug and addiction program she attended as part of a plea for her February 2021 arrest. The program has a &amp;ldquo;no touching&amp;rdquo; rule&amp;quot; contained within the program agreement, prosecutors say.</description></item><item><title>Texas Court Upholds Conviction, Sentence of Amber Guyger</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249578d278eac8fb3bbd0f5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 08:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249578d278eac8fb3bbd0f5/</guid><description>Texas’ highest criminal court upheld the murder conviction and 10-year prison sentence of Amber Guyger, the former Dallas police officer who fatally shot&amp;hellip;
Highlights Court of Criminal Appeals refused to hear Amber Guyger’s petition to review her 2019 conviction. The former Dallas police officer fatally shot Botham Jean in his apartment in 2018 after she said she mistook him for an intruder. Two justices — Judge Kevin Yeary and Judge Michelle Slaughter — filed a dissent.</description></item><item><title>Muslim woman, 26, is sentenced to death by hanging for blasphemy in Pakistan after sending caricatures of Prophet Mohammed over WhatsApp</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8b43b656818b6f13e4197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8b43b656818b6f13e4197/</guid><description>Aneeqa Ateeq, 26, was arrested in May 2020 and charged with posting &amp;lsquo;blasphemous material&amp;rsquo; as her WhatsApp status, according to a summary issued by the court.
Summary But an execution has never been carried out as courts have overruled sentenceBlasphemy is punishable by the death sentence in Muslim-majority PakistanA Muslim woman has been sentenced to death in Pakistan for sending caricatures of Prophet Muhammad over WhatsApp, a court said. Blasphemy is an act punishable by the death sentence in Muslim-majority Pakistan, although an execution has never been carried out for the crime.</description></item></channel></rss>