<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hide on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hide/</link><description>Recent content in hide on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 15:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A 9-year-old describes escaping through a window during the Uvalde school massacre as anger mounts over police response | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294de629a989c9ad3c29768/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294de629a989c9ad3c29768/</guid><description>As a gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, and started firing, one student said his wounded teacher texted 911 for help.
Highlights Gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, and started firing, one student said. Daniel, 9, said he survived by hiding under a table next to the wall. &amp;ldquo;I could see him staring at people in front of me,&amp;rdquo; Daniel said. The deadly rampage at Robb Elementary marked at least the 30th shooting at a K-12 school in just the first five months of this year.</description></item><item><title>Canadian authorities freeze financial assets for those involved in ongoing protests in Ottawa | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213ac8b47be889ab6ea7faa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213ac8b47be889ab6ea7faa/</guid><description>A weeks-long blockade in the Canadian capital has led to almost 200 arrests and prolonged suffering for businesses caught in the middle of protests against Covid-19 mandates.
Highlights Canadian authorities freeze the finances associated with certain individuals and companies believed to be involved in the ongoing protests in Ottawa. A weeks-long blockade in the Canadian capital has led to almost 200 arrests and prolonged suffering for businesses caught in the middle of protests against Covid-19 mandates.</description></item><item><title>The last 7 years have been the warmest on record as planet approaches critical threshold</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcc8b9b6c574658ae4d1de/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcc8b9b6c574658ae4d1de/</guid><description>The last seven years have been the seven warmest on record for the planet, new data shows, as Earth&amp;rsquo;s temperature continues its precarious climb due to heat-trapping fossil fuel emissions.
Summary Hide Caption 1 of 12 Photos: South Sudan&amp;rsquo;s worst flooding in decades A girl pulls what remains of her family&amp;rsquo;s house through polluted floodwaters. Hide Caption 2 of 12 Photos: South Sudan&amp;rsquo;s worst flooding in decades A woman collects driftwood to try to build a shelter for her family.</description></item></channel></rss>