<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nato on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/nato/</link><description>Recent content in nato on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/nato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Putin warns of possible military response over ‘aggressive’ Nato</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</guid><description>Description Russian leader’s speech to top commanders comes as tensions grow with the west over Ukraine
Summary Vladimir Putin has said he will consider a military response if Russia feels threatened by Nato, in a sign that he is not ready to de-escalate tensions over a potential invasion of Ukraine. In a combative speech on Tuesday, Putin – who has demanded “security guarantees” from Nato – told his top military commanders that the west was to blame for the rising tensions.</description></item></channel></rss>