<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nato on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nato/</link><description>Recent content in nato on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>US tells Putin to choose confrontation or dialogue over Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</guid><description>Secretary of state Antony Blinken says week of talks is moment of truth for Vladimir Putin
Summary Formal talks are under way between US and Russian officials in Geneva over the fate of Ukraine, amid low expectations and high tensions driven by fears that the Kremlin will order an invasion. The other path is confrontation and massive consequences for Russia if it renews its aggression on Ukraine. “We’re about to test the proposition of which path President Putin wants to take this week,” Blinken, told the ABC News programme This Week.</description></item><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Putin warns of possible military response over ‘aggressive’ Nato</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</guid><description>Description Russian leader’s speech to top commanders comes as tensions grow with the west over Ukraine
Summary Vladimir Putin has said he will consider a military response if Russia feels threatened by Nato, in a sign that he is not ready to de-escalate tensions over a potential invasion of Ukraine. In a combative speech on Tuesday, Putin – who has demanded “security guarantees” from Nato – told his top military commanders that the west was to blame for the rising tensions.</description></item></channel></rss>