<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nato on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nato/</link><description>Recent content in nato on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finland's Parliament approves Nato application | News | Yle Uutiset</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283ae30a12a2b223feafe78/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:21:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283ae30a12a2b223feafe78/</guid><description>Following a 14-hour debate, the motion was passed by 188 votes to 8.
Highlights Finland will seek to join the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation (Nato) President Sauli Niinistö and Prime Minister Sanna Marin (SDP) announced the move on Sunday. Following a 14-hour debate, the motion was passed by 188 votes to 8. A total of 212 speeches were made to Parliament during the debate that preceded the vote. The president and government are now able to put the official application process into motion, possibly as soon as later on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Sweden's ruling party backs joining NATO, paving way for bid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62815f419889176b513ea0b5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62815f419889176b513ea0b5/</guid><description>Sweden&amp;rsquo;s ruling Social Democrats said on Sunday they backed the country joining NATO, abandoning decades of opposition in the wake of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine and creating a large parliament majority in favour of membership.
Highlights Sweden&amp;rsquo;s ruling Social Democrats said on Sunday they backed the country joining NATO. With neighboring Finland already set to hand in its application, Prime Minister Magdalena Andersson is now all but certain to launch a formal application within days.</description></item><item><title>NATO warships arrive at Finnish port for training exercises</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626836f279b49ffa35e91d39/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 18:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626836f279b49ffa35e91d39/</guid><description>Three NATO warships arrived in the southwestern Finnish port of of Turku on Monday to train with Finland&amp;rsquo;s navy as Helsinki considers the possibility of joining the U.S.-led alliance amid increased tensions with Russia over Ukraine.
Highlights Three NATO warships arrived in the southwestern Finnish port of of Turku on Monday to train with Finland&amp;rsquo;s navy. Latvian minelayer LVNS Virsaitis and minehunters Estonian ENS Sakala and Dutch HNLMS Schiedam will train.</description></item><item><title>U.S. and NATO say Russia is building up troops near Ukraine, not withdrawing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d769e093fc1e733d0e5ed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 22:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d769e093fc1e733d0e5ed/</guid><description>The United States and NATO said Russia was still building up troops around Ukraine on Wednesday despite Moscow&amp;rsquo;s insistence it was pulling back, questioning President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s stated desire to negotiate a solution to the crisis.
Highlights Russia says video shows tanks, infantry fighting vehicles, and self-propelled artillery units leaving Crimea. U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said key Russian units were moving towards the border, not away. Russia&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said its forces were pulling back after exercises in southern and western military districts near Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Soldier Opens Fire, Kills Five Soldiers at Military Base</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2b4dca174bcde43071f3c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2b4dca174bcde43071f3c/</guid><description>The attacker opened fire with an assault rifle then fled the scene.
Highlights A Ukrainian National Guard soldier opened fire on security guards at a military factory in central Ukraine for reasons unknown, killing five people and wounding five others before fleeing. Interior Minister Denys Monastyrskiy named the soldier as Artem Ryabchuk and said he would “bear the strictest responsibility provided by law”. He said investigators would look into how the soldier passed a medical commission that allowed him access to weapons.</description></item><item><title>Kyiv's mayor decries Germany's offer of 5,000 helmets to Ukraine as a 'joke' and asks if 'pillows' are next</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f226f2180452bda9b3dace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f226f2180452bda9b3dace/</guid><description>Unlike other NATO members, Germany has declined to send weapons to Ukraine, renewing scrutiny of its motives.
Summary Germany is offering 5,000 helmets to Ukraine amid fears of a Russian invasion. &amp;ldquo;We will supply Ukraine with 5,000 helmets as a clear signal: We are at your side.&amp;rdquo; Nord Stream 2 bypasses Ukraine — depriving it of billions in gas transit fees. Even still, the Ukrainian government vehemently opposes Nord Stream 2.</description></item><item><title>Croatia To Withdraw Its Forces From NATO In Event Of Russia - Ukraine Conflict - President</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ffb43ec2567a2b727bd3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 08:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ffb43ec2567a2b727bd3/</guid><description>Croatia will withdraw its military from the NATO forces deployed in the region in the event of a conflict between Russia and Ukraine, President Zoran Milanovic said on Tuesday.I follow reports, according to which, NATO, not a separate state, not the United States, is strengthening its presence, sen ..
Summary (@FahadShabbir)BELGRADE (UrduPoint News / Sputnik - 25th January, 2022) Croatia will withdraw its military from the NATO forces deployed in the region in the event of a conflict between Russia and Ukraine, President Zoran Milanovic said on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine hit by ‘massive’ cyber-attack on government websites</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1c858146ceffe00e659d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1c858146ceffe00e659d9/</guid><description>Suspected Russian hackers leave message warning: ‘Ukrainians … be afraid and expect worse’
Summary Ukraine has been hit by a “massive” cyber-attack, with the websites of several government departments including the ministry of foreign affairs and the education ministry knocked out. Suspected Russian hackers left a message on the foreign ministry website, according to reports. NEWS IN KYIV: Several Ukrainian government websites down due to a major a cyberattack. But we can imagine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>US tells Putin to choose confrontation or dialogue over Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</guid><description>Secretary of state Antony Blinken says week of talks is moment of truth for Vladimir Putin
Summary Formal talks are under way between US and Russian officials in Geneva over the fate of Ukraine, amid low expectations and high tensions driven by fears that the Kremlin will order an invasion. The other path is confrontation and massive consequences for Russia if it renews its aggression on Ukraine. “We’re about to test the proposition of which path President Putin wants to take this week,” Blinken, told the ABC News programme This Week.</description></item><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Putin warns of possible military response over ‘aggressive’ Nato</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</guid><description>Description Russian leader’s speech to top commanders comes as tensions grow with the west over Ukraine
Summary Vladimir Putin has said he will consider a military response if Russia feels threatened by Nato, in a sign that he is not ready to de-escalate tensions over a potential invasion of Ukraine. In a combative speech on Tuesday, Putin – who has demanded “security guarantees” from Nato – told his top military commanders that the west was to blame for the rising tensions.</description></item></channel></rss>