<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>power on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/power/</link><description>Recent content in power on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 09:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/power/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ERCOT Asks Texans to Conserve Power Until 8 P.M., Through the Weekend</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f72e6104fd436f0e26b0e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f72e6104fd436f0e26b0e/</guid><description>ERCOT asking all Texans to conserve energy through the weekend as we head into potentially record heat.
Highlights ERCOT asks all Texans to conserve energy through the weekend as we head into potentially record heat. Six power plants dropped off the grid Friday, resulting in a loss of about 2,900 MW of generation &amp;ndash; that&amp;rsquo;s enough electricity to power about 580,000 homes. The Electric Reliability Council of Texas said, &amp;ldquo;unseasonably hot weather&amp;rdquo; was driving record demand across Texas.</description></item><item><title>Water is so low in the Colorado River, feds are holding some back so one dam can keep generating power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728a1923276fefa5f6eab5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728a1923276fefa5f6eab5/</guid><description>The decision will keep more water in Lake Powell, the reservoir located at the Glen Canyon Dam in northern Arizona.
Highlights The decision will keep more water in Lake Powell, the reservoir located at the Glen Canyon Dam in northern Arizona. Officials said the actions will help save water, protect the dam&amp;rsquo;s ability to produce hydropower and provide officials with more time to figure out how to operate the dam at lower water levels.</description></item><item><title>Lake Powell water officials face an impossible choice amid the West's megadrought - CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e185ce34e269f6de996c7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 05:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e185ce34e269f6de996c7/</guid><description>Lake Powell, the country&amp;rsquo;s second-largest reservoir, is drying up.
Highlights Glen Canyon Dam has lost about 16 percent of its capacity to generate power over the past several years. In a worst-case scenario, the Interior Department projects the dam could stop producing power by January. The agency is now weighing an emergency action that would buy the dam more time. Loss of power at the dam would also mean higher energy costs for customers as the price of fossil fuels skyrockets.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court blocks Biden vaccine mandate for businesses, backs health-care worker rule</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0cb3b85a13bc99466417f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0cb3b85a13bc99466417f/</guid><description>The Supreme Court ruled against the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s rule for OSHA, saying it did not have the power to require vaccination for millions of Americans.
Summary The rulings came three days after the Occupational Safety and Health Administration&amp;rsquo;s emergency measure for businesses started to take effect. The Supreme Court on Thursday blocked the Biden administration from enforcing its sweeping vaccine-or-test requirements for large private companies, but allowed a vaccine mandate to stand for medical facilities that take Medicare or Medicaid payments.</description></item><item><title>Czech Republic to end coal use by 2033, boost nuclear power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8e22fe146efa5c4b73ba9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8e22fe146efa5c4b73ba9/</guid><description>Summary PRAGUE (AP) — The new Czech government aims to phase out coal in energy production by 2033 while increasing the country&amp;rsquo;s reliance on nuclear and renewable sources, its policy program published on Friday said. Coal-fired power plants currently generate almost 50% of total Czech electricity output. “It must accelerate the plan.”The European Union member plans to become more reliant on nuclear power, which neighboring Germany has decided to phase out by the end of 2022.</description></item></channel></rss>