<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attacked on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attacked/</link><description>Recent content in attacked on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 14:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attacked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mona Lisa attacked with cake by man 'dressed as old lady in wheelchair'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294d093838e0dd5ce9877d1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 14:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294d093838e0dd5ce9877d1/</guid><description>Footage captured at the Louvre in Paris shows a person apparently wearing lipstick and a wig asking people to &amp;quot;think of the planet&amp;quot; after attacking the world&amp;rsquo;s most famous portrait.
Highlights A person dressed as an old woman in a wheelchair staged an attack on the Mona Lisa in Paris. Footage shows the person apparently wearing lipstick and a wig asking people to &amp;ldquo;think of the planet&amp;rdquo; The painting, considered an archetypal masterpiece of the Italian Renaissance, was not damaged.</description></item><item><title>Soldier dies after being attacked by bear on base in Alaska</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bfd95c55693f79bea8ecf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 18:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bfd95c55693f79bea8ecf/</guid><description>Officials say it happened during a training exercise. They&amp;rsquo;re still looking for the bear.
Highlights The soldier was part of a small group in a training area west of the Anchorage Regional Landfill when the bear attacked. The name of the soldier was being withheld pending next-of-kin notification. Alaska Wildlife Troopers were searching for the bear in the area, which is closed to the public for all recreational activity. Officials say the incident happened during a training exercise at Joint Base Elmendorf-Richardson in Alaska.</description></item><item><title>A man who attacked and blamed an Asian family for Covid-19 pleaded guilty to hate crimes charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217cb5c0f3d6d9f7c376611/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217cb5c0f3d6d9f7c376611/</guid><description>A 21-year-old Texas man pleaded guilty to federal hate crime charges after he brutally attacked and blamed an Asian family whom he believed to be Chinese for the Covid-19 pandemic, prosecutors announced Wednesday.
Highlights Jose Gomez III saw a Burmese family with three young children enter a Sam’s Club in Texas. He followed them into the store and attacked the family, slashing the father and a child who was then 6 years old.</description></item></channel></rss>