<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>worked on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worked/</link><description>Recent content in worked on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 22:11:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lawyer Sussmann, who worked for Clinton, acquitted of lying to FBI in 2016</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62969261b61f091cd31fb41b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 22:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62969261b61f091cd31fb41b/</guid><description>A jury cleared Michael Sussmann, a lawyer for Democrats, of lying to the FBI at the height of the 2016 campaign — a defeat for special counsel John Durham.
Highlights A federal jury acquits Michael Sussmann on a charge that he lied to the FBI in 2016 while acting on behalf of the Hillary Clinton campaign. The verdict comes after less than a full day of deliberations spread over parts of Friday and Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Two journalists exposing Mexico’s corruption and drug violence murdered within one week | Margarito Martínez Esquivel and José Luis Gamboa are the latest casualties in the world’s most dangerous country for reporters outside war zones</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8279278c8a4a62084a7ea/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8279278c8a4a62084a7ea/</guid><description>Margarito Martínez Esquivel and José Luis Gamboa are the latest casualties in the world’s most dangerous country for reporters outside war zones
Summary Mexico’s embattled press corps has suffered a shattering start to the new year with the murders of two journalists who had dared chronicle their country’s slide into drug- and corruption-fuelled violence. Martínez’s death came a week after another journalist, José Luis Gamboa, was fatally stabbed in the eastern state of Veracruz, another of Mexico’s most violent regions.</description></item></channel></rss>