<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>transfer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transfer/</link><description>Recent content in transfer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transfer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Norway has decided to additionally transfer anti-tank weapons to Ukraine, according to the website of the Norwegian Defense Ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245c55b8759cc5201539b88/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245c55b8759cc5201539b88/</guid><description>“Norway handed over another 2,000 anti-tank weapons (M72) to Ukraine. The weapons were donated,” the statement said.
Highlights Norway handed over another 2,000 anti-tank weapons to Ukraine. The weapons were donated to Ukraine by Norway, Norway said in a statement. Norway also handed over more than 3,000 other weapons to the country, the statement said. Ukraine has been fighting a growing insurgency in Ukraine since Ukraine began in 2010. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>National Archives had to retrieve Trump White House records from Mar-a-Lago</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62017cd922a2e3df0db29038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 20:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62017cd922a2e3df0db29038/</guid><description>President Donald Trump improperly removed multiple boxes from the White House that were&amp;hellip;
Highlights The boxes were retrieved by the National Archives and Records Administration from Trump&amp;rsquo;s Mar-a-Lago residence last month. They contained documents and other items that should have been turned over to the agency. The recovery of the boxes raises new concerns about his adherence to the Presidential Records Act. Trump advisers deny any nefarious intent and said the boxes contained mementos, gifts, letters from world leaders and other correspondence.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 patient whose family sued to keep him on ventilator dies after transfer from Mercy Hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 07:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</guid><description>Scott Quiner, a COVID-19 patient from Buffalo, Minnesota, whose wife sued Mercy Hospital in Coon Rapids to keep him on a ventilator, died Saturday morning at a Texas hospital, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney confirmed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;On behalf of the family of Scott Quiner, I would like to thank the public for the outpouring of love and support during this difficult time,&amp;rdquo; Holsten said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;The family now requests privacy while they grieve the loss of their beloved husband and father.</description></item></channel></rss>