<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>warns on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/warns/</link><description>Recent content in warns on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 20:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/warns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DHS warns of domestic violent extremists who praise Uvalde shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fb0c3d2836224903a3e78/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 20:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fb0c3d2836224903a3e78/</guid><description>Domestic violent extremists praised last month&amp;rsquo;s school shooting in Uvalde, Texas, and called for at least one copycat attack, the Department of Homeland Security said.
Highlights Department of Homeland Security reissued National Terrorism Advisory System Bulletin on Tuesday. The bulletin said domestic violent extremists are propagating disinformation and inciting grievances. Homeland Security officials are also concerned about possible fallout from an expected Supreme Court decision that could overturn Roe v. Wade.</description></item><item><title>Americans should get ready for $5 a gallon gas, analyst warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220b2b5d6af769c0d7c69af/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 12:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220b2b5d6af769c0d7c69af/</guid><description>The cost of filling up your car is soaring across much of the U.S as the Ukraine crisis further drives up oil prices.
Highlights The cost of filling up your car is soaring across much of the U.S. as the Ukraine crisis further drives up oil prices. Oil prices continue to rise as the war with Ukraine intensifies, experts say. The current national average price of gas is $3.61 per gallon, up 26 cents from February and roughly a dollar from a year ago.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan reports nine Chinese aircraft in its air defence zone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217af79d45b6a69b6fd1a23/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 16:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217af79d45b6a69b6fd1a23/</guid><description>Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s air force scrambled again on Thursday to warn away nine Chinese aircraft that entered its air defence zone, Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said, on the same day that Russia invaded Ukraine, a crisis being watched closely in Taipei.
Highlights Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s air force scrambled again on Thursday to warn away nine Chinese aircraft that entered its air defence zone. Taiwan has complained of regular such missions by the Chinese air force over the last two years, though the aircraft do not get close to Taiwan itself.</description></item><item><title>FDA warns consumers not to use certain Family Dollar products in 6 states after discovering more than 1,000 dead rodents at plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621124d6d524bb30f7191963/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621124d6d524bb30f7191963/</guid><description>The recall impacts stores in Alabama, Arkansas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Missouri and Tennessee, and products purchased between January 1, 2021, and today.
Highlights The FDA says it found more than 1,000 dead rodents after a fumigation at a distribution facility in Arkansas. Family Dollar says it is not aware of any reports of illness related to the recall. The FDA said it began an investigation into the West Memphis, Arkansas, distribution facility after receiving a consumer complaint in January.</description></item><item><title>U.S. truckers planning protest convoy, perhaps starting in L.A. for Super Bowl, DHS warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62059bdb633558b3b095dc33/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 23:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62059bdb633558b3b095dc33/</guid><description>The convoy, similar to the one in Canada, would then head east and might get to Washington in time for President Biden&amp;rsquo;s State of the Union address on March 1, the bulletin says.
Highlights Department of Homeland Security is warning U.S. law enforcement agencies that a group of truckers is planning a protest of COVID-19 vaccine mandates that could start as soon as this weekend in Los Angeles. The bulletin warns that the convoy &amp;ldquo;could severely disrupt transportation, federal government, and law enforcement operations through gridlock and potential counterprotests&amp;rdquo; The warning was circulated to law enforcement nationwide on Tuesday and was first reported by Yahoo News.</description></item><item><title>Moderna CEO says people may need fourth Covid shot as efficacy of boosters likely to decline over time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d82c13bce593c7edb848ce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d82c13bce593c7edb848ce/</guid><description>Summary Juan Medina | ReutersModerna CEO Stephane Bancel on Thursday said the efficacy of boosters against Covid-19 will likely decline over time, and people may need a fourth shot in the fall to increase their protection. However, Bancel said the efficacy of boosters will probably decline over the course of several months, similar to what happened with the first two doses. The Moderna CEO said governments, including the U.K. and South Korea, are already ordering the doses in preparation.</description></item><item><title>​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1317578f19497e1e890c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1317578f19497e1e890c9/</guid><description>​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions - EU Today
Summary ​Moscow warns Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensionsMoscow has warned Finland and Sweden against joining Nato amid rising tensions between Russia and the western military alliance. Maria Zakharova, the Russian foreign ministry spokeswoman, accused the alliance of trying to pull the two countries into its orbit, the Times reports. “It is quite obvious that the ascension of Finland and Sweden to Nato would have serious military and political consequences that would require an adequate response from Russia,” she said, not specifying what response Russia might take.</description></item></channel></rss>