<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/security/</link><description>Recent content in security on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Praise for Uvalde shooter and call for copycats is growing online, Homeland Security warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1fef4957202de9e9fc98d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1fef4957202de9e9fc98d/</guid><description>In a U.S. Dept. of Homeland Security bulletin released Thursday, officials sounded the&amp;hellip;
Highlights Homeland Security officials say online forums known for hosting violent extremist content are encouraging copycat attacks in the U.S. Department of Homeland Security bulletin released Tuesday morning. The bulletin comes as evidence of law enforcement’s calamitous mishandling of the shooting continues to emerge. A lone gunman shot and killed 19 children and two teachers at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, on May 20, killing two teachers and 19 children.</description></item><item><title>Russia pushed back from Kharkiv - report from front line</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628037ba7847e109e53f69eb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 23:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628037ba7847e109e53f69eb/</guid><description>Correspondent Quentin Sommerville and cameraman Darren Conway are with Ukrainian troops as they advance.
Highlights Half a dozen locals detained in the basement of one building suspected of aiding the enemy. Their eyes are covered with balaclavas taped over their heads, their hands tied. At least one woman is among them. They are left alone in a room, then taken away to the security services for questioning. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Rep. Madison Cawthorn caught bringing loaded gun through airport security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626852ae85a87c0c9952ec2f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626852ae85a87c0c9952ec2f/</guid><description>Madison Cawthorn, a Republican congressman from North Carolina, was caught trying to go through security with a loaded gun at Charlotte Douglas International Airport.
Highlights Madison Cawthorn, a Republican congressman from North Carolina, was caught trying to go through security with a loaded gun at Charlotte Douglas International Airport Tuesday morning. He was issued a citation for possession of a dangerous weapon on city property by Charlotte Mecklenburg police. This was the second time the congressman has been stopped trying to bring a weapon through airport security.</description></item><item><title>Temple Mount closed to Jews 'until further notice,' says site admin.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265f14fe87068c7e5eadf39/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265f14fe87068c7e5eadf39/</guid><description>Police made decision after ongoing clashes with Arab protesters at site
Highlights Police made decision after ongoing clashes with Arab protesters at site. Jewish prayers will be held at the gates of the Temple Mount and next to the Western, Southern, Eastern and Northern Walls. Clashes have broken out between Arabs and Israeli security forces at the site and al-Aqsa Mosque in recent days as Muslims celebrated Ramadan and Jews celebrated Passover.</description></item><item><title>Diplomats spar over 'edited' Russian letter: Russia has accused Canada of "kindergarten-level" diplomacy in a Twitter tiff over a social media post by Canada's United Nations mission.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62361d81660fb0073e45f1e6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62361d81660fb0073e45f1e6/</guid><description>Russia accuses Canada of &amp;lsquo;kindergarten&amp;rsquo; diplomacy in spat over a Russian letter sent to UN members.
Highlights Russia accuses Canada of &amp;lsquo;kindergarten&amp;rsquo; diplomacy in spat over a Russian letter sent to UN members. Russia: &amp;ldquo;Your diplomatic skills and good manners are at lowest ebb&amp;rdquo; Russia says it failed to secure enough support to win a non-permanent seat on the powerful UN Security Council. Russia&amp;rsquo;s first deputy permanent representative of Russia to the U.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy 'survives three assassination attempts in past week'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62222cb07315ad90267b81ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 15:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62222cb07315ad90267b81ed/</guid><description>The mercenaries reportedly track Zelenskyy&amp;rsquo;s every movement via his cell phone.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has reportedly survived three assassination attempts in the last week. The Kremlin-backed Wagner Group and Chechen special forces have both attempted to kill the Ukrainian president. The mercenaries are said to have been in Ukraine since January and are tracking Zelenkyy&amp;rsquo;s every movement via his cell phone. Zelenkey has refused to leave Kyiv even when offered help to get out of the country by the US.</description></item><item><title>Russian squad sent to assassinate Ukraine president has been 'eliminated'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621eef6cc0b2f74ee6aa6d8c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621eef6cc0b2f74ee6aa6d8c/</guid><description>The unit sent to dispose of President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has been defeated, it has been claimed today.
Highlights Head of the National Security and Defense Council has been eliminated. It comes as the TV tower in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s capital Kyiv has been hit by the Russian army. Local media reported that there were several explosions in the area. The head of the national security and defense council said the situation was &amp;lsquo;horrifying&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;a blatant violation of international law&amp;rsquo; and urged Russia to stop the violence in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>New Chinese hacking tool found, spurring U.S. warning to allies. “Chinese hacking tool that has been able to escape public attention for more than a decade.”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dba12870c7342f5be9657/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 06:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dba12870c7342f5be9657/</guid><description>Security researchers with U.S. cybersecurity firm Symantec said they have discovered a “highly sophisticated” Chinese hacking tool that has been able to escape public attention for more than a decade.
Highlights Security researchers with U.S. cybersecurity firm Symantec said they have discovered a “highly sophisticated” Chinese hacking tool. The tool, which it calls Daxin, has been able to escape public attention for more than a decade. The discovery was shared with the United States in recent months, who have shared the information with foreign partners.</description></item><item><title>Pentagon approves requests for National Guard as trucker convoy eyes D.C.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621686b063bf86a7320aeb06/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621686b063bf86a7320aeb06/</guid><description>The trucker convoy is expected to arrive in the D.C. area as soon as Wednesday.
Highlights National Guard will help during truck convoy protests headed to D.C. area. Truck drivers protesting vaccine requirements are expected to arrive late Wednesday or Thursday. About 700 National Guard personnel will be deployed to help control traffic at designated traffic posts and points leading to the Capitol. Trucker convoy is expected to depart Pennsylvania on Wednesday morning and drive to the area, arriving late Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Putin gets no support from UN Security Council over Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621596b70dd651dd6bc92e1b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 02:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621596b70dd651dd6bc92e1b/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin has received no support from members of the U.N. Security Council for his actions to bring separatists in eastern Ukraine under Moscow’s control
Highlights U.S. calls Putin&amp;rsquo;s moves a pretext for a further invasion of Ukraine. Russia recognizes independence of separatist regions of Luhansk and Donetsk, scenes of an eight-year war. Close ally China urges diplomacy and a peaceful solution. Russia accused the United States and its allies of egging on Ukraine &amp;ndash; which he says is not February 2014.</description></item><item><title>U.S. truckers planning protest convoy, perhaps starting in L.A. for Super Bowl, DHS warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62059bdb633558b3b095dc33/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 23:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62059bdb633558b3b095dc33/</guid><description>The convoy, similar to the one in Canada, would then head east and might get to Washington in time for President Biden&amp;rsquo;s State of the Union address on March 1, the bulletin says.
Highlights Department of Homeland Security is warning U.S. law enforcement agencies that a group of truckers is planning a protest of COVID-19 vaccine mandates that could start as soon as this weekend in Los Angeles. The bulletin warns that the convoy &amp;ldquo;could severely disrupt transportation, federal government, and law enforcement operations through gridlock and potential counterprotests&amp;rdquo; The warning was circulated to law enforcement nationwide on Tuesday and was first reported by Yahoo News.</description></item><item><title>Star witness in Ukraine impeachment saga sues Trump allies and alleges conspiracy to intimidate him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb357790ec5ce7283f38d9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 01:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb357790ec5ce7283f38d9/</guid><description>Retired Army Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman, who served on the National Security Council and emerged as a star witness against then-President Donald Trump during the 2019 Ukraine impeachment, is suing Donald Trump Jr., Rudy Giuliani and former Trump White House staffers, alleging they conspired against him.
Highlights Retired Army Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman served on the National Security Council and emerged as a star witness against then-President Donald Trump during the 2019 Ukraine impeachment.</description></item><item><title>Biden touts 'total unanimity' with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</guid><description>President Biden said Monday he and European leaders are in agreement following a call to discuss strategy in response to Russia’s military build-up along the Ukrainian border.
Summary Total unanimity with all the European leaders. We’ll talk about it later,” Biden said after a previously planned meeting with administration officials to discuss lowering prices. Biden met for 80 minutes earlier Monday with European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, European Council President Charles Michel, French President Emmanuel Macron Emmanuel Jean-Michel MacronDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;rsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine Biden huddling with European leaders on Russia&amp;rsquo;s military buildup near Ukraine MORE, British Prime Minister Boris Johnson Boris JohnsonDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;rsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine UK scrapping testing requirements for vaccinated arrivals MORE, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz, Italian Prime Minister Mario Draghi, NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg and Polish President Andrzej Duda.</description></item><item><title>Mexican journalist who told president she feared for her life shot dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efd85c1236c67fb3adec2e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 11:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efd85c1236c67fb3adec2e/</guid><description>Journalist Lourdes Maldonado López was killed in the Mexican border city of Tijuana on Sunday, days after news photographer Margarito Martínez was gunned down at his home there.
Summary Journalist Lourdes Maldonado López was killed in the Mexican border city of Tijuana on Sunday, days after news photographer Margarito Martínez was gunned down at his home there. According to local news reports, Maldonado was found dead of one gunshot inside a car outside her home.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew faces calls to pay for his own security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</guid><description>Growing clamour for royal to lose dukedom and taxpayer-funded Scotland Yard security detail
Summary The Duke of York faces calls to pay for his own security and relinquish his dukedom after being stripped of his military affiliations and royal patronages in the fallout over the civil sexual assault case against him. The calls come as his accuser, Virginia Giuffre, welcomed the New York court ruling that paved the way for her lawsuit against Prince Andrew to proceed to trial, as she pledged to “continue to expose the truth”.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops arrive in Kazakhstan, as dozens of protesters killed, thousands arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</guid><description>Russia sent paratroopers to Kazakhstan to help its government end mass protests there.
Summary Small numbers of Russian paratrooper units landed at an airbase in Kazakhstan, with Russian state media showing the soldiers disembarking from transport planes and off-loading armored vehicles. The number of Russian troops was unclear, but it was estimated from several hundred to a few thousand, alongside several hundred from Belarus, Tajikistan and Armenia that were also due to arrive.</description></item><item><title>Japan bans facial recognition tech exports due to China's human rights abuses: Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</guid><description>Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions | 2022-01-03 16:53:00
Summary A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. Tokyo has deemed the new measures necessary to prevent technologies from being used in this way. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>