<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/security/</link><description>Recent content in security on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prince Andrew faces calls to pay for his own security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</guid><description>Growing clamour for royal to lose dukedom and taxpayer-funded Scotland Yard security detail
Summary The Duke of York faces calls to pay for his own security and relinquish his dukedom after being stripped of his military affiliations and royal patronages in the fallout over the civil sexual assault case against him. The calls come as his accuser, Virginia Giuffre, welcomed the New York court ruling that paved the way for her lawsuit against Prince Andrew to proceed to trial, as she pledged to “continue to expose the truth”.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops arrive in Kazakhstan, as dozens of protesters killed, thousands arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</guid><description>Russia sent paratroopers to Kazakhstan to help its government end mass protests there.
Summary Small numbers of Russian paratrooper units landed at an airbase in Kazakhstan, with Russian state media showing the soldiers disembarking from transport planes and off-loading armored vehicles. The number of Russian troops was unclear, but it was estimated from several hundred to a few thousand, alongside several hundred from Belarus, Tajikistan and Armenia that were also due to arrive.</description></item><item><title>Japan bans facial recognition tech exports due to China's human rights abuses: Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</guid><description>Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions | 2022-01-03 16:53:00
Summary A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. Tokyo has deemed the new measures necessary to prevent technologies from being used in this way. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>