<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>registration on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/registration/</link><description>Recent content in registration on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 02:44:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/registration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tenth person charged with Florida voter fraud investigation over jailhouse registrations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a5b557535f8507dd50c8d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 02:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a5b557535f8507dd50c8d/</guid><description>“They told us that if we weren’t already convicted of our current crime then we were able to sign up and vote.&amp;quot;
Highlights 10th former jail inmate is facing felony voter fraud charges. The 46-year-old is accused of registering to vote and casting a ballot in the 2020 presidential election. At least eight of the inmates registered during voter registration drives organized by Alachua County’s Democratic elections supervisor, Kim A. Barton, in February and July 2020.</description></item><item><title>4th resident of The Villages arrested for allegedly casting multiple ballots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6313e0353c8342089944f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6313e0353c8342089944f/</guid><description>A fourth resident of The Villages has been arrested for allegedly casting multiple ballots in the 2020 election.
Summary THE VILLAGES, Fla. – A fourth resident of The Villages has been arrested as part of an ongoing investigation into voter fraud. Voter registration records show Barnes was not affiliated with a political party in Florida when he voted in the 2020 election. Barnes was also registered to vote in his original home state of Connecticut in 2020, records show.</description></item></channel></rss>