<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bucha on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bucha/</link><description>Recent content in bucha on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 19:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bucha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Hands tied, shot in ear and limbs': Bodies of men tortured, killed by Russian forces found in Bucha grave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d89d9d06c5329b3acb3d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 19:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d89d9d06c5329b3acb3d6/</guid><description>According to a Ukraine media reports, Ukrainian authorities filed criminal charges Thursday (April 28) against Russian soldiers allegedly involved in mass killings in Bucha.
Highlights Ukrainian authorities filed criminal charges Thursday (April 28) against Russian soldiers allegedly involved in mass killings in Bucha. According to police, on 29 April, a pit containing the bodies of three men who had been beaten up by Russian soldiers and then brutally killed was found.</description></item><item><title>‘They were all shot’: Russia accused of war crimes as Bucha reveals horror of invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a41bb1257dd0c87b4746b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a41bb1257dd0c87b4746b/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces liberating the town of Bucha near Kyiv find streets littered with corpses of civilians and burned-out Russian tanks
Highlights At least 20 bodies, all in civilian clothing, found strewn across a single street in Bucha, a town north-west of the capital. At least 280 other bodies have been buried in mass graves in the town, local residents say. British foreign secretary Liz Truss said she was ‘appalled’ by atrocities in town of Bucha.</description></item></channel></rss>