<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pay on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pay/</link><description>Recent content in pay on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 18:10:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>San Jose passes first U.S. law requiring gun owners to get liability insurance and pay annual fee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f18c40be2b21499173e8a2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 18:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f18c40be2b21499173e8a2/</guid><description>They&amp;rsquo;d also have to pay an annual fee. But opponents promised to fight the measure in court. People on both sides of the issue spoke at length before the vote was taken.
Summary The San Jose City Council overwhelmingly approved the measure despite opposition from gun owners who said it would violate their Second Amendment rights and promised to sue. Council members, including several who had lost friends to gun violence, said it was a step toward dealing with gun violence, which Councilman Sergio Jimenez called &amp;ldquo;a scourge on our society.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew faces calls to pay for his own security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</guid><description>Growing clamour for royal to lose dukedom and taxpayer-funded Scotland Yard security detail
Summary The Duke of York faces calls to pay for his own security and relinquish his dukedom after being stripped of his military affiliations and royal patronages in the fallout over the civil sexual assault case against him. The calls come as his accuser, Virginia Giuffre, welcomed the New York court ruling that paved the way for her lawsuit against Prince Andrew to proceed to trial, as she pledged to “continue to expose the truth”.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated Quebecers will have to pay a health tax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de6e90a2a0ddcc83b36c5a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de6e90a2a0ddcc83b36c5a/</guid><description>Quebec Premier François Legault said Tuesday the province would be demanding a significant &amp;quot;health contribution&amp;quot; from Quebecers who refuse to get their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine in the coming weeks.
Summary Quebec Premier François Legault said Tuesday the province would be imposing a health tax on Quebecers who refuse to get their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine in the coming weeks. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a health contribution for adults who refuse to be vaccinated for non-medical reasons,&amp;rdquo; Legault said at a news conference, in which he also announced an interim public health director to replace Dr.</description></item><item><title>Ireland Will Soon Pay Arts and Culture Workers a Basic Income to Help the Sector Bounce Back From the Pandemic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</guid><description>Ireland announces a basic income plan for artists in an effort to counter the ongoing effects of the pandemic and lockdown.
Summary Artists and culture workers in Ireland will soon be eligible for some much-needed financial support as the government readies a new basic income program. Ireland will commit roughly €25 million ($28.3 million) to the program, which it expects to implement early this year. It will pay some 2,000 people a basic income for three years.</description></item></channel></rss>