<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pay on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pay/</link><description>Recent content in pay on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 07:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sri Lanka defaults on debt for first time in its history</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62873e92f297e89f49f3d3ba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 07:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62873e92f297e89f49f3d3ba/</guid><description>The governor of the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank and two major credit rating agencies said it has defaulted.
Highlights Central bank governor P Nandalal Weerasinghe said: &amp;ldquo;Our position is very clear, we said that until they come to the restructure [of our debts], we will not be able to pay&amp;rdquo; Two major credit rating agencies said it has defaulted. The governor of the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank said the country was pre-emptively defaulted on Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Wealthiest Americans pay just 3.4% of income in taxes, investigation reveals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627414acd9c07786891bd528/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 18:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627414acd9c07786891bd528/</guid><description>Tax records from 2014 to 2018, analysed by ProPublica, show 25 Americans collectively earned $401bn but paid just $13.6bn
Highlights The wealthiest Americans paid just 3.4% of their annual income in taxes between 2014 and 2018. The average tax rate for the 400 richest Americans was 22% from 2013 to 2018. Wealthier Americans get their income through investments, like stocks, which are taxed at a lower rate than ordinary income. Ten of the top 15 earners on the list are billionaires who made their money in tech, earning an average of $2.</description></item><item><title>Judge orders Alex Jones to pay $1M in fees to 4 Sandy Hook parents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f25c25da9c3972d99d0ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f25c25da9c3972d99d0ac/</guid><description>The order is from the same Texas judge who is overseeing two upcoming trials to determine&amp;hellip;
Highlights The order is from the same Texas judge who is overseeing two upcoming trials to determine damages from defamation lawsuits Jones lost to Sandy Hook parents. Jones and his businesses have 30 days to pay the attorney fees and expenses for Neil Heslin and Scarlett Lewis, the parents of slain first-grader Jesse Lewis and Lenny Pozner.</description></item><item><title>Amazon internal chat app that censored talk of unions and ethics may 'never launch at all' Filter list reportedly would block 'living wage,' 'pay rises,' 'restroom,' etc</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f1c4ecc62ab9abd8ea471/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 17:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f1c4ecc62ab9abd8ea471/</guid><description>Amazon allegedly planned an internal messaging app that filtered words like &amp;quot;union,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;pay rise,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;ethics&amp;quot; alongside challenging and offensive terms. The company told The Register the software has not been approved and may never be deployed. Amazon
Highlights Amazon allegedly planned an internal messaging app that filtered words like &amp;ldquo;union,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;pay rise,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;ethics,&amp;rdquo; alongside challenging and offensive terms. The company told The Register the software has not been approved and may never be deployed.</description></item><item><title>Target will let shoppers use food stamps to pay for online orders</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246eedaa33edab987f888bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 12:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246eedaa33edab987f888bf/</guid><description>The US retail giant is following the footsteps of Walmart and Amazon, in a move to help attract lower-income shoppers.
Highlights Target will begin to accept payment online with food stamps in late April. Walmart and Amazon already accept food stamps on their websites since 2019. The move could help Target gain market share among lower-income shoppers. More than 3.2 million food-stamp households shopped online in January, double the number from a year before.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Springs to pay nearly $3 mln to family of Black man shot dead by police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</guid><description>A Colorado city has agreed to pay $2.9 million to settle a civil rights lawsuit filed by the family of a 19-year-old Black man who was fatally shot in the back by police in 2019, both sides in the litigation said on Tuesday.
Highlights De&amp;rsquo;Von Bailey was shot four times after he bolted from two Colorado Springs policemen who were questioning him about an armed robbery in August 2019. Police said they retrieved a handgun from Bailey after he was shot.</description></item><item><title>San Jose passes first U.S. law requiring gun owners to get liability insurance and pay annual fee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f18c40be2b21499173e8a2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 18:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f18c40be2b21499173e8a2/</guid><description>They&amp;rsquo;d also have to pay an annual fee. But opponents promised to fight the measure in court. People on both sides of the issue spoke at length before the vote was taken.
Summary The San Jose City Council overwhelmingly approved the measure despite opposition from gun owners who said it would violate their Second Amendment rights and promised to sue. Council members, including several who had lost friends to gun violence, said it was a step toward dealing with gun violence, which Councilman Sergio Jimenez called &amp;ldquo;a scourge on our society.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew faces calls to pay for his own security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2efeae8d39ae286d51959/</guid><description>Growing clamour for royal to lose dukedom and taxpayer-funded Scotland Yard security detail
Summary The Duke of York faces calls to pay for his own security and relinquish his dukedom after being stripped of his military affiliations and royal patronages in the fallout over the civil sexual assault case against him. The calls come as his accuser, Virginia Giuffre, welcomed the New York court ruling that paved the way for her lawsuit against Prince Andrew to proceed to trial, as she pledged to “continue to expose the truth”.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated Quebecers will have to pay a health tax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de6e90a2a0ddcc83b36c5a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de6e90a2a0ddcc83b36c5a/</guid><description>Quebec Premier François Legault said Tuesday the province would be demanding a significant &amp;quot;health contribution&amp;quot; from Quebecers who refuse to get their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine in the coming weeks.
Summary Quebec Premier François Legault said Tuesday the province would be imposing a health tax on Quebecers who refuse to get their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine in the coming weeks. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a health contribution for adults who refuse to be vaccinated for non-medical reasons,&amp;rdquo; Legault said at a news conference, in which he also announced an interim public health director to replace Dr.</description></item><item><title>Ireland Will Soon Pay Arts and Culture Workers a Basic Income to Help the Sector Bounce Back From the Pandemic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db933e352b7f19c55781ed/</guid><description>Ireland announces a basic income plan for artists in an effort to counter the ongoing effects of the pandemic and lockdown.
Summary Artists and culture workers in Ireland will soon be eligible for some much-needed financial support as the government readies a new basic income program. Ireland will commit roughly €25 million ($28.3 million) to the program, which it expects to implement early this year. It will pay some 2,000 people a basic income for three years.</description></item></channel></rss>