<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>york on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/york/</link><description>Recent content in york on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 14:09:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/york/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>"First Time In History": Cancer Vanishes For Every Patient In Drug Trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f5c0ccaa4a16d6258a673/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 14:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f5c0ccaa4a16d6258a673/</guid><description>A small group of people with rectal cancer just experienced something of a miracle as their cancer simply vanished after an experimental treatment.
Highlights A small group of people with rectal cancer just experienced something of a miracle as their cancer simply vanished after an experimental treatment. In a small clinical trial, 18 patients took a drug called Dostarlimab for around six months, and in the end, every one of them saw their tumours disappear.</description></item><item><title>Officials Arrest 41 People in $3.8 Million Shoplifting Ring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292e21d90aef8e10ab0f884/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 03:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292e21d90aef8e10ab0f884/</guid><description>Authorities announced the bust of a massive retail theft ring in New York City, charging 41 people with stealing luxury goods from stores like Bloomingdale&amp;rsquo;s and Macy&amp;rsquo;s, before reselling the merchandise on eBay.
Highlights Officials say 41 people stole around $3.5M in goods from stores like Bloomingdale&amp;rsquo;s, Duane Reade, and Sephora. The items would then be resold on the auction website eBay. Police say they are looking into other possible shoplifting schemes in New York City.</description></item><item><title>Judge dismisses Trump federal lawsuit against New York Attorney General Letitia James over her probe of business</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291f4fcc416c3706ecde433/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291f4fcc416c3706ecde433/</guid><description>Ex-President Donald Trump and his company are being investigated by New York Attorney General Letitia James over valuations of real estate assets.
Highlights A federal judge dismissed a federal lawsuit by former President Donald Trump that sought to bar a civil investigation of his business by New York Attorney General Letitia James. The ruling by U.S. District Judge Brenda Sannes came a day after a state appeals court in New York upheld subpoenas issued by James compelling Trump and two of his adult children to appear for questioning under oath as part of her probe.</description></item><item><title>‘Pharma bro’ Martin Shkreli released from federal prison and into New York halfway house</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285fbd7332bbbf1f5ae6e4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 08:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285fbd7332bbbf1f5ae6e4e/</guid><description>Martin Shkreli will his securities fraud sentence in September. He gained infamy for raising the price of a drug by more than 4,000%.
Highlights Martin Shkreli, 39, was sentenced to 7 years in prison in March 2018. &amp;ldquo;Getting out of real prison is easier than getting out of Twitter prison,&amp;rdquo; he wrote on Facebook. He gained infamy for raising the price of a drug by more than 4,000%. He was convicted of securities fraud in 2017.</description></item><item><title>9-Year-Old Girl Found Dead in NYC Home After Restaurant Below Calls Cops About Odor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283305f578af1aa023b4f5b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 05:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283305f578af1aa023b4f5b/</guid><description>Shalom Guifarro was found dead with body trauma off Lincoln Place.
Highlights Shalom Guifarro, 9, was found dead in her home in Crown Heights, Brooklyn. The medical examiner ruled the death a homicide. Police have not announced any arrests. The Administration for Children&amp;rsquo;s Protective Services says it is investigating. The girl was found unresponsive and had &amp;ldquo;trauma to her body,&amp;rdquo; a preliminary report from police said. Neighbors said they smelled a foul odor from the home before police arrived Sunday afternoon, and police questioned the girl&amp;rsquo;s mother, who was taken to the precinct for questioning after officers visited the home Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo shooting suspect planned to continue rampage down street, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282a1f5f0021dc365650e78/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282a1f5f0021dc365650e78/</guid><description>The 18-year-old suspected shooter accused of storming a Buffalo supermarket Saturday and killing 10 and injuring three others, planned to continue his bloody rampage.
Highlights Payton Gendron, 18, is accused of storming a Buffalo, New York, supermarket Saturday and killing 10 and injuring three others. Police say he planned to continue his bloody rampage down the street before he was stopped, police said. Police Commissioner Joseph Gramaglia said the supermarket attack was a hate crime as 11 of 13 people who were shot were Black.</description></item><item><title>Journalists from multiple news outlets test positive after White House Correspondents Dinner weekend</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272d0317e8669ae48342f8e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 19:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272d0317e8669ae48342f8e/</guid><description>Trevor Noah joked about the event becoming a superspreader — and now the cases are rolling in.
Highlights The annual White House Correspondents Dinner has led to the inevitable spread of Covid. Reporters and staffers from CNN, ABC News, NBC News, CBS News, Politico, and other participating news organizations have tested positive for the virus. Most notably, ABC&amp;rsquo;s Jon Karl, who shook hands with President Biden and sat next to Kim Kardashian, has fallen ill.</description></item><item><title>Hate crimes in New York City are up 76% this year compared to the same period in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c06160027fdf4c7e549d9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 12:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c06160027fdf4c7e549d9/</guid><description>Hate crimes in New York City have increased 76% so far this year compared to the same period last year, according to data from the New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force (HCTF) released this week.
Highlights New York City has seen a rise in hate crimes compared to last year. Hate crimes have increased 76% since January 1 to April 10, data shows. The data was released as part of the New York Police Department&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat hate crimes.</description></item><item><title>Trump ally Devin Nunes loses CNN defamation appeal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625880d192352602c15715a4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 20:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625880d192352602c15715a4/</guid><description>A federal appeals court said Devin Nunes, the former California congressman and an ally of former U.S. President Donald Trump, cannot revive his defamation lawsuit against CNN over reports he was involved in efforts to uncover damaging Ukraine-related information about Joe Biden.
Highlights A federal appeals court said Devin Nunes cannot revive his defamation lawsuit against CNN. The 2nd U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Manhattan said Nunes failed to seek a correction fast enough, or show he deserved &amp;ldquo;special damages&amp;rdquo; for economic loss.</description></item><item><title>US arrests yakuza leader over alleged drugs for missiles deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625088e289e9fc6c6d73c6b5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625088e289e9fc6c6d73c6b5/</guid><description>Japanese organised crime boss and three Thais accused of trying to secure US-made weapons for Myanmar rebels, LTTE.
Highlights Prosecutors say Japanese organised crime boss and three Thais aimed to secure US-made weapons for Myanmar armed groups and Tamil Tigers. Takeshi Ebisawa, Sompak Rukrasaranee, Somphob Singhasiri and Suksan Jullanan were arrested in New York on Monday and Tuesday on drug and arms trafficking and money laundering charges. The four men had been under investigation by US Drug Enforcement Administration agents in Thailand since at least 2019.</description></item><item><title>Mayor orders New York’s homeless camps dismantled ‘within two weeks’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fe51114fbb0e5908645e6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 04:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fe51114fbb0e5908645e6/</guid><description>Eric Adams says officials will place people in ‘healthy living conditions with wraparound services’ as homelessness debate swirls
Highlights Eric Adams says homeless people will be placed in &amp;lsquo;healthy living conditions&amp;rsquo; with wraparound services, he says. The number of people living in parks and on the streets is estimated at around 1,100. The issue of homelessness in New York has arisen amid a crime spike in the city and a series of high-profile violent attacks, though advocates point out that the city – and its homeless population – has been caught in a crisis over inadequate mental health services for many years.</description></item><item><title>Ex-prosecutor: Trump 'guilty of numerous felony violations'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623da388f676fc7e4a9394e8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 11:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623da388f676fc7e4a9394e8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A prosecutor who had been leading a criminal investigation into Donald Trump before quitting last month said in his resignation letter that he believes the former president is “guilty of numerous felony violations” and he disagreed with the Manhattan district attorney’s decision not to seek an indictment.
Highlights Mark Pomerantz told District Attorney Alvin Bragg there was “evidence sufficient to establish Mr. Trump’s guilt beyond a reasonable doubt” of allegations he falsified financial statements to secure loans and burnish his image as a wealthy businessman.</description></item><item><title>Citigroup to cover travel expenses for abortions as U.S. states curb access</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62338838c3f71afefd0801dc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62338838c3f71afefd0801dc/</guid><description>Citigroup Inc has started covering travel expenses for employees who go out of state for abortions because of newly enacted restrictions in Texas and other places, becoming the first major U.S. bank to make that commitment.
Highlights Citigroup Inc has started covering travel expenses for employees who go out of state for abortions because of newly enacted restrictions in Texas and other places. The new policy is &amp;ldquo;in response to changes in reproductive healthcare laws in certain states in the U.</description></item><item><title>Asian woman punched 125 times in New York attack; suspect charged with attempted murder as hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623013532bd52389fdf73657/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 04:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623013532bd52389fdf73657/</guid><description>A man was charged with attempted murder in what police have described as a &amp;quot;brutal hate crime&amp;quot; against an Asian woman in New York state last week, with video
Highlights Tammel Esco, 42, was arrested and accused of calling a 67-year-old woman an &amp;ldquo;Asian b&amp;mdash;-,&amp;rdquo; following her into a building and severely beating her Friday in Yonkers, New York state. The woman, who was not publicly identified, is stable and recovering in a hospital, police said.</description></item><item><title>Smartmatic can pursue election-rigging claims against Fox News, Giuliani</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</guid><description>A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming that Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.S. presidential election to favor Democrat Joe Biden.
Highlights A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew case dismissed by stipulation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62282a3d8f1421567b358855/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62282a3d8f1421567b358855/</guid><description>Prince Andrew case dismissed by stipulation
Highlights Court document states the case has been dismissed, &amp;ldquo;with prejudice&amp;rdquo; and that &amp;ldquo;each party&amp;rdquo; will bear their own costs and fees. The sum of the settlement was not disclosed. Prince Andrew had been set to stand trial for allegedly sexually assaulting dozens of girls in New York and Florida in 2009. He had settled a civil lawsuit for $500,000, which was the basis for the case to have the case dismissed.</description></item><item><title>RT America ceases productions and lays off most of its staff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622162ff61ab54382610fe97/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622162ff61ab54382610fe97/</guid><description>RT America will cease productions and lay off most of its staff, according to a memo from T&amp;amp;R Productions, the production company behind the Russian state-funded network, which CNN obtained.
Highlights RT America will cease productions and lay off most of its staff, according to a memo from T&amp;amp;R Productions. The news would mean an effective end to RT America. The network, one of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s main mouthpieces in the US, was dropped earlier this week by DirecTV.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutors in charge of Trump criminal probe have resigned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216d5492a86165971587e05/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216d5492a86165971587e05/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The two prosecutors in charge of the Manhattan district attorney’s criminal investigation into former President Donald Trump and his business dealings suddenly resigned Wednesday, throwing the future of the probe into question just as pressure was building on Trump on several legal fronts.
Highlights Carey Dunne and Mark Pomerantz, top deputies who had been tasked with running the investigation on a day-to-day basis, have suddenly resigned throwing the future of the probe into question.</description></item><item><title>Walmart drops mask mandate for vaccinated employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</guid><description>Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. State-mandated masks will no longer be required unless required by state or local government. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in pharmacies will be required to
Highlights Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in clinical care settings will be required to keep wearing masks. Several states, from New York to California, have issued their own plans to lift indoor mask mandates.</description></item><item><title>Deputy U.N. chief left near tears by rape accounts in Ethiopia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</guid><description>Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed said on Friday she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women, which she described as &amp;quot;your worst nightmare.”
Highlights Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed says she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women. Mohammed spoke to reporters in New York a day after returning from Ethiopia. She called for accountability for atrocities committed against women and recounted sights of famine in the crisis-torn country.</description></item><item><title>NJ to Lift School Masking Mandate in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</guid><description>New Jersey will lift its school mask mandate in the second week of March, Gov. Phil Murphy told the New York Times.
Highlights New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy announced Monday that the state will end its school mask mandate on March 7. Murphy said school districts can continue their own mandates if they want. Connecticut Gov. Ned Lamont announced that his state mask mandate will end on Feb. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Michael Avenatti Found Guilty of Stealing $300k from Stormy Daniels</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fda44f7e9557be0fb1b9af/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fda44f7e9557be0fb1b9af/</guid><description>Michael Avenatti, a former top critic of ex-President Donald Trump, represented porn star Stormy Daniels in various legal fights connected to Trump.
Highlights A New York jury convicts Michael Avenatti of swindling Stormy Daniels out of nearly $300,000. The guilty verdict on charges of wire fraud and aggravated identity theft at Avenatti&amp;rsquo;s trial in Manhattan federal court is his second criminal conviction in that court. Avenatti represented himself during the trial, where he had claimed he was owed the money he took from Daniels&amp;rsquo; $800,000 advance for her 2018 book, &amp;ldquo;Full Disclosure&amp;rdquo; Daniels: &amp;ldquo;I am ecstatic.</description></item><item><title>Tesla owners complain about 'phantom braking.' Federal safety regulator considers a probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcfb9f8f6ba958a8e37130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 10:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcfb9f8f6ba958a8e37130/</guid><description>Federal safety regulators are mulling a probe after Tesla owners complained that their cars were stopping for no reason.
Highlights Federal safety regulators are mulling a probe after Tesla owners complained that their cars were stopping for no reason. The issue may stem from Tesla&amp;rsquo;s automatic braking feature hitting the brakes when there is no need to do so. An investigation would be the final step before the agency would demand that the company recall the vehicles to fix the feature.</description></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani, three other Trump allies subpoenaed in January 6 riot probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</guid><description>Former New York mayor Rudy Giuliani Giuliani led efforts for Trump after the 2020 election to challenge results that showed President Joe Biden had won.
Summary Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, personal attorney to U.S. President Donald Trump, speaks in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 7, 2020. Eduardo Munoz | ReutersThe select House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot on Tuesday issued subpoenas to Rudy Giuliani, another former lawyer for ex-President Donald Trump, and two other allies.</description></item><item><title>New York and other north-eastern US states see a rapid fall in Covid cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</guid><description>Despite decreasing positivity rates, hospitals continue to struggle amid a surging patient load and staff shortages
Summary New York City and some north-eastern US states appear to be seeing rapid decreases in their numbers of Covid-19 cases in recent days, raising the possibility that the Omicron wave has now already peaked in some parts of America. “Overall, the prognosis, the forecast, for Covid is much brighter than it had been before.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew stripped of military titles and charities amid sex abuse lawsuit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</guid><description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.
Summary London (CNN) Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>New York will allow non-citizens to vote under controversial law | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</guid><description>A watershed moment for the most populous US city as opponents vow to challenge the law
Summary More than 800,000 non-citizens and “Dreamers” could vote in New York City municipal elections as early as next year, after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to become law on Sunday. Opponents have vowed to challenge the law, which the city council approved a month ago. Unless a judge halts its implementation, New York is the first major US city to grant widespread municipal voting rights to non-citizens.</description></item><item><title>Chinese American man attacked in New York last April dies of injuries | Attack on Yao Pan Ma, 61, drew attention amid rise in anti-Asian hate crimes and is now being treated as homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da41cace422fc77644dff8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da41cace422fc77644dff8/</guid><description>Attack on Yao Pan Ma, 61, drew attention amid rise in anti-Asian hate crimes and is now being treated as homicide
Summary A Chinese American man who was brutally attacked last April while collecting cans in East Harlem has died of his injuries and the case is now deemed a homicide, police in New York said on Saturday. Yao Pan Ma, 61, died on 31 December, police said. Jarrod Powell, 49, of New York City, was previously charged with attempted murder, felony assault and hate crime charges.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</guid><description>A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.
Summary New York (CNN Business) A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics. This pushed the quits rate to 3%, matching the high from September. Workers were most likely to quit their jobs in the hospitality industry, which had by far the highest quits rate at 6.</description></item></channel></rss>