<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>york on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/york/</link><description>Recent content in york on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/york/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rudy Giuliani, three other Trump allies subpoenaed in January 6 riot probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</guid><description>Former New York mayor Rudy Giuliani Giuliani led efforts for Trump after the 2020 election to challenge results that showed President Joe Biden had won.
Summary Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, personal attorney to U.S. President Donald Trump, speaks in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 7, 2020. Eduardo Munoz | ReutersThe select House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot on Tuesday issued subpoenas to Rudy Giuliani, another former lawyer for ex-President Donald Trump, and two other allies.</description></item><item><title>New York and other north-eastern US states see a rapid fall in Covid cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</guid><description>Despite decreasing positivity rates, hospitals continue to struggle amid a surging patient load and staff shortages
Summary New York City and some north-eastern US states appear to be seeing rapid decreases in their numbers of Covid-19 cases in recent days, raising the possibility that the Omicron wave has now already peaked in some parts of America. “Overall, the prognosis, the forecast, for Covid is much brighter than it had been before.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew stripped of military titles and charities amid sex abuse lawsuit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</guid><description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.
Summary London (CNN) Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>New York will allow non-citizens to vote under controversial law | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</guid><description>A watershed moment for the most populous US city as opponents vow to challenge the law
Summary More than 800,000 non-citizens and “Dreamers” could vote in New York City municipal elections as early as next year, after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to become law on Sunday. Opponents have vowed to challenge the law, which the city council approved a month ago. Unless a judge halts its implementation, New York is the first major US city to grant widespread municipal voting rights to non-citizens.</description></item><item><title>Chinese American man attacked in New York last April dies of injuries | Attack on Yao Pan Ma, 61, drew attention amid rise in anti-Asian hate crimes and is now being treated as homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da41cace422fc77644dff8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da41cace422fc77644dff8/</guid><description>Attack on Yao Pan Ma, 61, drew attention amid rise in anti-Asian hate crimes and is now being treated as homicide
Summary A Chinese American man who was brutally attacked last April while collecting cans in East Harlem has died of his injuries and the case is now deemed a homicide, police in New York said on Saturday. Yao Pan Ma, 61, died on 31 December, police said. Jarrod Powell, 49, of New York City, was previously charged with attempted murder, felony assault and hate crime charges.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</guid><description>A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.
Summary New York (CNN Business) A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics. This pushed the quits rate to 3%, matching the high from September. Workers were most likely to quit their jobs in the hospitality industry, which had by far the highest quits rate at 6.</description></item></channel></rss>