<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>york on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/york/</link><description>Recent content in york on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:12:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/york/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smartmatic can pursue election-rigging claims against Fox News, Giuliani</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</guid><description>A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming that Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.S. presidential election to favor Democrat Joe Biden.
Highlights A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew case dismissed by stipulation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62282a3d8f1421567b358855/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62282a3d8f1421567b358855/</guid><description>Prince Andrew case dismissed by stipulation
Highlights Court document states the case has been dismissed, &amp;ldquo;with prejudice&amp;rdquo; and that &amp;ldquo;each party&amp;rdquo; will bear their own costs and fees. The sum of the settlement was not disclosed. Prince Andrew had been set to stand trial for allegedly sexually assaulting dozens of girls in New York and Florida in 2009. He had settled a civil lawsuit for $500,000, which was the basis for the case to have the case dismissed.</description></item><item><title>RT America ceases productions and lays off most of its staff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622162ff61ab54382610fe97/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622162ff61ab54382610fe97/</guid><description>RT America will cease productions and lay off most of its staff, according to a memo from T&amp;amp;R Productions, the production company behind the Russian state-funded network, which CNN obtained.
Highlights RT America will cease productions and lay off most of its staff, according to a memo from T&amp;amp;R Productions. The news would mean an effective end to RT America. The network, one of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s main mouthpieces in the US, was dropped earlier this week by DirecTV.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutors in charge of Trump criminal probe have resigned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216d5492a86165971587e05/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216d5492a86165971587e05/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The two prosecutors in charge of the Manhattan district attorney’s criminal investigation into former President Donald Trump and his business dealings suddenly resigned Wednesday, throwing the future of the probe into question just as pressure was building on Trump on several legal fronts.
Highlights Carey Dunne and Mark Pomerantz, top deputies who had been tasked with running the investigation on a day-to-day basis, have suddenly resigned throwing the future of the probe into question.</description></item><item><title>Walmart drops mask mandate for vaccinated employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</guid><description>Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. State-mandated masks will no longer be required unless required by state or local government. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in pharmacies will be required to
Highlights Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in clinical care settings will be required to keep wearing masks. Several states, from New York to California, have issued their own plans to lift indoor mask mandates.</description></item><item><title>Deputy U.N. chief left near tears by rape accounts in Ethiopia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</guid><description>Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed said on Friday she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women, which she described as &amp;quot;your worst nightmare.”
Highlights Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed says she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women. Mohammed spoke to reporters in New York a day after returning from Ethiopia. She called for accountability for atrocities committed against women and recounted sights of famine in the crisis-torn country.</description></item><item><title>NJ to Lift School Masking Mandate in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</guid><description>New Jersey will lift its school mask mandate in the second week of March, Gov. Phil Murphy told the New York Times.
Highlights New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy announced Monday that the state will end its school mask mandate on March 7. Murphy said school districts can continue their own mandates if they want. Connecticut Gov. Ned Lamont announced that his state mask mandate will end on Feb. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Michael Avenatti Found Guilty of Stealing $300k from Stormy Daniels</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fda44f7e9557be0fb1b9af/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fda44f7e9557be0fb1b9af/</guid><description>Michael Avenatti, a former top critic of ex-President Donald Trump, represented porn star Stormy Daniels in various legal fights connected to Trump.
Highlights A New York jury convicts Michael Avenatti of swindling Stormy Daniels out of nearly $300,000. The guilty verdict on charges of wire fraud and aggravated identity theft at Avenatti&amp;rsquo;s trial in Manhattan federal court is his second criminal conviction in that court. Avenatti represented himself during the trial, where he had claimed he was owed the money he took from Daniels&amp;rsquo; $800,000 advance for her 2018 book, &amp;ldquo;Full Disclosure&amp;rdquo; Daniels: &amp;ldquo;I am ecstatic.</description></item><item><title>Tesla owners complain about 'phantom braking.' Federal safety regulator considers a probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcfb9f8f6ba958a8e37130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 10:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcfb9f8f6ba958a8e37130/</guid><description>Federal safety regulators are mulling a probe after Tesla owners complained that their cars were stopping for no reason.
Highlights Federal safety regulators are mulling a probe after Tesla owners complained that their cars were stopping for no reason. The issue may stem from Tesla&amp;rsquo;s automatic braking feature hitting the brakes when there is no need to do so. An investigation would be the final step before the agency would demand that the company recall the vehicles to fix the feature.</description></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani, three other Trump allies subpoenaed in January 6 riot probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</guid><description>Former New York mayor Rudy Giuliani Giuliani led efforts for Trump after the 2020 election to challenge results that showed President Joe Biden had won.
Summary Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, personal attorney to U.S. President Donald Trump, speaks in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 7, 2020. Eduardo Munoz | ReutersThe select House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot on Tuesday issued subpoenas to Rudy Giuliani, another former lawyer for ex-President Donald Trump, and two other allies.</description></item><item><title>New York and other north-eastern US states see a rapid fall in Covid cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</guid><description>Despite decreasing positivity rates, hospitals continue to struggle amid a surging patient load and staff shortages
Summary New York City and some north-eastern US states appear to be seeing rapid decreases in their numbers of Covid-19 cases in recent days, raising the possibility that the Omicron wave has now already peaked in some parts of America. “Overall, the prognosis, the forecast, for Covid is much brighter than it had been before.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew stripped of military titles and charities amid sex abuse lawsuit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</guid><description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.
Summary London (CNN) Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>New York will allow non-citizens to vote under controversial law | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</guid><description>A watershed moment for the most populous US city as opponents vow to challenge the law
Summary More than 800,000 non-citizens and “Dreamers” could vote in New York City municipal elections as early as next year, after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to become law on Sunday. Opponents have vowed to challenge the law, which the city council approved a month ago. Unless a judge halts its implementation, New York is the first major US city to grant widespread municipal voting rights to non-citizens.</description></item><item><title>Chinese American man attacked in New York last April dies of injuries | Attack on Yao Pan Ma, 61, drew attention amid rise in anti-Asian hate crimes and is now being treated as homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da41cace422fc77644dff8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da41cace422fc77644dff8/</guid><description>Attack on Yao Pan Ma, 61, drew attention amid rise in anti-Asian hate crimes and is now being treated as homicide
Summary A Chinese American man who was brutally attacked last April while collecting cans in East Harlem has died of his injuries and the case is now deemed a homicide, police in New York said on Saturday. Yao Pan Ma, 61, died on 31 December, police said. Jarrod Powell, 49, of New York City, was previously charged with attempted murder, felony assault and hate crime charges.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</guid><description>A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.
Summary New York (CNN Business) A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics. This pushed the quits rate to 3%, matching the high from September. Workers were most likely to quit their jobs in the hospitality industry, which had by far the highest quits rate at 6.</description></item></channel></rss>