<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>turkey on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/turkey/</link><description>Recent content in turkey on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 12:15:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/turkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Turkey has decided to give free Bayraktar TB2 to Ukraine by supporting the donation campaign initiated by Lithuania for Ukraine. With the money collected by Lithuania, ammunition will be purchased.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299fb38d493d6e475d70787/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 12:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299fb38d493d6e475d70787/</guid><description>Turkey has gifted a Bayraktar combat drone to Lithuania to be handed over to Ukraine, journalist and public figure Andri&amp;hellip;
Highlights Turkey and Baykar manufacturer have gifted a state-of-the-art Bayraktar TB2 combat drone to Lithuania. Last week, ordinary Lithuanians donated over 5 million euros in a fundraising campaign to purchase the drone for Ukraine. The drone will be ready within three weeks, and the Lithuanian Air Force will fly to pick it up and hand it over to Ukraine as soon as possible, Andrius Tapinas said.</description></item><item><title>Erdogan: Turkey's Syria operation could happen 'suddenly'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62954ed4d26b257248326f91/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 23:10:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62954ed4d26b257248326f91/</guid><description>ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey’s president told journalists that Ankara remains committed to rooting out a Syrian Kurdish militia from northern Syria. “Like I always say, we’ll come down on them suddenly one night.
Highlights Turkey&amp;rsquo;s President Recep Tayyip Erdogan spoke at a Turkish Technology and Aviation festival, held abroad for the first time, in Baku, Azerbaijan, Saturday, May 28, 2022. Without giving a specific timeline, Erdogan said that Turkey would launch a cross-border operation against the Syrian Kurdish People’s Protection Units, or YPG, which it considers a terrorist group linked to an outlawed Kurdish group that has led an insurgency against Turkey since 1984.</description></item></channel></rss>