<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arredondo on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arredondo/</link><description>Recent content in arredondo on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 16:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arredondo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde school district police chief sworn in as city council member a week after mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6297910ff357bcb272f07a50/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 16:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6297910ff357bcb272f07a50/</guid><description>Pete Arredondo, the Uvalde school district police chief who was the incident commander during the Robb Elementary school shooting, was sworn in as a city council member on Tuesday.
Highlights Pete Arredondo was the incident commander during the Robb Elementary school shooting. He was identified last week by the Texas Department of Public Safety as the person who decided not to breach the classroom where the shooter had holed up and waited for reinforcements.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde police chief who delayed officer response to shooting to join City Council</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291d9810cc9a70796c069ee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291d9810cc9a70796c069ee/</guid><description>The police chief who reportedly made the call not to immediately send officers into Robb Elementary School to confront a gunman was elected to Uvalde&amp;rsquo;s City Cou
Highlights Peter Arredondo, the chief of police for the Uvalde Consolidated Independent School District, stopped at least 19 officers from breaking into the school as the gunman opened fire for at least an hour. He believed that the shooter had barricaded himself and that the children were not under an active threat, Texas Department of Public Safety director Steven McCraw said Friday.</description></item></channel></rss>