<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thousands on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/thousands/</link><description>Recent content in thousands on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 17:18:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/thousands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thousands of detained Uyghurs pictured in leaked Xinjiang police files</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d1330dde770f697c7c2f5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 17:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d1330dde770f697c7c2f5/</guid><description>Documents detailing shoot-to-kill policy for people who try to escape published as UN human rights chief visits region
Highlights Documents detailing shoot-to-kill policy for people who try to escape have been published. Chinese authorities are accused of detaining more than 1 million Uyghurs and other Muslim minorities in Xinjiang. Michelle Bachelet is expected to visit the Xinjiang cities of Ürümümqi and Kashgar on Tuesday and Wednesday as part of a six-day trip to the region.</description></item><item><title>2 dead, 3 hurt in shooting at Houston flea market</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281a2f766463cc0f00016d8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 01:04:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281a2f766463cc0f00016d8/</guid><description>Two people are dead and three others are hurt in a shooting at a Houston flea market on Sunday, the Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said.
Highlights Thousands of people were at the busy flea market in Houston, Texas. Two people died on scene and three men were hospitalized in critical condition, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said. The shooting appeared to stem from an altercation between five men, the Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said.</description></item><item><title>Thousands of pro-Russia Serbs march in Belgrade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224891bf52dde79888106e9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 10:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224891bf52dde79888106e9/</guid><description>Flags and flares are paraded through the Serbian capital, as marchers show support for Moscow.
Highlights Up to 4,000 people take part in pro-Russia demonstration in Serbian capital. It was a show of support for Moscow after its invasion of Ukraine. Serbia has religious, ethnic and political ties with Russia that have existed for centuries. The Serbian capital is Serbia&amp;rsquo;s capital of Beljevevevlija, which borders Russia and Ukraine, has long been friendly with Russia.</description></item></channel></rss>