<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>states on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/states/</link><description>Recent content in states on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 21:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/states/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York governor signs bill criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4e36fe32d7d605f347c3f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4e36fe32d7d605f347c3f/</guid><description>New York&amp;rsquo;s governor signed legislation Wednesday criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards, according to a news release from her office.
Summary (CNN) New York&amp;rsquo;s governor signed legislation Wednesday criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards, according to a news release from her office. The law comes amid a fresh tightening of rules requiring proof of vaccination in cities across the United States &amp;ndash; including New York &amp;ndash; as the Omicron coronavirus variant spreads rapidly ahead of the Christmas holiday.</description></item><item><title>Omicron hits all 50 states less than a month after entering U.S.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</guid><description>With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was
Summary With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was first detected in the U.S., according to an NBC News tally. A day later, multiple states and territories set records for seven-day averages, including New York, Maine, Washington, D.</description></item></channel></rss>