<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>eu on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/eu/</link><description>Recent content in eu on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:11:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukrainian president signs formal request to join EU</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d3a73cbe9d491678a4a05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d3a73cbe9d491678a4a05/</guid><description>European Union leaders may discuss the possibility of Ukrainian membership at an informal summit in March, a senior EU official said on Monday, adding the issue was important for Ukraine in discussions with Russia on ending the conflict. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said on Monday that he had signed an official request…
Highlights EU leaders may discuss possibility of Ukrainian membership at an informal summit in March, a senior EU official said on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Spain dispatches warship to the Black Sea to boost Ukraine’s defences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9db750b7fa8a5cd2e4868/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9db750b7fa8a5cd2e4868/</guid><description>TVP World/Telewizja Polska S. A.
Summary Amidst growing tension and Russia’s ever-more realistic ambitions to invade Ukraine, Spain has sent off its warship to the Black Sea and said that it would dispatch even more to reinforce other EU states’ units, should the NATO-Russia talks turn out a fiasco and Russian aggression a reality. The centre-left cabinet of Spanish PM Pedro Sanchez confirmed that the warship had been sent off. According to “El Mundo” daily, Mr Albares was asked if Spain would send its troops to Ukraine in the event of Russia’s invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>