<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>month on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/month/</link><description>Recent content in month on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 05:26:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/month/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pride, Black History Month book displays among those no longer allowed at Lafayette public libraries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629849de68a5e656995eed65/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 05:26:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629849de68a5e656995eed65/</guid><description>Book displays highlighting controversial topics or specific segments of the population such as Pride Month, Black History Month, Women&amp;rsquo;s History Month, Native American history and Cajun heritage are no longer
Highlights Book displays highlighting controversial topics or specific segments of the population no longer exist. Pride Month, Black History Month, Women&amp;rsquo;s History Month and Native American history and Cajun heritage are no longer. Book displays no longer feature controversial topics such as Native American heritage and.</description></item><item><title>March breaks record for most tornados in a single month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62537c727be68abbd107b567/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62537c727be68abbd107b567/</guid><description>It was a chaotic meteorological transition into spring as March saw the highest number of tornadoes in a single month in U.S. history.
Highlights At least 218 tornadoes occurred in March, with many of the tornadoes happening toward the end of the month. More tornadoes and severe weather are expected in the coming days. More severe weather that could conjure up more tornadoes is expected over the next several days. On Sunday and Monday, tornadoes could pop up in eastern Oklahoma, northeast Texas, southern Missouri and much of Arkansas.</description></item><item><title>U.S. outbreaks of Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza doubled during past month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62407f08f579d1c56950aaba/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 15:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62407f08f579d1c56950aaba/</guid><description>Millions of birds in at least 17 states are being rapidly killed in a determined attempt to bring a dangerous strain of Avian flu under control. And Avian
Highlights Avian flu outbreaks in the United States during 2022 have already surpassed the minor detections experienced in 2016 and 2017. Millions of birds in at least 17 states are being rapidly killed in a determined attempt to bring a dangerous strain of Avian Flu under control.</description></item></channel></rss>