<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>graduation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/graduation/</link><description>Recent content in graduation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 23:09:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/graduation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1 shot dead and multiple wounded after shooting at Graduation party in Thomaston - Fox3 Now</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ab8e160ed0e940f900ab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 23:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ab8e160ed0e940f900ab/</guid><description>ONE person is dead and two more are wounded after a gunman opened fire at a graduation party attended by 200 people in Thomaston Atlanta.
Highlights At least 200 people, mostly teens, were in the Park Lane Event Center when the shooting happened. Two people with serious injuries were taken by helicopter to a hospital in Macon, Georgia. Police have not made any arrests, but they think the suspects are not from the Thomaston area because only one of the victims lived there.</description></item><item><title>3 high school graduations across the U.S. end with gunfire in less than 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629199529bcc774208de3f22/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 03:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629199529bcc774208de3f22/</guid><description>Three high school graduation ceremonies ended with shots fired in separate incidents in Louisiana, Michigan and Tennessee within the span of 24 hours this week.
Highlights Three high school graduation ceremonies ended with shots fired in separate incidents in Louisiana, Michigan and Tennessee within the span of 24 hours this week. At least one person was killed and seven others injured in collective shootings that resulted in the arrest of a 17-year-old gunman in Tennessee.</description></item><item><title>3 Air Force cadets who refused Covid vaccine won’t be commissioned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bc15f2c70ed12b11701dd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bc15f2c70ed12b11701dd/</guid><description>Three cadets at the U.S. Air Force Academy who have refused the Covid-19 vaccine will not be commissioned as military officers, the academy said Saturday.
Highlights The Air Force is the only military academy, so far, where cadets are not being commissioned due to vaccine refusal. The Naval Academy in Annapolis, Maryland, said Saturday that none of the Navy or Marine Corps seniors there are being prevented from commissioning. A fourth cadet who had refused the vaccine until about a week ago, decided to be vaccinated and will graduate and become an Air Force officer.</description></item></channel></rss>