<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>seven on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/seven/</link><description>Recent content in seven on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 08:16:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/seven/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gas theft ring in Florida stole at least $60K of fuel from stations to resell at half price, sheriff says.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bfad785affa04abbc68ee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 08:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bfad785affa04abbc68ee/</guid><description>Six men accused of stealing thousands of dollars of gasoline from Florida gas stations have been arrested, officials said Monday.
Highlights Six men are accused of stealing thousands of dollars of gasoline from Florida gas stations. A seventh man, Willian Penate-Arencibia, who is alleged to be their ringleader, is still at large. The suspects were selling the gas for half the price to truck drivers, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office alleged. The six men are charged with racketeering, conspiracy to commit racketeering and grand theft, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>ThedaCare loses court fight to keep health care staff who resigned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef59c276143456b5f4314e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef59c276143456b5f4314e/</guid><description>A hospital in northeastern Wisconsin has lost a court battle to keep health care staff who want to work elsewhere.
Summary A hospital in northeastern Wisconsin has lost a court battle to keep health care staff who want to work elsewhere. The civil court case between ThedaCare and Ascension Wisconsin comes at a time when health professionals are in great demand across the U.S. Just days before, seven former employees of ThedaCare were to start new jobs at Ascension&amp;rsquo;s St.</description></item></channel></rss>