<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>card on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/card/</link><description>Recent content in card on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 12:14:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/card/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vets call for end to use of flat-faced dogs on greeting cards. Concerns frequent images of ‘cute’ breeds such as pugs maintains their popularity despite animal cruelty warnings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fe69fc6e634089ac0412a4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 12:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fe69fc6e634089ac0412a4/</guid><description>Concerns frequent images of ‘cute’ breeds such as pugs maintains their popularity despite animal cruelty warnings
Highlights British Veterinary Association has written to the Greeting Card Association and card retailers. The BVA wants to stop using images of pugs and other flat-faced dogs and cats on cards. The campaign was first made four years ago, but there has been no real change on the ground. More than half of the brachycephalic dogs and a quarter of the cats that vets see need treatment for health issues related to how they look, the BVA said.</description></item><item><title>Amid rising prices, American families fall deeper in debt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</guid><description>Between inflation and ongoing supply chain issues, prices are rising and it&amp;rsquo;s eating away at the average family budget.
Summary Higher prices are already taking a toll. As consumers pay more for everything from groceries to gasoline, household income is failing to keep pace with a higher overall cost of living, according to recent reports. Over the past two years, median income fell 3% while the cost of living rose nearly 7%, due, in part, to rising housing and medical costs.</description></item></channel></rss>