<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>community on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/community/</link><description>Recent content in community on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:14:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former Meta employee caught in paedophile sting video after allegedly sending sexual messages to 13 year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</guid><description>Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’
Highlights Alleged paedophile caught in anti-paedophile sting by &amp;lsquo;Predator Catchers Indianapolis&amp;rsquo; He allegedly sent sexually explicit messages to someone he believed to be a 13-year-old. The man was the ‘manager of community development’ at Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta. A Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’ The man is no longer employed with the company and is ‘actively investigating’ the allegations.</description></item><item><title>13-Year-Old Student Dies of Fentanyl-Related Overdose at Hartford School: PD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</guid><description>A 13-year-old student at The Sport and Medical Sciences Academy in Hartford who was in grave condition because of an overdose has now died, according to police&amp;hellip;.
Summary The Hartford Public Schools superintendent has released a statement. &amp;ldquo;I extend my heart and offer my deepest condolences to the student’s family, friends, and loved ones for their loss. I ask that everyone keep the family, friends, and the entire school community at SMSA in their thoughts and prayers,&amp;rdquo; she said in part.</description></item><item><title>US hospitals struggle to match Walmart pay as staff flees omicron</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da881a85181d78d62d09f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da881a85181d78d62d09f0/</guid><description>Breaking news and updates from around the world.
Summary Some relief arrived in uniform in December: The state sent a couple of medics and other support staff from the National Guard. They mostly work in the emergency department, where every morning patients wait for hospital beds to open. Troy Bruntz runs Community Hospital, a 25-bed critical access facility in McCook, Nebraska. “That’s the only way we get people to come to work.</description></item></channel></rss>