<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>community on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/community/</link><description>Recent content in community on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 07:14:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>83-year-old woman attacked, killed by 3 dogs in northwest Calgary | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ef9a9c20a61ee2243f319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 07:14:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ef9a9c20a61ee2243f319/</guid><description>Police said the woman was found in the 1500 block of 21 Avenue N.W. at about 2 p.m., Sunday.
Highlights Calgary Police Service said the woman was found in the 1500 block of 21 Avenue N.W. at about 2 p.m. Sunday. Police said it’s believed she was gardening in a back alley when the dogs escaped from a neighbouring property and attacked her. The woman was taken to hospital in life-threatening condition and she later died from her injuries.</description></item><item><title>Police search for gunman who shot three Korean women at Texas hair salon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e4fa5b9f877259b920835/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 12:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e4fa5b9f877259b920835/</guid><description>A search is underway for a suspect who opened fire at a Dallas hair salon, and injured three Korean women inside before fleeing Wednesday, police say.
Highlights Dallas police are searching for a suspect who opened fire at a Dallas hair salon, and injured three Korean women inside before fleeing. The suspect, described as a Black male dressed in all black, walked into the business and started shooting, striking the three women, police say.</description></item><item><title>Disney employees are staging walkouts over company's response to the 'Don't Say Gay' bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62335f0ebe6e7928e7dd7849/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62335f0ebe6e7928e7dd7849/</guid><description>Last week, Disney and its CEO Bob Chapek bungled their response to Florida&amp;rsquo;s controversial bill dubbed &amp;quot;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay.&amp;quot; Now, some of the company&amp;rsquo;s employees are staging a walkout.
Highlights A Twitter account, &amp;ldquo;@DisneyWalkout,&amp;rdquo; and an associated website, &amp;ldquo;WhereIsChapek.com,&amp;rdquo; have organized a series of 15-minute daily walkouts. The action will culminate with a full-day walkout on March 22. It&amp;rsquo;s unknown how many employees are taking part, but Disney&amp;rsquo;s LGBTQ+ employee resource groups are not involved, according to a source.</description></item><item><title>Former Meta employee caught in paedophile sting video after allegedly sending sexual messages to 13 year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211b1e2c5c31e13a182bd2c/</guid><description>Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’
Highlights Alleged paedophile caught in anti-paedophile sting by &amp;lsquo;Predator Catchers Indianapolis&amp;rsquo; He allegedly sent sexually explicit messages to someone he believed to be a 13-year-old. The man was the ‘manager of community development’ at Facebook and Instagram parent company Meta. A Facebook spokesperson says ‘the seriousness of these allegations cannot be overstated’ The man is no longer employed with the company and is ‘actively investigating’ the allegations.</description></item><item><title>13-Year-Old Student Dies of Fentanyl-Related Overdose at Hartford School: PD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4dbe917c98352282a0929/</guid><description>A 13-year-old student at The Sport and Medical Sciences Academy in Hartford who was in grave condition because of an overdose has now died, according to police&amp;hellip;.
Summary The Hartford Public Schools superintendent has released a statement. &amp;ldquo;I extend my heart and offer my deepest condolences to the student’s family, friends, and loved ones for their loss. I ask that everyone keep the family, friends, and the entire school community at SMSA in their thoughts and prayers,&amp;rdquo; she said in part.</description></item><item><title>US hospitals struggle to match Walmart pay as staff flees omicron</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da881a85181d78d62d09f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da881a85181d78d62d09f0/</guid><description>Breaking news and updates from around the world.
Summary Some relief arrived in uniform in December: The state sent a couple of medics and other support staff from the National Guard. They mostly work in the emergency department, where every morning patients wait for hospital beds to open. Troy Bruntz runs Community Hospital, a 25-bed critical access facility in McCook, Nebraska. “That’s the only way we get people to come to work.</description></item></channel></rss>