<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gunman on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gunman/</link><description>Recent content in gunman on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 09:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gunman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Good night': Uvalde school shooting survivors describe gunman's words before opening fire</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291e692abc53a8be0a4e245/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 09:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291e692abc53a8be0a4e245/</guid><description>Survivors of the Robb Elementary School shooting are recounting the gunman&amp;rsquo;s eerie final words of &amp;quot;Good night&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;You&amp;rsquo;re all gonna die&amp;quot; before opening fire.
Highlights 11-year-old Miah Cerrillo, 11, said the gunman looked at one of her teachers in the eye and said, “Good night” before shooting her. Samuel Salinas, 10, was a student in teacher Irma Garcia’s class on Tuesday when the shooting unfolded. Samuel said he survived by playing dead after he got hit in the leg with shrapnel that hit a chair between him and the shooter.</description></item><item><title>Federal agents entered Uvalde school to kill gunman despite local police initially asking them to wait</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291a14b959660ffebec7e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291a14b959660ffebec7e82/</guid><description>Federal agents who went to Robb Elementary in Uvalde, Tex., on Tuesday to confront a gunman were told by local police to wait, but chose to enter the school.
Highlights Federal agents who went to Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, on Tuesday to confront a gunman were told by local police to wait and not enter the school. After about half an hour, the federal agents opted of their own volition to lead the “stack” of officers inside the school and take down the shooter, two senior federal law enforcement officials say.</description></item><item><title>Police face questions over response to Uvalde school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628feca253e1a461385da575/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 21:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628feca253e1a461385da575/</guid><description>A Texas law enforcement official now says the 18-year-old gunman who slaughtered 21 people, including 19 children, at an elementary school entered the building &amp;quot;unobstructed&amp;quot; through a door that was apparently unlocked.
Highlights The gunman entered the school &amp;ldquo;unobstructed,&amp;rdquo; a law enforcement official says. The gunman was apparently inside the building for at least three-quarters of an hour before U.S. Border Patrol agents stormed a classroom and killed him. The motive for the Texas school shooting is still under investigation.</description></item><item><title>Gunman in California church attack subdued by parishioners</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282ccb264f9e59da030c066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 22:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282ccb264f9e59da030c066/</guid><description>LAGUNA WOODS, Calif. (AP) — A gunman in a deadly attack at a Southern California church was a Chinese immigrant motivated by hate for Taiwanese people, authorities said. The shooter killed Dr.
Highlights Suspect identified as David Chou, 68, of Las Vegas. Shooter killed Dr. John Cheng, 52, and wounded five others during a lunch held by Irvine Taiwanese Presbyterian Church, which worships at Geneva Presbyterian Church in Laguna Woods, California.</description></item></channel></rss>