<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>uvalde on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uvalde/</link><description>Recent content in uvalde on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 07:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uvalde/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde school district police chief declines to answer CNN questions in first public comments in a week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629862835ceef11ad1cd8df8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 07:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629862835ceef11ad1cd8df8/</guid><description>Pedro &amp;quot;Pete&amp;quot; Arredondo, the embattled Uvalde school police chief who led the flawed law enforcement response to last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting and has remained out of the public eye since, spoke exclusively to CNN on Wednesday and declined to answer substantive questions about the massacre.
Highlights Pedro &amp;ldquo;Pete&amp;rdquo; Arredondo spoke exclusively to CNN about the school shooting last week. He declined to answer substantive questions about the massacre. 19 children and two teachers were killed in the shooting at Robb Elementary in Uvalde, Texas, last Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Teacher Closed Propped-Open Door Before Uvalde School Shooting: Police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296dc96ec3c53a05746ae29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296dc96ec3c53a05746ae29/</guid><description>New details are emerging about the door the Uvalde gunman used to gain access to the elementary school.
Highlights A Texas elementary school teacher propped the door open with a rock, police say. She then closed the door shut when she realized there was a shooter on campus, an official says. Investigators are still trying to interview the police chief who was the commander of the school shooting scene. 19 students and two teachers were killed in a classroom in Uvalde, Texas, on May 24.</description></item><item><title>'Good night': Uvalde school shooting survivors describe gunman's words before opening fire</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291e692abc53a8be0a4e245/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 09:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291e692abc53a8be0a4e245/</guid><description>Survivors of the Robb Elementary School shooting are recounting the gunman&amp;rsquo;s eerie final words of &amp;quot;Good night&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;You&amp;rsquo;re all gonna die&amp;quot; before opening fire.
Highlights 11-year-old Miah Cerrillo, 11, said the gunman looked at one of her teachers in the eye and said, “Good night” before shooting her. Samuel Salinas, 10, was a student in teacher Irma Garcia’s class on Tuesday when the shooting unfolded. Samuel said he survived by playing dead after he got hit in the leg with shrapnel that hit a chair between him and the shooter.</description></item><item><title>'Please send the police now': Uvalde student called 911 multiple times during shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291aeaa021c7a51c7009ce4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 05:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291aeaa021c7a51c7009ce4/</guid><description>At least two children called 911, one of whom begged for help, during Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s mass shooting at a Uvalde, Texas, elementary school.
Highlights One girl called 911 more than five times, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Steven C. McCraw said. He did not name the children but said both of them survived the attack at Robb Elementary School. 19 students and two teachers were killed in the shooting at a Uvalde, Texas, elementary school.</description></item><item><title>Shooter entered school through propped open door, had over 1,600 rounds of ammunition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62916f8eda334519cf99d403/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62916f8eda334519cf99d403/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — Nearly 20 officers stood in a hallway outside of the classrooms during this week&amp;rsquo;s attack on a Texas elementary school for more than 45 minutes before agents used a master key to open a door and confront a gunman, authorities said Friday. Caption: News Conference: Texas Department of Public Safety Director Steven McCraw.
Highlights Nearly 20 officers stood in hallway outside of classrooms during attack on Texas elementary school.</description></item></channel></rss>