<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>start on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/start/</link><description>Recent content in start on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Army to immediately start discharging vaccine refusers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb0fcd2956e6f3d6edda78/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb0fcd2956e6f3d6edda78/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Army said Wednesday it will immediately begin discharging soldiers who have refused to get the mandatory COVID-19 vaccine , putting more than 3,300 service members at risk of being thrown out soon.
Highlights The Army says it will immediately begin discharging soldiers who have refused to get the mandatory COVID-19 vaccine. The Marine Corps, Air Force and Navy have already discharged active-duty troops or entry-level personnel at boot camps for refusing the shots.</description></item><item><title>BBC licence fee to be abolished in 2027 and funding frozen | BBC</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4a0dda24de08bb5913fcb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 23:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4a0dda24de08bb5913fcb/</guid><description>Government announcement will force broadcaster to make deep cuts to its programme budgets
Summary The BBC will have to make deep cuts to its programme budgets after the government said the broadcaster’s funding would be frozen for the next two years, with the licence fee abolished completely in 2027. Dorries said: “This licence fee announcement will be the last. The BBC will have to negotiate with the government over an entirely new funding model when the final licence fee funding deal expires in 2027 – with potential options including a subscription service, part-privatisation, or direct government funding.</description></item><item><title>Russia hopes to start manufacturing Kalashnikov rifles in Venezuela soon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d19401a07e2b78e128123a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 12:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d19401a07e2b78e128123a/</guid><description>Russian officials Wednesday insisted the launch of the plant to manufacture Kalashnikov rifles in Venezuela had to be postponed during 2021 as a consequence of sanctions imposed by the United States, but the final works have been gaining pace lately thanks to cooperation from local authorities.
Summary Russia hopes to start manufacturing Kalashnikov rifles in Venezuela soon29th Wednesday, December 2021 - 20:59 UTC Full articleSanctions, corruption and COVID-19 were behind the plant&amp;rsquo;s successive delaysRussian officials Wednesday insisted the launch of the plant to manufacture Kalashnikov rifles in Venezuela had to be postponed during 2021 as a consequence of sanctions imposed by the United States, but the final works have been gaining pace lately thanks to cooperation from local authorities.</description></item></channel></rss>