<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wealth on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wealth/</link><description>Recent content in wealth on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 14:13:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wealth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Soaring food prices push more Cargill family members on to world’s richest 500 list | The super-rich</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d71eb1c72ce2e5e390db9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 14:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d71eb1c72ce2e5e390db9/</guid><description>Fortunes of siblings James Cargill, Austen Cargill and Marianne Liebmann up a fifth this year
Highlights Siblings James Cargill, Austen and Marianne Liebmann join ranks of the world’s 500 richest people. They have an estimated $5.4bn (£4.1bn) fortune – up a fifth so far this year. The UN said global food prices had soared to a record high because of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The war has disrupted Black Sea exports of crucial commodities from a region that had been producing more than a quarter of world&amp;rsquo;s wheat exports.</description></item><item><title>Hidden wealth of one of Putin’s 'inner circle' revealed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62551942a34159527f725a22/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 06:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62551942a34159527f725a22/</guid><description>Leaked documents show how sanctioned oligarch Suleiman Kerimov used shell companies to move $700m.
Highlights ICIJ and global partners to shed light on covert financial transactions linked to oligarchs and others close to the Kremlin. Mr Kerimov is among more than 4,000 Russians whose names appear in data obtained by the ICIJ. The data is part of Pandora Papers Russia - a new investigation by ICIJ of Russia&amp;rsquo;s oligarchs. ICIJ: &amp;lsquo;Pandora Papers Russia&amp;rsquo; - an ICIJ investigation into covert transactions by oligarchs linked to Russia&amp;rsquo;s financial elite in wake of Ukraine invasion.</description></item><item><title>Wealth of world's 10 richest men doubled in pandemic, Oxfam says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4ea07d4a78acdb7f01bd0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4ea07d4a78acdb7f01bd0/</guid><description>Covid-19 has made the rich richer while poverty has increased, the charity Oxfam says.
Summary &amp;ldquo;This year, what&amp;rsquo;s happening is off the scale,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s been a new billionaire created almost every day during this pandemic, meanwhile 99% of the world&amp;rsquo;s population are worse off because of lockdowns, lower international trade, less international tourism, and as a result of that, 160 million more people have been pushed into poverty.&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>