<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reported on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reported/</link><description>Recent content in reported on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:20:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reported/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oil giant Shell reports highest quarterly profit since 2008 on soaring commodity prices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273f92a6cb2c87cb97c8e54/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:20:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273f92a6cb2c87cb97c8e54/</guid><description>Shell&amp;rsquo;s bumper earnings echo profits seen across the oil and gas industry, even as many energy majors incur costly write-downs from exiting Russia.
Highlights Shell posted adjusted earnings of $9.1 billion for the three months through to the end of March. That compared with $3.2 billion over the same period a year earlier and $6.4 billion for fourth quarter of 2021. Shell&amp;rsquo;s results echo bumper profits seen across the oil and gas industry, even as many energy majors incur costly write-downs from exiting Russia.</description></item><item><title>Anti-Abortion Protester Free-Climbed Up Salesforce Tower This Morning</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272522d81b6a43a271fe464/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 10:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272522d81b6a43a271fe464/</guid><description>A man climbs San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s tallest tower to raise awareness about an anti-abortion doctor. The man has not yet reached the top of the tower. He is believed to be a &amp;quot;Pro-life&amp;quot; doctor.
Highlights A free-solo type climber decided to scale the outside of Salesforce Tower Tuesday morning. The tower is 1,070 feet tall, and with no windows it would seem this man needs to get to the top just in order to get there.</description></item><item><title>A mother says her son was sold in a mock slave auction. School district votes unanimously on action plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</guid><description>A North Carolina school board voted unanimously Monday to approve an action plan after reported racial bullying in the district, including a student-organized mock auction of Black students.
Highlights A group of parents and community members had called on the Chatham County School District to make changes after several reported racial bullying instances at schools in the district. Ashley Palmer said her Black son told her that some of his classmates were sold in a mock slave auction at J.</description></item><item><title>Death toll nears 6 million as pandemic enters its 3rd year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62252383ea2f3c96d25faf4b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 21:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62252383ea2f3c96d25faf4b/</guid><description>BANGKOK (AP) — The official global death toll from COVID-19 is on the verge of eclipsing 6 million — underscoring that the pandemic, now entering its third year, is far from over. The milestone is the latest tragic reminder of the unrelenting nature of the pandemic even as people are shedding masks, travel is resuming and businesses are reopening around the globe.
Highlights The official global death toll from COVID-19 is on the verge of eclipsing 6 million.</description></item><item><title>A Mexican woman reported a sexual assault in Qatar. She faces jail, 100 lashes.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62174c21f36484aa4d75ad52/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62174c21f36484aa4d75ad52/</guid><description>Mexican Paola Schietekat said she was sexually assaulted in Qatar where she worked but instead could face punishment if she goes back to the country she left.
Highlights Paola Schietekat was working in Qatar for the Supreme Committee for Delivery and Legacy. In June, she said she was assaulted in a violent incident by an acquaintance and fellow Latino who also worked in Qatar. The Mexican economist managed to leave Qatar with the help of Human Rights Watch and the World Cup body where she worked.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin value tumbles almost 50% since record November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef137208dd6c94540b2f7f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef137208dd6c94540b2f7f/</guid><description>Bitcoin has lost almost half its value since its November high, with cryptocurrency prices continuing to plunge as major economies look to curb their growing popularity.
Summary And it&amp;rsquo;s not just Bitcoin, as cryptocurrencies in general have had a dismal start to the year. Bitcoin has fallen over 8% in the last 24 hours, and was trading at $35,479 as of 9:30 am ET, according to CoinDesk . On Thursday, Reuters reported that Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank has Governmentsare cracking down as well.</description></item><item><title>Covid-19: French MPs get death threats over support for vaccine pass that would bar the unvaccinated from much of public life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</guid><description>They report the threats as they consider tougher restrictions on unvaccinated people in France.
Summary In an interview with BFM TV, she said she had reported the threats to the police and would not be deterred from supporting the vaccine pass. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>