<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reported on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reported/</link><description>Recent content in reported on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 21:12:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reported/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Death toll nears 6 million as pandemic enters its 3rd year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62252383ea2f3c96d25faf4b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 21:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62252383ea2f3c96d25faf4b/</guid><description>BANGKOK (AP) — The official global death toll from COVID-19 is on the verge of eclipsing 6 million — underscoring that the pandemic, now entering its third year, is far from over. The milestone is the latest tragic reminder of the unrelenting nature of the pandemic even as people are shedding masks, travel is resuming and businesses are reopening around the globe.
Highlights The official global death toll from COVID-19 is on the verge of eclipsing 6 million.</description></item><item><title>A Mexican woman reported a sexual assault in Qatar. She faces jail, 100 lashes.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62174c21f36484aa4d75ad52/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62174c21f36484aa4d75ad52/</guid><description>Mexican Paola Schietekat said she was sexually assaulted in Qatar where she worked but instead could face punishment if she goes back to the country she left.
Highlights Paola Schietekat was working in Qatar for the Supreme Committee for Delivery and Legacy. In June, she said she was assaulted in a violent incident by an acquaintance and fellow Latino who also worked in Qatar. The Mexican economist managed to leave Qatar with the help of Human Rights Watch and the World Cup body where she worked.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin value tumbles almost 50% since record November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef137208dd6c94540b2f7f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef137208dd6c94540b2f7f/</guid><description>Bitcoin has lost almost half its value since its November high, with cryptocurrency prices continuing to plunge as major economies look to curb their growing popularity.
Summary And it&amp;rsquo;s not just Bitcoin, as cryptocurrencies in general have had a dismal start to the year. Bitcoin has fallen over 8% in the last 24 hours, and was trading at $35,479 as of 9:30 am ET, according to CoinDesk . On Thursday, Reuters reported that Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank has Governmentsare cracking down as well.</description></item><item><title>Covid-19: French MPs get death threats over support for vaccine pass that would bar the unvaccinated from much of public life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</guid><description>They report the threats as they consider tougher restrictions on unvaccinated people in France.
Summary In an interview with BFM TV, she said she had reported the threats to the police and would not be deterred from supporting the vaccine pass. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>