<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>previous on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/previous/</link><description>Recent content in previous on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 10:14:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/previous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Italy Reports 70,520 Coronavirus Cases Today, 143 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626522ee29182268e6847435/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 10:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626522ee29182268e6847435/</guid><description>Italy reported 70,520 COVID-19 related cases on Saturday, against 73,212 the day before, the health ministry said, while the daily number of deaths fell to 143 from 202.
Highlights Italy reported 70,520 COVID-19 related cases on Saturday, against 73,212 the day before. The daily number of deaths fell to 143 from 202, Italy has registered 162,609 deaths linked to the outbreak. The country has reported 16.1 million cases to date, with 43 new admissions to intensive care units, decreasing from 46 on Friday.</description></item><item><title>‘No need’: Taliban dissolves Afghanistan election commission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8c9e4819225943d99fc8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8c9e4819225943d99fc8b/</guid><description>Taliban government scraps the panel that supervised polls during the previous Western-backed administration.
Summary Taliban government scraps the panel that supervised polls during the previous Western-backed administration. The Taliban has dissolved Afghanistan’s election commission, a panel that supervised polls during the previous Western-backed administration, says a spokesman for the government. “There is no need for these commissions to exist and operate,” spokesman Bilal Karimi said on Saturday, referring to the Independent Election Commission (IEC) and the Independent Electoral Complaints Commission.</description></item></channel></rss>