<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prices on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prices/</link><description>Recent content in prices on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amid rising prices, American families fall deeper in debt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</guid><description>Between inflation and ongoing supply chain issues, prices are rising and it&amp;rsquo;s eating away at the average family budget.
Summary Higher prices are already taking a toll. As consumers pay more for everything from groceries to gasoline, household income is failing to keep pace with a higher overall cost of living, according to recent reports. Over the past two years, median income fell 3% while the cost of living rose nearly 7%, due, in part, to rising housing and medical costs.</description></item><item><title>‘There is no money left’: Covid crisis leaves Sri Lanka on brink of bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</guid><description>Half a million people have sunk into poverty since the pandemic struck, with rising costs forcing many to cut back on food
Summary Sri Lanka is facing a deepening financial and humanitarian crisis with fears it could go bankrupt in 2022 as inflation rises to record levels, food prices rocket and its coffers run dry. One of the most pressing problems for Sri Lanka is its huge foreign debt burden.</description></item></channel></rss>