<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prices on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prices/</link><description>Recent content in prices on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 18:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Home prices surged over 20% in March as interest rates also rose, according to S&amp;amp;P Case-Shiller</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62965a319ee805a75e2057be/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 18:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62965a319ee805a75e2057be/</guid><description>Home prices continued to increase their gains, despite slower sales and higher mortgage rates.
Highlights Case-Shiller Home Price Index rose 20.6% in March. Tampa, Phoenix and Miami continued to see the highest annual gains. Phoenix slipped from the top gainer spot for the first time in three years. March&amp;rsquo;s reading was the highest year-over-year price change in more than 35 years of data. The average mortgage rate on the 30-year fixed mortgage stood at 3.</description></item><item><title>White House says it expects inflation to be 'extraordinarily elevated' in new report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254f2b515bc1b7b634c2f19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 03:32:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254f2b515bc1b7b634c2f19/</guid><description>The Biden administration is bracing for the Labor Department&amp;rsquo;s consumer price index report to show that inflation is &amp;quot;extraordinarily elevated.&amp;quot;
Highlights The Biden administration is bracing for Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s key consumer inflation report to show that the prices Americans pay soared in March. The Labor Department&amp;rsquo;s previous report failed to include the majority of the jump in oil and gas costs caused by the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s unprovoked invasion of Ukraine. The Bureau of Labor Statistics on Tuesday will issue its March update to the consumer price index, or CPI.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war pushes world food prices to record high</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252923055fd8134934d1105/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252923055fd8134934d1105/</guid><description>Ukraine war pushes world food prices to record high
Highlights Food and Agriculture Organization says world food prices hit an all-time high in March following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The disruption in export flows resulting from the Feb, 24 invasion and international sanctions against Russia has spurred fears of a global hunger crisis. Russia and Ukraine account for a huge share of the globe&amp;rsquo;s exports in several major commodities, including wheat, vegetable oil and corn.</description></item><item><title>Oil prices ease as nations agree to tap reserves</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249ab0c63c8d6984c519258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249ab0c63c8d6984c519258/</guid><description>Both Brent and US crude benchmarks settled down around 13 percent.
Highlights Both Brent and US crude benchmarks settled down around 13 percent in their biggest weekly falls in two years. US President Joe Biden announced the release of one million barrels per day (bpd) of crude oil for six months from May, which at 180 million barrels is the largest release ever from the US Strategic Petroleum Reserve (SPR) Member countries of the IEA did not agree on volumes or commitments of each country at their emergency meeting.</description></item><item><title>Oil prices fall, continuing downward trend from last week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622eb37ed3f9c222cc8cb606/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622eb37ed3f9c222cc8cb606/</guid><description>The fall came as a U.S. official said Russia was showing signs it might be willing to have substantive negotiations over Ukraine.
Highlights Oil prices fell on Sunday at the start of the session, extending last week&amp;rsquo;s decline. Prices fell last week as traders assessed potential improvements to the supply outlook that has been disrupted by the Ukraine crisis. Russia is showing signs it might be willing to have substantive negotiations over Ukraine, U.</description></item><item><title>Inflation rose 7.9% in February, more than expected as price pressures intensified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a5bf8a50dbb42fee93bfc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 20:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a5bf8a50dbb42fee93bfc/</guid><description>The consumer price index for February was expected to rise 7.8% over the past year, according to Dow Jones estimates.
Highlights Consumer price index rises 7.9% over the past 12 months, a fresh 40-year high for the closely followed gauge. Food prices rose 1% and food at home jumped 1.4%, both the fastest monthly gains since April 2020. Energy also was at the forefront of ballooning prices, up 3.5% for February and accounting for about one-third of the headline gain.</description></item><item><title>National average for a gallon of gas tops $4, the highest price at the pump since 2008</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224f9ee743e1aabb861a1c3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 18:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224f9ee743e1aabb861a1c3/</guid><description>Consumers are paying the most at the pump since 2008.
Highlights The national average for a gallon of gas hit $4.009 on Sunday, according to AAA, which is the highest since July 2008, not adjusted for inflation. The jump in prices follows a surge in the price of oil amid Russia&amp;rsquo;s war on Ukraine. The Biden administration has said for months that they are working to bring down prices at the pump, and in the fall tapped the Strategic Petroleum Reserve.</description></item><item><title>$10 toothpaste? U.S. household goods makers face blowback on price hikes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f34f8c5f64b2ee7524bf7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 09:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f34f8c5f64b2ee7524bf7/</guid><description>Get ready for the $10 tube of toothpaste.
Highlights Colgate-Palmolive CEO Noel Wallace said Colgate&amp;rsquo;s new Optic White Pro Series toothpaste is the type of premium product &amp;ldquo;vital&amp;rdquo; to its ability to raise prices. Some lawmakers and consumer advocates argue that companies are excessively raising prices in order to fuel profits and return money to shareholders. Target said on Tuesday in an earnings call that bumping up pricing is the last lever it pulls when faced with increased costs.</description></item><item><title>ERCOT kept prices high during the blackout per the governor's instructions, former head says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217e70513a835fa34ea31be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 20:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217e70513a835fa34ea31be/</guid><description>Gov. Greg Abbott&amp;rsquo;s office has said he was &amp;quot;not involved in any way&amp;quot; with the decision. Testimony from the former head of the Electric Reliability Council of Texas appears to contradict that.
Highlights Bill Magness says he was following Gov. Greg Abbott&amp;rsquo;s directions when he kept electricity prices as high as legally allowed in the aftermath of last February&amp;rsquo;s devastating blackout. Magness was testifying in a suit filed against the Electric Reliability Council of Texas by the Brazos Electric Cooperative.</description></item><item><title>World food prices jumped toward a record last month | Food News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd0937a0f9f1b4e05eae51/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd0937a0f9f1b4e05eae51/</guid><description>The United Nations’ index of prices rose 1.1 percent in January, pushed up by more pricey vegetable oils and dairy.
Highlights The United Nations’ index of prices rose 1.1% in January. The gauge is edging closer to 2011’s all-time high. The latest leg higher in the food index could further stretch household budgets. The poorest “segments in the population will feel the pinch the most,” a UN official says. Sugar marked the only commodity that eased during the month, while costs for meat, grain, dairy and vegetable oils rose.</description></item><item><title>Pay rises fail to keep up with the cost of living</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e72a6d346c0518f33dbace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 21:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e72a6d346c0518f33dbace/</guid><description>Data shows weekly wage growth fell for the first time since July 2020 but vacancies hit a new record.
Summary But he said: &amp;ldquo;It is important to remember that we are not alone in that. There&amp;rsquo;s a global phenomenon because the causes of inflation - whether it is supply chains or energy prices - are of course global in nature. But we are taking action to support people as best we can.</description></item><item><title>Amid rising prices, American families fall deeper in debt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</guid><description>Between inflation and ongoing supply chain issues, prices are rising and it&amp;rsquo;s eating away at the average family budget.
Summary Higher prices are already taking a toll. As consumers pay more for everything from groceries to gasoline, household income is failing to keep pace with a higher overall cost of living, according to recent reports. Over the past two years, median income fell 3% while the cost of living rose nearly 7%, due, in part, to rising housing and medical costs.</description></item><item><title>‘There is no money left’: Covid crisis leaves Sri Lanka on brink of bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d266ceaf339b2fdf6a6a93/</guid><description>Half a million people have sunk into poverty since the pandemic struck, with rising costs forcing many to cut back on food
Summary Sri Lanka is facing a deepening financial and humanitarian crisis with fears it could go bankrupt in 2022 as inflation rises to record levels, food prices rocket and its coffers run dry. One of the most pressing problems for Sri Lanka is its huge foreign debt burden. “When the economic crisis deepens beyond redemption, it is inevitable that the country will have a financial crisis too,” he said.</description></item></channel></rss>