<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>good on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/good/</link><description>Recent content in good on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 13:47:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/good/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shooting along Indiana highway where SUV was stopped kills 2</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284f8df15f536294c60de2b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 13:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284f8df15f536294c60de2b/</guid><description>Authorities say two men were fatally shot after a police officer and two good Samaritans stopped along a southern Indiana highway to help a driver who was stopped in the roadway
Highlights Police officer and two good Samaritans stopped along a southern Indiana highway to help a driver who was stopped in the roadway. The shooting happened Monday night after an officer with the Palmyra Police Department stopped to assist the “apparent stranded motorist” Indiana State Police didn’t say what precipitated the gunfire or who fired the shots.</description></item><item><title>A 4th dose of Covid-19 vaccine will be needed, Pfizer's CEO says, but the company is working on a shot to handle all variants</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e91132ad4d596158076df/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e91132ad4d596158076df/</guid><description>Pfizer is also hoping to make a vaccine that will protect against all variants. &amp;quot;If we are able to achieve that, then I think it is very easy to follow and remember so that we can go back to really the way (we) used to live,&amp;quot; th CEO told CBS on Sunday.
Highlights Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla says people will need a fourth dose of Covid-19 vaccine. Bourla: &amp;ldquo;Many variants are coming, and Omicron was the first one that was able to evade &amp;ndash; in a skillful way &amp;ndash; the immune protection that we&amp;rsquo;re giving&amp;rdquo; Bourla said protection after three doses is &amp;ldquo;not that good against infections&amp;rdquo; Pfizer is also hoping to make a vaccine that will protect against all variants, Bourla told CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Face the Nation&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;It is necessary, a fourth (dose) for right now,&amp;rdquo; the CEO said on CBS&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Facing the Nation,&amp;quot; Bourla added.</description></item></channel></rss>