<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>church on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/church/</link><description>Recent content in church on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 18:15:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/church/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Christian revival at school prompts student walkout in W.Va.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620404831adf972f50500dba/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620404831adf972f50500dba/</guid><description>Students in a West Virginia city have staged a walkout to protest a Christian assembly they were forced to attend during school hours
Highlights West Virginia students protest Christian assembly they were forced to attend during school hours. Separation of church and state is one of the founding tenets of the U.S. Constitution. More than 100 students staged a walkout during their homeroom period to protest the assembly. Student: &amp;ldquo;My rights are non-negotiable.</description></item><item><title>At many churches, pandemic hits collection plates, budgets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e46b6aa8ee25cae015685b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e46b6aa8ee25cae015685b/</guid><description>Biltmore United Methodist Church of Asheville, North Carolina, is for sale. Already financially strapped because of shrinking membership and a struggling preschool, the congregation was dealt a crushing blow by the coronavirus.
Summary Attendance plummeted, with many staying home or switching to other churches that stayed open the whole time. Already financially strapped because of shrinking membership and a struggling preschool, the congregation was dealt a crushing blow by the coronavirus.</description></item></channel></rss>