<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>church on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/church/</link><description>Recent content in church on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 14:09:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/church/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eight Missouri ministers accused of sex abuse in Southern Baptist Convention report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62937e7b8ec93d1f6d78da30/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 14:09:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62937e7b8ec93d1f6d78da30/</guid><description>The Southern Baptist Convention on Thursday released a once-secret and lengthy list of accused sex abusers within the denomination.
Highlights The Southern Baptist Convention releases a 205-page list of accused sex abusers. The list is a compilation of ministers and church workers who have been credibly accused of sexual abuse. It comes after the release of a 300-page report by an independent investigator. The report says leaders of the Southern Baptist denomination for decades have received reports of sex abuse committed by church workers, pastors and others.</description></item><item><title>Police: 31 dead in church fair stampede in southern Nigeria</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62928f6eed81ded3aeb06156/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62928f6eed81ded3aeb06156/</guid><description>Police say a stampede at a church charity event in southern Nigeria has left 31 people dead and seven injured
Highlights Police say stampede at a church charity event in southern Nigeria has left 31 people dead and seven injured. One witness said the dead included a pregnant woman and “many children” Police said the stampede took place at an annual “Shop for Free” program organized by the Kings Assembly Pentecostal church in Rivers state.</description></item><item><title>Gunman in California church attack subdued by parishioners</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282ccb264f9e59da030c066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 22:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282ccb264f9e59da030c066/</guid><description>LAGUNA WOODS, Calif. (AP) — A gunman in a deadly attack at a Southern California church was a Chinese immigrant motivated by hate for Taiwanese people, authorities said. The shooter killed Dr.
Highlights Suspect identified as David Chou, 68, of Las Vegas. Shooter killed Dr. John Cheng, 52, and wounded five others during a lunch held by Irvine Taiwanese Presbyterian Church, which worships at Geneva Presbyterian Church in Laguna Woods, California.</description></item><item><title>Multiple People Hit in Shooting at Laguna Woods Church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281892ae15ab0452fcce0a6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 23:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281892ae15ab0452fcce0a6/</guid><description>Multiple people were hit in a shooting at Geneva Presbyterian Church in the Laguna Woods area of Orange County. A suspected shooter is in custody and a gun has&amp;hellip;
Highlights At least five people have been injured in a shooting at a church in Laguna Woods, Orange County. The suspected shooter is in police custody, but the motive for the shooting is not yet known. Thirty to 40 witnesses will need to be interviewed, including people who were inside the church at the time.</description></item><item><title>Church linked to San Jose kidnapping also tied to apparent exorcism death of 3-year-old girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2fc63cee467d12289735/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 10:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2fc63cee467d12289735/</guid><description>Disturbing details have come to light regarding a San Jose church where an alleged exorcism claimed the life of a 3-year-old girl.
Highlights Police were called to the South Bay church in September for a separate incident that involved the death of a 3-year-old girl. The death occurred at the Iglesia Evangelicas Apostoles y Profetas as family members were trying to rid the girl of an evil spirit. The medical examiner said ultimately the child died of asphyxia due to suffocation.</description></item><item><title>Priest attacked with knife in Nice, France</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62664a2a3f7b74b7726a055a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 07:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62664a2a3f7b74b7726a055a/</guid><description>A man decribed as mentally unstable attacked a priest with a knife in a church in Nice, southern France, officials said on Sunday.
Highlights A man attacked a priest with a knife in Nice, France, officials said on Sunday. The attacker had no criminal record and was known to have purchased a knife several days earlier. The assault came as France was voting in the second round of presidential elections. The man was named as a 31-year-old man who had not been seen in the public eye since the attack.</description></item><item><title>Christian revival at school prompts student walkout in W.Va.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620404831adf972f50500dba/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620404831adf972f50500dba/</guid><description>Students in a West Virginia city have staged a walkout to protest a Christian assembly they were forced to attend during school hours
Highlights West Virginia students protest Christian assembly they were forced to attend during school hours. Separation of church and state is one of the founding tenets of the U.S. Constitution. More than 100 students staged a walkout during their homeroom period to protest the assembly. Student: &amp;ldquo;My rights are non-negotiable.</description></item><item><title>At many churches, pandemic hits collection plates, budgets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e46b6aa8ee25cae015685b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e46b6aa8ee25cae015685b/</guid><description>Biltmore United Methodist Church of Asheville, North Carolina, is for sale. Already financially strapped because of shrinking membership and a struggling preschool, the congregation was dealt a crushing blow by the coronavirus.
Summary Attendance plummeted, with many staying home or switching to other churches that stayed open the whole time. Already financially strapped because of shrinking membership and a struggling preschool, the congregation was dealt a crushing blow by the coronavirus.</description></item></channel></rss>