<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>going on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/going/</link><description>Recent content in going on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 16:15:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/going/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Cowards': Teacher who survived Uvalde shooting slams police response Arnulfo Reyes, from hospital bed, vows students won’t "die in vain."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f799188dad29d9f60f8e2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 16:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f799188dad29d9f60f8e2/</guid><description>Less than two weeks after surviving the second-most deadly school shooting in U.S. history, Arnulfo Reyes offered the most vivid account yet of what transpired in Uvalde.
Highlights Arnulfo Reyes tells ABC News anchor Amy Robach how he survived May 24 school shooting in Uvalde, Texas. Reyes says he told his students, &amp;ldquo;Get under the table and act like you&amp;rsquo;re asleep&amp;rdquo; When he turned around, he saw a blur &amp;ndash; and then gunfire, he says.</description></item><item><title>Murder case dismissed after Cincinnati police detective finds gun during jury selection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cf0441d16b99041a51691/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 08:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cf0441d16b99041a51691/</guid><description>Prosecutors dismissed charges against Delrico Peoples after the lead detective found the alleged murder weapon already in evidence.
Highlights Murder case dismissed after Cincinnati police detective finds gun during jury selection. Prosecutors dismissed charges against Delrico Peoples after the lead detective found the alleged murder weapon. Brandon Phoenix, 18, was struck by a stray bullet as he waited for his bus at a Mount Airy bus stop in 2019. Prosecutors say a preliminary analysis shows the gun may be the same one that killed Phoenix.</description></item><item><title>Shields Up: U.S. officials preparing for potential Russian cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625cf39939981094c84e5cdc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 05:14:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625cf39939981094c84e5cdc/</guid><description>Bill Whitaker reports on the proven capabilities of Russia&amp;rsquo;s hackers, who just a few years ago were able to infiltrate the computer network of a Kansas nuclear power plant.
Highlights U.S. cyber defenders say they&amp;rsquo;re bracing themselves with &amp;ldquo;Shields Up&amp;rdquo; initiative. The agency helps secure computer networks in 16 sectors deemed vital to national security, like energy, finance and communications. The Biden administration has been releasing sensitive intelligence and dire warnings that the Kremlin is preparing to launch a new generation of cyberattacks on American soil.</description></item><item><title>Ex-officer accused of endangering Breonna Taylor's neighbors found not guilty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222571cca57d538b9076966/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 18:16:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222571cca57d538b9076966/</guid><description>Former Louisville, Kentucky, police officer Brett Hankison was found not guilty on all counts Thursday after he was accused of endangering a couple and their 5-
Highlights Brett Hankison was accused of endangering Cody Etherton, his partner, Chelsey Napper and their 5-year-old son. The jury reached their verdict after deliberating for a little over three hours following nearly two weeks of testimony. Police were at the complex to raid a neighboring apartment that belonged to Breonna Taylor in connection to a narcotics investigation.</description></item><item><title>Actress Lindsey Pearlman found dead after going missing in LA</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62121417c05200d0928ec69f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62121417c05200d0928ec69f/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — Actor Lindsey Erin Pearlman, who had roles in “General Hospital,” “American Housewife” and other shows, was found dead days after she was reported missing in Los Angeles, authorities said.
Highlights Lindsey Erin Pearlman, 43, was last seen around noon last Sunday, ABC 7 reported. Her body was found Friday morning, Feb. 18, 2022, when officers responded to a call for a death investigation in a residential neighborhood of Hollywood.</description></item></channel></rss>