<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>junior on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/junior/</link><description>Recent content in junior on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 02:59:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/junior/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Officer ‘motorboated’ subordinate at promotion ceremony, retires after guilty plea</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285b25965fdddb99c5f8a55/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 02:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285b25965fdddb99c5f8a55/</guid><description>A plea deal let the officer keep his retirement, court records revealed.
Highlights Capt. Billy Joe Crosby Jr., a logistics officer, was sentenced to 30 days in prison. He pleaded guilty to assault consummated by battery and conduct unbecoming. Crosby was the officer-in-charge of an outpost in Jordan in May 2021. The plea deal also prevented the judge from dismissing him from the Army, which would have kept him from collecting his retirement.</description></item><item><title>Massachusetts High School junior prom ends early due to students yelling racial slur while song was playing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62783231117069ae5523752b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 21:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62783231117069ae5523752b/</guid><description>Hamilton-Wenham Regional High School&amp;rsquo;s junior prom ended early on April 28. Students heard yelling the racial slur during a song, school officials said. Police have also been called into the investigation.
Highlights Students heard yelling the N-word at a junior prom. The song was playing at the time of the incident. Police have been called to the school. The incident occurred at a high school in the middle of the night.</description></item><item><title>Erriyon Knighton, teen who broke Usain Bolt junior records, shatters another</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626eb2caa93a3e4dde8643fb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626eb2caa93a3e4dde8643fb/</guid><description>Erriyon Knighton, who last year at age 17 broke Usain Bolt junior sprint records, shattered his own U20 record in the 200m.
Highlights Erriyon Knighton broke Usain Bolt junior sprint records last year at age 17. Knighton clocked 19.49 seconds in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, the world’s fastest time since the 2012 Olympics. His time is the second-fastest 200m ever recorded by an American after Michael Johnson&amp;rsquo;s then-world record 19.32 at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics.</description></item></channel></rss>