<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>assessment on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/assessment/</link><description>Recent content in assessment on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:18:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/assessment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A construction project caused damage to 100-million-year-old dinosaur tracks in Utah</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c6bb55e390136656ae5dc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:18:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c6bb55e390136656ae5dc/</guid><description>A project to replace the boardwalk at the Mill Canyon Dinosaur Tracksite in Moah, Utah, cause minor damage to tracks and trace fossils at the site, a Bureau of Land Management paleontologist found.
Highlights A project to replace the boardwalk at the Mill Canyon Dinosaur Tracksite in Moab, Utah, caused minor damage to dinosaur tracks. The site dates back more than 100 million years and contains more than 200 dinosaur tracks and traces of at least 10 different animals.</description></item><item><title>UK Says Russia Is Planning To Overthrow Ukraine’s Government - Buzzfeed News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</guid><description>“The information being released today shines a light on the extent of Russian activity designed to subvert Ukraine, and is an insight into Kremlin thinking,” Foreign Secretary Liz Truss said in a statement shared with BuzzFeed News.
Summary BAKHMUT, Ukraine — Russia has drawn up plans to install a pro-Kremlin former member of parliament to lead Ukraine as it considers a new invasion of the country and the overthrow of its central government, according to a British assessment shared with BuzzFeed News.</description></item></channel></rss>