<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>region on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/region/</link><description>Recent content in region on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 03:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/region/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justice Department charges 12 medical professionals for allegedly fueling the opioid epidemic in Appalachian region</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62733de66bf74f4d6b235120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 03:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62733de66bf74f4d6b235120/</guid><description>A 24-year-old patient died from a morphine overdose after a dentist allegedly wrote three opioid prescriptions for the patient in five days.
Highlights A dozen defendants across eight federal districts have been charged in connection with the illegal prescription and distribution of 5.1 million pills. The defendants span seven states and account for approximately $7 million in opioid-related fraud loss, the Justice Department says. One pharmacist in Florida allegedly sold 219,567 pills of oxycodone and 112,840 pills of hydromorphone on the black market between 2019 and 2021.</description></item><item><title>Police: More than 900 civilian bodies found in Kyiv region</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b14bf6cb27277aae31e57/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:11:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b14bf6cb27277aae31e57/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of more than 900 civilians have been discovered in the region surrounding the Ukrainian capital following Russia&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal — most of them fatally shot, police said Friday, an indication that many people were &amp;quot;simply executed.”
Highlights More than 900 civilians have been discovered in the region surrounding the Ukrainian capital following Russia’s withdrawal, police say. Police data indicates 95% died from gunshot wounds, an indication many people were “simply executed” Police: More bodies are being found every day under rubble and in mass graves, with the largest number found in Bucha, where there were more than 350.</description></item><item><title>7.3-magnitude earthquake strikes near Japan coast, triggering tsunami advisory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623245071d91ba8ef84a4d31/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 20:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623245071d91ba8ef84a4d31/</guid><description>A massive 7.3-magnitude earthquake struck near Namie, Japan, triggering a one-meter-high tsunami advisory in the region 11 years after it was devastated by a deadly quake.
Highlights The earthquake near Namie, Japan, was reported just before 11 a.m. ET on Wednesday. The Japan Meteorological Agency said the quake struck about 36 miles below the sea. Two aftershocks in Japan left seven people injured including six from falling objects. The northern Japan region was devastated by a deadly 9.</description></item><item><title>French army says senior al Qaeda leader killed in Mali</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226e598150870837e2d2394/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226e598150870837e2d2394/</guid><description>France&amp;rsquo;s army said Monday that its anti-jihadist force in Mali had killed Yahia Djouadi, a &amp;quot;senior leader&amp;quot; of Al-Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM) responsible for finance and logistics.
Highlights Yahia Djouadi was a &amp;ldquo;senior leader&amp;rdquo; of Al-Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM) responsible for finance and logistics. He was killed overnight from February 25 to 26 around (160 kilometres (100 miles) north of Timbuktu in central Mali) His death &amp;ldquo;once again weakens Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s governance&amp;rdquo; in Mali, French army says.</description></item><item><title>Queen refuses to pay Prince Andrew's sex abuse case legal fees, forces him to quickly sell chalet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7e5a55acc8b609ef71b22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 07:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7e5a55acc8b609ef71b22/</guid><description>Summary This content is not available in your region READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Scottish 'witches' in line for apology hundreds of years after being burned at the stake</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d258bd05a1e3f8c8fa8e2b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d258bd05a1e3f8c8fa8e2b/</guid><description>Summary This content is not available in your region READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>