<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukraine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraine/</link><description>Recent content in ukraine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:10:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine’s amateur army: Thousands of young civilians are drafted into the military and trained for war in desperate bid to fend off Putin’s 100,000 well-trained troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</guid><description>Young Ukrainian men and women, some as young as 21, have been taking part in Kyiv Territorial Defence unit training over the weekend, as they prepare for a possible conflict with Moscow.
Summary In the event of a potential invasion by Russia, these youngsters will be part of the country&amp;rsquo;s civil resistance that will carry on the fight against Russian soldiers if the Ukrainian military is overwhelmed. Tatiana, who is enrolled in a military reserve program, joined hundreds of other young Ukrainians in a Kyiv Territorial Defence Unit training exercise on Saturday in a snow-covered forest in Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Ireland tells Russia that naval exercises off our coast 'not welcome'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</guid><description>Mr Coveney said that Foreign Ministers will be pushing Russia to &amp;quot;defuse tensions&amp;quot; along the Ukrainian border, where it has amassed troops in recent &amp;hellip;
Summary The Government has told Russia that naval exercises off the Irish coast are &amp;ldquo;not welcome&amp;rdquo;, but Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney has accepted that they are legal. Russian naval exercises are due to take place in early February, approximately 240km off the southwest coast and within Ireland’s Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) but not in Ireland’s territorial waters.</description></item><item><title>Erdogan Warns Russia Against Invading Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s supply of combat drones to Ukraine has drawn the wrath of Russia.
Summary Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Tuesday warned Russia against invading Ukraine, calling the former Soviet republic a &amp;ldquo;powerful&amp;rdquo; country with international friends. Speaking to Turkish reporters in Albania, Erdogan said he intended to discuss the rising tensions with Russian President Vladimir Putin. &amp;ldquo;You cannot handle these things by saying &amp;lsquo;I will invade something, I will take it&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; Turkish media quoted Erdogan as saying.</description></item><item><title>Germany signals it could halt gas pipeline if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</guid><description>Germany signalled on Tuesday that it could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if Moscow invades Ukraine, and Western nations rallied behind Kyiv over a Russian troop buildup that has stoked fears of war.
Summary As fears of conflict rose, Britain said this week it had begun supplying Ukraine with anti-tank weapons, Canada&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister visited Ukraine and German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock held talks in Moscow and Kyiv to try to ease tensions.</description></item><item><title>White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine 'at any point'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</guid><description>White House press secretary Jen Psaki told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S.
Summary White House press secretary Jen Psaki Jen PsakiBiden commends wireless giants for delaying 5G rollout near key airports Briefing in brief: Free COVID-19 test site in testing phase before launch Wednesday White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;at any point&amp;rsquo; MORE told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S. believes that Russia could carry out an attack on Ukraine “at any point,” underscoring the immediacy of the threat should Moscow decide to take action.</description></item><item><title>Russia cannot 'tolerate' NATO's 'gradual invasion' of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;quot;tolerate&amp;quot; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;quot;gradual invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine.
Summary Russian President Vladimir Putin Vladimir Vladimirovich PutinRussia cannot &amp;lsquo;tolerate&amp;rsquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;gradual invasion&amp;rsquo; of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says Fears of Russian invasion of Ukraine rise despite US push for diplomacy Overnight Defense &amp;amp; National Security — US says Russia prepping &amp;lsquo;false flag&amp;rsquo; operation MORE&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;ldquo;tolerate&amp;rdquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;ldquo;gradual invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US intelligence indicates Russia preparing operation to justify invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</guid><description>The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.
Summary Washington (CNN) The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>