<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukraine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraine/</link><description>Recent content in ukraine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 03:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On Monday, near Kyiv, chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay and his team were attacked. Camera operator Richie Mockler took two rounds to his body armour, Stuart was wounded.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222d537abe5cc55cf5cf389/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 03:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222d537abe5cc55cf5cf389/</guid><description>On Monday, near Kyiv, chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay and his team were attacked. Camera operator Richie Mockler took two rounds to his body armour, Stuart was wounded. Their experience illustrates the scale of the mayhem and violence as Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion enters a new and deadlier phase.
Highlights As with many wars, the Russian invasion of Ukraine changes constantly, battlefields appear suddenly in previously quiet areas, kinetic places go silent. The journey took us hours as we left central Kyiv through a city now being strengthened with extra soldiers.</description></item><item><title>Top Russian general killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</guid><description>Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky, the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division, was killed in fighting in Ukraine earlier this week.
Highlights Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky was the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division. His death was confirmed by a local officers’ organization in the Krasnodar region in southern Russia. The circumstances of his death were not immediately clear. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>The teenager that tracked Elon Musk's jet is now tracking Russian oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</guid><description>Jack Sweeney, a Florida teen who tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online has a new aviation-themed target: Russian oligarchs and billionaires.
Highlights Jack Sweeney, 19, tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online. He recently launched two new automated Twitter handles — @RUOligarchJets and @Putinjet — following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The two profiles have amassed nearly 300,000 followers combined and provide nearly live updates of the private jets&amp;rsquo; movements. Russia&amp;rsquo;s oligarchs face economic chaos at home and punishment by the West after President Vladimir Putin ordered his troops into Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>China Asked Russia to Delay Ukraine War Until After Olympics, U.S. Officials Say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622024296fff817336c459c6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 02:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622024296fff817336c459c6/</guid><description>A Western intelligence report indicates that Chinese officials had some level of direct knowledge about President Vladimir V. Putin’s war plans or intentions.
Highlights The ambitious joint statement that the two nations issued during that meeting alarmed American and European officials. It was the first time China had explicitly sided with Russia on issues concerning NATO and European security. A Western intelligence report indicates that Chinese officials had some level of direct knowledge about President Vladimir V.</description></item><item><title>Georgia to apply ‘immediately’ for EU membership: Ruling party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220108a46bb2e085fd04a12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:49:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220108a46bb2e085fd04a12/</guid><description>Georgia will “immediately” apply for EU membership, the Black Sea nation’s ruling party said Wednesday, a day after the European Parliament backed war-torn
Highlights Georgia will “immediately” apply for EU membership, the Black Sea nation’s ruling party said Wednesday. Decision follows a day after the European Parliament backed war-torn Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s bid to apply for membership. The vote was seen in Georgia as a window of opportunity to advance its own EU aspirations.</description></item><item><title>Russian Police jail kids aged 7-11 for bringing flowers &amp;amp; “No to War” signs to Ukraine’s embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fc14b51949d11cab426fe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fc14b51949d11cab426fe/</guid><description>In an emergency session, the General Assembly voted 141-5 to condemn Russia and demand that it end its war in Ukraine. Also, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defense minister accused Russia of deploying “the criminal tactics of long-range shelling of peaceful cities,” and Moscow police jailed children who carried &amp;quot;No to War&amp;quot; signs.
Highlights Russia claims it has taken over the southern Ukrainian city of Kherson, but Ukrainian officials sharply dispute this. Russia shuts down two leading Russian media outlets over critical coverage of the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Cyberattack on NATO could trigger collective defence clause - official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dff6be9fbb6a79c99423d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dff6be9fbb6a79c99423d/</guid><description>A cyberattack on a NATO member state could trigger Article 5, its collective defence clause, a NATO official said on Monday, amid concerns that chaos in cyberspace around Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine could spill over into other territories.
Highlights A cyberattack on a NATO member state could trigger Article 5, its collective defence clause. The military alliance has for years made clear that a serious cyberattack could trigger the clause, but such a scenario has so far been largely hypothetical.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine establishing foreign legion for volunteers from abroad - President</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bf7625119d14fa45e97a7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bf7625119d14fa45e97a7/</guid><description>Ukraine is establishing a foreign &amp;quot;international&amp;quot; legion for volunteers from abroad, President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said on Sunday.
Highlights Ukraine is establishing a foreign &amp;ldquo;international&amp;rdquo; legion for volunteers from abroad, President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said on Sunday. Ukraine is established a &amp;ldquo;foreign legion&amp;rdquo; for volunteers, the president said. Zelenskyy said in a statement that he is still in the capital, in Kyiv, Ukraine February 25, 2022 in this screengrab obtained from a handout video.</description></item><item><title>Putin puts Russia's nuclear forces on alert, cites sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bbfe519af4fd00ee355b4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 18:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bbfe519af4fd00ee355b4/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Sunday said that Ukraine and Russia would conduct the first diplomatic talks since the Kremlin-launched invasion.
Highlights Russian forces are using siege tactics against Chernihiv, a senior defense official says. The move raises the specter of more civilian casualties as the fighting worsens in Ukraine. The Pentagon says the Russian military still has not seized control of any Ukrainian cities. Russia has put about two-thirds of the fighting force it had amassed around Ukraine into the country already, the official adds.</description></item><item><title>Officials: Defenders of Ukrainian island may still be alive and now POWs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b406b5688d1ccead3a1c7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 09:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b406b5688d1ccead3a1c7/</guid><description>The defenders of the small Ukrainian island of Zmiinyi in the Black Sea may still be alive, according to a statement released on Saturday by the State Border Guard Service of Ukraine (SBGSU).
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine is encountering &amp;ldquo;stiffer than expected&amp;rdquo; resistance from the Ukrainian military and unexpected difficulties supplying its forces. Russia is suffering heavier losses in personnel, armor and aircraft than expected, US officials say. Russia has yet to establish air supremacy over Ukraine, a senior defense official says.</description></item><item><title>Anti-war sentiment grows in Russia despite govt crackdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</guid><description>As Russian troops were closing in on the Ukrainian capital, more and more Russians at home were speaking out against the invasion even as the government&amp;rsquo;s official rhetoric grew increasingly harsher
Highlights At least 460 people in 34 cities were detained over anti-war protests on Saturday, including over 200 in Moscow. An online petition to stop the attack on Ukraine garnered over 780,000 signatures by Saturday evening. A prominent contemporary art museum in Moscow called Garage announced Saturday it was halting its work on exhibitions and postponing them “until the human and political tragedy that is unfolding in Ukraine has ceased&amp;quot; Dmitry Medvedev said Moscow may respond to Western sanctions by opting out of the last nuclear arms deal with the U.</description></item><item><title>For the first time ever, the NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia's ongoing invasion of Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621945ea275bd3d32f600f59/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 21:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621945ea275bd3d32f600f59/</guid><description>For the first time, the NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s ongoing invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The force consists of land, air, sea and special operations forces from the allies. It&amp;rsquo;s not clear how many troops the response force will contain. US President Joe Biden has been clear that US troops are deploying to eastern Europe to help bolster NATO countries nervous about Russia&amp;rsquo;s aggressive actions, and they will not be fighting in Ukraine, which is not a member of the NATO alliance.</description></item><item><title>Patreon suspends donation page for nonprofit giving body armor to Ukrainian army</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218900507807c94a24b695c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218900507807c94a24b695c/</guid><description>Come Back Alive is looking to use money it has collected through Patreon to distribute armor and helmets to soldiers. Now it&amp;rsquo;s abilities are limited.
Highlights Russia invaded Ukraine late Wednesday, and over $300,000 rolled in, including many donations of less than $1,000. A nonprofit organization collecting donations to distribute body armor, medical kits, and helmets to Ukrainian soldiers. The organization last received money from its Patreon page in August, its director, Taras Chmut, told CNBC in an interview.</description></item><item><title>Explosions are heard in Ukraine port city of Mariupol: Fears shelling is underway - Public</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217bcc78ade673d3bc36b82/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217bcc78ade673d3bc36b82/</guid><description>PUBLIC UK Bring the Latest News Exclusives, Sport, Celebrities, Showbiz, Politics, Business, Lifestyle, Travel and Tech info for you 24/7.
Highlights Explosions had been heard within the Ukrainian port town of Mariupol, as fears mount that shelling is underway. The explosions come just hours after the U.S. warned the Ukrainian govt that Putin’s troops are ‘in a position to move now’ with an invasion of Ukraine, with 80 according to cent of Russian infantrymen now assembled across the nation in assault positions.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine moves to impose state of emergency as U.S., allies pressure Russia with sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</guid><description>Russia had all of the necessary military capabilities Wednesday to launch a full-scale invasion into neighboring Ukraine, a senior U.S. defense official said.
Highlights At least five Ukrainian websites were hit by cyberattacks ahead of state of emergency vote. Russia evacuates its embassy in Kyiv, state news agency reports. U.S., Europe and other allies impose first salvo of sanctions on Moscow. Secretary of State Antony Blinken cancels a meeting with Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister.</description></item><item><title>White House calls Russian moves on Ukraine an invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country — a move that could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S.
Highlights Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country. The move could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S. said an invasion was already underway there. Western leaders said Tuesday that Russian troops have moved into rebel-held areas in eastern Ukraine after Putin&amp;rsquo;s recognition of their independence.</description></item><item><title>Germany halts approval of gas pipeline Nord Stream 2 after Russia’s actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</guid><description>Germany on Tuesday halted the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring natural gas from Russia directly to Europe.
Highlights Germany halts certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline to bring gas to Europe. The pipeline is designed to bring natural gas directly to Europe from Russia. Germany&amp;rsquo;s president said the country would not accept the recognition of the two pro-Russian separatist regions in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>UK to impose sanctions on Russia over ‘attack on Ukraine’s sovereignty’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214ef4f2af705c3e3ca77ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214ef4f2af705c3e3ca77ac/</guid><description>Boris Johnson announces plans after Vladimir Putin backs independence for breakaway states and sends troops into Ukrainian territory
Highlights UK to sign off a package of sanctions against Russia on Tuesday morning. Initial signs were that the package would target ‘those complicit in the violation of Ukraine’s territorial integrity’ Russia has massed about 190,000 troops – with separatists accounting for another 30,000. The UK has been in close discussions with the EU and the US about launching coordinated sanctions.</description></item><item><title>U.S. has intel that Russian commanders have orders to proceed with Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</guid><description>The intelligence indicates that commanders on the ground making specific plans for how they would maneuver in their sector of the battlefield.
Highlights U.S. intelligence indicates Russian commanders have received orders to proceed with an invasion of Ukraine. Defense minister of Belarus announced Russia will be extending military drills near Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northern borders. Russia has massed roughly 150,000 troops, warplanes and equipment on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s three sides, escalating tensions with neighboring country.</description></item><item><title>More than 130,000 Russian troops now staged outside Ukraine: U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 01:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</guid><description>Some airlines cancelled flights to the Ukrainian capital and troops there unloaded fresh shipments of weapons from NATO members Sunday, as its president sought to project confidence in the face of U.S. warnings of possible invasion within days by a growing number of Russian forces.
Highlights NEW: U.S. intelligence officials believe targeting the military exercise is just one of multiple options that Russia has weighed as a possibility for a false pretext for an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky claims Vladimir Putin is putting illegal pressure on Britain's political system</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 13:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</guid><description>Mikhail Khodorkovsky says Russian meddling is happening &amp;quot;directly and indirectly&amp;quot; in Britain - and it must be stopped.
Highlights Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky calls out &amp;lsquo;dangerous, illegal&amp;rsquo; pressure by Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;cronies&amp;rsquo; in the UK. Former head of oil giant Yukos was imprisoned for eight years by Putin&amp;rsquo;s government for tax evasion and theft in a controversial case. He says Putin is &amp;ldquo;capable of all sorts of actions, including ill-judged ones&amp;rdquo; Putin is &amp;lsquo;in fact afraid&amp;rsquo; of a war with Ukraine, says ex-Russian oligarch.</description></item><item><title>U.S. accuses Russia of planning "staged" video as pretext for Ukraine attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc532c1271b37261546b23/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 22:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc532c1271b37261546b23/</guid><description>The U.S. has not provided specific evidence for its claims.
Highlights The U.S. says Russia is considering staging a &amp;ldquo;fabricated attack&amp;rdquo; by Ukrainian forces, an official says. The official says Russian intelligence services are &amp;ldquo;intimately involved&amp;rdquo; in the planning of the fabricated attack. It&amp;rsquo;s the second time in recent weeks that the Biden administration has publicly accused Russia of plotting an operation that would serve as a pretext to invade Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Soldier Opens Fire, Kills Five Soldiers at Military Base</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2b4dca174bcde43071f3c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2b4dca174bcde43071f3c/</guid><description>The attacker opened fire with an assault rifle then fled the scene.
Highlights A Ukrainian National Guard soldier opened fire on security guards at a military factory in central Ukraine for reasons unknown, killing five people and wounding five others before fleeing. Interior Minister Denys Monastyrskiy named the soldier as Artem Ryabchuk and said he would “bear the strictest responsibility provided by law”. He said investigators would look into how the soldier passed a medical commission that allowed him access to weapons.</description></item><item><title>Norway's PM says Russia build-up is 'a sign of weakness'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1eea8cda0a75a8fbe2fe4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1eea8cda0a75a8fbe2fe4/</guid><description>UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Norway’s prime minister, whose country borders Russia and is a founding member of NATO, said Wednesday he believes it’s “a sign of weakness” that President Vladimir Putin has to express Moscow’s political views by an “extraordinary” military buildup.
Summary UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Norway’s prime minister, whose country borders Russia and is a founding member of NATO, said Wednesday he believes it’s “a sign of weakness” that President Vladimir Putin has to express Moscow’s political views by an “extraordinary” military buildup.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine urges calm, saying Russian invasion not imminent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s leaders sought Tuesday to reassure the nation that an invasion from neighboring Russia was not imminent, even as they acknowledged the threat is real and received a shipment of U.S.
Summary British Prime Minister Boris Johnson also said he is prepared to send troops to protect NATO allies in Europe. Fighting between Ukrainian forces and Russia-backed rebels has killed over 14,000 people, and efforts to reach a settlement have stalled.</description></item><item><title>Biden touts 'total unanimity' with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</guid><description>President Biden said Monday he and European leaders are in agreement following a call to discuss strategy in response to Russia’s military build-up along the Ukrainian border.
Summary Total unanimity with all the European leaders. We’ll talk about it later,” Biden said after a previously planned meeting with administration officials to discuss lowering prices. Biden met for 80 minutes earlier Monday with European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, European Council President Charles Michel, French President Emmanuel Macron Emmanuel Jean-Michel MacronDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;rsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine Biden huddling with European leaders on Russia&amp;rsquo;s military buildup near Ukraine MORE, British Prime Minister Boris Johnson Boris JohnsonDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;rsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine UK scrapping testing requirements for vaccinated arrivals MORE, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz, Italian Prime Minister Mario Draghi, NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg and Polish President Andrzej Duda.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s amateur army: Thousands of young civilians are drafted into the military and trained for war in desperate bid to fend off Putin’s 100,000 well-trained troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</guid><description>Young Ukrainian men and women, some as young as 21, have been taking part in Kyiv Territorial Defence unit training over the weekend, as they prepare for a possible conflict with Moscow.
Summary In the event of a potential invasion by Russia, these youngsters will be part of the country&amp;rsquo;s civil resistance that will carry on the fight against Russian soldiers if the Ukrainian military is overwhelmed. Tatiana, who is enrolled in a military reserve program, joined hundreds of other young Ukrainians in a Kyiv Territorial Defence Unit training exercise on Saturday in a snow-covered forest in Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Ireland tells Russia that naval exercises off our coast 'not welcome'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</guid><description>Mr Coveney said that Foreign Ministers will be pushing Russia to &amp;quot;defuse tensions&amp;quot; along the Ukrainian border, where it has amassed troops in recent &amp;hellip;
Summary The Government has told Russia that naval exercises off the Irish coast are &amp;ldquo;not welcome&amp;rdquo;, but Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney has accepted that they are legal. Russian naval exercises are due to take place in early February, approximately 240km off the southwest coast and within Ireland’s Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) but not in Ireland’s territorial waters.</description></item><item><title>Erdogan Warns Russia Against Invading Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s supply of combat drones to Ukraine has drawn the wrath of Russia.
Summary Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Tuesday warned Russia against invading Ukraine, calling the former Soviet republic a &amp;ldquo;powerful&amp;rdquo; country with international friends. Speaking to Turkish reporters in Albania, Erdogan said he intended to discuss the rising tensions with Russian President Vladimir Putin. &amp;ldquo;You cannot handle these things by saying &amp;lsquo;I will invade something, I will take it&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; Turkish media quoted Erdogan as saying.</description></item><item><title>Germany signals it could halt gas pipeline if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</guid><description>Germany signalled on Tuesday that it could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if Moscow invades Ukraine, and Western nations rallied behind Kyiv over a Russian troop buildup that has stoked fears of war.
Summary As fears of conflict rose, Britain said this week it had begun supplying Ukraine with anti-tank weapons, Canada&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister visited Ukraine and German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock held talks in Moscow and Kyiv to try to ease tensions.</description></item><item><title>White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine 'at any point'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</guid><description>White House press secretary Jen Psaki told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S.
Summary White House press secretary Jen Psaki Jen PsakiBiden commends wireless giants for delaying 5G rollout near key airports Briefing in brief: Free COVID-19 test site in testing phase before launch Wednesday White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;at any point&amp;rsquo; MORE told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S. believes that Russia could carry out an attack on Ukraine “at any point,” underscoring the immediacy of the threat should Moscow decide to take action.</description></item><item><title>Russia cannot 'tolerate' NATO's 'gradual invasion' of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;quot;tolerate&amp;quot; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;quot;gradual invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine.
Summary Russian President Vladimir Putin Vladimir Vladimirovich PutinRussia cannot &amp;rsquo;tolerate&amp;rsquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;gradual invasion&amp;rsquo; of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says Fears of Russian invasion of Ukraine rise despite US push for diplomacy Overnight Defense &amp;amp; National Security — US says Russia prepping &amp;lsquo;false flag&amp;rsquo; operation MORE&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;ldquo;tolerate&amp;rdquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;ldquo;gradual invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US intelligence indicates Russia preparing operation to justify invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</guid><description>The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.
Summary Washington (CNN) The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>