<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukraine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraine/</link><description>Recent content in ukraine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:18:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NATO is no longer bound by commitments to Russia and will beef up Eastern Europe presence, says deputy secretary general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294fc331528a4330fdec89e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294fc331528a4330fdec89e/</guid><description>The NATO-Russia agreement signed 25 years ago no longer binds the Alliance because Russia itself violated the agreement &amp;hellip;
Highlights NATO-Russia agreement signed 25 years ago no longer binds the Alliance because Russia itself violated the agreement by invading Ukraine, says NATO Deputy Secretary General Mircea Geoană, visiting Vilnius. NATO pledged not to permanently deploy significant forces in central and eastern Europe, including the Baltic states. Russia has committed to refrain from aggression against its neighbours and is not complying, he says.</description></item><item><title>The US Has a Plan to Document Human Rights Violations in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62848f81c52e7e347565abb1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 06:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62848f81c52e7e347565abb1/</guid><description>The government will fund a project to help humanitarians on the ground and gather evidence of war crimes.
Highlights The newly established Conflict Observatory will use open source imagery to collect evidence of possible war crimes in Ukraine. The Observatory will have access to commercial satellite data and imagery from the government. It does not plan to make its data open source, unlike many other projects, according to the researcher. The move would be the first of its kind but would be too costly and resource-intensive for other organizations to replicate.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine win Eurovision with UK in second</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62810a59db3813eb5c2d34ea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62810a59db3813eb5c2d34ea/</guid><description>Ukraine wins the final of the Song Contest, followed by the UK, Spain, Sweden and then Serbia.
Highlights Kalush Orchestra wins the Song Contest, followed by the UK, Spain, Sweden and then Serbia. Ukraine fans flocked to Telegram to share their excitement at the news. Many people have been describing the country&amp;rsquo;s win as a &amp;ldquo;victory&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;glory to the heroes&amp;rdquo; Others have thanked friendly countries for voting and sharing their support for the country.</description></item><item><title>Russia fires barrage of hypersonic missiles at Odesa after celebrating patriotic holiday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ab90bf63c7d760d151266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 19:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ab90bf63c7d760d151266/</guid><description>A roundup of events on Day 76 of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine: Lithuania voted to recognize genocide; Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s vital Black Sea port of Odesa came under repeated missile attack; and the United Nations estimates the civilian death toll is much higher than records show.
Highlights The UN&amp;rsquo;s top human rights body will hold a special session on Thursday to discuss the deteriorating human rights situation in Ukraine. Lithuania has joined Canada in recognizing Russia&amp;rsquo;s actions as genocide.</description></item><item><title>CIA Director: US “sees no practical evidence” that Russia is planning nuclear strikes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627744c8e19655f5e9112b8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 04:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627744c8e19655f5e9112b8b/</guid><description>The CIA director said the United States does not see Russia preparing for a nuclear strike
Highlights CIA director William Burns said the U.S. does not see Russia preparing for a nuclear strike. The preparations for such a strike are monitored from satellites, Burns said. Burns said Putin is in such a mindset that he cannot allow himself to be defeated. The second phase of the Russian invasion of Ukraine may be &amp;ldquo;even riskier&amp;rdquo; than the first phase, Burns noted.</description></item><item><title>Russians plunder $5M farm vehicles from Ukraine -- to find they've been remotely disabled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626edb655f10285f693a0d27/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626edb655f10285f693a0d27/</guid><description>Russian troops in the occupied city of Melitopol have stolen all the equipment from a farm equipment dealership &amp;ndash; and shipped it to Chechnya, according to a Ukrainian businessman in the area.
Highlights Russian troops in the occupied city of Melitopol have stolen all the equipment from a farm equipment dealership – and shipped it to Chechnya, according to a Ukrainian businessman. But after a journey of more than 700 miles, the thieves were unable to use any of the equipment – because it had been locked remotely.</description></item><item><title>The U.N. has confirmed that an operation to evacuate people from a steel plant in the bombed-out Ukrainian city of Mariupol is underway.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ec078c074e1aef79af4f4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 17:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ec078c074e1aef79af4f4/</guid><description>ZAPORIZHZHIA, Ukraine (AP) — A long-awaited effort to evacuate people from a steel plant in the Ukrainian city of Mariupol was underway Sunday, the United Nations said, while U.S.
Highlights A long-awaited effort to evacuate people from a steel plant in the Ukrainian city of Mariupol was underway Sunday. U.S. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi revealed she visited Ukraine’s president to show unflinching American support. She is the most senior American lawmaker to travel to Ukraine since Russia invaded Ukraine on Feb.</description></item><item><title>Russian spy plane violates Swedish air space</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626dc299c92005c8b9f806c3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626dc299c92005c8b9f806c3/</guid><description>A Russian reconnaissance plane briefly violated Sweden’s airspace on Friday, Swedish defense officials said on Saturday, as the Scandinavian country
Highlights A Russian reconnaissance plane briefly violated Sweden’s airspace on Friday, Swedish defense officials said on Saturday. The plane was flying east of Bornholm, a Danish island in the Baltic, before it headed toward Swedish territory. The incident comes as the Scandinavian country ponders a bid for NATO membership after Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia forced to merge depleted units in eastern Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d6ebb27d68f068026eac0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d6ebb27d68f068026eac0/</guid><description>Russian forces are increasing the intensity of their offensive, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry says.
Highlights Women and mothers of Ukrainian fighters trapped in Mariupol plead with the government to do more to get the men out. They say they&amp;rsquo;re ready to act as a human shield, if that helps evacuate the men to safety. The number of those holed-up is unclear but it’s thought to be hundreds, including some children. The fighters’ relatives say the men are exhausted, dirty and hungry with food and water supplies running out.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine accuses Russian forces of seizing 2,000 artworks in Mariupol</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ce19263899f92fa512651/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 07:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ce19263899f92fa512651/</guid><description>City council is reportedly preparing materials to initiate criminal proceedings over mass cultural looting
Highlights Russian forces have accused Russian forces of seizing “over 2,000 artworks” from museums in the occupied city of Mariupol and moving the pieces to areas of the Russian-controlled Donbas region. The haul includes several original works by the 19th-century. Russian President Vladimir Putin has ‘lost’ the art of Russian landscape in which he rejected Ukraine’s independent identity, language and traditions,” the city council said in a statement posted on its Telegram channel on Thursday.</description></item><item><title>04/28/2022 - US left behind $7 billion of military equipment in Afghanistan after 2021 withdrawal, Pentagon report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626aa07aaec07837eb62fa57/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 14:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626aa07aaec07837eb62fa57/</guid><description>View the latest news and breaking news today for U.S., world, weather, entertainment, politics and health at CNN.com.
Highlights The US gave a total of $18.6 billion of equipment to the Afghan National Defense and Security Forces from 2005 to 2021. Equipment worth $7.12 billion remained in Afghanistan after the US military withdrawal was completed in August. The Defense Department has no plans to return to Afghanistan to &amp;ldquo;retrieve or destroy&amp;rdquo; the equipment, a report says.</description></item><item><title>Russia imposes travel ban on Kamala Harris, Mark Zuckerberg; Canadians hit too | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626328a6f8577908184616a7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 22:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626328a6f8577908184616a7/</guid><description>Russia calls its incursion a &amp;quot;special military operation&amp;quot; to demilitarise and &amp;quot;denazify&amp;quot; Ukraine. Kyiv and its Western allies reject that as a false pretext for an illegal war of aggression. | World News
Highlights Russia has also hit 61 Canadian citizens with the ‘indefinite’ travel ban. Russia had earlier this week announced the second phase of the war in Eastern Ukraine with the &amp;ldquo;Battle of Donaty&amp;rdquo; Russia calls its incursion a &amp;ldquo;special military operation&amp;rdquo; to demilitarise and &amp;ldquo;denazify&amp;rdquo; Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US State Department looking at possibly labeling Russia a state sponsor of terrorism</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e2ac84f677ed2801dcef4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 03:22:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e2ac84f677ed2801dcef4/</guid><description>US State Department officials are looking at every tool available to them to hold Russia accountable for the war in Ukraine, including the possibility of labeling Russia a state sponsor of terrorism, according to a senior administration official. The process could take weeks before a determination is made, the official said.
Highlights US State Department officials are looking at every tool available to hold Russia accountable for the war in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russian Orthodox leader backs war in Ukraine, divides faith</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625de2d6a93834d312bee831/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 22:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625de2d6a93834d312bee831/</guid><description>Patriarch Kirill has angered many in echoing the language Vladimir Putin uses to justify the Ukraine invasion.
Highlights Patriarch Kirill has become one of the war’s most prominent backers. His sermons echo, and in some cases even supply, the rhetoric that Vladimir Putin has used to justify the assault on cities and civilians. In the process, he has caused deep schisms in the global Orthodox Church, with priests in Ukraine, elsewhere in Europe and the U.</description></item><item><title>Russia warned the US about weapons shipments to Ukraine. Military analyst calls it a bluff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bbe08bd5a6a0deb6b9c3b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 07:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bbe08bd5a6a0deb6b9c3b/</guid><description>Ret. Lt. Gen. Mark Hertling discusses Russian President Putin being forced to pivot his military strategy in Ukraine due to varying terrain, and how his forces lack the adaptability to make drastic changes that may be necessary.
Highlights Ret. Gen. Mark Hertling discusses Russian President Putin being forced to pivot his military strategy in Ukraine. Hertling says Putin&amp;rsquo;s forces lack the adaptability to make drastic changes that may be necessary. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy says Ukraine captured pro-Putin politician Viktor Medvedchuk who escaped house arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62565bffb59d3b5f0770f639/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62565bffb59d3b5f0770f639/</guid><description>Zelenskyy posted a photo on social media showing a disheveled Medvedchuk seated by a radiator clasped in handcuffs.
Highlights Viktor Medvedchuk had been under house arrest on treason charges since last year. He allegedly escaped shortly after Russia launched its invasion in late February. His lawyers have denied wrongdoing. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Security Service posted a mugshot of him on its official Twitter account, along with a cavalier warning for other Russia-allied Ukrainians.</description></item><item><title>Pro-Russian vehicle convoys spark outrage in Germany</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255b4000b26eb57a01d9ba1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 17:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255b4000b26eb57a01d9ba1/</guid><description>From shop fronts spattered with paint to insults thrown in the street, attacks on the Russian community in Germany have spiked since the start of the war in Ukraine.
Highlights Attacks on the Russian community in Germany have spiked since the start of the war in Ukraine. Some Russians have staged demonstrations &amp;lsquo;against Russophobia&amp;rsquo; in Germany, which has the largest Russian diaspora in the EU. Demonstrations have sparked a backlash, with many interpreting them as a show of support for Russia&amp;rsquo;s military aggression in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Pro-Russian protesters in Germany outnumbered by Ukraine supporters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62532bb32c167a11cb067d87/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 19:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62532bb32c167a11cb067d87/</guid><description>Pro-Russians on Sunday staged demonstrations in the German cities of of Frankfurt and Hanover, where they were far outnumbered by supporters of Ukraine, local police said.
Highlights Pro-Russians staged demonstrations in German cities of of Frankfurt and Hanover, where they were far outnumbered by supporters of Ukraine. Around 3,500 Ukraine supporters gathered in Hanover in the city centre, police said. Around 235,000 Russian citizens live in Germany, according to government statistics from late 2020.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war pushes world food prices to record high</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252923055fd8134934d1105/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252923055fd8134934d1105/</guid><description>Ukraine war pushes world food prices to record high
Highlights Food and Agriculture Organization says world food prices hit an all-time high in March following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The disruption in export flows resulting from the Feb, 24 invasion and international sanctions against Russia has spurred fears of a global hunger crisis. Russia and Ukraine account for a huge share of the globe&amp;rsquo;s exports in several major commodities, including wheat, vegetable oil and corn.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainians shocked by 'crazy' scene at Chernobyl after Russian pullout reveals radioactive contamination</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251cd0e880d18b3a17a13ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251cd0e880d18b3a17a13ba/</guid><description>The sudden ear-piercing beep of a radiation meter fills the room as a Ukrainian soldier walks in. This is where Russian soldiers were living at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, and radiation levels are now higher than normal.
Highlights CNN was given exclusive access to Chernobyl nuclear power plant for the first time since it came back into Ukrainian control. Russian soldiers held Chernobyl for a month and are thought to have been operating in contaminated areas most of the time.</description></item><item><title>Lithuania expels Russian ambassador, downgrades diplomatic ties</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b1a7747e04a77047dc816/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b1a7747e04a77047dc816/</guid><description>On Monday, Lithuania downgraded its diplomatic ties with Russia and ordered the ambassador to leave the country.
Highlights Lithuania downgrades diplomatic ties with Russia and orders ambassador to leave country. Russian consulate in Klaipėda ordered to close, while Lithuania’s current ambassador to Moscow will also return to the country. Foreign Minister Gabrielius Landsbergis said: &amp;ldquo;The brutality of the Russian occupation forces has gone beyond any norms of the civilised world&amp;rdquo; Lithuania also ordered the Lithuanian ambassador to Ukraine to return to Kyiv, while the ambassador to Russia is returning to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Slovakia Expels 35 Russian Diplomats</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245d42d421e08168bc52b2d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245d42d421e08168bc52b2d/</guid><description>Change in rules set to take effect from Friday, but Kremlin decree indicates workaround for foreign currency purchases.
Highlights Most Russian troops stationed at Ukraine’s defunct Chernobyl nuclear power plant have left the site, according to state nuclear operator Energoatom. President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s decree indicates a workaround for foreign currency purchases. Foreign buyers of Russian gas will have to use special accounts at Gazprombank to pay for the import of the energy source.</description></item><item><title>Facebook fails to label 80% of posts promoting bioweapons conspiracy theory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245ab8f36c6bcab5d73fcd7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 13:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245ab8f36c6bcab5d73fcd7/</guid><description>A study found that external articles shared on the bioweapons myth were not labeled as ‘false information’ or ‘missing context’
Highlights Facebook failed to label 80% of posts promoting a conspiracy theory that the US is funding the use of bioweapons in Ukraine. Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH) studied a sample of posts from between 24 February and 14 March. The White House has condemned the myth, saying it may have been manufactured by Moscow to justify a possible use of chemical weapons against Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin disrespecting families as it stalls return of dead soldiers, says Zelenskiy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62427cfef063648fb8a5f1ff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 03:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62427cfef063648fb8a5f1ff/</guid><description>Ukrainian president criticises Russian authorities for not agreeing on scheme to have remains sent home
Highlights Ukrainian president accuses Russian authorities of disrespecting families of dead soldiers. Claims Kremlin was affording less respect to those killed during invasion of Ukraine than is usually given to dead pets. Russia has insisted on calling a “special military operation” in Ukraine. Nato last week estimated the Russian death toll to be between 7,000 and 15,000.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine is using Elon Musk’s Starlink for drone strikes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240c59180866cbc2b07ebeb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240c59180866cbc2b07ebeb/</guid><description>Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s satellites are connecting Ukraine with the internet. Starlink was conceived as a civilian program — but Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s military can also use it to guide drones and strike Russian tanks and positions.
Highlights Elon Musk tweeted: “Starlink service is now active in Ukraine. More terminals en route” Ukrainian Vice Prime Minister Mykhailo Fedorov took to Twitter to ask the Texas businessman to activate his Starlink satellites for use in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian refugee wins Jerusalem Marathon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240564881b565fb6d819218/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240564881b565fb6d819218/</guid><description>Veretska competed in the race after fleeing Ukraine in late February with her 11-year-old daughter
Highlights Valentyna Veretska, 31, of Mykolaiv, Ukraine, was the first woman across the finish line in 2:45:54. She was invited to the race after her third-place finish at the Riyadh Half Marathon in Saudi Arabia in early March. Her husband stayed behind in Ukraine, since men of fighting age (18-60) are not allowed to leave. Ageze Guadie, 33, from Israel, finished first in the men’s category, with a time of 2:37:17.</description></item><item><title>Russia reasserts right to use nuclear weapons in Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f2d8fcba1345c55860f54/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f2d8fcba1345c55860f54/</guid><description>Senior politician Dmitry Medvedev says Moscow’s nuclear doctrine does not require enemy state to use such weapons first
Highlights Russia threatens to use nuclear weapons against Ukraine, says Russian President Vladimir Putin. Russia has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest number of nuclear weapons, says Putin. Putin says Russia is prepared to use any nuclear weapons without the help of the U.S. military. Russia’s defence minister says he is ‘prepared to defend the sovereignty’ of the country and its allies in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says 400,000 citizens have been forcibly taken to Russia | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f04bd01220c9f7da9856f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 12:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f04bd01220c9f7da9856f/</guid><description>Ukraine accused Moscow on Thursday of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians from shattered Ukrainian cities to Russia, while the Kremlin has said the people relocated from Ukraine wanted to go to Russia.
Highlights Ukraine accuses Moscow of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians to Russia. The Kremlin gave nearly identical numbers for those who have been relocated, but it said they wanted to go to Russia. Some have reported shortages of food and water there.</description></item><item><title>Russians transiting Lithuania to be met with Ukraine war photos: ‘do you approve of this?’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ea09d181a4558dfa1a031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ea09d181a4558dfa1a031/</guid><description>Vilnius railway station has set up a photo exhibition, displaying images from the war in Ukraine to passengers on Russia&amp;hellip;
Highlights Vilnius railway station has set up a photo exhibition, displaying images from the war in Ukraine to passengers on Russian transit trains between Moscow and Kaliningrad. The photos, which show people injured during the war, mourning people, as well as destroyed buildings, also bear inscriptions in Russian: &amp;ldquo;Today, Putin is killing the peaceful population of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Canadian sniper ‘Wali’ alive in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623abb694403b29c031ad60d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 06:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623abb694403b29c031ad60d/</guid><description>Russian reports had said former Canadian soldier had been quickly killed in fighting
Highlights Reports of a famed Canadian sniper’s demise at the hand of Russian forces in Ukraine have proved premature. The man known as “Wali” spoke with the Star in a video interview Tuesday in which he said he had been “the last to learn” of his own death. The 40-year-old Quebec soldier, who asked that his real name not be used, left in early March to join Ukrainian forces on the front lines.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Russia's deadline passes with Ukraine refusing to lay down arms and surrender Mariupol</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238f87d1cacb75a71f4c666/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 22:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238f87d1cacb75a71f4c666/</guid><description>Ukrainian citizens will &amp;quot;have to speak up and respond to this or that form of compromise&amp;quot;, President Volodymyr Zelenskyy says.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy says security &amp;lsquo;compromises&amp;rsquo; to end Russian invasion will need referendum. Issues of concern include security guarantees offered in lieu of NATO membership. Another curfew lasting 40 hours from Monday night has been announced in the capital Kyiv. Russia has continued to bombard the devastated Mariupol and intensified its attacks on Kyiv, while also targeting another port city - Odesa - for the first time.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine suspends 11 political parties with links to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623841b04519b969f5435a62/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 09:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623841b04519b969f5435a62/</guid><description>Zelenskiy says parties such as Viktor Medvedchuk’s Opposition Platform for Life are ‘aimed at division or collusion’
Highlights Eleven Ukrainian political parties have been suspended because of links with Russia. Ukrainian president Volodymyr Zelenskiy says they are &amp;lsquo;aimed at division or collusion&amp;rsquo; Most of the parties affected were small, but one of them has 44 seats in the 450-seat parliament. The Opposition Platform for Life, Ukraine’s biggest opposition party, is led by Viktor Medvedchuk, a pro-Moscow oligarch with close ties to the Russian president, Vladimir Putin.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine crisis: claims Mariupol women and children forcibly sent to Russia | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62377c4f724c580c6303ab2e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 19:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62377c4f724c580c6303ab2e/</guid><description>Thousands of resident illegally taken across border, says Mariupol council, as reports emerge its art school has been bombed while 400 were sheltering inside
Highlights Mariupol authorities say Russian forces have deported several thousand residents to Russia. Reports emerge that Russian forces bombed an art school where 400 people were taking shelter. The claims have not been independently verified, but the council’s statement is one of several reports about residents being taken to Russia, where authorities have referred to “refugees” arriving from the strategic port.</description></item><item><title>Russian mercenaries in Ukraine linked to far-right extremists</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62376f2abc630ac53fd2951d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 18:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62376f2abc630ac53fd2951d/</guid><description>Wagner Group connected to white supremacists, Tech against Terrorism investigation finds
Highlights The study was carried out in conjunction with the Russian Defence Ministry and the U.S. Department of Defence. The study has been carried out under the guise of the ‘denazification’ of the country’s military, the “deny military” of the nation, “theatre” and “vigorous” forces, such as the government, are “almost certainly” aimed at the ’deny” national security forces, the military, and the government.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskiy calls for peace talks with Moscow, urges Swiss to target oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62371bb76b9730d766122619/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 12:19:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62371bb76b9730d766122619/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy called on Saturday for comprehensive peace talks with Moscow and also urged Switzerland to do more to crack down on Russian oligarchs who he said were helping wage war on his country with their money.
Highlights Britain says Russia now pursuing strategy of attrition that could exacerbate humanitarian crisis. Russia says its hypersonic missiles have destroyed a large underground depot for missiles and aircraft ammunition in the western Ivano-Frankivsk region.</description></item><item><title>Russian Cosmonauts Enter Space Station Wearing Flight Suits with Colors Similar to Ukraine Flag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235ba5df00b4edf5590c8c0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235ba5df00b4edf5590c8c0/</guid><description>A three-man crew of Russian cosmonauts entered the International Space Station wearing bright yellow flight suits with blue trim. The colors are similar to those used on the flag of Ukraine, which Russia invaded last month.
Highlights Three Russian cosmonauts entered the International Space Station wearing bright yellow flight suits with blue trim. The colors are similar to those used on the flag of Ukraine, which Russia invaded last month. The three-man crew will return to Earth on March 30 carrying Anton Shkaplerov, Pyotr Dubrov and Mark Vande Hei back to Earth.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: Arnold Schwarzenegger's anti-war video trends on Russian social media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234d92ebf7812e4e7882ae4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 19:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234d92ebf7812e4e7882ae4/</guid><description>In the video the actor warns Russians they are being fed misinformation over the Ukraine war.
Highlights The actor warns Russians they are being fed misinformation over the Ukraine war. &amp;ldquo;The strength and the heart of the Russian people have always inspired me,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;That is why I hope that you will let me tell you the truth about the war in Ukraine,&amp;rdquo; the actor says in a video posted on YouTube.</description></item><item><title>Germany warns against Russia’s Kaspersky anti-virus software</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231b8627e8769dc8754ba10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 10:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231b8627e8769dc8754ba10/</guid><description>Kaspersky could be implicated in hacking assaults amid Russia’s war in Ukraine, BSI says. Russia&amp;rsquo;s military and intelligence activities in Ukraine mean there is “a considerable risk of a successful IT attack’, agency
Highlights Cyber security agency BSI warns of &amp;lsquo;considerable risk&amp;rsquo; of successful IT attack. Companies and operators of critical infrastructure are particularly vulnerable but individuals could also be hit. The United States banned government agencies from using Kaspersky software as early as 2017.</description></item><item><title>McDonald's will temporarily close 850 restaurants in Russia, nearly 2 weeks after Putin invaded Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia after the company took heat for staying silent on the war in Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s says it will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia. The decision comes nearly two weeks after Russian forces invaded Ukraine. PepsiCo, Starbucks and Coco-Cola also announced similar step-backs from the country. McDonald&amp;rsquo;s restaurants in Russia and Ukraine account for 2% of its systemwide sales, 9% of revenue and 3% of operating income.</description></item><item><title>Zara and Paypal suspend business in Russia over Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62239a0dc3a04433ebcea83d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 17:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62239a0dc3a04433ebcea83d/</guid><description>Inditex, which owns Zara and several other major brands, will close all of its 502 stores in Russia.
Highlights Inditex, which owns Zara and several other major brands, will close all of its 502 stores in Russia. &amp;ldquo;We believe that such actions will motivate the youth and active population of Russia to proactively stop the disgraceful military aggression,&amp;rdquo; Mr Fedorov said in a letter posted on his Twitter account on Friday.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine still has 'significant majority' of its military aircraft -U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223455e5b1741458a5adda2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223455e5b1741458a5adda2/</guid><description>Ukraine still has a &amp;quot;significant majority&amp;quot; of its military aircraft available nine days after Russian forces started their invasion of the country, a U.S. defense official said on Friday.
Highlights Ukraine still has a “significant majority” of its military aircraft available nine days after Russian forces started their invasion of the country, a U.S. defense official said on Friday. The Pentagon has established a new hotline with Russia’s ministry of defense to prevent “miscalculation, military incidents and escalation” in the region.</description></item><item><title>Russian forces driven out of Ukrainian city of Mykolayiv, governor says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222fff07bd262783764044d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 06:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222fff07bd262783764044d/</guid><description>Russian forces were driven out of the Ukrainian city of Mykolayiv after attacking it on Friday but fighting continued around the city outskirts, regional governor Vitaliy Kim said.
Highlights Russian forces driven out of Ukrainian city of Mykolayiv after attacking it on Friday. Fighting continued around the city outskirts, regional governor Vitaliy Kim said. Russian forces were driven out but fighting continued around city outskirts of city, he said. Ukrainian city is one of Russia&amp;rsquo;s most densely populated cities in eastern Ukraine, the region has been hit by pro-Russian separatists.</description></item><item><title>On Monday, near Kyiv, chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay and his team were attacked. Camera operator Richie Mockler took two rounds to his body armour, Stuart was wounded.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222d537abe5cc55cf5cf389/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 03:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222d537abe5cc55cf5cf389/</guid><description>On Monday, near Kyiv, chief correspondent Stuart Ramsay and his team were attacked. Camera operator Richie Mockler took two rounds to his body armour, Stuart was wounded. Their experience illustrates the scale of the mayhem and violence as Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion enters a new and deadlier phase.
Highlights As with many wars, the Russian invasion of Ukraine changes constantly, battlefields appear suddenly in previously quiet areas, kinetic places go silent. The journey took us hours as we left central Kyiv through a city now being strengthened with extra soldiers.</description></item><item><title>Top Russian general killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</guid><description>Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky, the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division, was killed in fighting in Ukraine earlier this week.
Highlights Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky was the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division. His death was confirmed by a local officers’ organization in the Krasnodar region in southern Russia. The circumstances of his death were not immediately clear. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>The teenager that tracked Elon Musk's jet is now tracking Russian oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</guid><description>Jack Sweeney, a Florida teen who tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online has a new aviation-themed target: Russian oligarchs and billionaires.
Highlights Jack Sweeney, 19, tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online. He recently launched two new automated Twitter handles — @RUOligarchJets and @Putinjet — following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The two profiles have amassed nearly 300,000 followers combined and provide nearly live updates of the private jets&amp;rsquo; movements. Russia&amp;rsquo;s oligarchs face economic chaos at home and punishment by the West after President Vladimir Putin ordered his troops into Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>China Asked Russia to Delay Ukraine War Until After Olympics, U.S. Officials Say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622024296fff817336c459c6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 02:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622024296fff817336c459c6/</guid><description>A Western intelligence report indicates that Chinese officials had some level of direct knowledge about President Vladimir V. Putin’s war plans or intentions.
Highlights The ambitious joint statement that the two nations issued during that meeting alarmed American and European officials. It was the first time China had explicitly sided with Russia on issues concerning NATO and European security. A Western intelligence report indicates that Chinese officials had some level of direct knowledge about President Vladimir V.</description></item><item><title>Georgia to apply ‘immediately’ for EU membership: Ruling party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220108a46bb2e085fd04a12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:49:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220108a46bb2e085fd04a12/</guid><description>Georgia will “immediately” apply for EU membership, the Black Sea nation’s ruling party said Wednesday, a day after the European Parliament backed war-torn
Highlights Georgia will “immediately” apply for EU membership, the Black Sea nation’s ruling party said Wednesday. Decision follows a day after the European Parliament backed war-torn Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s bid to apply for membership. The vote was seen in Georgia as a window of opportunity to advance its own EU aspirations.</description></item><item><title>Russian Police jail kids aged 7-11 for bringing flowers &amp;amp; “No to War” signs to Ukraine’s embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fc14b51949d11cab426fe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fc14b51949d11cab426fe/</guid><description>In an emergency session, the General Assembly voted 141-5 to condemn Russia and demand that it end its war in Ukraine. Also, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defense minister accused Russia of deploying “the criminal tactics of long-range shelling of peaceful cities,” and Moscow police jailed children who carried &amp;quot;No to War&amp;quot; signs.
Highlights Russia claims it has taken over the southern Ukrainian city of Kherson, but Ukrainian officials sharply dispute this. Russia shuts down two leading Russian media outlets over critical coverage of the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Cyberattack on NATO could trigger collective defence clause - official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dff6be9fbb6a79c99423d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dff6be9fbb6a79c99423d/</guid><description>A cyberattack on a NATO member state could trigger Article 5, its collective defence clause, a NATO official said on Monday, amid concerns that chaos in cyberspace around Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine could spill over into other territories.
Highlights A cyberattack on a NATO member state could trigger Article 5, its collective defence clause. The military alliance has for years made clear that a serious cyberattack could trigger the clause, but such a scenario has so far been largely hypothetical.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine establishing foreign legion for volunteers from abroad - President</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bf7625119d14fa45e97a7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bf7625119d14fa45e97a7/</guid><description>Ukraine is establishing a foreign &amp;quot;international&amp;quot; legion for volunteers from abroad, President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said on Sunday.
Highlights Ukraine is establishing a foreign &amp;ldquo;international&amp;rdquo; legion for volunteers from abroad, President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said on Sunday. Ukraine is established a &amp;ldquo;foreign legion&amp;rdquo; for volunteers, the president said. Zelenskyy said in a statement that he is still in the capital, in Kyiv, Ukraine February 25, 2022 in this screengrab obtained from a handout video.</description></item><item><title>Putin puts Russia's nuclear forces on alert, cites sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bbfe519af4fd00ee355b4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 18:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bbfe519af4fd00ee355b4/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Sunday said that Ukraine and Russia would conduct the first diplomatic talks since the Kremlin-launched invasion.
Highlights Russian forces are using siege tactics against Chernihiv, a senior defense official says. The move raises the specter of more civilian casualties as the fighting worsens in Ukraine. The Pentagon says the Russian military still has not seized control of any Ukrainian cities. Russia has put about two-thirds of the fighting force it had amassed around Ukraine into the country already, the official adds.</description></item><item><title>Officials: Defenders of Ukrainian island may still be alive and now POWs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b406b5688d1ccead3a1c7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 09:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b406b5688d1ccead3a1c7/</guid><description>The defenders of the small Ukrainian island of Zmiinyi in the Black Sea may still be alive, according to a statement released on Saturday by the State Border Guard Service of Ukraine (SBGSU).
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine is encountering &amp;ldquo;stiffer than expected&amp;rdquo; resistance from the Ukrainian military and unexpected difficulties supplying its forces. Russia is suffering heavier losses in personnel, armor and aircraft than expected, US officials say. Russia has yet to establish air supremacy over Ukraine, a senior defense official says.</description></item><item><title>Anti-war sentiment grows in Russia despite govt crackdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</guid><description>As Russian troops were closing in on the Ukrainian capital, more and more Russians at home were speaking out against the invasion even as the government&amp;rsquo;s official rhetoric grew increasingly harsher
Highlights At least 460 people in 34 cities were detained over anti-war protests on Saturday, including over 200 in Moscow. An online petition to stop the attack on Ukraine garnered over 780,000 signatures by Saturday evening. A prominent contemporary art museum in Moscow called Garage announced Saturday it was halting its work on exhibitions and postponing them “until the human and political tragedy that is unfolding in Ukraine has ceased&amp;quot; Dmitry Medvedev said Moscow may respond to Western sanctions by opting out of the last nuclear arms deal with the U.</description></item><item><title>For the first time ever, the NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia's ongoing invasion of Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621945ea275bd3d32f600f59/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 21:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621945ea275bd3d32f600f59/</guid><description>For the first time, the NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s ongoing invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The force consists of land, air, sea and special operations forces from the allies. It&amp;rsquo;s not clear how many troops the response force will contain. US President Joe Biden has been clear that US troops are deploying to eastern Europe to help bolster NATO countries nervous about Russia&amp;rsquo;s aggressive actions, and they will not be fighting in Ukraine, which is not a member of the NATO alliance.</description></item><item><title>Patreon suspends donation page for nonprofit giving body armor to Ukrainian army</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218900507807c94a24b695c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218900507807c94a24b695c/</guid><description>Come Back Alive is looking to use money it has collected through Patreon to distribute armor and helmets to soldiers. Now it&amp;rsquo;s abilities are limited.
Highlights Russia invaded Ukraine late Wednesday, and over $300,000 rolled in, including many donations of less than $1,000. A nonprofit organization collecting donations to distribute body armor, medical kits, and helmets to Ukrainian soldiers. The organization last received money from its Patreon page in August, its director, Taras Chmut, told CNBC in an interview.</description></item><item><title>Explosions are heard in Ukraine port city of Mariupol: Fears shelling is underway - Public</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217bcc78ade673d3bc36b82/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217bcc78ade673d3bc36b82/</guid><description>PUBLIC UK Bring the Latest News Exclusives, Sport, Celebrities, Showbiz, Politics, Business, Lifestyle, Travel and Tech info for you 24/7.
Highlights Explosions had been heard within the Ukrainian port town of Mariupol, as fears mount that shelling is underway. The explosions come just hours after the U.S. warned the Ukrainian govt that Putin’s troops are ‘in a position to move now’ with an invasion of Ukraine, with 80 according to cent of Russian infantrymen now assembled across the nation in assault positions.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine moves to impose state of emergency as U.S., allies pressure Russia with sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</guid><description>Russia had all of the necessary military capabilities Wednesday to launch a full-scale invasion into neighboring Ukraine, a senior U.S. defense official said.
Highlights At least five Ukrainian websites were hit by cyberattacks ahead of state of emergency vote. Russia evacuates its embassy in Kyiv, state news agency reports. U.S., Europe and other allies impose first salvo of sanctions on Moscow. Secretary of State Antony Blinken cancels a meeting with Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister.</description></item><item><title>White House calls Russian moves on Ukraine an invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country — a move that could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S.
Highlights Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country. The move could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S. said an invasion was already underway there. Western leaders said Tuesday that Russian troops have moved into rebel-held areas in eastern Ukraine after Putin&amp;rsquo;s recognition of their independence.</description></item><item><title>Germany halts approval of gas pipeline Nord Stream 2 after Russia’s actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</guid><description>Germany on Tuesday halted the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring natural gas from Russia directly to Europe.
Highlights Germany halts certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline to bring gas to Europe. The pipeline is designed to bring natural gas directly to Europe from Russia. Germany&amp;rsquo;s president said the country would not accept the recognition of the two pro-Russian separatist regions in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>UK to impose sanctions on Russia over ‘attack on Ukraine’s sovereignty’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214ef4f2af705c3e3ca77ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214ef4f2af705c3e3ca77ac/</guid><description>Boris Johnson announces plans after Vladimir Putin backs independence for breakaway states and sends troops into Ukrainian territory
Highlights UK to sign off a package of sanctions against Russia on Tuesday morning. Initial signs were that the package would target ‘those complicit in the violation of Ukraine’s territorial integrity’ Russia has massed about 190,000 troops – with separatists accounting for another 30,000. The UK has been in close discussions with the EU and the US about launching coordinated sanctions.</description></item><item><title>U.S. has intel that Russian commanders have orders to proceed with Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</guid><description>The intelligence indicates that commanders on the ground making specific plans for how they would maneuver in their sector of the battlefield.
Highlights U.S. intelligence indicates Russian commanders have received orders to proceed with an invasion of Ukraine. Defense minister of Belarus announced Russia will be extending military drills near Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northern borders. Russia has massed roughly 150,000 troops, warplanes and equipment on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s three sides, escalating tensions with neighboring country.</description></item><item><title>More than 130,000 Russian troops now staged outside Ukraine: U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 01:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</guid><description>Some airlines cancelled flights to the Ukrainian capital and troops there unloaded fresh shipments of weapons from NATO members Sunday, as its president sought to project confidence in the face of U.S. warnings of possible invasion within days by a growing number of Russian forces.
Highlights NEW: U.S. intelligence officials believe targeting the military exercise is just one of multiple options that Russia has weighed as a possibility for a false pretext for an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky claims Vladimir Putin is putting illegal pressure on Britain's political system</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 13:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffc958b52c5883869cddfd/</guid><description>Mikhail Khodorkovsky says Russian meddling is happening &amp;quot;directly and indirectly&amp;quot; in Britain - and it must be stopped.
Highlights Exiled Russian oligarch Mikhail Khodorkovsky calls out &amp;lsquo;dangerous, illegal&amp;rsquo; pressure by Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;cronies&amp;rsquo; in the UK. Former head of oil giant Yukos was imprisoned for eight years by Putin&amp;rsquo;s government for tax evasion and theft in a controversial case. He says Putin is &amp;ldquo;capable of all sorts of actions, including ill-judged ones&amp;rdquo; Putin is &amp;lsquo;in fact afraid&amp;rsquo; of a war with Ukraine, says ex-Russian oligarch.</description></item><item><title>U.S. accuses Russia of planning "staged" video as pretext for Ukraine attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc532c1271b37261546b23/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 22:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc532c1271b37261546b23/</guid><description>The U.S. has not provided specific evidence for its claims.
Highlights The U.S. says Russia is considering staging a &amp;ldquo;fabricated attack&amp;rdquo; by Ukrainian forces, an official says. The official says Russian intelligence services are &amp;ldquo;intimately involved&amp;rdquo; in the planning of the fabricated attack. It&amp;rsquo;s the second time in recent weeks that the Biden administration has publicly accused Russia of plotting an operation that would serve as a pretext to invade Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Soldier Opens Fire, Kills Five Soldiers at Military Base</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2b4dca174bcde43071f3c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2b4dca174bcde43071f3c/</guid><description>The attacker opened fire with an assault rifle then fled the scene.
Highlights A Ukrainian National Guard soldier opened fire on security guards at a military factory in central Ukraine for reasons unknown, killing five people and wounding five others before fleeing. Interior Minister Denys Monastyrskiy named the soldier as Artem Ryabchuk and said he would “bear the strictest responsibility provided by law”. He said investigators would look into how the soldier passed a medical commission that allowed him access to weapons.</description></item><item><title>Norway's PM says Russia build-up is 'a sign of weakness'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1eea8cda0a75a8fbe2fe4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1eea8cda0a75a8fbe2fe4/</guid><description>UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Norway’s prime minister, whose country borders Russia and is a founding member of NATO, said Wednesday he believes it’s “a sign of weakness” that President Vladimir Putin has to express Moscow’s political views by an “extraordinary” military buildup.
Summary UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Norway’s prime minister, whose country borders Russia and is a founding member of NATO, said Wednesday he believes it’s “a sign of weakness” that President Vladimir Putin has to express Moscow’s political views by an “extraordinary” military buildup.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine urges calm, saying Russian invasion not imminent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s leaders sought Tuesday to reassure the nation that an invasion from neighboring Russia was not imminent, even as they acknowledged the threat is real and received a shipment of U.S.
Summary British Prime Minister Boris Johnson also said he is prepared to send troops to protect NATO allies in Europe. Fighting between Ukrainian forces and Russia-backed rebels has killed over 14,000 people, and efforts to reach a settlement have stalled.</description></item><item><title>Biden touts 'total unanimity' with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f048dcc2cbcb7e97455ead/</guid><description>President Biden said Monday he and European leaders are in agreement following a call to discuss strategy in response to Russia’s military build-up along the Ukrainian border.
Summary Total unanimity with all the European leaders. We’ll talk about it later,” Biden said after a previously planned meeting with administration officials to discuss lowering prices. Biden met for 80 minutes earlier Monday with European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, European Council President Charles Michel, French President Emmanuel Macron Emmanuel Jean-Michel MacronDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;rsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine Biden huddling with European leaders on Russia&amp;rsquo;s military buildup near Ukraine MORE, British Prime Minister Boris Johnson Boris JohnsonDefense &amp;amp; National Security — Pentagon puts 8,500 troops on high alert Biden touts &amp;rsquo;total unanimity&amp;rsquo; with European leaders after call on Russia-Ukraine UK scrapping testing requirements for vaccinated arrivals MORE, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz, Italian Prime Minister Mario Draghi, NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg and Polish President Andrzej Duda.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s amateur army: Thousands of young civilians are drafted into the military and trained for war in desperate bid to fend off Putin’s 100,000 well-trained troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</guid><description>Young Ukrainian men and women, some as young as 21, have been taking part in Kyiv Territorial Defence unit training over the weekend, as they prepare for a possible conflict with Moscow.
Summary In the event of a potential invasion by Russia, these youngsters will be part of the country&amp;rsquo;s civil resistance that will carry on the fight against Russian soldiers if the Ukrainian military is overwhelmed. Tatiana, who is enrolled in a military reserve program, joined hundreds of other young Ukrainians in a Kyiv Territorial Defence Unit training exercise on Saturday in a snow-covered forest in Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Ireland tells Russia that naval exercises off our coast 'not welcome'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 06:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef9214f2587d233efac532/</guid><description>Mr Coveney said that Foreign Ministers will be pushing Russia to &amp;quot;defuse tensions&amp;quot; along the Ukrainian border, where it has amassed troops in recent &amp;hellip;
Summary The Government has told Russia that naval exercises off the Irish coast are &amp;ldquo;not welcome&amp;rdquo;, but Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney has accepted that they are legal. Russian naval exercises are due to take place in early February, approximately 240km off the southwest coast and within Ireland’s Exclusive Economic Zone (EEZ) but not in Ireland’s territorial waters.</description></item><item><title>Erdogan Warns Russia Against Invading Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s supply of combat drones to Ukraine has drawn the wrath of Russia.
Summary Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Tuesday warned Russia against invading Ukraine, calling the former Soviet republic a &amp;ldquo;powerful&amp;rdquo; country with international friends. Speaking to Turkish reporters in Albania, Erdogan said he intended to discuss the rising tensions with Russian President Vladimir Putin. &amp;ldquo;You cannot handle these things by saying &amp;lsquo;I will invade something, I will take it&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; Turkish media quoted Erdogan as saying.</description></item><item><title>Germany signals it could halt gas pipeline if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e78d8fbf3f4b130cb14066/</guid><description>Germany signalled on Tuesday that it could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if Moscow invades Ukraine, and Western nations rallied behind Kyiv over a Russian troop buildup that has stoked fears of war.
Summary As fears of conflict rose, Britain said this week it had begun supplying Ukraine with anti-tank weapons, Canada&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister visited Ukraine and German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock held talks in Moscow and Kyiv to try to ease tensions.</description></item><item><title>White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine 'at any point'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7469359f5ca923e505478/</guid><description>White House press secretary Jen Psaki told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S.
Summary White House press secretary Jen Psaki Jen PsakiBiden commends wireless giants for delaying 5G rollout near key airports Briefing in brief: Free COVID-19 test site in testing phase before launch Wednesday White House says Russia could launch attack in Ukraine &amp;lsquo;at any point&amp;rsquo; MORE told reporters on Tuesday that the U.S. believes that Russia could carry out an attack on Ukraine “at any point,” underscoring the immediacy of the threat should Moscow decide to take action.</description></item><item><title>Russia cannot 'tolerate' NATO's 'gradual invasion' of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;quot;tolerate&amp;quot; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;quot;gradual invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine.
Summary Russian President Vladimir Putin Vladimir Vladimirovich PutinRussia cannot &amp;rsquo;tolerate&amp;rsquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;gradual invasion&amp;rsquo; of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says Fears of Russian invasion of Ukraine rise despite US push for diplomacy Overnight Defense &amp;amp; National Security — US says Russia prepping &amp;lsquo;false flag&amp;rsquo; operation MORE&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;ldquo;tolerate&amp;rdquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;ldquo;gradual invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US intelligence indicates Russia preparing operation to justify invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</guid><description>The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.
Summary Washington (CNN) The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>