<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>company on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/company/</link><description>Recent content in company on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 09:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spotify CEO condemns Rogan's use of racial slurs, but says company won't be 'silencing' him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200e28519f8be851f2333a1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200e28519f8be851f2333a1/</guid><description>Daniel Ek, the chief executive of Spotify, addressed Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s past use of racial slurs on Sunday night, telling staff in a memo that while he found the comments &amp;quot;incredibly hurtful&amp;quot; and inconsistent with company values, he did not believe &amp;quot;silencing&amp;quot; the podcaster was the answer.
Highlights Daniel Ek, the chief executive of Spotify, addressed Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s past use of racial slurs on Sunday night. He told staff in a memo that while he found the comments &amp;ldquo;incredibly hurtful&amp;rdquo; and inconsistent with company values, he did not believe &amp;ldquo;silencing&amp;rdquo; the podcaster was the answer.</description></item><item><title>Amazon increases the price of Prime nearly 17% to $139 per year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</guid><description>Amazon hasn&amp;rsquo;t raised the price of its Prime membership program since 2018, when it increased from $99 to $119, the current fee.
Highlights Amazon is raising the price of its annual Prime membership to $139 from $119. Amazon also raised the monthly price of a Prime membership from $12.99 to $14.99. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s annual increase amounts to about a 17% rise in price. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock rose more than 14% at one point on Thursday in extended trading.</description></item><item><title>Spotify stocks fall as executives seek to reassure amid Rogan controversy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</guid><description>Subscriber outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter earnings as the company’s shares fell nearly 18% in late trading
Highlights Spotify forecast current-quarter subscribers lower than Wall Street expectations. Company&amp;rsquo;s shares fell as much as 18% in late trading after Spotify reported the subscriber outlook. The outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter revenue, which came in higher than analysts’ estimates. CEO Daniel Ek acknowledged the Joe Rogan controversy at the outset of the earnings conference call. He said he was proud of the steps Spotify took following the concerns raised by the medical and scientific communities and he said policies were developed with input from external and internal and external exports.</description></item><item><title>Neil Young Wants His Music Off Spotify Over Joe Rogan Vaccine Misinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 07:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</guid><description>Neil Young demanded that Spotify remove his music, citing its spread of vaccine misinformation via &amp;quot;The Joe Rogan Experience&amp;quot; podcast.
Summary Neil Young wants his music pulled from Spotify, citing the spread of vaccine misinformation on the popular Joe Rogan Experience podcast as the cause. “They can have Rogan or Young. Not both,” Young wrote in an open letter to his management team and record label posted to his Neil Young Archives website, according to Rolling Stone.</description></item><item><title>Shkreli ordered to return $64M, is barred from drug industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Martin Shkreli must return $64.6 million in profits he and his former company reaped from jacking up the price and monopolizing the market for a lifesaving drug, a federal judge ruled Friday while also barring the provocative, imprisoned ex-CEO from the pharmaceutical industry for the rest of his life.
Summary FILE - Former Turing Pharmaceuticals CEO Martin Shkreli attends the House Committee on Oversight and Reform Committee hearing on Capitol Hill in Washington, Feb.</description></item><item><title>Ford beats out Tesla to become the auto industry’s top growth stock in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3f08f7a56bd392cbecb87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3f08f7a56bd392cbecb87/</guid><description>Ford accomplished this largely thanks to a leadership change in October 2020 from industry outsider Jim Hackett to auto veteran Jim Farley.
Summary In this article FThe all-electric Ford F-150 Lightning truck during an augmented reality presentation at the Motor Bella Auto Show in Pontiac, Michigan, on Tuesday, Sept. 21, 2021. He told CNBC the day before that the company halted reservations of the F-150 Lightning after they hit 200,000 units.</description></item></channel></rss>