<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>company on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/company/</link><description>Recent content in company on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:17:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Investors force Home Depot to review wood-sourcing policy over logging concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c6a2fffa2675311b3dfb1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c6a2fffa2675311b3dfb1/</guid><description>Environmental science and conservation news
Highlights Some of Home Depot&amp;rsquo;s plywood is allegedly sourced from vulnerable forests in Ecuador’s Chocó region and the Brazilian Cerrado. A proposal passed requiring the home improvement giant to reevaluate policies related to sustainability certifications of wood suppliers. Investors and conservationists have pressured Home Depot to clean up its supply chain. Home Depot has around 2,300 locations across North America and a significant wood importer. The company doesn’t offer specific figures on how much it imports from where wood comes from, but has no specific limits on where it buys it.</description></item><item><title>U.S. imposes sanctions on 27 Gazprombank executives, Russian TV stations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278bf2b7b8694a859a95612/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 07:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278bf2b7b8694a859a95612/</guid><description>The United States on Sunday unveiled sanctions against three Russian television stations, banned Americans from providing accounting and consulting services to Russians, and sanctioned executives from Gazprombank to punish Moscow for its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights U.S. unveils sanctions against three Russian television stations, banned Americans from providing accounting and consulting services to Russians. Measures leveled against Gazprombank executives were the first involving the giant Russian gas exporter. Eight executives from Sberbank, which holds one-third of Russia&amp;rsquo;s banking assets, were added to the sanctions list.</description></item><item><title>Court in Fiji approves U.S. warrant to seize Russian-owned mega-yacht</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273e9a3de069e6f5988e8b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273e9a3de069e6f5988e8b1/</guid><description>American and Fijian officials claim the $325 million Amadea is owned by sanctioned billionaire Suleiman Kerimov.
Highlights American and Fijian officials claim the $325 million Amadea is the property of Suleiman Kerimov, an oligarch who built his fortune on gold mining. Kerimov was sanctioned in March by the United States, United Kingdom and European Union in response to the Russian invasion of Ukraine. The Cayman Islands-flagged yacht berthed in Fiji on April 13, according to local reports and maritime analytics website Marine Traffic.</description></item><item><title>Levi Strauss to reimburse abortion travel for employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272dec9a5f9b96fe31e7d26/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272dec9a5f9b96fe31e7d26/</guid><description>Levi Strauss &amp;amp; Co said on Wednesday it will reimburse travel expenses for its full- and part-time employees who need to travel to another state for health care services, including abortions.
Highlights Levi Strauss &amp;amp; Co. will reimburse travel expenses for its full- and part-time employees who need to travel to another state for health care services, including abortions. The apparel company best known for its jeans is the latest U.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Workers Won't Get Paid for COVID leave anymore</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e420c65d258013cf1bb9b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 08:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e420c65d258013cf1bb9b/</guid><description>All U.S.-based Amazon workers who test positive for Covid-19 will now get up to five days of excused, unpaid leave, the company told workers in a notice.
Highlights Amazon is cutting paid time off for front-line U.S. workers who test positive for Covid-19, effective Monday. The e-commerce giant has slowly pulled back its Covid policies as vaccines have become more widely available and the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention changed its guidance.</description></item><item><title>Judge rules Amazon must reinstate fired warehouse worker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e8bc09ce7c6afb8c0be1a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 10:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e8bc09ce7c6afb8c0be1a/</guid><description>A judge has ruled Amazon must reinstate a former employee who was fired in the early days of the pandemic after leading a protest calling for the company to do more to protect workers against COVID-19
Highlights A judge has ruled Amazon must reinstate a former employee who was fired in the early days of the pandemic after leading a protest calling for the company to do more to protect workers against COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>U.S. consumer bureau sues TransUnion, executive for continued deceptive marketing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256b000be6d1668e32d0584/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256b000be6d1668e32d0584/</guid><description>A U.S. consumer watchdog on Tuesday sued TransUnion and one of its former executives, accusing the credit reporting agency of tricking consumers into making recurring payments after the company was fined in 2017 for similar activity.
Highlights Consumer Financial Protection Bureau sues TransUnion and one of its former executives. Suit accuses the credit reporting agency of tricking consumers into making recurring payments after the company was fined in 2017 for similar activity.</description></item><item><title>Shell to exit joint ventures with Gazprom and pull out of Nord Stream 2</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e46ed2e1ac0f8f1fb805a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 16:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e46ed2e1ac0f8f1fb805a/</guid><description>British oil major to exit joint ventures with Gazprom after BP pledged to sell its 20% Rosneft stake
Highlights Shell said it would ‘exit its joint ventures with Gazprom and related entities’, which are worth about $3bn. The oil company said its staff in Ukraine and other countries have been working together to manage the company’s response to the crisis locally. Shell will also end its involvement in the Nord Stream 2 pipeline project, in which it holds a 10% stake worth $1bn.</description></item><item><title>OpenSea confirms hacker stole NFTs 'worth £1.25m' from 32 users</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213d68af4ee53c4e95e0176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 18:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213d68af4ee53c4e95e0176/</guid><description>According to the blockchain analysis company PeckShield, at least 254 non-fungible tokens were stolen as a result of an unknown attack.
Highlights At least 254 non-fungible tokens (NFTs) were stolen from dozens of users on the popular trading platform OpenSea. The company&amp;rsquo;s chief executive confirmed on Twitter that the company believed the hacker made $1.7m (£1.25m) from selling the stolen NFTs. The thefts have prompted a scare in the cryptocurrency community, where many people are attempting to realise enormous gains by investing in largely unregulated assets.</description></item><item><title>Lawsuit accuses Cincinnati health staffing company of labor trafficking</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e11463a5faaf5bd96139b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 09:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e11463a5faaf5bd96139b/</guid><description>A health care staffing company based in Cincinnati is being sued by workers it recruited from the Philippines, who are accusing the company of violating federal and state human trafficking laws.
Highlights Fast-growing Health Carousel is headquartered in Cincinnati, has an Austin Landing office, and in recent years has acquired other Dayton-area staffing firms. The lawsuit was first filed in March 2020 and is seeking class action status. The plaintiffs are still working on getting certification for their proposed class action lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s brain chip company, Neuralink, faces animal abuse claims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c876ee99a0e206c987ae1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 05:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c876ee99a0e206c987ae1/</guid><description>An animal welfare group alleges that monkey test subjects endured ‘crude surgeries’ and ‘extreme suffering’
Highlights Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s brain chip company Neuralink is defending itself against claims that monkeys were tortured and left to die in horrific experiments at its facilities. The group Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine (PCRM) said the research caused “extreme suffering” in monkeys. PCRM obtained hundreds of pages of health records, necropsy reports and other documents related to the $1.</description></item><item><title>Hertz files thousands of car theft complaints against customers every year. A judge ruled they have to make that data public.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205c2d66c30d55dbe9e9b5f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205c2d66c30d55dbe9e9b5f/</guid><description>The company already faces 230 claims by people who allege they were falsely arrested for stealing rental cars based on erroneous reports from Hertz.
Highlights Hertz must make public the number of renters it accuses of stealing its cars. The company already faces 230 claims in bankruptcy court by people who say they were falsely arrested for stealing rental cars based on erroneous reports. CBS News&amp;rsquo; legal team filed a formal objection to the attempt to keep that and other statistics secret.</description></item><item><title>Community in Ecuador punished for trying to stop alleged palm oil pollution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201a76333ed1612be4736dd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 23:13:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201a76333ed1612be4736dd/</guid><description>A legal loophole allowed palm oil companies in Ecuador to establish plantations on ancestral land that belongs to small communities. This is the first in a two-part series.
Highlights A legal loophole allowed palm oil companies in Ecuador to establish plantations on ancestral land that belongs to small communities. Residents say that agricultural chemicals and waste from plantations and palm oil processing mills is polluting the water sources on which they depend.</description></item><item><title>Spotify CEO condemns Rogan's use of racial slurs, but says company won't be 'silencing' him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200e28519f8be851f2333a1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200e28519f8be851f2333a1/</guid><description>Daniel Ek, the chief executive of Spotify, addressed Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s past use of racial slurs on Sunday night, telling staff in a memo that while he found the comments &amp;quot;incredibly hurtful&amp;quot; and inconsistent with company values, he did not believe &amp;quot;silencing&amp;quot; the podcaster was the answer.
Highlights Daniel Ek, the chief executive of Spotify, addressed Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s past use of racial slurs on Sunday night. He told staff in a memo that while he found the comments &amp;ldquo;incredibly hurtful&amp;rdquo; and inconsistent with company values, he did not believe &amp;ldquo;silencing&amp;rdquo; the podcaster was the answer.</description></item><item><title>Amazon increases the price of Prime nearly 17% to $139 per year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</guid><description>Amazon hasn&amp;rsquo;t raised the price of its Prime membership program since 2018, when it increased from $99 to $119, the current fee.
Highlights Amazon is raising the price of its annual Prime membership to $139 from $119. Amazon also raised the monthly price of a Prime membership from $12.99 to $14.99. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s annual increase amounts to about a 17% rise in price. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock rose more than 14% at one point on Thursday in extended trading.</description></item><item><title>Spotify stocks fall as executives seek to reassure amid Rogan controversy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</guid><description>Subscriber outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter earnings as the company’s shares fell nearly 18% in late trading
Highlights Spotify forecast current-quarter subscribers lower than Wall Street expectations. Company&amp;rsquo;s shares fell as much as 18% in late trading after Spotify reported the subscriber outlook. The outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter revenue, which came in higher than analysts’ estimates. CEO Daniel Ek acknowledged the Joe Rogan controversy at the outset of the earnings conference call. He said he was proud of the steps Spotify took following the concerns raised by the medical and scientific communities and he said policies were developed with input from external and internal and external exports.</description></item><item><title>Neil Young Wants His Music Off Spotify Over Joe Rogan Vaccine Misinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 07:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</guid><description>Neil Young demanded that Spotify remove his music, citing its spread of vaccine misinformation via &amp;quot;The Joe Rogan Experience&amp;quot; podcast.
Summary Neil Young wants his music pulled from Spotify, citing the spread of vaccine misinformation on the popular Joe Rogan Experience podcast as the cause. “They can have Rogan or Young. Not both,” Young wrote in an open letter to his management team and record label posted to his Neil Young Archives website, according to Rolling Stone.</description></item><item><title>Shkreli ordered to return $64M, is barred from drug industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Martin Shkreli must return $64.6 million in profits he and his former company reaped from jacking up the price and monopolizing the market for a lifesaving drug, a federal judge ruled Friday while also barring the provocative, imprisoned ex-CEO from the pharmaceutical industry for the rest of his life.
Summary FILE - Former Turing Pharmaceuticals CEO Martin Shkreli attends the House Committee on Oversight and Reform Committee hearing on Capitol Hill in Washington, Feb.</description></item><item><title>Ford beats out Tesla to become the auto industry’s top growth stock in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3f08f7a56bd392cbecb87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3f08f7a56bd392cbecb87/</guid><description>Ford accomplished this largely thanks to a leadership change in October 2020 from industry outsider Jim Hackett to auto veteran Jim Farley.
Summary In this article FThe all-electric Ford F-150 Lightning truck during an augmented reality presentation at the Motor Bella Auto Show in Pontiac, Michigan, on Tuesday, Sept. 21, 2021. He told CNBC the day before that the company halted reservations of the F-150 Lightning after they hit 200,000 units.</description></item></channel></rss>