<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>swedish on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/swedish/</link><description>Recent content in swedish on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 14:11:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/swedish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Swedish and Finnish PMs quiet on Nato plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224c0fe468a527a709adb3b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 14:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224c0fe468a527a709adb3b/</guid><description>Prime Minister Sanna Marin did not want to say on Saturday whether Finland and Sweden were seeking special non-Nato partner status with the United States.
Highlights Finland and Sweden say their countries are deepening cooperation in the wake of Russia&amp;rsquo;s assault on Ukraine. Prime Minister Sanna Marin says public opinion on Nato membership is shifting in both countries. PMs did not comment on whether Finland or Sweden were seeking special non-Nato partner status with the United States.</description></item><item><title>Sweden and Finland to further strengthen security cooperation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223b5c9bb3e58e7c05ad246/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 19:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223b5c9bb3e58e7c05ad246/</guid><description>Sweden and Finland will further strengthen their security cooperation in light of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine, the prime ministers of both countries said on Saturday, but they were non-committal on joining NATO.
Highlights Sweden and Finland will further strengthen their security cooperation in light of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine, the prime ministers of both countries said on Saturday. Finnish Prime Minister Sanna Marin said it was &amp;ldquo;understandable&amp;rdquo; that more people in both countries now want to join NATO.</description></item></channel></rss>