<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>climate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/climate/</link><description>Recent content in climate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 21:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/climate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suicides indicate wave of ‘doomerism’ over escalating climate crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288039c598e39186817f5dc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 21:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288039c598e39186817f5dc/</guid><description>While alarm over wildfires, droughts, flooding and societal unrest is on the rise, not many of us talk about climate angst
Highlights Wynn Bruce, a 50-year-old photographer who lived in Boulder, Colorado, set himself on fire on the steps of the US supreme court. Police officers plunged orange traffic cones into the court’s marbled fountain and hurled water at him. Four years ago, David Buckel, a civil rights lawyer, doused himself with gasoline and set himself alight in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Prospect Park.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey’s Last Two Coal Power Plants to Close within Months</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241ed37658363f0cde99272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 17:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241ed37658363f0cde99272/</guid><description>The New Jersey Board of Public Utilities (NJBPU) approved a petition filed by Atlantic City Electric Co. (ACE) that modifies power purchase agreements
Highlights Atlantic City Electric Co. (ACE) modifies power purchase agreements (PPAs) and power sales agreements (PSAs) Under the agreements, coal-fired generation will cease on or around May 31, 2022. ACE customers will see up to $30 million in energy bill savings through the end of 2024. New Jersey Board of Public Utilities (NJBPU) approved a petition filed by ACE that modifies the agreements.</description></item><item><title>Exxon Mobil loses appeal to stop climate change probes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231645207d13f324cfb5f4f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 04:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231645207d13f324cfb5f4f/</guid><description>A U.S. federal appeals court on Tuesday rejected Exxon Mobil Corp&amp;rsquo;s effort to stop Massachusetts and New York from probing whether the oil company lied to investors and the public regarding what it knew about climate change.
Highlights The 2nd U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Manhattan said Exxon could not sue in federal court because it was pursuing the same case in Massachusetts state courts. It also said Exxon&amp;rsquo;s federal case against New York Attorney General Letitia James was moot after she decided not to appeal a state judge&amp;rsquo;s dismissal of her lawsuit against the company.</description></item><item><title>Holes the size of city blocks are forming in the Arctic seafloor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62311d9747bc33b77d62c8c3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 23:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62311d9747bc33b77d62c8c3/</guid><description>Marine scientists have discovered deep sinkholes &amp;ndash; including one larger than a city block of six-story buildings &amp;ndash; and ice-filled hills that have formed &amp;quot;extraordinarily&amp;quot; rapidly on a remote part of the Arctic seafloor.
Highlights Scientists find sinkholes and ice-filled hills that have formed &amp;ldquo;extraordinarily&amp;rdquo; rapidly on a remote part of the Arctic seafloor. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time an area of submerged permafrost, a frozen layer of Earth&amp;rsquo;s surface, has been surveyed in this way.</description></item><item><title>All the Beijing snow is human-made -- a resource-intensive, 'dangerous' trend as planet warms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff831bc0a051246b6a2cd2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 08:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff831bc0a051246b6a2cd2/</guid><description>Natural snow is becoming less reliable for winter sports, which has led venues to lean more on artificial. But that comes at a cost.
Highlights Climate variability has forced the Winter Games to be virtually 100% reliant on artificial snow. Human-made snow is incredibly resource-intensive, requiring massive amounts of energy and water to produce in a climate that&amp;rsquo;s getting warmer and warmer. The region surrounding the outdoor Olympic venues is in an extreme drought this winter, but even in normal years, it isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly suitable for snow sports.</description></item></channel></rss>