<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>accused on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/accused/</link><description>Recent content in accused on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 11:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/accused/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Red Power Ranger Actor Among 19 Accused in North Texas PPP Scheme – NBC 5 Dallas-Fort Worth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a199b8b0f2359b2dfebb3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a199b8b0f2359b2dfebb3/</guid><description>Nineteen people, including the actor who played the Red Power Ranger on television, are facing federal charges after being accused of conspiracy to commit wire&amp;hellip;
Highlights Austin St. John, whose real name is Jason Lawrence Geiger, was named in an indictment returned by a federal grand jury on May 12. The actor was best known for his role in the 1990s children&amp;rsquo;s children&amp;rsquo;s superhero show “Mighty Morphin’s Gold Ranger in the “Power Rangers Zeo” St John played the Red Power Ranger in 1996 in the TV show and recently, in 2020, wore the red ranger&amp;rsquo;s red suit again.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Russia accused of targeting hospitals in 'terror bombing' campaign</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278a41d9aa33a0d7af7a690/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 05:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278a41d9aa33a0d7af7a690/</guid><description>Russia has been accused of waging psychological warfare against the Ukrainian people by targeting hospitals, as Sky News analysis shows that almost 60% of attacks on healthcare facilities worldwide this year have been carried out by Russian forces.
Highlights World Health Organisation has recorded 186 of these attacks since the invasion began. They have killed at least 73 healthcare workers and patients in Ukraine. Tell-tale signs suggest the bombings are consistent with a deliberate Russian tactic.</description></item><item><title>Ex-deputy accused of posing as wedding guest to steal gifts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276c49631d14c24b7fecf5d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 19:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276c49631d14c24b7fecf5d/</guid><description>Authorities say a retired sheriff’s deputy posed as a guest at two Phoenix-area weddings to steal boxes of cards containing thousands of dollars, and is under investigation in a series of similar crimes
Highlights Landon Earl Rankin, 54, was arrested Wednesday in the thefts at private venues in April. Rankin was a deputy with the Pinal County Sheriff’s Office, joining the agency in 1994. Police learned of at least seven similar crimes in other Phoenix-area jurisdictions, a spokesman says.</description></item><item><title>Florida man strangles parents, kisses underage stepsister, and attacks deputy. All on his birthday.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246a614bb3e080633937696/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246a614bb3e080633937696/</guid><description>A 22-year-old Deltona man is facing eight felony charges after tackling a deputy during a violent fight, according to the Volusia County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.
Highlights The alleged fight started when the suspect’s girlfriend said she saw him forcibly kiss his 16-year-old stepsister. The incident happened on March 29, which also happened to be the birthday of the suspect, Russell Slimon. Russell is facing 10 charges including eight felonies including battery, child abuse and resisting arrest.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee woman accused of 23 sex crimes involving 9 students at a high school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233f9bf5a9fc19d3e8aadd5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233f9bf5a9fc19d3e8aadd5/</guid><description>A 38-year-old Tennessee woman is facing 23 counts of sex crimes involving nine minors at a high school.
Highlights Melissa Blair, 38, was indicted on 23 charges, including 18 counts of aggravated statutory rape. She is accused of setting up meetings with the victims through social media and offering items in return for sexual favors. The alleged crimes occurred from early in 2020 to late 2021, McMinn County Sheriff Joe Guy said.</description></item></channel></rss>