<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>decision on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/decision/</link><description>Recent content in decision on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:13:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/decision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'I made the right decision,' says Yukon musher penalized by Iditarod for sheltering dogs in storm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247f785973e14bf74d28b06/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247f785973e14bf74d28b06/</guid><description>After being penalized by the Iditarod Trail Sled Dog for sheltering her dogs during a fierce storm, Yukon musher Michelle Philipps said she has no regrets about what she did.
Highlights Yukon musher Michelle Phillips was penalized for sheltering her dogs during a fierce storm. Phillips says she has no regrets about what she did. The decision to punish the mushers was made by Iditarod race marshal Mark Nordman. The three mushers were penalized by being dropped from 17th to 18th in the 1,510-kilometre race.</description></item><item><title>Russian, Belarusian athletes banned from Winter Paralympic Games as IPC reverses ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62221e27ab9cc78d32106724/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 14:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62221e27ab9cc78d32106724/</guid><description>Russian and Belarusian athletes have been banned from the Winter Paralympic Games, less than 24 hours after the IPC announced it would allow Russian and Belarusian athletes to compete as neutral athletes.
Highlights The IPC reversed course and expelled athletes from Russia and Belarus. The change came less than 24 hours after the IPC announced it would allow Russians and Belarusians to compete when the Games open Friday. &amp;ldquo;We were trying to protect the Games from war,&amp;rdquo; IPC president Andrew Parsons said Thursday.</description></item><item><title>North Korea: Missile programme funded through stolen crypto, UN report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62007bf96c66ac62d8c6a158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 01:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62007bf96c66ac62d8c6a158/</guid><description>Investigators say cyber-attackers stole over $50 million in digital assets between 2020 and mid-2021.
Highlights UN report finds humanitarian situation in North Korea continuing to worsen. It said this was likely to be the result of the country&amp;rsquo;s decision to close its borders during the pandemic. Investigators say cyber-attackers stole over $50 million in digital assets between 2020 and mid-2021. UN report also found that North Korea&amp;rsquo;s humanitarian situation continues to worsen.</description></item><item><title>NASCAR rejects 'Let's Go Brandon' sponsorship, Brandonbilt Motorsports says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7f3c19f0269b84c42ecc1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7f3c19f0269b84c42ecc1/</guid><description>NASCAR has rejected Xfinity Series driver Brandon Brown&amp;rsquo;s sponsorship deal with cryptocurrency meme coin LGBcoin &amp;ndash; a reference to the controversial &amp;quot;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Brandon&amp;quot; phrase, his team acknowledged to CNN on Wednesday.
Summary (CNN) NASCAR has rejected Xfinity Series driver Brandon Brown&amp;rsquo;s sponsorship deal with cryptocurrency meme coin LGBcoin &amp;ndash; a reference to the controversial &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Brandon&amp;rdquo; phrase, his team acknowledged to CNN on Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;NASCAR did not speak with Brandonbilt Motorsports prior to making their decision to rescind the approval and multiple attempts to set-up a conversation to address this matter went unacknowledged,&amp;rdquo; Max Marcucci, Brandonbilt Motorsports spokesperson said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>