<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>park on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/park/</link><description>Recent content in park on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:52:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A teenager in Utah died after a tunnel he was digging in a sand dune collapsed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62844325902f359e063568f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62844325902f359e063568f1/</guid><description>A 13-year-old boy in Utah died from injuries sustained in a dune collapse last weekend, according to Utah State Parks.
Highlights Park rangers believe the teen had been digging a tunnel in the side of a sand dune at Coral Pink Sand Dunes State Park. The tunnel collapsed, trapping him underneath the sand, Utah State Parks says. A family member witnessed the collapse about 5:30 p.m., and he was located six-and-a-half feet beneath the sand.</description></item><item><title>Shenandoah National Park growing by hundreds of acres</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277cff553fa47ab8934195b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 14:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277cff553fa47ab8934195b/</guid><description>The Shenandoah National Park can expand by hundreds of acres thanks to land-protection efforts.
Highlights Shenandoah National Park can expand by hundreds of acres thanks to land-protection efforts. Land protection efforts have led to the park expanding by more than 200,000 acres. You have permission to edit this article. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Missing hiker's body found in LA park with dog by his side</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624948e4e125d5c23b8798db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624948e4e125d5c23b8798db/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A hiker who went missing two weeks ago was found dead in Griffith&amp;hellip;
Highlights Oscar Alejandro Hernandez, 29, was reported missing on March 16. His body was found Thursday night in a remote area of the sprawling urban park. His dog, King, was alive but emaciated. Hernandez was found with his dog by his side, authorities said. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Betty Reid Soskin, America’s oldest active ranger, retires at the age of 100</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624725e72db5ecaed9d93fbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 16:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624725e72db5ecaed9d93fbd/</guid><description>She began working with the National Park Service at 84 to reveal ‘untold stories’ of Black people’s efforts during the second world war
Highlights Betty Reid Soskin worked at the Rosie the Riveter/WWII Home Front national historical park in Richmond, California. She was a file clerk in a segregated Union hall in the San Francisco Bay area during the conflict. Her efforts at the park – and her 100th birthday last fall – have captivated the public and received coverage from numerous media outlets, including a profile in the New York Times and a portrait taken by Annie Leibovitz.</description></item><item><title>City of Marquette closing road nightly to save salamanders</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62411f6e47eec6be204787ef/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62411f6e47eec6be204787ef/</guid><description>MARQUETTE, Mich. (AP) — An Upper Peninsula city is closing a portion of a road to vehicular traffic every night to protect migrating salamanders. The city of Marquette is closing a portion of Peter White Drive in Presque Isle Park from 8 p.m.
Highlights The city of Marquette is closing a portion of Peter White Drive in Presque Isle Park from 8 p.m. to 8 a.m., until April 15. Road barricades will be placed and removed daily to prevent vehicular traffic in the migration area.</description></item><item><title>Snow leopard dies at Illinois zoo after contracting Covid-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</guid><description>A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois.
Summary (CNN) A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois. before death, according to a Rilu, an 11-year-old snow leopard, struggled with Covid-19 induced pneumoniabefore death, according to a post on the Miller Park Zoo verified Instagram account. &amp;ldquo;Rilu arrived at the Miller Park Zoo in 2011 from the Oklahoma City Zoo,&amp;rdquo; the post said.</description></item></channel></rss>