<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>heavy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/heavy/</link><description>Recent content in heavy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 06:17:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/heavy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Germany agrees to send heavy weapons to Ukraine after major policy U-turn | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268dfeea79ba879da7d314b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 06:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268dfeea79ba879da7d314b/</guid><description>Germany has agreed to deliver anti-aircraft tanks to Ukraine, the German Defense Ministry announced on Tuesday, a move that underscores a major shift in its approach to providing military help to Ukraine.
Highlights Germany has agreed to deliver anti-aircraft tanks to Ukraine, the German Defense Ministry announced on Tuesday. The move underscores a major shift in Germany&amp;rsquo;s approach to providing military help to Ukraine. Germany initially resisted calls to provide weaponry to Kyiv, agreeing only to provide humanitarian help and medical equipment.</description></item><item><title>Russia faces heavy losses as it attacks Ukraine on all fronts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bdb60662b7d392ad85cbe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bdb60662b7d392ad85cbe/</guid><description>Russia lost 14 planes, 8 helicopters, 102 tanks, 536 BBM, 15 heavy machine guns, and 1 BUK missile since Feb. 24. Russia also lost over 3,500 soldiers, Ukraine’s Armed Forces said
Highlights Russia has lost 14 planes, 8 helicopters, 102 tanks, 536 BBM, 15 heavy machine guns, and 1 BUK missile since Feb. The Kremlin also lost over 3,500 soldiers, Ukraine’s Armed Forces said on Feb. Russia has begun redeploying reserve units in the areas bordering Ukraine and continues to carry out airstrikes on airfields, military depots, and civilians.</description></item><item><title>Removing trucks could be almost 'impossible,' say heavy towing experts | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201ee35b056c6045f7e942e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201ee35b056c6045f7e942e/</guid><description>Heavy-duty towing experts say it will be difficult or impossible to remove the hundreds of heavy trucks entrenched in Ottawa&amp;rsquo;s downtown — unless the drivers allow it.
Highlights CBC counted 40 trucks on Kent Street and 109 on Wellington Street Friday, with dozens more on other streets spread around the downtown core. The City of Ottawa has declared a state of emergency amid the protests. Sources say companies contracted by the city are refusing to tow trucks involved with the demonstration.</description></item></channel></rss>