<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>army on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/army/</link><description>Recent content in army on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 18:16:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/army/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukrainian troops killed commander of Russia's 49th Combined Arms Army - Arestovych</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e06f3aab0cf7686bfd91d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 18:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e06f3aab0cf7686bfd91d/</guid><description>Ukrainian troops have killed Lieutenant General Yakov Rezantsev, commander of the 49th Combined Arms Army of the Russian Southern Military District. — Ukrinform.
Highlights Ukrainian troops have killed Lieutenant General Yakov Rezantsev, commander of the 49th Combined Arms Army of the Russian Southern Military District. The enemy general was liquidated at the airfield in Chornobaivka, the Kherson region, a freelance adviser to the head of the President&amp;rsquo;s Office said this at a briefing on Friday, March 25.</description></item><item><title>UN accuses Myanmar army of war crimes, torture, killings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234cc2d2ef7b24c3ae215c7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 18:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234cc2d2ef7b24c3ae215c7/</guid><description>In its first broad human rights report since Myanmar’s coup, UN says army has shown flagrant disregard for human life.
Highlights In first broad human rights report since Myanmar’s coup, UN says army has shown flagrant disregard for human life. Many victims were shot in the head, burned to death, arrested arbitrarily, tortured, or used as human shields, the report says. The military has denied atrocities have taken place and has blamed “terrorists” for causing unrest.</description></item><item><title>French army says senior al Qaeda leader killed in Mali</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226e598150870837e2d2394/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 05:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226e598150870837e2d2394/</guid><description>France&amp;rsquo;s army said Monday that its anti-jihadist force in Mali had killed Yahia Djouadi, a &amp;quot;senior leader&amp;quot; of Al-Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM) responsible for finance and logistics.
Highlights Yahia Djouadi was a &amp;ldquo;senior leader&amp;rdquo; of Al-Qaeda in the Islamic Maghreb (AQIM) responsible for finance and logistics. He was killed overnight from February 25 to 26 around (160 kilometres (100 miles) north of Timbuktu in central Mali) His death &amp;ldquo;once again weakens Al Qaeda&amp;rsquo;s governance&amp;rdquo; in Mali, French army says.</description></item><item><title>Black female WWII unit recognized with congressional honor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dd62e05407eb0b7a77687/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 08:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dd62e05407eb0b7a77687/</guid><description>BOSTON (AP) — The House voted Monday to award the only all-female, Black unit to serve in Europe during World War II with the Congressional Gold Medal. The 422-0 vote follows a long-running campaign to recognize the 6888th Central Postal Directory Battalion.
Highlights The 6888th Central Central. Central. Center for the New York Democratic Rep. Brian Higgins, who sponsored the. post office bill, was given the “Indiana. Hunt-Martin” after veteran Indiana.</description></item><item><title>Swiss army bans WhatsApp, Telegram and Signal due to privacy concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db22c6d3ae192757fa6692/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db22c6d3ae192757fa6692/</guid><description>Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s army has banned the use of WhatsApp whilst on duty, a spokesman confirmed Thursday, in favour of a Swiss messaging service deemed more secure in terms of data protection.
Summary The ban also applies to using other messaging apps like Signal and Telegram on soldiers’ private phones during service operations. READ MORE: Swiss army launches fitness app for future recruitsThe recommendation applies “to everyone”, including conscripts doing their military service and those returning for refresher courses, army spokesman Daniel Reist told AFP.</description></item></channel></rss>