<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sales on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sales/</link><description>Recent content in sales on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:14:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Court: California's under-21 gun sales ban unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cb3ca51c5b0ab13d60e8d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cb3ca51c5b0ab13d60e8d/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A U.S. appeals court ruled Wednesday that California’s ban on the sale of semiautomatic weapons to adults under 21 is unconstitutional. In a 2-1 ruling, a panel of the San Francisco-based 9th U.S.
Highlights A U.S. appeals court ruled Wednesday, May 11, that California’s ban on the sale of semiautomatic weapons to adults under 21 is unconstitutional. The court said the law violates the Second Amendment right to bear arms.</description></item><item><title>Legal Weed Sales in New Jersey to Begin April 21</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259007cf3aed1b98939f770/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 05:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259007cf3aed1b98939f770/</guid><description>Legal sales of marijuana in New Jersey will begin April 21, Gov. Phil Murphy said Thursday.
Highlights People aged 21 and over in the state will be able to purchase cannabis and cannabis products without a medical card on that date. Voters approved the legal sale of marijuana in New Jersey in 2020, but the state has taken this long to establish the rules governing its sale and approve companies to sell it.</description></item><item><title>Etsy sellers protest fees by halting their sales for a week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625526a4dbb66051e0a6343f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 07:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625526a4dbb66051e0a6343f/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Some vendors on Etsy say they are halting sales of their items on the site for a week to protest a hike in the fees the crafts e-commerce marketplace charges them. Starting Monday, Etsy sellers must pay a 6.5% commission on each transaction, up from the 5% in place since 2018.
Highlights Etsy sellers say they are halting sales of their items on the site for a week to protest a hike in fees the crafts e-commerce marketplace charges them.</description></item><item><title>Walmart says it is raising truckers’ pay and starting a training program as it grapples with driver shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fe0bb488d355f55ec5200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fe0bb488d355f55ec5200/</guid><description>Walmart is trying to expand the pipeline of truck drivers amid a national shortage.
Highlights Walmart says truck drivers will now make between $95,000 and $110,000 in their first year with Walmart. The retailer is ramping up recruiting efforts for truck drivers amid a tight market for trucking labor. The shortage of truck drivers in the U.S. hit an all-time high of more than 80,000 workers last year, trade group says.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer expects $54 billion in 2022 sales on Covid vaccine and treatment pill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62030e3e3d8878d511b366da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:44:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62030e3e3d8878d511b366da/</guid><description>Pfizer expects to sell $32 billion of its Covid-19 shots and $22 billion of its antiviral coronavirus treatment pill Paxlovid.
Highlights Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter revenue more than doubled overall to $23.84 billion year-over-year, driven by $12.5 billion in sales of its Covid vaccine. Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla said sales of Paxlovid could be higher than the company&amp;rsquo;s guidance, but the expectations are based on deals signed or close to being signed. The company&amp;rsquo;s share was down more than 5.</description></item></channel></rss>