<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sweden on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sweden/</link><description>Recent content in sweden on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sweden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Poland and Sweden refuse to play Russia in World Cup qualifiers because of Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b6c116f6ca2b76e5c5d86/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b6c116f6ca2b76e5c5d86/</guid><description>Polish and Bayern Munich star Robert Lewandowski said he can&amp;rsquo;t &amp;quot;imagine playing&amp;quot; against Russia while its military continues to attack Ukraine.
Highlights Poland and Sweden will not play Russia in World Cup playoff qualifiers. Poland&amp;rsquo;s football association president Cezary Kulesza said in a tweet it is &amp;ldquo;time to act!&amp;rdquo; The decision comes days after FIFA President Gianni Infantino failed to condemn the actions of Russian President Vladimir Putin. Russia was set to play Poland on March 24 in a semifinal playoff game in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Sweden launches 'Psychological Defence Agency' to counter propaganda from Russia, China and Iran</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d509ded3f46322c6f67172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d509ded3f46322c6f67172/</guid><description>The new agency is tasked with countering disinformation and boosting the population&amp;rsquo;s resilience in the face of possible influence operation
Summary Sweden has launched a new agency dedicated to defending the country against disinformation, propaganda and psychological warfare in the latest part of its efforts to bring military and civil defence back towards Cold War levels. A soon-to-be-published study for Sweden&amp;rsquo;s Civil Contingencies Agency (MSB) has found that as many as 10 per cent of Swedes read articles from Sputnik News, Russia&amp;rsquo;s international propaganda agency.</description></item></channel></rss>