<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>florida on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/florida/</link><description>Recent content in florida on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:38:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/florida/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida man gets life in prison for traveling to Vietnam to sexually abuse minors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286e2f77d5186c91f46d440/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286e2f77d5186c91f46d440/</guid><description>Christopher Edwin Day, 52, traveled to Vietnam to have sexual encounters with Vietnamese boys. Court records say he flew back and forth disguising himself as an English teacher. Some of the boys, according to the DOJ, were lured with promises
Highlights Christopher Edwin Day, 52, traveled to Vietnam to have sexual encounters with minor Vietnamese boys. Court records say he flew back and forth disguising himself as an English teacher. Some of the boys, according to the DOJ, were lured with promises of money and gifts.</description></item><item><title>Florida jury finds ex-deputy who threw teen to the ground not guilty of child abuse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62807fadf48052eaa73573e5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 04:21:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62807fadf48052eaa73573e5/</guid><description>A Florida jury on Thursday found a former sheriff’s deputy not guilty in an incident in which he slammed a 15-year-old girl to the ground in 2019, local media reported.
Highlights Willard Miller, 41, called the jury’s not guilty verdict on one count of child abuse a vindication. Miller was charged with felony child abuse following the Sept. 25, 2019, incident at Pompano Beach school. Miller testified that the girl had kicked his leg from behind, and the defense argued that he did not intend for the hard fall but the child&amp;rsquo;s leg got caught in a chair.</description></item><item><title>A passenger with no flying experience landed a plane in a Florida airport after the pilot became incapacitated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bbbf0b58031d21ab6cffb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bbbf0b58031d21ab6cffb/</guid><description>A passenger with no flying experience safely landed a private plane in a Florida airport Tuesday afternoon, May 10, when the pilot became incapacitated.
Highlights Passenger with no flying experience safely landed private plane at Palm Beach International Airport. Two people were aboard the single-engine Cessna 208 when the pilot had a &amp;ldquo;possible medical issue&amp;rdquo; The condition of the pilot was not immediately known. Passenger can be heard saying he doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to fly the plane, according to LiveATC.</description></item><item><title>Teens shot trying to break into man's car were 13 and 16-years-old, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bf246ad859237b7d3b81d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 14:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bf246ad859237b7d3b81d/</guid><description>According to investigators, the call first came in around 2 a.m. as a report of a car burglary with shots fired on Martinwood Drive.
Highlights Two teenagers were shot by a man after reportedly trying to break into his car, Orange County deputies said. The call first came in around 2 a.m. as a report of a car burglary with shots fired on Martinwood Drive in Pine Hills. The victim said the suspects made &amp;ldquo;threatening movements toward him&amp;rdquo; and so he fired several shots.</description></item><item><title>Florida judge overturns CDC mask mandate for public transit, planes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dc6fcfec3ce61fc6b3d84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 20:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dc6fcfec3ce61fc6b3d84/</guid><description>The court&amp;rsquo;s ruling comes less than a week after the CDC extended the mandate for 15 days, amid a rise in Covid infections nationwide due to the more contagious omicron BA.2 subvariant.
Highlights A judge in Florida vacated the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s national Covid mask mandate for planes and other forms of public transportation. The Health Freedom Defense Fund, a group that opposes public health mandates, and two individuals who argued that wearing masks while flying exacerbated their anxiety and panic attacks first filed the lawsuit in July 2021.</description></item><item><title>11-foot hammerhead shark washes up on Florida beach</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d1e89536a2f1d2ec79352/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d1e89536a2f1d2ec79352/</guid><description>An 11-foot hammerhead shark washed up on a beach in southern Florida, much to beachgoers&amp;rsquo; surprise.
Highlights A female great hammerhead shark washed up on Pompano Beach, north of Fort Lauderdale, Florida. A team of scientists from the American Shark Conservancy took samples and identified the shark. The female was pregnant and weighed around 500 lbs, a conservation scientist says. A member of the team encountered the body with a hook in its mouth, which usually indicates someone was fishing for a large animal like a hammerhead, she says.</description></item><item><title>Florida man arrested for allegedly masturbating on a flight to Boston</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62540cf59b01a6b56a6b4813/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 11:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62540cf59b01a6b56a6b4813/</guid><description>A Florida man was arrested for allegedly masturbating and exposing his penis to a woman next to him on a flight from Newark to Boston.
Highlights Donald Edward Robinson, 76, of Bonita Springs, Florida, was charged with one count of lewd, indecent, and obscene acts while in the special aircraft jurisdiction of the U.S. He was arrested Sunday morning at Boston Logan International Airport and will appear in a federal court in Boston at a later date.</description></item><item><title>16-year-old killed when teens wearing body armor take turns shooting at each other in Florida, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250978f6d6c0ae440f105bb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 20:14:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250978f6d6c0ae440f105bb/</guid><description>A 16-year-old boy was killed when he and another teen took turns shooting at each other while wearing a form of body armor, according to police.
Highlights Joshua Vining and Colton Whitler, both 17, were arrested Thursday in connection with the fatal shooting of Christopher Leroy Broad Jr. Police said Vining fatally shot Broad as the two were taking turns shooting at each other while wearing a vest containing “a form of body armor” An 18-year-old who was with the group — identified as Evan Vowell — recorded the shooting on his cell phone and turned over the footage to be used as evidence.</description></item><item><title>‘Don’t Say Gay’ bill signed by Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624217413a25172f5258a9ff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624217413a25172f5258a9ff/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed a bill on Monday that forbids instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade, a policy that has drawn intense national scrutiny from critics who argue it marginalizes LGBTQ people.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signs a bill that forbids instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade. Critics say the bill marginalizes LGBTQ people, marginalizes them.</description></item><item><title>Florida Mandates Personal Finance Education in High Schools</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623db8bcfa014a1a30e85ae4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623db8bcfa014a1a30e85ae4/</guid><description>On Tuesday, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed bill SB 1054, which mandates personal finance education for high school graduation.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed bill SB 1054 into law on Tuesday. The legislation was unanimously passed by both the state House of Representatives and Senate in March. Florida is the latest in a growing trend of states adopting legislation that includes personal finance education for students. Currently, there are 54 bills pending in 26 states, according to Next Gen Personal Finance&amp;rsquo;s bill tracker.</description></item><item><title>'I killed a lady on the bridge': Florida drawbridge tender arrested after 79-year-old woman falls to her death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62353b33bd50d4a1d8aa1022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62353b33bd50d4a1d8aa1022/</guid><description>A Florida bridge tender has been arrested for manslaughter, one month after a 79-year-old grandmother fell to her death from a drawbridge that began rising while she was still walking on it. Police said surveillance video and deleted text messages between the bridge tender and her supervisor showed she lied to investigators.
Highlights Police arrested 43-year-old Artissua Lafay Paulk at her home Thursday afternoon. Police said surveillance video and deleted text messages between Paulk and her supervisor showed she lied in her statement to police.</description></item><item><title>Disney employees are staging walkouts over company's response to the 'Don't Say Gay' bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62335f0ebe6e7928e7dd7849/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 16:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62335f0ebe6e7928e7dd7849/</guid><description>Last week, Disney and its CEO Bob Chapek bungled their response to Florida&amp;rsquo;s controversial bill dubbed &amp;quot;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay.&amp;quot; Now, some of the company&amp;rsquo;s employees are staging a walkout.
Highlights A Twitter account, &amp;ldquo;@DisneyWalkout,&amp;rdquo; and an associated website, &amp;ldquo;WhereIsChapek.com,&amp;rdquo; have organized a series of 15-minute daily walkouts. The action will culminate with a full-day walkout on March 22. It&amp;rsquo;s unknown how many employees are taking part, but Disney&amp;rsquo;s LGBTQ+ employee resource groups are not involved, according to a source.</description></item><item><title>South Florida visitor spends night in stranger’s home thinking it was his Airbnb</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62308494f129f2bade794753/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 12:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62308494f129f2bade794753/</guid><description>Paul Drecksler had just arrived in Miami to officiate a friend’s wedding. After a long day of traveling, he got to what he thought was his unlocked room, around 2 a.m. The homeowner showed him
Highlights Paul Drecksler spent the night in what he thought was his Airbnb in Miami. He woke up the next morning to a very confused homeowner. He said he accidentally got the address wrong from the Airbnb app into the Google maps.</description></item><item><title>Man hit, killed by higher-speed train in Florida</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f072f43ccc917041eea60/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 09:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f072f43ccc917041eea60/</guid><description>Authorities say a Brightline train struck and killed a pedestrian, raising the death toll since the higher-speed train line resumed operations in South Florida.
Highlights Authorities say a Brightline train struck and killed a pedestrian, raising the death toll since the higher-speed train line resumed operations in South Florida. Brightline has the worst fatality rate in the nation, according to an ongoing Associated Press analysis of Federal Railroad Administration data. Its trains have fatally struck 59 people since beginning test runs in 2017, an average of about one death every 33,000 miles (about 53,000 kilometers) Central Florida’s SunRail has the second-worst rate among railroads that operate at least 100,000 mile (about 161,000 km) annually.</description></item><item><title>Feds rescind license extension for Florida nuclear plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62190e349d310a8c070bb15a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 17:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62190e349d310a8c070bb15a/</guid><description>Federal officials have reversed a decision to allow a South Florida nuclear power plant to continue running for another 30 years by ordering a new review of potential environmental risks, including those posed by climate change
Highlights Federal officials have reversed a decision to allow a South Florida nuclear power plant to continue running for another 30 years. The U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission issued an order Thursday to reverse a 2019 decision by a previous, Republican-led commission.</description></item></channel></rss>