<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>moscow on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/moscow/</link><description>Recent content in moscow on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 22:15:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/moscow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian Orthodox leader backs war in Ukraine, divides faith</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625de2d6a93834d312bee831/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 22:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625de2d6a93834d312bee831/</guid><description>Patriarch Kirill has angered many in echoing the language Vladimir Putin uses to justify the Ukraine invasion.
Highlights Patriarch Kirill has become one of the war’s most prominent backers. His sermons echo, and in some cases even supply, the rhetoric that Vladimir Putin has used to justify the assault on cities and civilians. In the process, he has caused deep schisms in the global Orthodox Church, with priests in Ukraine, elsewhere in Europe and the U.</description></item><item><title>Russia starts military drill on disputed islands off Japan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ebd12f9028d36c83a5bb2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 07:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ebd12f9028d36c83a5bb2/</guid><description>The Russian military starts a military exercise involving more than 3,000 troops on a chain of islands including those disputed with Japan, Russian news agency Interfax reports.
Highlights It is the first drill on the disputed islands off Japan&amp;rsquo;s northernmost main island of Hokkaido since Russia&amp;rsquo;s Foreign Ministry announced earlier this week it will suspend territorial talks with Japan. Some hundreds of military vehicles are participating in the drill under a scenario of launching a counterattack against enemy forces attempting to land.</description></item><item><title>Thousands of pro-Russia Serbs march in Belgrade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224891bf52dde79888106e9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 10:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224891bf52dde79888106e9/</guid><description>Flags and flares are paraded through the Serbian capital, as marchers show support for Moscow.
Highlights Up to 4,000 people take part in pro-Russia demonstration in Serbian capital. It was a show of support for Moscow after its invasion of Ukraine. Serbia has religious, ethnic and political ties with Russia that have existed for centuries. The Serbian capital is Serbia&amp;rsquo;s capital of Beljevevevlija, which borders Russia and Ukraine, has long been friendly with Russia.</description></item><item><title>Moscow braces for market meltdown Monday as new sanctions hit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c849b5fcf3096bfcf75a1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 08:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c849b5fcf3096bfcf75a1/</guid><description>Russian currency expected to plunge in first day’s trading since Swift ban and ECB says state-owned Sberbank subsidiaries are set to collapse
Highlights The U.S. and European Union announced unprecedented sanctions over the weekend. “There are no available measures with a realistic chance of restoring this. position at group level and in each of its subsidiaries within the. subsidiaries,” the company said in a statement. ‘I think for one of the largest.</description></item><item><title>US holds firm on Ukraine’s right to join Nato in its response to Russian demands</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2c2e2367bed77f481b21b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2c2e2367bed77f481b21b/</guid><description>US officials also offer negotiate on European security with Moscow but won’t move on most contentious issue
Highlights The US has presented its written response to Russian demands on Ukraine, but made clear that it did not change Washington’s support for Ukraine’s right to pursue Nato membership, the most contentious issue in relations with Moscow. Blinken was speaking hours after his Russian counterpart, Sergei Lavrov, threatened “retaliatory measures” if the US response did not satisfy the Kremlin.</description></item></channel></rss>