<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>oath on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oath/</link><description>Recent content in oath on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 05:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oath/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Member of Georgia chapter of Oath Keepers pleads guilty to conspiracy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cc56062f2754f3d2d446f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 05:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cc56062f2754f3d2d446f/</guid><description>According to the Department of Justice, on April 29, a member of the Georgia chapter of Oath Keepers has pleaded guilty to seditious conspiracy and obstruction of an official proceeding for his actions before, during, and after the breach of the U. S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021. His and others’ actions disrupted a joint session of the U. S. Congress convened to ascertain and count the electoral votes related to the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Far-right Oath Keepers leader to stay in jail until Capitol attack trial, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210d04a29cf3c7dddf34048/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 11:11:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210d04a29cf3c7dddf34048/</guid><description>Stewart Rhodes ‘presents a clear and convincing danger’ after spending thousands on weapons before riot, judge says
Highlights Stewart Rhodes &amp;lsquo;presents a clear and convincing danger&amp;rsquo; after spending thousands on weapons before riot, judge says. US district judge Amit Mehta said Rhodes spent thousands of dollars on weapons and equipment. Rhodes is accused of spearheading a conspiracy to block the certification of the presidential election by recruiting others and even stationing armed ‘quick reaction force’ units outside of Washington to be ready to stop the peaceful transfer of power.</description></item></channel></rss>