<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>names on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/names/</link><description>Recent content in names on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 01:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/names/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia Is Leaking Data Like a Sieve</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e0b139ee1592822d733bb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 01:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e0b139ee1592822d733bb/</guid><description>Ukraine claims to have doxed Russian troops and spies, while hacktivists are regularly leaking private information from Russian organizations.
Highlights Ukraine claims to have doxed 1,600 Russian troops in one fell swoop. Another data set allegedly contains details of 620 Russian spies registered to work at the Moscow office of the FSB. The data offers unparalleled glimpses into closed-off private institutions and may be a gold mine for investigators. Both sides in this conflict are very good at information operations, says Philip Ingram, a former colonel in British military intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell to reveal identity of ‘8 John Does’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4f80e917579524bf69b14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 05:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4f80e917579524bf69b14/</guid><description>Convicted sex-trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell will no longer fight to protect the identity of eight men who allegedly had sex with young women she and her billionaire paedophile pal Jeffrey Epstein procured for them.
Summary The British socialite and convicted sex-trafficker has ended her fight to keep the identity of eight “John Does” a secret, her lawyer said in a letter. Convicted sex-trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell will no longer fight to protect the identity of eight men who allegedly had sex with young women she and her billionaire paedophile pal Jeffrey Epstein procured for them.</description></item></channel></rss>