<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>transgender on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transgender/</link><description>Recent content in transgender on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 17:14:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transgender/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Percentage of LGBTQ adults in U.S. has doubled over past decade, Gallup finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e823d13b3946626becdb6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 17:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e823d13b3946626becdb6/</guid><description>The percent of U.S. adults who identify as something other than heterosexual has doubled over the last 10 years, from 3.5 percent in 2012 to 7.1 percent,
Highlights Gallup poll: Percentage of U.S. adults who identify as LGBTQ has doubled over the last 10 years. Generation Z adults are the most likely to identify as bisexual, compared to Generation X, baby boomers and traditionalists. Gallup predicts the number of LGBTQ-identifying adults will only increase — and likely at a much faster rate than past generations.</description></item><item><title>16 UPenn swimmers ask school not to challenge transgender policy that could block teammate Lia Thomas from competing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd79f118918c9a0ff5d84f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 19:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd79f118918c9a0ff5d84f/</guid><description>Letter on behalf of 16 members of UPenn swim team asks school to not challenge NCAA transgender athlete policy
Highlights Letter asks school and Ivy League not to challenge NCAA&amp;rsquo;s new transgender athlete participation policies. The letter was written by Olympic champion in swimming on behalf of 16 members of the Penn swim team. University of Pennsylvania swimmer Lia Thomas won the women&amp;rsquo;s 100- and 200-yard freestyle at Harvard last month.</description></item></channel></rss>