<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>transgender on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transgender/</link><description>Recent content in transgender on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 19:08:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transgender/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Candidate for San Diego County Sheriff leaves job, loses endorsement after transgender comments</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293c482f0f1b7cab3fa2e64/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 19:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293c482f0f1b7cab3fa2e64/</guid><description>During an April candidates forum, Republican John Hemmerling commented on where transgender women should use the bathroom. He says he left his job this week with the City Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office to focus on the election, not because of backlash from his comments.
Highlights Republican John Hemmerling left his job as the chief criminal criminal prosecutor in the City Attorney’s office this week. Video surfaced showing him making comments about where transgender women should use the bathroom.</description></item><item><title>New Yorkers can now choose an 'X' gender marker on their state IDs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292f524f64f5f4a0137f934/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292f524f64f5f4a0137f934/</guid><description>Residents of New York can now choose an &amp;quot;X&amp;quot; marker for their gender on state identification cards
Highlights Residents of New York can now choose an &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; marker for their gender on state identification cards. The Gender Recognition Act will go into full effect on June 24. The legislation will allow people to attest to their own gender identity when petitioning a court or updating an identification document. It will also eliminate the requirement to publish name changes in a local newspaper, and allow parents the choice to be designated as &amp;ldquo;father,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;mother&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;parent&amp;rdquo; on their child&amp;rsquo;s birth certificate, the legislation will also allow parents to be named &amp;ldquo;father&amp;rdquo; on the birth certificate of their child, among other things, the act will go to full effect.</description></item><item><title>Transgender medication law in Alabama blocked by judge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ff1f8cdded64bf88124cd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 18:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ff1f8cdded64bf88124cd/</guid><description>MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — A federal judge on Friday blocked part of an Alabama law that made it a felony to prescribe gender-affirming puberty blockers and hormones to transgender minors.
Highlights A federal judge on Friday, May 13, 2022 blocked part of an Alabama law that made it a felony to prescribe gender-affirming puberty blockers and hormones to transgender minors. U.S. District Judge Liles Burke issued a preliminary injunction to stop the state from enforcing the medication ban, which took effect May 8, while a lawsuit goes forward.</description></item><item><title>Judge orders US Bureau of Prisons to find surgeon for transgender inmate's gender affirming surgery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260acf8cffbb1f9f2d31fe8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260acf8cffbb1f9f2d31fe8/</guid><description>A federal judge in Illinois on Monday ruled that the US Bureau of Prisons (BOP) has to immediately find a qualified surgeon so that a transgender prisoner, Cristina Nichole Iglesias, can receive gender-affirming surgery, court documents show.
Highlights A federal judge in Illinois has ordered the US Bureau of Prisons (BOP) to find a qualified surgeon so that a transgender prisoner, Cristina Nichole Iglesias, can receive gender-affirming surgery. The BOP &amp;ldquo;employed tactics similar to the game of Plinko on The Price is Right,&amp;rdquo; Chief Judge Nancy Rosenstengel said in Monday&amp;rsquo;s ruling.</description></item><item><title>Texas court halts child abuse investigations into parents of trans kids</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ae48e11821b66a2b5cfb1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 09:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ae48e11821b66a2b5cfb1/</guid><description>A Texas appeals court has once again halted child abuse investigations into parents of trans children who provide gender-affirming care.
Highlights An appeals court has again blocked the state from investigating gender-affirming care for trans children as child abuse. In February, Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton published an opinion saying such procedures are &amp;ldquo;abuse&amp;rdquo; Texas Gov. Greg Abbott ordered the Department of Family and Protective Services to investigate gender affirmation procedures.</description></item><item><title>Texas confirms 9 investigations of transgender minors receiving gender-affirming health care</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c3a89d1a6c3f95592d1f7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 06:16:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c3a89d1a6c3f95592d1f7/</guid><description>Texas has opened nine alleged abuse investigations of minors receiving gender-affirming health care, Patrick Crimmins, a Department of Family and Protective Services (DFPS) spokesman, confirmed to CNN Thursday.
Highlights Texas has opened nine alleged abuse investigations of minors receiving gender-affirming health care. Civil rights groups said in a court hearing last week they were aware of at least three families under investigation. Gov. Greg Abbott last month directed the state family services department to investigate alleged abuse.</description></item><item><title>Percentage of LGBTQ adults in U.S. has doubled over past decade, Gallup finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e823d13b3946626becdb6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 17:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e823d13b3946626becdb6/</guid><description>The percent of U.S. adults who identify as something other than heterosexual has doubled over the last 10 years, from 3.5 percent in 2012 to 7.1 percent,
Highlights Gallup poll: Percentage of U.S. adults who identify as LGBTQ has doubled over the last 10 years. Generation Z adults are the most likely to identify as bisexual, compared to Generation X, baby boomers and traditionalists. Gallup predicts the number of LGBTQ-identifying adults will only increase — and likely at a much faster rate than past generations.</description></item><item><title>16 UPenn swimmers ask school not to challenge transgender policy that could block teammate Lia Thomas from competing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd79f118918c9a0ff5d84f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 19:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd79f118918c9a0ff5d84f/</guid><description>Letter on behalf of 16 members of UPenn swim team asks school to not challenge NCAA transgender athlete policy
Highlights Letter asks school and Ivy League not to challenge NCAA&amp;rsquo;s new transgender athlete participation policies. The letter was written by Olympic champion in swimming on behalf of 16 members of the Penn swim team. University of Pennsylvania swimmer Lia Thomas won the women&amp;rsquo;s 100- and 200-yard freestyle at Harvard last month.</description></item></channel></rss>