<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>version on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/version/</link><description>Recent content in version on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 19:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/version/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mississippi becomes 37th U.S. state to legalize medical marijuana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc28b32058cec7c9c20fb8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 19:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc28b32058cec7c9c20fb8/</guid><description>Mississippi joined 36 other U.S. states in legalizing marijuana for medical use on Wednesday, as the governor signed legislation permitting cannabis for treatment of severe, debilitating health conditions such as cancer, AIDS and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Highlights Mississippi joins 36 other U.S. states in legalizing marijuana for medical use on Wednesday. The governor signed legislation permitting cannabis for treatment of severe, debilitating health conditions such as cancer, AIDS and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease. Governor Tate Reeves said the final version passed last week by the Republican-controlled legislature was designed to curb recreational marijuana use.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan Shuts Internet as Government Offices Burn in Protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6232724b78673076499ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 23:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6232724b78673076499ca/</guid><description>The Kazakh president requested the peacekeeping troops as an uprising, sparked by a gas price increase in the resource-rich Central Asian nation, headed toward a fifth day.
Summary MOSCOW — A Russian-led military alliance said late Wednesday that it would send peacekeeping forces to Kazakhstan at the invitation of the country’s president to help put down a growing protest movement there. He did not elaborate on how many soldiers could be mobilized or how long they might stay.</description></item></channel></rss>