<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>changes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/changes/</link><description>Recent content in changes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 21:13:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/changes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Most medical debt to be removed from credit reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234f5b7fc5f4d7185c5cff2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234f5b7fc5f4d7185c5cff2/</guid><description>Experian, Equifax and TransUnion have been working on the changes for months. The changes will remove nearly 70% of medical debt from consumer credit reports. The credit reporting agencies have been under pressure from the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau.
Highlights Experian, Equifax and TransUnion have been working on the changes for months. The changes will remove nearly 70% of medical debt from consumer credit reports. The credit reporting agencies have been under pressure from the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau to address the issues surrounding medical debt.</description></item><item><title>Meta employees left to do their own laundry as perks get cut | Silicon Valley | The Guardian</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</guid><description>Facebook parent company tells workers they will no longer receive free valet service and meals will be delayed
Highlights Facebook parent company tells employees it will be cutting down on onsite perks including free laundry, dry cleaning and valet service. The daily free dinner will be pushed back from 6pm to 6.30pm due to company cutbacks. Employees will now have to decide between a free meal or a free ride home.</description></item><item><title>More Miami voters report illegitimate party affiliation changes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202cec0f735cd232780bfa8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202cec0f735cd232780bfa8/</guid><description>Miami-Dade Elections Department 2021-22 records show more than 5,000 registered Democrats switched their party affiliation to Republican.
Highlights Miami-Dade Elections Department 2021-22 records show more than 5,000 registered Democrats switched their party affiliation to Republican. The increase comes just as more victims of third-party registrations are coming forward to report that their voter registration was altered without their permission. Republicans celebrated that the number of registered Republican voters in Florida surpassed Democrats in November, credited the change to an aggressive voter registration campaign.</description></item><item><title>Meta shares plunge as Facebook owner misses on earnings, forecast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb72ede85b942e7d365927/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 06:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb72ede85b942e7d365927/</guid><description>Facebook owner Meta Platforms Inc&amp;rsquo;s shares plunged more than 20% late on Wednesday after the social media company posted a weaker-than-expected forecast, blaming Apple&amp;rsquo;s privacy changes and increased competition for users from rivals like TikTok.
Highlights Facebook owner Meta Platforms Inc&amp;rsquo;s (FB.O) shares plunged more than 20% late on Wednesday after the social media company posted a weaker-than-expected forecast. Facebook’s global daily active users declined from the previous quarter for the first time, to 1.</description></item></channel></rss>