<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>walmart on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/walmart/</link><description>Recent content in walmart on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 23:13:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/walmart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge orders Walmart to rehire worker with Down syndrome, provide more than $50,000 in back pay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a8602f4138df8c5744981/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 23:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a8602f4138df8c5744981/</guid><description>The judge, however, denied a request by a federal agency for the retailer to be under tighter government scrutiny for five years.
Highlights Marlo Spaeth prevailed in a disability discrimination lawsuit related to her firing from a Wisconsin store. The judge denied a request to force Walmart to take other actions for the next five years in light of how it treated the woman. Walmart told CNBC on Wednesday that it would comply with the order to give Spaeth her job back.</description></item><item><title>Toddler Shoots Mother, Infant Sibling at Granbury, Texas Walmart</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d73cfc46f7dda712559f72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d73cfc46f7dda712559f72/</guid><description>A toddler accidentally shot his mother and infant sibling outside a Granbury, Texas Walmart Wednesday, police said.
Summary A woman and her infant child are injured after a toddler accidentally fired a gun in a car parked outside a Granbury Walmart on Wednesday morning. Police said a 1-year-old child and a 3-month-old child were inside a vehicle at the time of the incident. The mother of the children, a 23-year-old woman, was standing outside next to the driver’s door while their father, a 26-year-old man, was standing at the rear of the truck.</description></item></channel></rss>