<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>james on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/james/</link><description>Recent content in james on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/james/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trump pays contempt fine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889eb5ac15ad9924e1b9e3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889eb5ac15ad9924e1b9e3/</guid><description>His legal team is expected to file additional documents today related to a sprawling civil financial fraud probe by New York.
Highlights Trump has paid the $110,000 fine levied after he was held in contempt by a New York judge. An attorney for Trump also filed more than a dozen affidavits due Friday in an effort to purge the contempt finding. Trump was fined $10,000 per day through May 6, the date of his most recent attempt to satisfy Judge Arthur Engoron&amp;rsquo;s demands.</description></item><item><title>Grand jury indicts man accused in Brooklyn subway mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278f74d2a1ca44d849baaaa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 11:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278f74d2a1ca44d849baaaa/</guid><description>Frank James, 62, is accused of shooting 10 people on a Manhattan-bound train on April 12. Police estimate James fired a gun 33 times while onboard an N train, police say. The day before the attack, James posted a
Highlights Frank James, 62, is charged with committing a terrorist attack or other violence against a mass transportation system. James is accused of setting off smoke grenades and firing a gun on a crowded train in Brooklyn.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting: Suspect Frank James posted racist rants to YouTube for years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6257134ca769d476db4dc20e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 18:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6257134ca769d476db4dc20e/</guid><description>Frank James, now considered a suspect in connection with the Brooklyn subway shooting, posted a string of antagonistic video rants to a YouTube channel for years.
Highlights Frank James posted hour-long, profanity-laced rants on YouTube channel for years. Police have identified James as a person of interest in the Brooklyn subway shooting. James posted rants about race, politics and current events. At times, he sharply criticized Black Europeans and Americans using strings of slurs and racism, as well as women and the homeless.</description></item><item><title>Parents of teen charged in school shooting to stand trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621849448fcfdc1d906600e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621849448fcfdc1d906600e5/</guid><description>A judge on Thursday ordered the parents of a 15-year-old boy charged with killing four students at his Michigan high school to stand trial on involuntary manslaughter charges.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley is charged as an adult with first-degree murder, assault with intent to murder, terrorism and gun charges in the Nov. 30 shooting at Oxford High School. The 15-year-old is accused of killing four students and a teacher at the Michigan school.</description></item><item><title>Judge says Trump and two adult children must testify in New York attorney general probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eecab10766fd4312e9a23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eecab10766fd4312e9a23/</guid><description>Lawyers for Trump, Donald Trump Jr. and Ivanka Trump attacked New York Attorney General Letitia James for political bias against Trump.
Highlights A New York judge rules that Donald Trump and two of his adult children must comply with subpoenas. The judge also ordered them to turn over evidence for a civil investigation by the state&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s Office. Attorney General Letitia James is investigating whether the Trump Organization improperly stated the valuations of various real estate assets to obtain more favorable loans, insurance rates and tax benefits.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope: Sun shield is fully deployed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4b5719dc7edbace949c41/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4b5719dc7edbace949c41/</guid><description>The unfurling of the observatory&amp;rsquo;s giant sun shade is a major milestone for the $10bn mission.
Summary Its shield is deployed but its mirrors are still stowedThe new James Webb telescope has passed a major milestone in its quest to image the first stars to shine in the cosmos. &amp;ldquo;Unfolding Webb&amp;rsquo;s sun shield in space is an incredible milestone, crucial to the success of the mission,&amp;rdquo; said Greg Robinson, Webb&amp;rsquo;s program director at Nasa Headquarters.</description></item></channel></rss>