<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rioters on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rioters/</link><description>Recent content in rioters on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 18:18:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rioters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Swedish police shoot 3 during fresh riots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dab574b086a07f485d7f7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 18:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dab574b086a07f485d7f7/</guid><description>Three people were injured as police fired warning shots at rioters in the eastern city of Norrkoping. The unrest had started after a far-right politician threatened to burn a copy of the Quran.
Highlights Police fire warning shots at rioters in city of Norrkoping in eastern Sweden. Rioters had gathered after far-right politician threatened to burn copies of the Quran. Sweden&amp;rsquo;s Justice Minister Morgan Johansson tells rioters to &amp;ldquo;Go home, immediately&amp;rdquo; Similar clashes in recent days have caused damage and injuries in several Swedish cities.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioters’ tears, remorse don’t spare them from jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1da39b41e6d4d720586bc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1da39b41e6d4d720586bc/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Florida business owner Robert Palmer cheered on the violence at the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 before he joined the fray. Screaming obscenities, he hurled a wooden plank and a fire extinguisher at police officers trying to ward off the mob.
Summary The Justice Department has undertaken the largest investigation in its history with the probe into rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6. The Justice Department has undertaken the largest investigation in its history with the probe into rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>