<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>scriptsrc on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/scriptsrc/</link><description>Recent content in scriptsrc on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 21:12:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/scriptsrc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>France: Four neo-Nazis arrested for planning 'Jew hunt' during soccer match</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bca879668686dd7523827/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 21:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bca879668686dd7523827/</guid><description>The men, aged between 45-53, were affiliated with far-right neo-Nazi groups and had intended on &amp;quot;hunting Jews&amp;quot; during a soccer match in Strasbourg.
Highlights Four neo-Nazi men in France&amp;rsquo;s Alsace region were indicted for possessing and trafficking an &amp;ldquo;impressive&amp;rdquo; amount of weapons that were intended for use against Jews, prosecutor Edwige Roux-Morizot said on Friday. The men, aged between 45-53, had intended on &amp;ldquo;hunting Jews&amp;rdquo; during a soccer match in Strasbourg, she said.</description></item><item><title>Drunk man leads German police to Nazi altar, weapons</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7785c451687abc1d007c0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7785c451687abc1d007c0/</guid><description>Police confiscated, among other things, a belt of ammunition, two knives, a butterfly knife and three brass knuckles - two of which had blades.
Summary A call from a drunken man led German police officers to a secret Nazi altar, filled with memorabilia, weapons and even pictures of Nazi dictator Adolf Hitler, German police reported. The 53-year-old man had called from his apartment Tuesday night asking for help. Responding, police arrived at his apartment and found a large arsenal of weapons, including knives and firearms, as well as an altar-like structure filled with Nazi iconographyThe man was taken to the hospital.</description></item></channel></rss>