<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>16 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/16/</link><description>Recent content in 16 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/16/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. traffic deaths hit highest level in 16 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62842c383463f9c0d99d8e24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62842c383463f9c0d99d8e24/</guid><description>An estimated 42,915 people died in motor vehicle traffic crashes in the U.S. in 2021.
Highlights An estimated 42,915 people died in motor vehicle traffic crashes in the U.S. in 2021, according to data released Tuesday from the Department of Transportation. The number represents a 10.5% increase from 2020, when 38,824 deaths were reported. Texas is estimated to have had the highest amount of deaths at 4,573, followed by California and Florida.</description></item><item><title>Conservative group trying to ban 16 books from Polk Schools, calling them pornographic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fef6ec6c15d692ed4120d8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 22:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fef6ec6c15d692ed4120d8/</guid><description>A conservative political group in Florida complained that 16 books in public schools&amp;rsquo; libraries contain pornographic material harmful to children.
Highlights Conservative group trying to ban 16 books from Polk Schools, calling them pornographic. Polk County Public Schools Regional Assistant Superintendent John Hill and several of his colleagues gathered 16 books out of media centers Tuesday morning. County Citizens Defending Freedom, a conservative political group, complained to Superintendent Frederick Heid that the novels, graphic novels, autobiographies, and sex education books contain pornographic material harmful to children.</description></item></channel></rss>