<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>zone on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/zone/</link><description>Recent content in zone on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 13:17:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/zone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Newly discovered rainbow-colored fish lives in the ocean's 'twilight zone'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622deeae23d4f0619114f7cc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 13:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622deeae23d4f0619114f7cc/</guid><description>Far beneath the waves surrounding the Maldives, there&amp;rsquo;s a living rainbow in the ocean&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;twilight zone.&amp;quot; Say hello to the rose-veiled fairy wrasse, a colorful species of fish that&amp;rsquo;s new to science.
Highlights The rose-veiled fairy wrasse is the first fish to be described by a Maldivian scientist. The scientific name Cirrhilabrus finifenmaa is a nod to the pink rose, the national flower of the Maldives. Researchers first found the fish in the 1990s, but they thought it was an adult belonging to the red velvet fairy wrasses.</description></item><item><title>NATO rejects Ukraine no-fly zone, says 'not part of this' war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622355028f384398240255d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 12:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622355028f384398240255d6/</guid><description>NATO on Friday rejected Ukrainian calls to help it protect its skies from Russian missiles and warplanes, wary of being dragged into Moscow&amp;rsquo;s war on its neighbour, but Europe promised more sanctions to punish Russian President Vladimir Putin.
Highlights NATO rejects Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s request to set up no-fly zone over Ukraine. G7 countries say they will hold accountable those responsible for war crimes and refuse to recognise any Russian territorial gains. NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg: &amp;ldquo;We are not part of this conflict&amp;rdquo; U.</description></item></channel></rss>