<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bodies on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bodies/</link><description>Recent content in bodies on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:43:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bodies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine: 200 bodies found in basement in Mariupol's ruins</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628da5d03f2bc72094e1eef3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628da5d03f2bc72094e1eef3/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Workers digging through the rubble of an apartment building in Mariupol found 200 bodies in the basement, Ukrainian authorities said Tuesday, as more horrors come to light in the ruined city that has seen some of the worst suffering of the 3-month-old war .
Highlights The town of Bakhmut has been coming under increasing artillery strikes, particularly over the last week, as Russian forces try to press forward to encircle the city of Sieverodonetsk.</description></item><item><title>War in Ukraine: Street in Bucha found strewn with dead bodies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a0db01163a6eda7b4c0fd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a0db01163a6eda7b4c0fd/</guid><description>A reporter entering Bucha, near Kyiv, counts at least 20 bodies of men, one with his hands tied.
Highlights AFP reporter entering Bucha, near Kyiv, counts at least 20 bodies of men, one with his hands tied. Sixteen of the 20 bodies seen by AFP lay either on the pavement or by the verge. Three were sprawled in the middle of the road, and another lay on his side in the courtyard of a destroyed house.</description></item><item><title>Mexico finds 17 bodies buried in backyards, patios</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230c983a8d7e5f566e21889/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 17:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230c983a8d7e5f566e21889/</guid><description>MEXICO CITY (AP) — Volunteer searchers in northern Mexico led authorities to a series of grisly finds: 17 bodies or skeletal remains buried in the backyards and patios of houses in a low-income housing development, prosecutors in the northern border state of Sonora said late Sunday.
Highlights Bodies found at abandoned houses in the city of Ciudad Obregon. Bodies had apparently been killed between six months and a year ago, prosecutors say.</description></item></channel></rss>