<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>worst on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worst/</link><description>Recent content in worst on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/worst/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Study finds Western megadrought is the worst in 1,200 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ae1ac91656a521e5d6581/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ae1ac91656a521e5d6581/</guid><description>In tree ring records dating back to AD 800, the only multidecade drought that came close to today&amp;rsquo;s was in the 1500s. Researchers say climate change is a factor and the U.S. must plan for less water.
Highlights Study finds Western megadrought is the worst in 1,200 years, according to new study. Western U.S. and northern Mexico are experiencing their driest period in at least 1,000 years. Federal water managers declared the first-ever water shortage along the Colorado River last year.</description></item><item><title>Former Milwaukee Co. judge sentenced in child pornography case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6a56bc347458a800ce097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6a56bc347458a800ce097/</guid><description>Brett Blomme, 39, was sentenced to nine years in prison after pleading guilty to the charge on Sept. 28.
Summary MADISON, Wis. (WMTV) - A federal attorney reminded the public that “no one is above the law” Wednesday during the sentencing of a former Milwaukee County Children’s Court judge for distribution of child pornography. Brett Blomme, 39, was sentenced to nine years in prison after pleading guilty to the charge on Sept.</description></item></channel></rss>