<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kansas on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kansas/</link><description>Recent content in kansas on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 12:25:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kansas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kansas Court Strikes Down Gerrymandered Congressional Map</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267e4adb323b2ef0a275abd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 12:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267e4adb323b2ef0a275abd/</guid><description>Kansas Court Strikes Down Gerrymandered Congressional Map Redistricting | The Well News | Pragmatic, Governance, Fiscally Responsible, News &amp;amp; Analysis
Highlights A Kansas judge tosses out a congressional district map drawn by the state’s Republican-controlled Legislature. The map was an unlawful partisan gerrymander aimed at diluting the power of Black and Hispanic voters in and around Kansas City. The ruling is the first time a Kansas judge has applied the state constitution to congressional redistricting.</description></item><item><title>Pink Floyd, a flamingo on the lam from a Kansas zoo since 2005, is seen again in Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62457f3910c71fd8ee9632d5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 10:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62457f3910c71fd8ee9632d5/</guid><description>A video posted by the Coastal Fisheries Division of the Texas Parks and Wildlife Department shows the fugitive flamingo wading into Cox Bay about 120 miles southwest of Houston.
Highlights Pink Floyd, a flamingo on the lam from a Kansas zoo since 2005, is seen again in Texas. A video shows the bird wading into Cox Bay near Port Lavaca, about 120 miles southwest of Houston. Pink Floyd fled from the Sedgwick County Zoo in Wichita, Kan.</description></item><item><title>Omicron explosion spurs nationwide breakdown of services</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da25b91336888dc9c6523b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da25b91336888dc9c6523b/</guid><description>Ambulances in Kansas speed toward hospitals then suddenly change direction because hospitals are full. Employee shortages in New York City cause delays in trash and subway services and diminish the ranks of firefighters and emergency workers.
Summary (AP Photo/Mark J. Terrill)Ambulances in Kansas speed toward hospitals then suddenly change direction because hospitals are full. Employee shortages in New York City cause delays in trash and subway services and diminish the ranks of firefighters and emergency workers.</description></item></channel></rss>