<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>leaders on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/leaders/</link><description>Recent content in leaders on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:15:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/leaders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arkansas doctor sued for allegedly giving inmates ivermectin without their consent recognized by local leaders for "job well done"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202a521237a41fc9d175b2f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202a521237a41fc9d175b2f/</guid><description>The doctor has also been sued dozens of times for allegedly providing inadequate medical care to detainees, including for mistreating broken bones.
Highlights Dr. Robert Karas has been accused of treating COVID-positive detainees with anti-parasitic drug ivermectin. The ACLU has sued Karas on behalf of four inmates for the alleged treatment. Local officials agreed to commend Karas for a &amp;ldquo;job well done&amp;rdquo; in his handling of the coronavirus pandemic. The local doctor has not shied away from touting the use of the drug to treat COVID, despite the CDC and other agencies advising against doing so.</description></item><item><title>California man driving to White House to kill leaders on 'hit list' arrested in Iowa, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</guid><description>A heavily armed California man was arrested in Iowa after he told law enforcement officers that he would &amp;quot;do whatever it takes&amp;quot; to kill government leaders on
Summary The man, Kuachua Brillion Xiong, 25, has been held in the Pottawattamie County Jail in Council Bluffs since Thursday, according to sheriff&amp;rsquo;s records. Xiong had been driving from his home near Sacramento, California, since Dec. 18 &amp;ldquo;with the intention of driving straight to the White House &amp;hellip; to kill persons in power,&amp;rdquo; Larson wrote.</description></item></channel></rss>