<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dna on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dna/</link><description>Recent content in dna on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 23:13:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dna/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Very hungry bear ‘Hank the Tank’ is in fact three bears, DNA shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6219627ea04ef6082175e301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 23:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6219627ea04ef6082175e301/</guid><description>Officials say a trio of oversized bears is responsible for home invasions that had been blamed on a 500lb black bear dubbed Hank the Tank
Highlights California Department of Fish and Wildlife will soon begin trapping bears in Lake Tahoe area. The agency says the bears are responsible for more than 150 incidents in the region straddling Northern California and Nevada. One of the Hanks smashed a window on Friday and squeezed into a house in the Tahoe Keys neighbourhood.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco Police reportedly link woman to crime using DNA taken from her rape kit San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 15:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</guid><description>San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out
Highlights San Francisco police used DNA collected from rape exam to link a woman to a crime, district attorney says. District attorney Chesa Boudin says use of victims’ DNA could violate the state&amp;rsquo;s Victims’ Bill of Rights as well as constitutional laws related to unreasonable searches and seizures. State senator Scott Wiener, who represents the city, says lawmakers are seeking to determine whether a change in state law was needed to prevent the practice.</description></item><item><title>Official: Police used fake DNA reports during interrogations.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03087cd2c300f48f763a1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03087cd2c300f48f763a1/</guid><description>VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — Virginia Beach police used forged documents that linked people&amp;rsquo;s DNA to a crime to get them to confess or cooperate with investigators, Virginia&amp;rsquo;s outgoing attorney general announced Wednesday.
Summary VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — Virginia Beach police used forged documents that linked people’s DNA to a crime to get them to confess or cooperate with investigators, Virginia’s outgoing attorney general announced Wednesday. Virginia Beach police serve a city of about 450,000 people along the state’s coast.</description></item></channel></rss>