<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>taking on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/taking/</link><description>Recent content in taking on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 03:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/taking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US State Department looking at possibly labeling Russia a state sponsor of terrorism</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e2ac84f677ed2801dcef4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 03:22:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e2ac84f677ed2801dcef4/</guid><description>US State Department officials are looking at every tool available to them to hold Russia accountable for the war in Ukraine, including the possibility of labeling Russia a state sponsor of terrorism, according to a senior administration official. The process could take weeks before a determination is made, the official said.
Highlights US State Department officials are looking at every tool available to hold Russia accountable for the war in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pepper-Sprayed Man Taking Photos of His Own Children in Arlington: Police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625acec4c676a0d4b268a865/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 14:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625acec4c676a0d4b268a865/</guid><description>Police are looking for a woman who pepper-sprayed a man who was taking photos of his own children in Arlington, Virginia, police said.
Highlights Police are looking for a woman who pepper-sprayed a man who was taking photos of his own children in Arlington, Virginia. The woman reported the man to a security officer Tuesday afternoon in the 1100 block of S. Hayes Street, which is the block where Pentagon City Mall is located.</description></item><item><title>Theater in Mariupol where hundreds were taking refuge has been bombed, according to city council</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623285a34b67a03263c69177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:50:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623285a34b67a03263c69177/</guid><description>The Mariupol City Council has posted an image of the Ukrainian city&amp;rsquo;s theater — where hundreds of people are said to have taken shelter — after it sustained heavy damage in a bombing Wednesday.
Highlights CNN video shows a burned-out theater in the heart of the city of Mariupol. Hundreds of people are said to have been killed in the attack. The Russian city is said to be the largest in number and size of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest city.</description></item></channel></rss>