<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>appeals on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/appeals/</link><description>Recent content in appeals on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:11:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/appeals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Harvey Weinstein’s rape conviction upheld by appeals court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629919579f8d18e53b7203d8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629919579f8d18e53b7203d8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A New York appeals court on Thursday upheld Harvey Weinstein’s rape conviction and 23-year prison sentence, rejecting the former movie mogul’s claim that the judge at his landmark #MeToo trial unfairly allowed women to testify about allegations that weren’t part of the case.
Highlights Harvey Weinstein was convicted in New York in February 2020 of forcibly performing oral sex on a TV and film production assistant, Mimi Haley, in 2006 and raping an aspiring actress in 2013.</description></item><item><title>An appeals court finds Florida's social media law unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d03c3e2cada4724b26a66/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d03c3e2cada4724b26a66/</guid><description>In a blow to Gov. Ron DeSantis, a three-judge panel of the 11th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals said social media companies&amp;rsquo; moderation and curation efforts were protected by the First Amendment.
Highlights An appeals court finds Florida&amp;rsquo;s social media law unconstitutional. The law would require large social media companies to publish standards on how it decides to &amp;ldquo;censor, deplatform, and shadow ban&amp;rdquo; The law was signed by GOP Gov. Ron DeSantis in 2021.</description></item><item><title>AP News: High court reimposes Boston Marathon bomber's death sentence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622264466f6d31bf66694658/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 19:11:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622264466f6d31bf66694658/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court has reinstated the death sentence for Boston Marathon bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev. The justices, by a 6-3 vote Friday, agreed with the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s arguments that a federal appeals court was wrong to throw out the sentence of death a jury imposed on Tsarnaev for his role in the bombing that killed three people near the finish line of the marathon in 2013.
Highlights The Supreme Court reinstated the death sentence for Boston Marathon bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev.</description></item></channel></rss>