<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>country on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/country/</link><description>Recent content in country on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:09:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/country/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>San Francisco Giants manager: 'I don't plan on coming out for the anthem going forward until I feel better about the direction of our country'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62929d8c4f33c669c86a6cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:09:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62929d8c4f33c669c86a6cce/</guid><description>San Francisco Giants manager Gabe Kapler told reporters ahead of his team&amp;rsquo;s Friday game against the Cincinnati Reds that he intends to forgo the pregame US national anthem moving forward.
Highlights Kapler: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t plan on coming out for the anthem going forward until I feel better about the direction of our country&amp;rdquo; Kapler questioned whether the U.S. is truly &amp;ldquo;the land of the free and the home of the brave&amp;rdquo; Comments come after 19 children and two adults were killed at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, by a lone, 18-year-old gunman.</description></item><item><title>No Sri Lankan, rich or poor, spared as economic crisis worsens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252bb8797dda73995d854d5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 11:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252bb8797dda73995d854d5/</guid><description>Savings evaporate, businesses face closure and the Sri Lankan poor struggle to eat as value of the rupee plummets.
Highlights The value of the Sri Lankan rupee has plummeted by 30 per cent against the U.S. dollar this year, making it the worst-performing currency in the world. Food prices have doubled in less than a year, with onions, dhal and rice costing double what they used to. In middle-class neighbourhoods, owners of cafés, bakeries and salons have had to let go of staff and are facing the prospect of closing shop altogether.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: Johnson pledges aid to Zelensky in Kyiv meeting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62524e87dc7deb178ccb2916/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62524e87dc7deb178ccb2916/</guid><description>The PM offers Ukraine 120 armoured vehicles during a visit No 10 calls a &amp;quot;show of solidarity&amp;quot; .
Highlights PM offers Ukraine 120 armoured vehicles during a visit No 10 calls a &amp;ldquo;show of solidarity&amp;rdquo; No 10 offers the vehicles as a show of solidarity with Ukraine. The PM said he has seen the tragic effects of the war, an &amp;ldquo;inexcusable and unnecessary war&amp;rdquo; No10 calls the visit to Ukraine an &amp;ldquo;indefensible and inexcusable&amp;rdquo; war.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine begs for assistance, claiming that Russia is attempting to partition the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241d0a9f0fbde6fee1a8077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 15:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241d0a9f0fbde6fee1a8077/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky accused the West of cowardice Sunday while another top official said Russia was trying to split the nation in two, like North and South Korea.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy calls for fighter jets and tanks to be handed over to the West. Another top official says Russia is trying to split Ukraine in two, like North and South Korea. Russia quickly bans interview from being published from publication by Russian media.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says Moscow is forcibly taking civilians to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d7a2279b617c4551293a2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d7a2279b617c4551293a2/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine accused Moscow on Thursday of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians from shattered Ukrainian cities to Russia, where some may be used as “hostages” to pressure Kyiv to give up.
Highlights Ukraine says 402,000 people, including 84,000 children, have been taken to Russia. The Kremlin gave nearly identical numbers for those who have been relocated, but said they wanted to go to Russia. Ukraine’s rebel-controlled eastern regions are predominantly Russian-speaking, and many people there have supported close ties to Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky refuses US offer to evacuate, saying 'I need ammunition, not a ride'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b08330e17b424031d49a1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b08330e17b424031d49a1/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has turned down an offer from the United States of evacuation from the capital city Kyiv, the Ukraine embassy in Britain said Saturday on Twitter.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has turned down an offer from the United States of evacuation from the capital city Kyiv, the Ukraine embassy in Britain said Saturday on Twitter. &amp;ldquo;The fight is here; I need ammunition, not a ride,&amp;rdquo; he told the US, according to the embassy.</description></item><item><title>Champions League final should not be held in Russia, says Foreign Secretary Liz Truss</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216792828c5450c89f05c57/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216792828c5450c89f05c57/</guid><description>European football&amp;rsquo;s yearly showpiece is due to be held in St Petersburg in May, but the match could now be moved to another host city due to the Ukraine crisis. Foreign Secretary Liz Truss tells Sky News the match &amp;quot;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;quot; be held in Russia.
Highlights Foreign Secretary Liz Truss tells Sky News the match &amp;ldquo;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo; be held in Russia. European football&amp;rsquo;s yearly showpiece is due to be held on 28 May in St Petersburg.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky: Make potential sanctions on Russia public, before a possible invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 05:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said Saturday sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify. He told CNN&amp;rsquo;s Chief International Anchor Christiane Amanpour that he disagreed with the stance that sanctions should only be listed after a potential Russian invasion takes place.</description></item><item><title>Thailand Becomes First Country in Asia to Decriminalize Marijuana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f27c96bd7d2a935b235346/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f27c96bd7d2a935b235346/</guid><description>Thailand on Tuesday became the first country in Asia to approve the de facto decriminalization of marijuana, though authorities have left a grey area around its recreational use.
Highlights (BANGKOK) — Thailand on Tuesday became the first country in Asia to approve the de facto decriminalization of marijuana, though authorities have left a grey area around its recreational use. A tangle of related laws means that production and possession of marijuana remains regulated for the time being, leaving the legal status of recreational marijuana use in a grey area.</description></item><item><title>New Zealand pledges Defence Force assistance to Tonga in aftermath of largest volcanic eruption of the 21st century.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e45d52e05452f4250a3b6e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e45d52e05452f4250a3b6e/</guid><description>Summary This content is not available in your region READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Novak Djokovic pictured with young players the day after lawyers say he tested positive for COVID | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da17978f86b29d4bd88492/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da17978f86b29d4bd88492/</guid><description>A photograph taken by the Tennis Association of Serbia showed the world number one meeting with the youngsters but it is not clear if he knew he had coronavirus at the time.
Summary World tennis number one Novak Djokovic appears to have been photographed with young players the day after his lawyers said he tested positive for COVID-19. Djokovic is currently being held in an immigration detention centre in Australia after arriving in the country without proof of vaccination.</description></item><item><title>Scottish 'witches' in line for apology hundreds of years after being burned at the stake</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d258bd05a1e3f8c8fa8e2b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d258bd05a1e3f8c8fa8e2b/</guid><description>Summary This content is not available in your region READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Covid hospitalizations are rising across the country, even in high-vaccination states</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</guid><description>Hospitalization rates have increased in 29 states and territories since Nov. 1, according to an NBC News analysis of data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary The latest surge that is driving up the number of Covid cases across the country is also putting more people in hospitals, even in highly vaccinated states. Hospitalizations around the nation have risen 39 percent from Nov.</description></item></channel></rss>