<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>video on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/video/</link><description>Recent content in video on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 22:08:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police Release Photo After Witnesses Claimed ‘Unarmed’ Pregnant Women Was Shot 5 Times During Arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629934d10ec5aadb0d86095e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 22:08:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629934d10ec5aadb0d86095e/</guid><description>In Kansas City, Missouri, Police Were Responding To A Carjacking Report When 26-year-old Leonna Hale Attempted To Cooperate With Officers Before Being Shot Five Times And Handcuffed On The Ground.
Highlights Leonna Hale, 26, was shot 5 times in Kansas City, Missouri, on Friday. Police were responding to reports of a carjacking when they encountered a pregnant woman and her boyfriend at a Family Dollar. Police report states that officers determined that Hale was armed.</description></item><item><title>More than 800 Houston ISD teachers say they won't be returning to the classroom next year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293ef235eea5a7c3472ef91/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293ef235eea5a7c3472ef91/</guid><description>Houston Teacher’s United tweeted that 1 in 12 teachers in Houston Independent School District have given notice that they won’t be returning next year.
Highlights More than 800 Houston ISD teachers say they won&amp;rsquo;t be returning to the classroom next year. Houston Teacher’s United tweeted that 1 in 12 teachers in Houston Independent School District have given notice that they won’t be returning next year. The number of new applicants for HISD teacher positions is up 40% over this time last year.</description></item><item><title>Store employees fight off hammer-swinging thieves during Newport Beach smash-and-grab robbery: video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c5e378c4c6350ebf7787f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 04:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c5e378c4c6350ebf7787f/</guid><description>A smash-and-grab robbery at a Huntington Beach jewelry store ended with store workers fighting back against the hammer-swinging thieves.
Highlights A smash-and-grab robbery at a jewelry store in Huntington Beach ended with an employee counterpunch. The incident happened at about noon at the Princess Bride Jewelry store in the Bella Terra Mall. Four hooded individuals entered the jewelry store, the first suspect smashes the front jewelry case with a hammer. The employees successfully fought off all four robbers, and the suspects fled the area before police arrived.</description></item><item><title>Mike Tyson won't face charges in altercation with JetBlue passenger, district attorney says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ad559b36ace3deff42ed5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 21:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ad559b36ace3deff42ed5/</guid><description>A California district attorney on Tuesday declined to file charges against Mike Tyson after the former heavyweight boxing champion was recorded on video in a
Highlights A California district attorney on Tuesday declined to file charges against Mike Tyson after the former heavyweight boxing champion was recorded on video in a physical altercation with another passenger on a JetBlue flight. San Mateo County District Attorney Steve Wagstaffe made the decision after reviewing police reports and videos of the April 20 incident.</description></item><item><title>Sheriff's office releases video of shark-infested waters off Florida coast, warns of "dangers below the water"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1fa208dfd0c92b109c6e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 08:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1fa208dfd0c92b109c6e/</guid><description>&amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s important to be aware of the dangers below the water as well as above,&amp;quot; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office wrote.
Highlights The Pasco Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office in Florida released aerial video of shark-infested waters off the Gulf Coast, warning the public to &amp;ldquo;be aware of the dangers below the water as well as above&amp;rdquo; The sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office did not identify the type of sharks in the aerial video but they appear to resemble blacktip sharks, which were captured on drone video last year off Florida near Singer Island.</description></item><item><title>Jurors reject array of defenses at Capitol riot trials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267746727132310c74fd86d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 04:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267746727132310c74fd86d/</guid><description>Jurors have heard — and rejected — an array of excuses and arguments from the first rioters to be tried for storming the U.S. Capitol. The next jury to get a Capitol riot case could hear another novel defense this week at the trial of a retired New York City police officer.
Highlights Thomas Webster, a 20-year veteran of the NYPD, has claimed he was acting in self-defense when he tackled a police officer who was trying to protect the Capitol from a mob on Jan.</description></item><item><title>Officer's camera misses key moment of Patrick Lyoya's death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bda2f9c861e98fc50f5af/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 09:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bda2f9c861e98fc50f5af/</guid><description>Body camera footage of Patrick Lyoya’s fatal encounter with a Michigan police officer shows a close-up view of an intense struggle, but the video goes dark 42 seconds before the officer shoots the Black man in the head.
Highlights Patrick Lyoya, 26, was shot and killed about 8:10 a.m., on April 4, after what police said was a traffic stop. The shooting was captured by Lyoya’s passenger, with a cellphone, and a doorbell camera across the street.</description></item><item><title>'Very scary video' shows parents, kids attacking basketball referee at church athletic facility</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253e3d28eceab262d3b1142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 08:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253e3d28eceab262d3b1142/</guid><description>Police are investigating after a basketball referee was attacked by a group of young basketball players and parents.
Highlights Fight broke out during a game on Sunday afternoon at the Stronghold Christian Church in Lithonia, Georgia. The referee suffered serious injuries and was rushed to the hospital. Video of the incident that has since gone viral shows children and adults punching and kicking the ref. The church&amp;rsquo;s pastor has since released a statement, saying, &amp;ldquo;It is our hope and prayer that those who enter our facility will conduct themselves in the best manner&amp;rdquo; An AAU representative on Monday said it was not a sanctioned AAU game and that the organization had nothing to do with the game or violence that broke out on the court.</description></item><item><title>Former Picayune police officer receives maximum sentence for child porn charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62514e0dbffd455e23bb3dc8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62514e0dbffd455e23bb3dc8/</guid><description>A Picayune man will spend the next 30 years in prison after pleading guilty to producing a video of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct.
Highlights Joshua Christopher Stockstill enticed a child to engage in sexually explicit conduct so he could capture it on his cellphone camera. The video circulated for nearly two years before the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children became aware of it in July 2021.</description></item><item><title>More than 300 dogs found dead in Ukrainian shelter after weeks without food or water due to the war, charity says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bc2b2f421eb6bb877ba14/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 04:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bc2b2f421eb6bb877ba14/</guid><description>Disturbing footage appeared to show dead dogs on the floor of the shelter.
Highlights WARNING: GRAPHIC IMAGES. Video appears to show dead dogs at an animal shelter in Borodyanka, Ukraine. The shelter&amp;rsquo;s 485 dogs remained locked in their cages from the beginning of the war in late February until the end of April. By the time the volunteers finally gained access to the shelter on April 1, all but 150 of the animals had died.</description></item><item><title>A 22-year-old was attacked on the subway by a person shouting anti-gay slurs, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a1be41d95673c743932e0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 22:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a1be41d95673c743932e0/</guid><description>The New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force is investigating an incident in which an unidentified individual was captured on video shouting anti-gay slurs and attacking a 22-year-old on the subway, the NYPD announced this week.
Highlights The New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force is investigating an incident in which an unidentified individual was captured on video shouting anti-gay slurs and attacking a 22-year-old on the A-train. The individual then spit at the victim and repeatedly punched her in the face and head, police say.</description></item><item><title>Buddy, the cat mauled by two dogs in Frankford, heads to foster care</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249b9967a171534a1420b65/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249b9967a171534a1420b65/</guid><description>Buddy, the cat who was mauled by two dogs in Frankford, was taken into foster care Friday morning by a veterinarian who tended to him at the BluePearl Pet Hospital in Philadelphia. The pet will be monitored at his foster home before the Pennsylvania SPCA possibly puts him up for adoption.
Highlights The Pennsylvania SPCA said it will monitor Buddy&amp;rsquo;s progress at his foster home before possibly putting him up for adoption.</description></item><item><title>Police corner black man, twice, for 'wearing a coat'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62449e66fc5d72893b232ea5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 18:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62449e66fc5d72893b232ea5/</guid><description>Eric Taylor, 20, has video evidence showing him being ‘cornered’ by three law enforcement vehicles on Monday, March 28th, at 10:15pm when he was travelling to work from a restaurant. He was
Highlights Eric Taylor, 20, was recently stopped and searched by police officers for being &amp;rsquo;not dressed for the climate&amp;rsquo; He has video evidence showing him being ‘cornered’ by three law enforcement vehicles on Monday, March 28th, at 10:15pm when he was travelling to work from a restaurant.</description></item><item><title>Off-duty officer put his knee on a 12-year-old's neck for more than 20 seconds while breaking up school fight, video shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236b7d9c7f1413873ed895a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236b7d9c7f1413873ed895a/</guid><description>Surveillance video released by the Kenosha Unified School District Friday shows an off-duty Kenosha police officer put his knee on the neck of a 12-year-old girl to restrain her for more than 20 seconds while attempting to break up a fight in the cafeteria of Lincoln Middle School.
Highlights Surveillance video released by the Kenosha Unified School District shows an off-duty officer put his knee on the neck of a 12-year-old girl to restrain her for more than 20 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: Arnold Schwarzenegger's anti-war video trends on Russian social media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234d92ebf7812e4e7882ae4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 19:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234d92ebf7812e4e7882ae4/</guid><description>In the video the actor warns Russians they are being fed misinformation over the Ukraine war.
Highlights The actor warns Russians they are being fed misinformation over the Ukraine war. &amp;ldquo;The strength and the heart of the Russian people have always inspired me,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;That is why I hope that you will let me tell you the truth about the war in Ukraine,&amp;rdquo; the actor says in a video posted on YouTube.</description></item><item><title>Russian attacks hit at least 9 Ukrainian medical facilities, visual evidence shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d6192b36dc296ba7345b1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d6192b36dc296ba7345b1/</guid><description>A Washington Post analysis verified nine incidents where hospitals faced direct damage as a result of a reported Russian attack. Three of the facilities specifically served women or children.
Highlights The Washington Post examined more than 500 videos and photos, reviewed social media posts from the hospitals, spoke to witnesses and hospital employees. It verified nine incidents, including the strike in Mariupol, where hospitals faced direct damage as a result of a reported Russian attack.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky refuses US offer to evacuate, saying 'I need ammunition, not a ride'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b08330e17b424031d49a1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 05:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b08330e17b424031d49a1/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has turned down an offer from the United States of evacuation from the capital city Kyiv, the Ukraine embassy in Britain said Saturday on Twitter.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has turned down an offer from the United States of evacuation from the capital city Kyiv, the Ukraine embassy in Britain said Saturday on Twitter. &amp;ldquo;The fight is here; I need ammunition, not a ride,&amp;rdquo; he told the US, according to the embassy.</description></item><item><title>Connecticut Man Arrested After Racist Tirade Over Smoothie, Cops Say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edec720ff1e559f57c5e50/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edec720ff1e559f57c5e50/</guid><description>A Connecticut man, James Iannazzo, was arrested on bias intimidation and trespassing charges after a racist tirade at a smoothie shop, cops say - and Merrill&amp;hellip;
Summary Roughly 30 minutes later, police say he called 911 from his home for a child having an allergic reaction. When employees couldn&amp;rsquo;t answer, cops say Iannazzo became irate, yelling vulgarly, throwing a drink at one employee and questioning her immigration status. Cops say he was asked to leave and refused, even attempting to open a locked &amp;ldquo;Employees Only&amp;rdquo; door to get behind the store&amp;rsquo;s counter.</description></item><item><title>Three men convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery sentenced to life in prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8b805d451137bd8cc0f83/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8b805d451137bd8cc0f83/</guid><description>The three white men convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery, a Black man, in Georgia were sentenced Friday to life in prison.
Summary The three white men convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery, a Black man, in Georgia were sentenced Friday to life in prison. The sentences for Travis McMichael, who shot Arbery; and his father, Gregory McMichael, do not carry the possibility of parole. An attorney for Travis McMichael said he &amp;ldquo;should have the opportunity to show that he&amp;rsquo;s grown, to show that he&amp;rsquo;s changed.</description></item><item><title>John Madden, football legend, dies at 85</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbcf4c809e5182b7aa7d4b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbcf4c809e5182b7aa7d4b/</guid><description>Summary The NFL announced Madden’s passing today. Madden’s influence on the sport of football is impossible to overstate. But as great a coach as he was, he did more for the sport after he retired from coaching. The youngest generation of football fans that can’t even remember him as a broadcaster, let alone as a coach, is still influenced by Madden’s giant presence in the sport. John Madden may have been the single most influential person in the history of the sport of football.</description></item><item><title>Teen who urinated on WW2 memorial and posted video online is jailed for four years.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</guid><description>The 19-year-old male was found to have &amp;lsquo;desecrated&amp;rsquo; a portrait of a war veteran, and was deemed guilty under a strict new law introduced in March this year following a similar case
Summary A teenager has been sentenced to four years in prison after being seen urinating on a World War Two memorial. 19-year-old Matvey Yuferov actually recorded himself urinating on a portrait of a World War Two veteran on November 25, in the Moscow district of Izmailovo, and uploaded the footage online.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest bystander for filming traffic stop, allegedly interfering with investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 05:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</guid><description>Description Killeen police arrest a man for interfering with an officer.
Summary KILLEEN, Texas (KWTX) - The Killeen Police Department arrested a man early Saturday morning for interfering with an officer conducting a traffic stop. “I have a right to be there. I have a right to record and I also have a right to free speech,” could be heard from the unnamed individual in the video. The video which is just over 130 Seconds long shows a man walking down the sidewalk when he sees police conducting a traffic stop.</description></item></channel></rss>