<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>data on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/data/</link><description>Recent content in data on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 23:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former top Republican lawmaker in Colorado received leak of voting data</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282dad5a12759331f0644f9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 23:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282dad5a12759331f0644f9/</guid><description>A former Republican minority leader of the Colorado legislature is among the recipients of a trove of sensitive voting data leaked by a county official working with activists seeking to prove President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s false stolen-election claims, according to court records reviewed by Reuters.
Highlights Elbert County clerk Dallas Schroeder, a former Republican minority leader of the Colorado legislature, is among the recipients of a trove of sensitive voting data leaked by a county official.</description></item><item><title>U.S. plastic recycling rate drops to close to 5% - report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273b10be042fe9f5187ce4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 11:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273b10be042fe9f5187ce4e/</guid><description>The rate of plastic waste recycling in the United States fell to between 5%-6% in 2021 as some countries stopped accepting U.S. waste exports and as plastic waste generation surged to new highs, according to a report released on Wednesday.
Highlights Report: U.S. plastic waste recycling rate fell to between 5-6% in 2021. Decline coincides with a sharp drop in plastic waste exports, which had counted as recycled plastic. China and Turkey have since implemented plastic import bans and other countries set plastic waste contamination limits.</description></item><item><title>COVID cases continue steep decline in U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222040052acfee18920c8ba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 12:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222040052acfee18920c8ba/</guid><description>COVID case rates continued a steep decline over the last few weeks with the seven-day rolling average dropping to roughly 59,000 cases a day.
Highlights COVID case rates continued a steep decline over the last two weeks with the seven-day rolling average dropping to roughly 59,000 cases a day. The lowest case rates were seen in Nebraska with six cases per 100,000 people, followed by Delaware and Maryland. Montana and Alaska had the highest rates at 49 cases per cent and 47 in Alaska.</description></item><item><title>State data shows how often judges approved no-knock warrants</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621929cd888a87495d733dab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 19:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621929cd888a87495d733dab/</guid><description>New data that police departments across the state are now required to track is providing a glimpse into how often judges have approved no-knock search warrants. The data from the Minnesota Bureau of Criminal Apprehension shows judges signed off on at least 70 no-knock warrants since last September. That’s when a state law took effect […]
Highlights New data shows judges signed off on at least 70 no-knock warrants since last September.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says 'massive cyber attack' has shut down government websites | World News | Sky News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ac3a71633353f21ddbc6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ac3a71633353f21ddbc6/</guid><description>Asked whether Russia was suspected as being behind the attack, a spokesman said: &amp;quot;It&amp;rsquo;s too early to draw conclusions, but there is a long record of Russian assaults against Ukraine.&amp;quot;
Summary Ukraine has been hit by a &amp;ldquo;massive cyber attack&amp;rdquo;, knocking a number of key government websites offline and issuing a warning to the public to &amp;ldquo;expect the ​​​​​​​worst&amp;rdquo;. Websites for the foreign ministry, national security and defence council and the government&amp;rsquo;s cabinet of ministers were among those affected.</description></item></channel></rss>