<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>voting on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/voting/</link><description>Recent content in voting on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:16:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/voting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Federal judge blocks Florida restrictive voting law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246d0a4218d330f871ce3ff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246d0a4218d330f871ce3ff/</guid><description>A federal judge barred Florida from enforcing the bulk of its new restrictive voting law on Thursday, siding with advocates who said the law was discriminatory.
Highlights A federal judge declared the bulk of Florida&amp;rsquo;s new voting rules unconstitutional and issued a permanent injunction barring their enforcement. The Florida law, known as Senate Bill 90, added new restrictions on drop boxes, third-party voter registration, mail voting, and &amp;ldquo;line warming&amp;rdquo; activities like giving voters food and water while they wait in line to cast a ballot.</description></item><item><title>Judge strikes down 4 Arkansas voting laws as unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62355908597240a054c4b714/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 04:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62355908597240a054c4b714/</guid><description>Four Arkansas voting laws passed last year were struck down Friday after a Pulaski County circuit judge ruled that all four violated the Arkansas Constitution by placing undue burdens on voters.
Highlights Four laws passed by the General Assembly last year affecting voters in Arkansas were struck down Friday. Pulaski County Circuit Judge Wendell Griffen ruled that all four of the laws violated the Arkansas Constitution by placing undue burdens on voters.</description></item><item><title>Alaska Supreme Court upholds ranked choice voting and top-four primary</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea4c03f24e7810db62532d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea4c03f24e7810db62532d/</guid><description>Summary Bethel citizens vote at the Yupiit Piciryarait Cultural Center in Bethel, Alaska on Nov. 3, 2020. (Katie Basile/KYUK)The Alaska Supreme Court on Wednesday upheld as valid a voter-approved election system that would end party primaries in the state and institute ranked choice voting in general elections. The new system, narrowly approved by voters in 2020, is unique among states and set to be used for this year’s elections. Under the open primary, the top four vote-getters in a race, regardless of party affiliation, would advance to the general election, where ranked choice voting would be used.</description></item></channel></rss>