<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blood on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/blood/</link><description>Recent content in blood on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 08:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/blood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lavrov claims Zelensky has Jewish blood 'just like Hitler'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f93924659d0fc6cf9f535/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f93924659d0fc6cf9f535/</guid><description>The Russian Foreign Minister attacked the President of Ukraine in an interview in Italy and reiterated the claims that his country has elements of Nazism.
Highlights Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov attacked Ukraine and its president Volodymyr Zelensky in an interview in Italy. Claimed that &amp;ldquo;the fact that he is a Jew does not negate the Nazi elements in his country&amp;rdquo; Lavrov also said that the upcoming anniversary of Russia&amp;rsquo;s liberation at the end of World War II will have no bearing on Moscow&amp;rsquo;s military operations in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Body found in duffel bag in Queens park; Orsolya Gaal identified, police questioning teen son</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d3a54ac3c8570c8a697be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d3a54ac3c8570c8a697be/</guid><description>A woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a duffel bag in a New York City park Saturday. Police are now questioning her teen son.
Highlights A woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a duffel bag in a Queens park early Saturday morning. Police say she was not dismembered but placed in the bag and closed off. Police are now questioning her teen son. The family of four lives in the home where she was found dead in Queens park.</description></item><item><title>Polish state has ‘blood on its hands’ after death of woman refused an abortion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</guid><description>Family says young mother’s health deteriorated rapidly after the twins she was carrying died a week apart in the womb
Summary The family of a Polish woman who died on Tuesday after doctors refused to perform an abortion when the foetus’s heart stopped beating have accused the government of having “blood on their hands”. Her death comes a year after Poland introduced one of the most restrictive abortion laws in Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>