<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>global on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/global/</link><description>Recent content in global on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 20:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/global/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Fossil fuels are choking humanity’: Major UN report sounds the alarm on climate impacts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d2d0583ddef185fb07540/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 20:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d2d0583ddef185fb07540/</guid><description>The IPCC&amp;rsquo;s latest report examines the impacts of the climate emergency on nature and people around the world.
Highlights The world faces unavoidable climate hazards in the next two decades with global heating of 1.5 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels. The U.N. &amp;rsquo;s Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, approved by 195 member states, makes clear that minor, reactive or incremental changes are no longer sufficient to tackle the climate emergency. The analysis provides world leaders with a gold standard summation of modern climate science at a time when there are fears Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine could distract policymakers from taking coordinated action.</description></item><item><title>Extreme heat in oceans ‘passed point of no return’ in 2014</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb3cf5463bd63d051ae416/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 02:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb3cf5463bd63d051ae416/</guid><description>Formerly rare high temperatures now covering half of seas and devastating wildlife, study shows
Highlights Extreme heat in the world’s oceans passed the ‘point of no return’ in 2014 and has become the new normal. In some hotspots, extreme temperatures occur 90% of the time, severely affecting wildlife. Scientists analysed sea surface temperatures over the last 150 years, which have risen because of global heating. By 2019, the proportion of the global ocean suffering extreme heat was 57%, according to the study.</description></item><item><title>United States is world’s biggest plastic polluter, report finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c41e9670811afb6b1c14a8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c41e9670811afb6b1c14a8/</guid><description>None
Summary The United States is by far the biggest contributor to global plastic waste in the world, according to a new report submitted to the federal government Wednesday that called for a national strategy to tackle the growing crisis. On average, every American generates 130 kilograms (286 pounds) of plastic waste per year, with Britain next on the list at 99 kilos per person per year, followed by South Korea at 88 kilos per year.</description></item></channel></rss>