<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>v on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/v/</link><description>Recent content in v on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 08:24:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/v/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court potential shock move on abortion sends protesters onto Washington streets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270e682e170eb5e76ac974c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 08:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270e682e170eb5e76ac974c/</guid><description>Anti-abortion activists and pro-abortion rights supporters took to the streets of Washington on Tuesday after news that the U.S. Supreme Court may overturn the 1973 Roe v Wade ruling that legalized abortion.
Highlights A leaked initial draft majority opinion suggests the court has voted to overturn Roe v. Wade. The ruling would be the court&amp;rsquo;s most sweeping since former President Donald Trump succeeded in naming three justices to the court, cementing a 6-3 conservative majority.</description></item><item><title>Leaked U.S. Supreme Court decision suggests majority set to overturn Roe v. Wade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270af6417eb586e1237bcc2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 04:28:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270af6417eb586e1237bcc2/</guid><description>The U.S. Supreme Court looks set to vote to overturn the Roe v. Wade decision that legalized abortion nationwide, according to a leaked initial draft majority opinion published by Politico on Monday.
Highlights Leaked report says Roe v Wade ruling was wrong, says U.S. Supreme Court. Leaked opinion written by Justice Samuel Alito preparing for a majority of the court to overturn the landmark Roe v. Wade abortion rights decision later this year.</description></item></channel></rss>