<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>writing on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/writing/</link><description>Recent content in writing on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 05:12:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Montana hiker found dead after suspected grizzly bear attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ff22dc91a0e979c49615a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 05:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ff22dc91a0e979c49615a/</guid><description>A hiker who had been reported missing in Montana earlier this week was found dead Friday after a suspected encounter with a grizzly bear.
Highlights Craig Clouatre, 40, was hiking with a friend Wednesday in the Six Mile Creek area. He was found dead Friday after a suspected encounter with a grizzly bear, sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office says. Sheriff Brad Bichler says the pair were supposed to meet back up Wednesday night, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t show up that night.</description></item><item><title>Israeli attack over Damascus kills two -Syrian State Media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622749ea068e2734fc60ad23/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 12:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622749ea068e2734fc60ad23/</guid><description>An Israeli attack over the Syrian capital Damascus on Monday killed two civilians and left some material damage, Syrian State Media reported citing a military source.
Highlights Israel has mounted frequent attacks against what it has described as Iranian targets in Syria. Tehran-backed forces including Lebanon&amp;rsquo;s Hezbollah have deployed over the last decade to support President Bashar al-Assad in Syria&amp;rsquo;s war. &amp;ldquo;Our air defences downed most of the Israeli missiles,&amp;rdquo; the military source said.</description></item></channel></rss>