<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>girl on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/girl/</link><description>Recent content in girl on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 05:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/girl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Please send the police now': Uvalde student called 911 multiple times during shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291aeaa021c7a51c7009ce4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 05:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291aeaa021c7a51c7009ce4/</guid><description>At least two children called 911, one of whom begged for help, during Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s mass shooting at a Uvalde, Texas, elementary school.
Highlights One girl called 911 more than five times, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Steven C. McCraw said. He did not name the children but said both of them survived the attack at Robb Elementary School. 19 students and two teachers were killed in the shooting at a Uvalde, Texas, elementary school.</description></item><item><title>A 15-year-old suspect has been arrested in the shooting death of an 11-year-old girl in the Bronx, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62897134ced30d853be4fa0a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 23:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62897134ced30d853be4fa0a/</guid><description>A 15-year-old was arrested Friday in connection with the fatal shooting of an 11-year-old girl in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Bronx neighborhood earlier this week, police said.
Highlights Kyhara Tay, 11, was shot in the abdomen with a stray bullet in the Bronx on Monday. A 15-year-old was arrested Friday in connection with the shooting, police say. The shooting comes as New York City grapples with an uptick of gun violence that has reached even the city’s youngest.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana girl, 4, dies after grandmother allegedly forced her to drink bottle of whiskey</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62640952c85330f1c8831916/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62640952c85330f1c8831916/</guid><description>A Louisiana child died after the girl’s grandmother forced her to drink a bottle of whiskey while her mother watched, authorities said Friday.
Highlights China Record, 4, was found with a blood alcohol level of.68 after officers were dispatched to a home east of Baton Rouge on Thursday morning. She was forced to drink half a bottle of whiskey while her mother watched, police said. Her cause of death was acute alcohol poisoning, the East Baton Rouge Coroner’s Office said.</description></item><item><title>Racism cited as factor in police strip search of girl, 15, at London school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62336c90b37f1469895cc677/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62336c90b37f1469895cc677/</guid><description>Black child’s ordeal, which involved exposure of intimate body parts, took place without parental consent, review finds
Highlights Police strip searched 15-year-old girl in London school&amp;rsquo;s medical room. Investigation finds racism was likely to have been an ‘influencing factor’ in officers’ actions. Police apologised for what a senior officer described as the child’s “truly regrettable” treatment. Child was made to bend over, spread her legs and use her hands to spread her buttocks while coughing.</description></item><item><title>LAPD to release video in police killing of 14-old-girl in clothing store</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61caee65fe7e5178a754e2f4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61caee65fe7e5178a754e2f4/</guid><description>The death of Valentina Orellana-Peralta, who was shopping with her mother for a holiday dress, raises concerns about police use of deadly force
Summary The Los Angeles police department has released body-camera footage and surveillance video of an incident in which an officer shot and killed a 14-year-old girl inside a department store while firing at another person. Valentina Orellana-Peralta was killed when police fired on a suspect inside a department store.</description></item><item><title>Sheriff: ‘Sexual predator’ facing charges after 6-year-old girl tests positive for STD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7a2897d63738fed8bdc51/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7a2897d63738fed8bdc51/</guid><description>Summary SUPERIOR, Ariz. (WHDH) — A man referred to by authorities as a “sexual predator” is facing charges after a 6-year-old girl reportedly tested positive for a sexually transmitted disease. Deputies were contacted by a Queen Creek urgent care clinic on Nov. 14 after a 6-year-old child tested positive for a sexually transmitted disease, the sheriff’s office said. During the investigation, the child revealed that her father’s roommate, identified as Sullivan, had sexually assaulted her, the sheriff’s office added.</description></item></channel></rss>