<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>masturbating on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/masturbating/</link><description>Recent content in masturbating on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 04:20:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/masturbating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bay Area cop charged with masturbating in front of family during domestic violence call</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281d104ea9e6d681ed13356/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 04:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281d104ea9e6d681ed13356/</guid><description>The officer is now on administrative leave.
Highlights Matthew Dominguez, 32, charged with misdemeanor indecent exposure after responding to a domestic violence call. His arraignment is scheduled for June 22. The officer is now on administrative leave, the District Attorney’s Office said. An officer investigating the kidnapping of 3-month-old Brandon Cuellar was allegedly drunk during the investigation, tipping off an FBI agent at the scene, KRON reported. This is not the first misconduct incident within the past month involving San Jose police in the Bay Area since an officer was drunk during an investigation into a kidnapping of a baby boy, according to a KRON report.</description></item><item><title>Florida man arrested for allegedly masturbating on a flight to Boston</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62540cf59b01a6b56a6b4813/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 11:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62540cf59b01a6b56a6b4813/</guid><description>A Florida man was arrested for allegedly masturbating and exposing his penis to a woman next to him on a flight from Newark to Boston.
Highlights Donald Edward Robinson, 76, of Bonita Springs, Florida, was charged with one count of lewd, indecent, and obscene acts while in the special aircraft jurisdiction of the U.S. He was arrested Sunday morning at Boston Logan International Airport and will appear in a federal court in Boston at a later date.</description></item><item><title>Man arrested after allegedly masturbating in Florida Starbucks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f6aa4a03a6a2565a8053e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 16:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f6aa4a03a6a2565a8053e/</guid><description>A 27-year-old self-described model was arrested last week after allegedly masturbating in front of horrified onlookers inside a Starbucks cafe.A self-
Highlights Blake Reign, 27, was allegedly seen by several witnesses pleasuring himself at the Starbucks on Collins Ave and 29th Street in Miami Beach, Florida. He was charged with lewd and lascivious behaviour, disorderly conduct in an establishment, and resisting an officer without violence. Police used ‘closed fist distraction blows’ and kicked him in the lower back area as well, according to the arrest report.</description></item></channel></rss>