<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hurt on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hurt/</link><description>Recent content in hurt on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hurt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 injured, 3 law enforcement officials hurt after gunfire erupts in Charleston, S.C.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296b67248eaf29125585fc3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296b67248eaf29125585fc3/</guid><description>Ten people were injured and three law enforcement officials were hurt Monday night after gunfire erupted in downtown Charleston, South Carolina, according to police.
Highlights Four of the 10 people injured were in critical condition in hospitals. A 17-year-old was among the injured, the rest were adults, police said. Two Charleston County Sheriff’s Office deputies were assaulted while trying to control the crowd, resulting in minor injuries. The shooting occurred during a violent Memorial Day weekend, a preliminary count found that gun violence left at least 156 people dead and 412 injured from 5 p.</description></item><item><title>Reports of active shooter at Richland Fred Meyer; injuries reported</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202263a42a6c9866f7add7b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 08:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202263a42a6c9866f7add7b/</guid><description>[UPDATE 11:45 p. m. Monday] Richland Police announced 39-year-old Aaron Christopher Kelly, the suspect in Monday morning&amp;rsquo;s shooting has been arrested. Police also say the surviving victim of the shooting is currently in critical condition in an area hospital. &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; Images have been released by law enforcement of the suspected shooter from the Fred Meyer in Richland. Police tell us a white male fired shots inside the Richland Fred Meyer this morning.</description></item><item><title>Outlets hurt by dwindling public interest in news in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca61aa085cc54e084f7f8a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 01:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca61aa085cc54e084f7f8a/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. To a large degree, 2021 represented the inevitable hangover.
Summary (AP Photo)NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. The Trump era saw explosive subscriber growth for some digital news sites like The New York Times and Washington Post.</description></item></channel></rss>