<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pushed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pushed/</link><description>Recent content in pushed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 15:14:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pushed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We’re finished’: Sri Lankans pushed to the brink by financial crisis ......Thousands take to the streets to call for the resignation of president Gotabaya Rajapaksa</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252f418071746bcc5289c64/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252f418071746bcc5289c64/</guid><description>Thousands take to the streets to call for the resignation of president Gotabaya Rajapaksa
Highlights Sri Lanka has descended into its worst financial crisis since independence. Food, fuel, medicine and electricity have become increasingly scarce. Calls for the president, Gotabaya Rajapaksa – frequently referred to as Gota – to step down. Young people furious at what they see as their own futures being set alight by divisions and incompetencies of the older generation.</description></item><item><title>Activists pushed the IRS to drop facial recognition. They won, but they're not done yet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622772a6c8559758bcd68c03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 15:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622772a6c8559758bcd68c03/</guid><description>The IRS backed away from a plan to use facial-recognition software to verify users of its website. Privacy and digital rights activists were buzzing about a recent victory. The IRS will keep using facial recognition for the rest of the tax-
Highlights The IRS backed away from using facial-recognition software to verify users of its website. Privacy and digital rights activists were among those urging the IRS to back away from the plan.</description></item></channel></rss>