<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>astroworld on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/astroworld/</link><description>Recent content in astroworld on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 06:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/astroworld/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Travis Scott, Astroworld Victims Battle in Court Over Rapper’s Charity Initiative</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d8ca37fa9ea0c3eb74ff9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 06:18:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d8ca37fa9ea0c3eb74ff9/</guid><description>Attorneys for the families of Astroworld victims are fighting with Travis Scott&amp;rsquo;s lawyers over a gag order in the case.
Highlights Attorneys for Astroworld victims are fighting with Travis Scott&amp;rsquo;s lawyers over a gag order that’s been imposed on lawyers working on the massive case. The families of a young boy killed at the festival say Scott is using the media – specifically the launch of a charitable initiative called Project HEAL – to try to win favor with potential jurors.</description></item><item><title>In wake of Astroworld tragedy, Houston, Harris County officials launch joint special events task force</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620903d25bc9494c44a4c415/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 13:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620903d25bc9494c44a4c415/</guid><description>Mayor Turner said the group will avoid studying what went wrong at the deadly 2021&amp;hellip;
Highlights Houston-Harris Special Events Task Force formed by Houston Mayor Sylvester Turner and Precinct 2 Commissioner Adrian Garcia. Ten concert-goers were killed and hundreds injured following a massive crowd surge at the Nov. 5 NRG Stadium concert. The city&amp;rsquo;s office of special events manages annually nearly 1,000 events attended by more than 10 million people. Turner: &amp;ldquo;The line of demarcation between the city and county properties is invisible to the public&amp;rdquo; The task force will make recommendations to improve communication, protocols and permitting requirements in Houston and Harris County &amp;ldquo;to ensure consistent operation standards for future events,&amp;rdquo; officials said.</description></item></channel></rss>