<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2018 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2018/</link><description>Recent content in 2018 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 22:09:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Illinois man convicted of giving son rifle he used to kill 4</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286c009e3eab34dff2e5e63/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 22:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286c009e3eab34dff2e5e63/</guid><description>An Illinois man faces up to three years in prison after being convicted of illegally giving his son an assault-style rifle he later used to shoot and kill four people in 2018 at a Waffle House in Tennessee
Highlights Jeffrey Reinking convicted of illegal delivery of a firearm to a person who had been treated for mental illness within the past five years. Prosecutors said Reinking knew his son, Travis Reinking, had undergone mental health treatment in 2016.</description></item><item><title>Tesla stockholders ask judge to silence Musk in fraud case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d02621548d4d67b4cc1fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d02621548d4d67b4cc1fa/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A group of Tesla shareholders suing CEO Elon Musk over some 2018 tweets about taking the company private is asking a federal judge to order Musk to stop commenting on the case. Lawyers for stockholders of the Austin, Texas-based company also say in court documents that the judge in the case has ruled that Musk&amp;rsquo;s tweets about having “funding secured” to take Tesla private were false, and that his comments also violate a 2018 court settlement with U.</description></item></channel></rss>