<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>private on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/private/</link><description>Recent content in private on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/private/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amazon’s Twitch, Discord, 4chan face New York AG probe after Buffalo shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285ed4fa471f2a8fba31693/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285ed4fa471f2a8fba31693/</guid><description>Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Twitch, Discord, 4chan and 8chan will be among the platforms her office will probe.
Highlights New York&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General Letitia James will investigate social media companies in connection to the shooting. The shooter initially livestreamed his actions to Twitch during the massacre at Tops grocery store on Saturday. James&amp;rsquo; office will also focus on 4chan, 8chan and Discord, but is not limited to those platforms. Investigators will look at online resources the gunman &amp;ldquo;used to discuss and amplify his intentions and acts to carry out this attack,&amp;rdquo; the AG said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Tesla stockholders ask judge to silence Musk in fraud case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d02621548d4d67b4cc1fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d02621548d4d67b4cc1fa/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A group of Tesla shareholders suing CEO Elon Musk over some 2018 tweets about taking the company private is asking a federal judge to order Musk to stop commenting on the case. Lawyers for stockholders of the Austin, Texas-based company also say in court documents that the judge in the case has ruled that Musk&amp;rsquo;s tweets about having “funding secured” to take Tesla private were false, and that his comments also violate a 2018 court settlement with U.</description></item><item><title>Popular anti-work subreddit goes private after awkward Fox News interview</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f26ea5a7d3953292a90809/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 10:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f26ea5a7d3953292a90809/</guid><description>r/antiwork subreddit goes dark after Fox News interview
Highlights A wildly popular subreddit called r/antiwork, where users discuss ways to reform exploitative labour systems and commiserate over pandemic working conditions, has suddenly gone private after a testy interview between Fox News anchor Jesse Watters and one of the forum’s moderators. r/antiwork has been around since 2013, but has seen a rocket-ship rise to popularity during the strains of the pandemic. The group was so popular Fox News sought to interview one of its moderators, Doreen Ford.</description></item></channel></rss>