<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>justice on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/justice/</link><description>Recent content in justice on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/justice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justice Dept. to review response to Texas school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294482e2f8a584828810c6d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294482e2f8a584828810c6d/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — The Justice Department said Sunday it will review the law enforcement response to the Texas school shooting, an unusual federal look back prompted by questions about the shifting and at times contradictory information from authorities that have enraged a community in shock and sorrow.
Highlights The Justice Department will review the law enforcement response to the Texas school shooting. The review will be conducted in a fair, impartial and independent manner and the findings will be made public.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court says leaked abortion draft is authentic; Roberts orders investigation into leak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271656c74189e2f9d880aa9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 17:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271656c74189e2f9d880aa9/</guid><description>Roberts noted that the Supreme Court draft ruling, which would overturn decades-old abortion protections, does not represent the court&amp;rsquo;s final decision.
Highlights Chief Justice John Roberts confirms authenticity of leaked draft court opinion that would toss out longstanding abortion rights. The 98-page draft opinion was penned by Justice Samuel Alito, one of six conservatives on a court that has moved sharply to the right in the wake of the Trump administration.</description></item><item><title>'Freedom Convoy' leader Pat King charged with perjury, obstruction of justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fa55b9246872611c71b20/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 06:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fa55b9246872611c71b20/</guid><description>Ottawa convoy protest organizer Pat King is now facing perjury and obstruction of justice charges related to testimony he gave at his bail review hearing last week.
Highlights Ottawa convoy protest organizer Pat King is now facing perjury and obstruction of justice charges related to testimony he gave at his bail review hearing last week. King was arrested on Feb. 18 on charges relating to his involvement in the three-week protest against COVID-19 restrictions that overran the streets of Ottawa.</description></item><item><title>Jackson confirmed as first Black female high court justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f46293f1eb44866a7eef0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f46293f1eb44866a7eef0/</guid><description>The Senate confirmed Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Thursday, shattering a historic barrier by securing her place as the first Black female justice.
Highlights The Senate confirmed Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Thursday. She will take her seat when Justice Stephen Breyer retires this summer, solidifying the liberal wing of the 6-3 conservative-dominated court. Jackson will be just the third Black justice, after Thurgood Marshall and Clarence Thomas.</description></item><item><title>U.S. unveils charges against 4 Russian officials over 2012-18 hacking campaigns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623dc78486bfb4084eadeedb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 13:46:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623dc78486bfb4084eadeedb/</guid><description>U.S. and British officials on Thursday accused the Russian government of running a years-long campaign to hack into critical infrastructure, including an American nuclear plant and a Saudi oil refinery.
Highlights U.S. and British officials accuse Russian government of running a years-long campaign to hack into critical infrastructure. Announcement was paired with the unsealing of criminal charges against four Russian government officials. Thousands of computers in 135 countries were affected between 2012 and 2018, prosecutors said.</description></item><item><title>Justice Clarence Thomas hospitalized with 'flu-like symptoms'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237ef5ea0c2fa89cc91603c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 03:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237ef5ea0c2fa89cc91603c/</guid><description>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was admitted to Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, DC, on Friday evening &amp;quot;after experiencing flu-like symptoms,&amp;quot; the court&amp;rsquo;s public information office said Sunday evening, but he does not have Covid-19.
Highlights Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was admitted to Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, DC, on Friday evening. Thomas was diagnosed with an infection, and is being treated with intravenous antibiotics. Thomas is expected to be released from the hospital in a day or two.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Proud Boys chairman Tarrio ordered detained pending trial in Capitol riot case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231807d650ab0795eef6523/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231807d650ab0795eef6523/</guid><description>A U.S. judge ordered former Proud Boys chairman Enrique Tarrio be detained while he awaits trial on charges stemming from the U.S. Capitol riots, a Justice Department spokesperson confirmed.
Highlights Former Proud Boys chairman Enrique Tarrio ordered to be detained while he awaits trial on charges stemming from the riots at the U.S. Capitol. Tarrio, 38, is among the most high-profile of more than 775 people criminally charged for their roles in the assault on the Capitol by supporters of then-President Donald Trump in an effort to keep Congress from certifying Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s election victory.</description></item><item><title>Justice Department sues Missouri over new gun law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e9e653ba01b42eabb3110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e9e653ba01b42eabb3110/</guid><description>JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. (AP) — The Department of Justice on Wednesday sued Missouri over a contested new law banning local police from enforcing federal gun laws just days after pulling out of a state crime-fighting partnership.
Highlights Missouri law declares ‘invalid’ federal gun regulations that don’t have an equivalent in Missouri law. Agencies risk being sued for $50,000 by private citizens who believe their Second Amendment rights have been violated. Law also wrecked the crime-fighting partnership with U.</description></item><item><title>NY couple charged with conspiring to launder $4.5 billion in Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203296ceacc02ba39e47676/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 02:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203296ceacc02ba39e47676/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department announced Tuesday its largest-ever financial seizure — more than $3.6 billion — and the arrests of a New York couple accused of conspiring to launder billions of dollars in cryptocurrency stolen from the 2016 hack of a virtual currency exchange.
Highlights Ilya &amp;ldquo;Dutch&amp;rdquo; Lichtenstein, a 34-year-old citizen of Russia and the United States, and his wife, Heather Morgan, 31, were arrested in Manhattan on Tuesday morning.</description></item><item><title>Ahmaud Arbery's family says they rejected a plea deal for federal hate crime charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8fe4e74331aeeab779bbb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8fe4e74331aeeab779bbb/</guid><description>Travis McMichael, his father Gregory McMichael and William &amp;quot;Roddie&amp;quot; Bryan were convicted in state murder charges in November.​
Summary The family of Ahmaud Arbery rejected a plea deal in the federal civil rights case of two of the men convicted of shooting and killing Arbery while he was jogging in a Brunswick, Georgia, neighborhood in February 2020, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney said. Cooper-Jones told &amp;ldquo;CBS Mornings&amp;rdquo; she rejected the deal because she wants the men to stand trial in court for those charges.</description></item></channel></rss>