<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>claims on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/claims/</link><description>Recent content in claims on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/claims/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Family of Abducted Girl Claims Inaction of Dallas Police &amp;amp; Mavs in Sex Trafficking Case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e75d75ff24d07ddad92a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e75d75ff24d07ddad92a1/</guid><description>“The American Airlines Center (and the Dallas Mavericks) are grateful that the teenager has been found.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; - A statement from the Mavs.
Highlights 15-year-old girl from North Richland Hills is now home after being abducted by a man at an April 8 Dallas Mavericks game at American Airlines Center. Family still seeks answers, and is pressing the Mavs, AAC and Dallas Police for not acting swiftly enough regarding the crime. The girl&amp;rsquo;s father informed police at the game when he realized she was missing, but was told to report the allegations to his hometown North Richlands Hills Police.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine crisis: claims Mariupol women and children forcibly sent to Russia | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62377c4f724c580c6303ab2e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 19:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62377c4f724c580c6303ab2e/</guid><description>Thousands of resident illegally taken across border, says Mariupol council, as reports emerge its art school has been bombed while 400 were sheltering inside
Highlights Mariupol authorities say Russian forces have deported several thousand residents to Russia. Reports emerge that Russian forces bombed an art school where 400 people were taking shelter. The claims have not been independently verified, but the council’s statement is one of several reports about residents being taken to Russia, where authorities have referred to “refugees” arriving from the strategic port.</description></item><item><title>Missiles target US consulate in Erbil, Iraq - report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622de12e396d148f81a89950/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 12:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622de12e396d148f81a89950/</guid><description>No casualties were reported in the attack.
Highlights Iran&amp;rsquo;s Islamic Revolutionary Guards Corps (IRGC) claims responsibility for missile attack on northern Iraq&amp;rsquo;s Erbil. IRGC: &amp;ldquo;Strategic Center of Conspiracy and Evil of the Zionists&amp;rdquo; was targeted by powerful and point-to-point missiles of the IRGC. The attack came as negotiations stalled in Vienna over Iran&amp;rsquo;s nuclear deal with the U.S. State Department called it an &amp;ldquo;outrageous attack&amp;rdquo; No Americans were hurt and no damage to US government facilities in Erbil, the State Department said.</description></item><item><title>Smartmatic can pursue election-rigging claims against Fox News, Giuliani</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62288b5d5c131c86c2cbb549/</guid><description>A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming that Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.S. presidential election to favor Democrat Joe Biden.
Highlights A New York state judge on Tuesday said Smartmatic can pursue its $2.7 billion defamation lawsuit claiming Fox News Network, Rudolph Giuliani and others falsely accused the electronic voting systems maker of helping rig the 2020 U.</description></item><item><title>House Jan. 6 panel alleges Trump engaged in 'criminal conspiracy'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ccef23c77e8c46500c4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 14:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ccef23c77e8c46500c4e/</guid><description>The 221-page filing marks the committee’s most formal effort to link the former president to a federal crime, though the actual import of the filing is not clear since lawmakers do not have the power to bring charges on their own and can only make a referral to the Justice Department.
Highlights House committee says it found evidence that Trump and his associates engaged in a “criminal conspiracy” to prevent Congress from certifying the results of the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>US claims Russia planning ‘false-flag’ operation to justify Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e21ccb3d1b05d76fae2d3d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e21ccb3d1b05d76fae2d3d/</guid><description>Officials say Moscow has already positioned saboteurs in Ukraine, on day Ukraine hit by ‘massive’ cyber-attack
Summary Moscow has persistently portrayed the crisis as a military threat from Ukraine against Russia, without providing any evidence. “We have information that indicates Russia has already pre-positioned a group of operatives to conduct a false flag operation in eastern Ukraine,” Jen Psaki, the White House spokeswoman, said. The hackers left a message on the foreign ministry website, according to reports.</description></item><item><title>Judge rejects Proud Boys' First Amendment claims in January 6 case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbdd6a99ece942cc1c1dd0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbdd6a99ece942cc1c1dd0/</guid><description>A federal judge is allowing a major January 6 conspiracy case against four Proud Boys leaders to move forward, rejecting their bid to throw out the charges.
Summary (CNN) A federal judge is allowing a major January 6 conspiracy case against four Proud Boys leaders to move forward, rejecting their bid to throw out the charges. The judge also rejected the defendants&amp;rsquo; claims that the riot could have been a protected First Amendment demonstration.</description></item></channel></rss>