<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>basement on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/basement/</link><description>Recent content in basement on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:43:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/basement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine: 200 bodies found in basement in Mariupol's ruins</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628da5d03f2bc72094e1eef3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628da5d03f2bc72094e1eef3/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Workers digging through the rubble of an apartment building in Mariupol found 200 bodies in the basement, Ukrainian authorities said Tuesday, as more horrors come to light in the ruined city that has seen some of the worst suffering of the 3-month-old war .
Highlights The town of Bakhmut has been coming under increasing artillery strikes, particularly over the last week, as Russian forces try to press forward to encircle the city of Sieverodonetsk.</description></item><item><title>US far-right podcaster charged after machine guns found in basement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083eb1f56717984e2c4926/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083eb1f56717984e2c4926/</guid><description>Joseph Paul Berger and his father, Joseph Raymond Berger, arrested last week and charged with multiple firearms offenses
Highlights Joseph Paul Berger, 32, and Joseph Raymond Berger, 67, charged with multiple firearms offenses. Federal prosecutors claim they found cache of weapons in locked basement at home in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania. Prosecutors claim he espouses strong anti-government and anti-law enforcement views. Joseph Berger goes by the moniker “GlockDoctor1488” – 1488 being a popular coded signal among neo-Nazi neo-Nazis, with “14” referencing the slogan “We must secure the existence of our people and a future for white children” and “Heil Hitler” in the Alt-Right Armory podcast.</description></item></channel></rss>