<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>donor on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/donor/</link><description>Recent content in donor on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 11:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/donor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anonymous donor clears student debt of Wiley College graduates in Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e3d30916c1a696774ada9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 11:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e3d30916c1a696774ada9/</guid><description>Students graduating from a historically Black college in East Texas were told at their commencement ceremony that an anonymous donor had paid their balances.
Highlights Anonymous donor pays student balances owed to Wiley College in East Texas. The estimated total for the balances owed by the graduating class of 2022 was about $300,000. The 2007 movie “The Great Debaters” starring Denzel Washington was inspired by the 1935 debate in which Wiley prevailed over the University of Southern California’s nationally-known, powerhouse team at a time when the nation was heavily segregated.</description></item><item><title>Ed Buck, wealthy political activist and donor, sentenced to 30 years in prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625971b7af00962fc2dd146e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625971b7af00962fc2dd146e/</guid><description>He was found guilty on charges that he injected the men with methamphetamine in exchange for sex, leading to overdoses
Highlights Ed Buck, 67, sentenced to 30 years in prison on charges that he supplied and personally injected gay men with methamphetamine in exchange for sex. He was found guilty in July on all nine counts, including having a drug house, distributing methamphetamine and enticing men to travel for prostitution. Buck, a wealthy white man active in gay causes and animal rights issues, has given more than $500,000, mostly to Democratic politicians and causes since 2000.</description></item></channel></rss>