<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>beijing on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/beijing/</link><description>Recent content in beijing on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 17:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/beijing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>China reports first COVID deaths in more than a year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62360f056b0b6ee0e8b09830/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 17:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62360f056b0b6ee0e8b09830/</guid><description>Mainland China reported its first COVID-19 deaths in more than a year on Saturday, according to a post on the National Health Commission&amp;rsquo;s website that said two people died in the northeastern region of Jilin.
Highlights Mainland China reported its first COVID-19 deaths in more than a year on Saturday. Two people died in the northeastern region of Jilin, China&amp;rsquo;s northeastern region. One of the dead was not vaccinated, a senior official with the National Health Commission said.</description></item><item><title>'I hate this sport': Tears, anger accompany medals for Russian figure skaters | CBC Sports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62115d3c700239761638f8f5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62115d3c700239761638f8f5/</guid><description>The gold medallist said she felt empty. The silver medallist pledged never to skate again. The favourite left in tears without saying a word. After one of the most dramatic nights in their sport&amp;rsquo;s history, Russia&amp;rsquo;s trio of teenage figure skating stars each enter an uncertain future.
Highlights Anna Shcherbakova and Kamila Valieva face uncertain futures at Beijing 2022. The Russian trio of teenage figure skating stars each enter uncertain futures after one of the most dramatic nights in their sport&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>All the Beijing snow is human-made -- a resource-intensive, 'dangerous' trend as planet warms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff831bc0a051246b6a2cd2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 08:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff831bc0a051246b6a2cd2/</guid><description>Natural snow is becoming less reliable for winter sports, which has led venues to lean more on artificial. But that comes at a cost.
Highlights Climate variability has forced the Winter Games to be virtually 100% reliant on artificial snow. Human-made snow is incredibly resource-intensive, requiring massive amounts of energy and water to produce in a climate that&amp;rsquo;s getting warmer and warmer. The region surrounding the outdoor Olympic venues is in an extreme drought this winter, but even in normal years, it isn&amp;rsquo;t particularly suitable for snow sports.</description></item><item><title>Kenya withdraws from Beijing Winter Olympics</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e80b7532c9e01de5f0aed4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 13:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e80b7532c9e01de5f0aed4/</guid><description>There were two Olympics and one Paralympics hopefuls in line to qualify.
Summary Kenya has pulled out of the 2022 Winter Olympics scheduled for February 4 to 20 in Beijing, China. There were two Olympics and one Paralympics hopefuls on the path to Beijing 2022, namely Sabrina Simader (Alpine skiing), Dennis Moronge (Cross-country skiing) and Daniel Katheku Safari (Para skiing). Simader was the only one who had met the qualification standard, while the rest depended on wild cards for participation.</description></item></channel></rss>