<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>murder on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/murder/</link><description>Recent content in murder on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:07:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/murder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alleged 'boogaloo' extremist sentenced to 41 years in murder of federal officer | The former Air Force staff sergeant pleaded guilty in the May 2020 murder of David Patrick Underwood.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bad4edb568a82743be61f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bad4edb568a82743be61f/</guid><description>Former Air Force staff Steven Carrillo sergeant pleaded guilty earlier this in the May 2020 murder of David Patrick Underwood.
Highlights Steven Carrillo, 33, pleaded guilty earlier this year to a federal murder charge in the killing of David Patrick Underwood and the attempted murder of Underwood’s colleague. Carrillo admitted to posting messages on Facebook a day before the shooting asking anyone if they were “down to boogaloo” Carrillo also admitted firing 19 rounds from a homemade AR-15 rifle from the back of a white van being driven by a man he connected with online.</description></item><item><title>Derek Chauvin appeals his murder conviction in the death of George Floyd</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694f87ecd648ae1b44f5dc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694f87ecd648ae1b44f5dc/</guid><description>Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has asked the state Court of Appeals to overturn his conviction for the 2020 murder of George Floyd, according to an appeal filed Monday.
Highlights Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has asked the state Court of Appeals to overturn his conviction for the 2020 murder of George Floyd. The 82-page filing lists more than a dozen aspects of the case and trial that Chauvin&amp;rsquo;s attorney argues tainted the proceedings.</description></item><item><title>Man without legs kidnapped from wheelchair, shot to death and left in field, DA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624708bbfdd178ec7caa9ce8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 14:14:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624708bbfdd178ec7caa9ce8/</guid><description>Jerome Nichols, 24, and another man kidnapped 41-year-old Ramarreao Prince Akins outside of a grocery store. A month later, Nichols was arrested for Akins’s murder. Authorities are still trying to identify
Highlights Jerome Nichols, 24, and another man kidnapped 41-year-old Ramarreao Prince Akins outside of a grocery store. A month later, Nichols was arrested for Akins’s murder. Surveillance video shows them driving away from the grocery store in a green Saturn SUV.</description></item><item><title>84-year-old man exonerated after 46 years in prison sues Cleveland for withholding evidence in wife's murder case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c1eae18519f3cc456b0b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 04:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c1eae18519f3cc456b0b6/</guid><description>Isaiah Andrews, 84, who was exonerated of his wife&amp;rsquo;s murder last fall after spending 46 years in prison, filed a federal civil rights lawsuit against the City of Cleveland in the U.S. District Court Northern District of Ohio Monday.
Highlights Isaiah Andrews, 84, filed a federal civil rights lawsuit against the City of Cleveland Monday. Andrews was exonerated of his wife&amp;rsquo;s murder last fall after spending 46 years in prison. The lawsuit alleges police withheld critical evidence about Regina Andrews&amp;rsquo; murder on September 18, 1974.</description></item><item><title>Man charged with murder in fatal shooting at Oregon racial justice protest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216bf91ec0e067ec35d31e5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216bf91ec0e067ec35d31e5/</guid><description>An Oregon man accused of killing one person and injuring five after opening fire on demonstrators in Portland was charged Tuesday with murder and other crimes, authorities said.
Highlights Benjamin Smith, 43, is charged with second-degree murder, four counts of attempted murder and multiple counts of assault. He is accused of killing one person and injuring five after opening fire on demonstrators in Portland. The shooting ended after someone returned fire, hitting Smith in the hip area, the prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s office says.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Oklahoma police officer gets 25 years for 2014 killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9df60fca97f931fb5862a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9df60fca97f931fb5862a/</guid><description>A federal judge has sentenced a former Oklahoma police officer to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter’s boyfriend
Summary A federal judge has sentenced a former Oklahoma police officer to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter’s boyfriendTULSA, Okla. &amp;ndash; A former Oklahoma police officer was sentenced Friday to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend after being convicted of second-degree murder the fifth time he went on trial in the case.</description></item></channel></rss>