<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>increases on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/increases/</link><description>Recent content in increases on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 08:16:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/increases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>British Columbia becomes first jurisdiction to tie minimum wage increases to inflation. On June 1 minimum wage will go up to $15.65, up 45 cents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62304b3a7260a47421e79df4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 08:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62304b3a7260a47421e79df4/</guid><description>On June 1, 2022, B.C.&amp;rsquo;s lowest-paid workers will get a pay boost, with the general minimum wage increasing from $15.20 to $15.65 an hour.
Highlights B.C. &amp;rsquo;s minimum wage will increase from $11.35 to $15.65 an hour on June 1, 2022. Increase of 2.8% will also apply to the live-in camp leader and live in home support worker minimum daily wages. Minimum wage increases tied to inflation are part of government&amp;rsquo;s plan to build an economy that works for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Walt Disney World increases prices for multiday and Park Hopper tickets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211e9b15217312822869442/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 07:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211e9b15217312822869442/</guid><description>Walt Disney World Resort is raising ticket prices for guests visiting the parks for multiple days.
Highlights This is the first major adjustment to the Orlando, Florida-based theme parks&amp;rsquo; ticket pricing since March 2019. Base tickets for those attending any of Disney&amp;rsquo;s four theme parks in Florida for between one and three days have not been altered. But prices of multiday passes for between four and 10 days are up between 2% and 6%.</description></item><item><title>Amazon increases the price of Prime nearly 17% to $139 per year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</guid><description>Amazon hasn&amp;rsquo;t raised the price of its Prime membership program since 2018, when it increased from $99 to $119, the current fee.
Highlights Amazon is raising the price of its annual Prime membership to $139 from $119. Amazon also raised the monthly price of a Prime membership from $12.99 to $14.99. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s annual increase amounts to about a 17% rise in price. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock rose more than 14% at one point on Thursday in extended trading.</description></item></channel></rss>