<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>da on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/da/</link><description>Recent content in da on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:06:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/da/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former Philadelphia police officer who fatally shot 12-year-old in back charged with murder, DA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62709c1bd1fc2a1a3408a61e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62709c1bd1fc2a1a3408a61e/</guid><description>A former Philadelphia police officer who fatally shot a 12-year-old boy in the back in March has been charged with first-degree murder, District Attorney Larry Krasner announced Monday, saying the boy was unarmed and on the ground when the officer fired.
Highlights Edsaul Mendoza, 26, was one of four plainclothes officers in an unmarked car when he fatally shot a 12-year-old boy in the back in March. The boy was unarmed and on the ground when the officer fired, the DA says.</description></item><item><title>DA declines to charge Alameda police for death of Mario Gonzalez. Coroner ruled death a homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250ee01fcaee5df204566fc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 02:23:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250ee01fcaee5df204566fc/</guid><description>The Alameda County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office on Thursday determined there would be no charges against the officers involved in the death of 26-year-old Mario Gonzalez, according to the officers&amp;rsquo; attorney.
Highlights Mario Gonzalez, 26, stopped breathing after three officers sat on his back trying to arrest him. Alameda County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office determined there would be no charges against the officers involved in the death of 26-year-old Mario Gonzalez. DA O&amp;rsquo;Malley said she couldn&amp;rsquo;t prove beyond a reasonable doubt that the officers acted unlawfully.</description></item></channel></rss>