<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trump on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trump/</link><description>Recent content in trump on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 07:14:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trump SPAC is down 44% since Elon Musk disclosed Twitter stake</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62679bbc61b32a4d1d6322a6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62679bbc61b32a4d1d6322a6/</guid><description>Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s quest to become a social media mogul is dealing a blow to Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s social venture.
Highlights Digital World Acquisition Corporation, the controversial blank-check firm that plans to merge with Trump Media &amp;amp; Technology Group, fell 13% on Monday to close at $35.71. That&amp;rsquo;s the lowest level since the Trump deal was announced last October. The selloff comes as Musk reaches a deal to take over Twitter, one of the Big Tech companies Trump had vowed to take on.</description></item><item><title>Judge finds Trump in contempt in legal fight with NY AG</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266f252cb0340c9aba0614b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 19:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266f252cb0340c9aba0614b/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A New York judge found former President Donald Trump in contempt of court and set in motion $10,000 daily fines Monday for failing to adequately respond to a subpoena issued by the state&amp;rsquo;s attorney general as part of a civil investigation into his business dealings.
Highlights A New York judge found former president Donald Trump in contempt of court for failing to adequately respond to a subpoena issued by the state’s attorney general as part of a civil investigation into his business dealings.</description></item><item><title>House Jan. 6 panel alleges Trump engaged in 'criminal conspiracy'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ccef23c77e8c46500c4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 14:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ccef23c77e8c46500c4e/</guid><description>The 221-page filing marks the committee’s most formal effort to link the former president to a federal crime, though the actual import of the filing is not clear since lawmakers do not have the power to bring charges on their own and can only make a referral to the Justice Department.
Highlights House committee says it found evidence that Trump and his associates engaged in a “criminal conspiracy” to prevent Congress from certifying the results of the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Biden orders release of Trump White House logs to Congress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d5a95e486b50bd850c2ff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 20:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d5a95e486b50bd850c2ff/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is ordering the release of Trump White House visitor logs to the House committee investigating the riot of Jan. 6, 2021, once more rejecting former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s claims of executive privilege.
Highlights President Joe Biden is ordering the release of Trump White House visitor logs to the House committee investigating the riot of Jan. 6, 2021. The committee has sought a trove of data from the National Archives, including presidential records that Trump had fought to keep private.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Trump's request to block release of White House records from January 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8de5b0d7f72459feb655f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8de5b0d7f72459feb655f/</guid><description>President Joe Biden had refused to invoke executive privilege, as Donald Trump wanted to prevent White House records from going to the January 6 riot panel.
Summary The Supreme Court on Wednesday rejected a request by former President Donald Trump to block White House records from being sent to a House select committee investigating the January 6 Capitol riot. The ruling, which Trump cannot appeal, sets the stage for more than 700 pages of Trump White House records to soon be sent by the National Archives to the committee, which had issued a subpoena for them.</description></item><item><title>New York attorney general asks court to enforce subpoenas of Trump children in tax fraud probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</guid><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization.
Summary New York Attorney General Letitia James has subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization, court filings made public Monday reveal. The state attorney general &amp;ldquo;is engaged in a criminal investigation that has an active grand jury.</description></item><item><title>Iran vows revenge for Soleimani killing if Trump not put on trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3aa3c52f0d8ce973f182e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3aa3c52f0d8ce973f182e/</guid><description>Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi, speaking on the second anniversary of the assassination of General Qassem Soleimani by the United States, said that former U.S. President Donald Trump must face trial for the killing or Tehran would take revenge.
Summary DUBAI, Jan 3 (Reuters) - Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi, speaking on the second anniversary of the assassination of General Qassem Soleimani by the United States, said that former U.S. President Donald Trump must face trial for the killing or Tehran would take revenge.</description></item><item><title>Cheney: January 6 committee has 'firsthand testimony' that Ivanka asked Trump to intervene during insurrection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</guid><description>Members of the House select committee investigating January 6 said Sunday that they have critical testimony about communications to former President Donald Trump on the day of the deadly attack.
Summary Wyoming Rep. Liz Cheney, the vice chair of the committee and one of its two Republican members, told ABC News that the panel has &amp;ldquo;firsthand testimony&amp;rdquo; that during the attack, Trump&amp;rsquo;s daughter and then-senior adviser Ivanka Trump asked him to intervene.</description></item></channel></rss>