<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trump on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trump/</link><description>Recent content in trump on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York attorney general asks court to enforce subpoenas of Trump children in tax fraud probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</guid><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization.
Summary New York Attorney General Letitia James has subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization, court filings made public Monday reveal. The state attorney general &amp;ldquo;is engaged in a criminal investigation that has an active grand jury.</description></item><item><title>Iran vows revenge for Soleimani killing if Trump not put on trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3aa3c52f0d8ce973f182e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3aa3c52f0d8ce973f182e/</guid><description>Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi, speaking on the second anniversary of the assassination of General Qassem Soleimani by the United States, said that former U.S. President Donald Trump must face trial for the killing or Tehran would take revenge.
Summary DUBAI, Jan 3 (Reuters) - Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi, speaking on the second anniversary of the assassination of General Qassem Soleimani by the United States, said that former U.S. President Donald Trump must face trial for the killing or Tehran would take revenge.</description></item><item><title>Cheney: January 6 committee has 'firsthand testimony' that Ivanka asked Trump to intervene during insurrection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</guid><description>Members of the House select committee investigating January 6 said Sunday that they have critical testimony about communications to former President Donald Trump on the day of the deadly attack.
Summary Wyoming Rep. Liz Cheney, the vice chair of the committee and one of its two Republican members, told ABC News that the panel has &amp;ldquo;firsthand testimony&amp;rdquo; that during the attack, Trump&amp;rsquo;s daughter and then-senior adviser Ivanka Trump asked him to intervene.</description></item></channel></rss>