<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lane on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lane/</link><description>Recent content in lane on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-cop pleads guilty to manslaughter in George Floyd killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285604b04b797a582783e3e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285604b04b797a582783e3e/</guid><description>A former Minneapolis police officer has pleaded guilty to a state charge of aiding and abetting second-degree manslaughter in the death of George Floyd
Highlights Thomas Lane pleads guilty to aiding and abetting second-degree manslaughter. He will avoid what could have been a lengthy state sentence if he was convicted of murder. Lane and two other officers have already been convicted on federal counts of willfully violating Floyd&amp;rsquo;s rights. The guilty plea comes a week before the two-year anniversary of Floyd’s May 25, 2020, killing.</description></item><item><title>Feds offer no plea deals to 3 former cops charged with violating George Floyd's rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df79b738ce923aef1fa166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 01:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df79b738ce923aef1fa166/</guid><description>No last-minute plea deals are in the works for three former police officers charged with civil rights violations in the death of George Floyd, a prosecutor said.
Summary Chauvin pleaded guilty last month to federal civil rights charges stemming from the May 25, 2020, death of the 46-year-old Black man during an attempted arrest. Multiple videos showed Kueng and Lane helping Chauvin hold down Floyd, while Thao kept witnesses at bay.</description></item></channel></rss>