<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>true on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/true/</link><description>Recent content in true on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:15:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/true/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>World true pandemic death toll nearly 15 million, says WHO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62745a696a0bf7f0b74bf6e2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62745a696a0bf7f0b74bf6e2/</guid><description>These include deaths from Covid and from the indirect effects of the pandemic over two years worldwide.
Highlights These calculations also take into account deaths which were not directly because of Covid but instead caused by its knock-on effects. It also accounts for poor record-keeping in some regions, and sparse testing at the start of the crisis. These include deaths from Covid and from the indirect effects of the pandemic over two years worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Uncounted: Inaccurate death certificates across the country hide the true toll of COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6510ea9a285ffc4406b2f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6510ea9a285ffc4406b2f/</guid><description>In some counties, half of the spike in deaths during the pandemic is attributed to COVID-19. Researchers say that points to an undercount
Summary In those communities, official COVID-19 deaths account for just half of the increase in deaths in 2020. Those deaths, especially those that weren’t properly investigated,make up at least some of Lafayette’s missing COVID deaths, according to experts. Talamo, Lafayette Parish’s chief medicolegal investigator, said he doesn’t think COVID-19 deaths are going uncounted, instead blaming suicides or drug overdoses.</description></item></channel></rss>