<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>measures on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/measures/</link><description>Recent content in measures on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 04:15:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/measures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EU announces new Russia sanctions with U.S. and others, including SWIFT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621afad5d9bb3d9ced374cce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 04:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621afad5d9bb3d9ced374cce/</guid><description>The United States and its allies on Saturday moved to block certain Russian banks' access to the SWIFT international payment system in further punishment of Moscow as it continues its military assault against Ukraine.
Highlights U.S. and its allies move to block certain Russian banks' access to the SWIFT international payment system in further punishment of Moscow. Measures will include restrictions on the Russian central bank&amp;rsquo;s international reserves, the nations said in a joint statement.</description></item><item><title>‘The economy cannot stay open’: Omicron’s effects ricochet across US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e05ab95a38c94edbdeee3f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e05ab95a38c94edbdeee3f/</guid><description>Biden has vowed to keep businesses and schools open but some experts wonder if that’s possible given nature of Covid variant
Summary Joe Biden has vowed to keep businesses and schools open, but some experts wonder if that’s possible given the nature of Omicron and the lack of adequate measures to combat it. “The economy cannot stay open and schools cannot stay open when so many people are getting sick,” said Margaret Thornton, an educational researcher at Princeton School of Public and International Affairs.</description></item></channel></rss>