<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>generals on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/generals/</link><description>Recent content in generals on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 21:10:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/generals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Army officer who reported Trump probably faced retaliation, inquiry finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286b217023b102e0a6eaae8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 21:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286b217023b102e0a6eaae8/</guid><description>Yevgeny Vindman, a former White House adviser, &amp;quot;was the subject of unfavorable personnel actions&amp;quot; after raising alarm about President Donald Trump’s actions toward Ukraine, the Defense Department&amp;rsquo;s inspector general determined.
Highlights Yevgeny Vindman and his twin brother raised alarm about President Trump’s actions toward Ukraine. The report says it is “more likely than not’t” that the Army officer was the subject of ‘unfair personnel actions’ that were in reprisal for his communications with superiors.</description></item><item><title>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, who has fought vaccine mandates, tests positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e932b6e160ce5e691613c2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e932b6e160ce5e691613c2/</guid><description>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, who has fought vaccine mandates, tests positive for COVID-19
Summary AUSTIN, Texas (TEXAS TRIBUNE) - Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton has tested positive for COVID-19, his office said Wednesday. The communications staff at the attorney general’s office told The Texas Tribune in an unsigned statement that Paxton had tested positive. The attorney general’s office did not immediately say whether Paxton was vaccinated. It did not release further information on when Paxton tested positive or how he may have contracted it.</description></item></channel></rss>