<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>miles on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/miles/</link><description>Recent content in miles on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/miles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Like an inferno:' US West burning at furious pace so far</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ebc8bc73006448b9d24b0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ebc8bc73006448b9d24b0/</guid><description>LAGUNA NIGUEL, Calif. (AP) — Wildfires are on a furious pace early this year — from a California hilltop where mansions with multimillion-dollar Pacific Ocean views were torched to remote New Mexico mountains charred by a month-old monster blaze.
Highlights Wind-driven flames have torn through vegetation that is extraordinarily dry from years-long drought exacerbated by climate change. More than 2,000 square miles (5,180 square kilometers) have burned so far this year — the most at this point since 2018.</description></item><item><title>Nearing Earth is an asteroid the size of two Empire State Buildings.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265306e6cf02ffd3d91548e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 11:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265306e6cf02ffd3d91548e/</guid><description>On Thursday, April 28, a massive asteroid the size of the Empire State Building will speed past the Earth.
Highlights On Thursday, April 28, a massive asteroid the size of the Empire State Building will speed past the Earth. The asteroid, known as 418135 (2008 AG33), will be traveling at speeds of up to 23,264 miles per hour. Its width is estimated to be between 1,150 and 2,560 feet. That speed is 11 times faster than a rifle bullet, which travels at around 2,050 mph.</description></item><item><title>Man hit, killed by higher-speed train in Florida</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f072f43ccc917041eea60/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 09:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f072f43ccc917041eea60/</guid><description>Authorities say a Brightline train struck and killed a pedestrian, raising the death toll since the higher-speed train line resumed operations in South Florida.
Highlights Authorities say a Brightline train struck and killed a pedestrian, raising the death toll since the higher-speed train line resumed operations in South Florida. Brightline has the worst fatality rate in the nation, according to an ongoing Associated Press analysis of Federal Railroad Administration data. Its trains have fatally struck 59 people since beginning test runs in 2017, an average of about one death every 33,000 miles (about 53,000 kilometers) Central Florida’s SunRail has the second-worst rate among railroads that operate at least 100,000 mile (about 161,000 km) annually.</description></item><item><title>Deputy Virginia AG resigns after posts surface of her applauding Jan. 6 rioters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205cad80c6d2d1894afda44/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 02:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205cad80c6d2d1894afda44/</guid><description>A Republican deputy attorney general in Virginia resigned from her position Thursday after Facebook posts surfaced showing she had applauded Jan. 6 rioters and
Highlights Monique Miles resigned from her position Thursday after Facebook posts surfaced showing she had applauded Jan. 6 rioters and falsely claimed that Donald Trump won the 2020 presidential election. The Virginia attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office became aware of these posts by Miles Thursday when The Washington Post shared screenshots it obtained of her previous comments.</description></item></channel></rss>