<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>injured on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/injured/</link><description>Recent content in injured on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:21:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/injured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suspect in South Carolina mall shooting on house arrest after judge sets $25,000 bond</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</guid><description>The suspect in a South Carolina mall shooting in which nine people were wounded has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor after
Highlights Nine people were injured in a shooting in South Carolina early Sunday morning. The victims are ages 15 to 73. The suspect has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor. Police say no deaths have been reported in the shooting in Hampton County, South Carolina.</description></item><item><title>A woman was killed and nine officers injured in Phoenix shooting and barricade situation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091152376e25fb314a521a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 14:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091152376e25fb314a521a/</guid><description>A woman was fatally shot and nine police officers were injured early Friday in a Phoenix suburb, police said.
Highlights Police identify the suspect as 36-year-old Morris Jones, 36, who was found dead inside the home. A woman was fatally shot and nine police officers were injured early Friday in a Phoenix suburb, police said. The officers were responding to a report of a shooting in Buckeye, west of Phoenix, Arizona.</description></item><item><title>Woman killed and four others injured after man opens fire on bus in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd18c1d5419180d5e6ffe5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 12:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd18c1d5419180d5e6ffe5/</guid><description>The bus, bound for Los Angeles, had stopped in Oroville when the 21-year-old passenger began shooting as people exited the vehicle
Highlights A 43-year-old woman was killed and four others were injured as a Greyhound bus stopped at a convenience store in Oroville, northern California. The suspect, Asahdi Coleman, 21, had exhibited “paranoid behavior’, police say. He allegedly opened fire randomly as people exited the bus, shooting through seats and windshield.</description></item></channel></rss>