<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>injured on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/injured/</link><description>Recent content in injured on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 18:11:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/injured/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>At least 12 dead in another weekend of mass shootings across America</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e431cd5e8306359b43cf0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 18:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e431cd5e8306359b43cf0/</guid><description>The first weekend of June marked a greater number of mass shooting deaths in the United States than the previous three-day weekend, which ended with Memorial Day.
Highlights The first weekend of June had a greater number of mass shooting deaths in the United States than the previous three-day weekend, which ended with Memorial Day. The tally for weekend violence through Sunday night was at least 12 killed and at least 38 injured in mass shootings.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Dozens feared dead after bomb hits school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627808d1c5b3e534085a9c33/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627808d1c5b3e534085a9c33/</guid><description>A Ukrainian official says 60 people may be dead after an air strike on a village school in Luhansk.
Highlights UN has recorded at least 2,345 civilian deaths and 2,919 injured in Ukraine. Thousands of combatants are also believed to have been killed or injured on both sides. At least 60 people may be dead after an air strike on a village school in Luhansk, Ukraine, an official says. More than 2,000 people have died since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion began on 24 February, the UN said last month.</description></item><item><title>Shooting with 'multiple' victims reported at Kissimmee-area Target</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a5b0a486829444faea2f0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 09:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a5b0a486829444faea2f0/</guid><description>One person is dead, and three others were injured after a shooting at a Target store Wednesday night in Kissimmee, Florida.
Highlights One person is dead, and three others injured after a shooting at a Target store in Kissimmee, Florida. Two of Osceola County Sheriff Marcos R. Lopez said two of his deputies were involved in the shooting and are OK. The parking lot was blocked off with yellow investigative tape and more than a dozen vehicles were in the area, according to a FOX 35 crew.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in South Carolina mall shooting on house arrest after judge sets $25,000 bond</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</guid><description>The suspect in a South Carolina mall shooting in which nine people were wounded has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor after
Highlights Nine people were injured in a shooting in South Carolina early Sunday morning. The victims are ages 15 to 73. The suspect has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor. Police say no deaths have been reported in the shooting in Hampton County, South Carolina.</description></item><item><title>A woman was killed and nine officers injured in Phoenix shooting and barricade situation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091152376e25fb314a521a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 14:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091152376e25fb314a521a/</guid><description>A woman was fatally shot and nine police officers were injured early Friday in a Phoenix suburb, police said.
Highlights Police identify the suspect as 36-year-old Morris Jones, 36, who was found dead inside the home. A woman was fatally shot and nine police officers were injured early Friday in a Phoenix suburb, police said. The officers were responding to a report of a shooting in Buckeye, west of Phoenix, Arizona.</description></item><item><title>Woman killed and four others injured after man opens fire on bus in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd18c1d5419180d5e6ffe5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 12:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd18c1d5419180d5e6ffe5/</guid><description>The bus, bound for Los Angeles, had stopped in Oroville when the 21-year-old passenger began shooting as people exited the vehicle
Highlights A 43-year-old woman was killed and four others were injured as a Greyhound bus stopped at a convenience store in Oroville, northern California. The suspect, Asahdi Coleman, 21, had exhibited “paranoid behavior’, police say. He allegedly opened fire randomly as people exited the bus, shooting through seats and windshield.</description></item></channel></rss>