<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>uber on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uber/</link><description>Recent content in uber on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/uber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pennsylvania man charged in killing of Uber driver who begged for her life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211c076d3569ae4f6d0f37e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:16:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211c076d3569ae4f6d0f37e/</guid><description>A Pennsylvania man is accused of killing an Uber driver who vanished last week in what authorities described Friday as a fatal robbery.
Highlights Christina Spicuzza, 38, disappeared Feb. 10 after driving for Uber in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. She was found dead from a single gunshot wound, police say. A dash cam inside her car captured Crew allegedly pointing a gun at her neck as she drove. Crew allegedly tried to transfer money to his girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s phone, a criminal complaint says.</description></item><item><title>Uber rider billed $600 after being stranded on I-95 during snow storm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d64d479ddf2fc971f5936d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d64d479ddf2fc971f5936d/</guid><description>A Richmond man not only got stranded on Interstate 95 in Virginia during this week’s snowstorm but was also hit with a massive Uber bill.
Summary Andrew Peters from Richmond not only got stranded on Interstate 95 during this week&amp;rsquo;s snowstorm but was also hit with a massive Uber bill. Andrew Peters, from Richmond, Virginia, not only got stranded on the highway but was also hit with a massive Uber bill.</description></item></channel></rss>