<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russian on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russian/</link><description>Recent content in russian on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine rules out territorial concessions, as Russia steps up attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bb50b28d5e7b260085460/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bb50b28d5e7b260085460/</guid><description>Kyiv revealed its worst military losses from a single attack of the Ukraine war on Monday, saying 87 people had been killed last week when Russian forces struck a barracks housing troops at a training base in the north.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president says 87 people were killed when Russian forces struck barracks housing troops at a training base in the north last week. The disclosure that scores had been killed in the attack demonstrated Russia&amp;rsquo;s ability to inflict huge losses, even far from the front.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian speaks out after Russian troops buried him alive - CNN Video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283948721539f5897e649ba/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283948721539f5897e649ba/</guid><description>CNN&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Bell speaks with a Ukrainian who, along with his brothers, was beaten, shot and buried by Russian soldiers.
Highlights CNN&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Bell speaks with a Ukrainian who, along with his brothers, was beaten, shot and buried by Russian soldiers. He tells how he was beaten and killed by Russian forces in Ukraine. His brothers were beaten and shot by Russian troops, and his brothers were killed and buried. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bell talks with the Ukrainian who was killed by the Russians at the hands of the Russian army in Ukraine in 2010.</description></item><item><title>McDonald’s says it will sell its Russia business after previously pausing operations due to Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283675b4bfb41f007c69f11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 09:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283675b4bfb41f007c69f11/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said it will sell its business in Russia, a little more than two months after it paused operations in the country due to its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s has more than 800 restaurants and 62,000 employees in Russia. Franchisees operate only 15% of its Russian locations, while the company owns the rest. &amp;ldquo;If you can&amp;rsquo;t go to America, come to McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in Moscow,&amp;rdquo; was a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s ad slogan at the time in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Flood saves Ukrainian village from Russian occupation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628231af7abe16d3e534ab68/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 11:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628231af7abe16d3e534ab68/</guid><description>The intentional flooding of a small village north of Kyiv that created a quagmire and submerged cellars and fields, but prevented a Russian attack on the capital, was worth all the sacrifice, residents said.
Highlights Ukrainian forces opened a dam early in the war in Demydiv, causing the Irpin River to flood the village and thousands of acres around. The move has since been credited with stopping Russian soldiers and tanks from breaking through Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s lines.</description></item><item><title>Men and boys among alleged rape victims of Russian soldiers in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272b6d28740d75f9abcb471/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272b6d28740d75f9abcb471/</guid><description>UN chief on sexual violence warns dozens of cases under investigation are ‘tip of the iceberg’
Highlights UN special representative on sexual violence in war warns dozens of cases of rape by invading forces are already under investigation. UN envoy Pramila Patten urges survivors to come forward and report rape cases. Russian forces still hold swathes of territory in the south and east of the country. Victims range from men and women of all ages, from children to elderly people, UN says.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelensky Says Russian Troops Came Close To Capturing Him And His Family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c0fedd00fe590fad89470/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 16:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c0fedd00fe590fad89470/</guid><description>The Ukrainian leader is praised globally for his courage amid the Russian attack. Zelensky refused US offer to leave the country.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said in a recent interview that Russian troops came very close to capturing him and his family. He made the revelation while speaking to Time magazine, while recalling the intense early days of the Ukraine war. Russian President Vladimir Putin announced the invasion on February 24, and Zelenski recalled from the memories that exist “in a fragmented way” The President said he was informed that a Russian strike teams had parachuted into Kyiv to kill or capture him and.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops use rape as 'an instrument of war' in Ukraine, rights groups allege</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262c640d35e7b2c430daa1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 15:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262c640d35e7b2c430daa1c/</guid><description>When Russian troops invaded Ukraine and began closing in on its capital, Kyiv, Andrii Dereko begged his 22-year-old stepdaughter Karina Yershova to leave the suburb where she lived.
Highlights Karina Yershova&amp;rsquo;s stepfather says she was killed by Russian soldiers. Police told her family she had been killed by pro-Russian soldiers, he says. Human rights groups say they have been working around the clock to deal with a growing number of sexual abuse cases.</description></item><item><title>US defense secretary being regularly briefed on any potential Russian nuclear moves, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260238cfeeb91a52b763db3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260238cfeeb91a52b763db3/</guid><description>The United States&amp;rsquo; military is keeping a constant watch on Russia&amp;rsquo;s nuclear arsenal as the war in Ukraine continues.
Highlights US officials are more concerned about the threat of Russia using nuclear weapons than at any time since the Cold War, sources say. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin is being briefed two or three times a week by the top US general who oversees US nuclear weapons and defenses. The US has not seen any indication Russia has made any moves to prepare nuclear weapons for use during the war.</description></item><item><title>Celebrity chef's Ukraine charity kitchen destroyed by Russian missile</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e53d70a5aa310872f5e20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 06:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e53d70a5aa310872f5e20/</guid><description>One of the restaurant partners of the World Central Kitchen (WCK) was struck on Saturday, according to the nonprofit kitchen&amp;rsquo;s CEO Nate Mook, who confirmed the news on Twitter, revealing that four staff members had been injured in the blast.
Highlights One of the World Central Kitchen&amp;rsquo;s partners in Ukraine has been hit by a Russian missile. Four staff members were injured in the blast, according to the charity&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine rejects deadline to surrender in Mariupol as Russia threatens to eliminate resistance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c597b9b07feed7b6ad22c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c597b9b07feed7b6ad22c/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces besieged in Mariupol have rejected Russia&amp;rsquo;s demands to surrender and are still resisting an unrelenting assault on the southeastern port city, top Ukrainian officials said on Sunday.
Highlights NEW: Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says &amp;ldquo;not one big city in Ukraine has fallen&amp;rdquo; NEW: He says more than 900 cities, towns and villages have been freed from Russian occupation since Moscow took control. Russia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defense called on the Ukrainian soldiers still in Mariupol to surrender by 1 p.</description></item><item><title>Russia warned the US about weapons shipments to Ukraine. Military analyst calls it a bluff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bbe08bd5a6a0deb6b9c3b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 07:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bbe08bd5a6a0deb6b9c3b/</guid><description>Ret. Lt. Gen. Mark Hertling discusses Russian President Putin being forced to pivot his military strategy in Ukraine due to varying terrain, and how his forces lack the adaptability to make drastic changes that may be necessary.
Highlights Ret. Gen. Mark Hertling discusses Russian President Putin being forced to pivot his military strategy in Ukraine. Hertling says Putin&amp;rsquo;s forces lack the adaptability to make drastic changes that may be necessary. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Russian war worsens fertilizer crunch, risking food supplies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625686fb27132b2e83776a3e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 08:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625686fb27132b2e83776a3e/</guid><description>KIAMBU COUNTY, Kenya (AP) — Monica Kariuki is about ready to give up on farming. What is driving her off her 10 acres of land outside Nairobi isn’t bad weather, pests or blight — the traditional agricultural curses — but fertilizer: It costs too much.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s war in Ukraine has pushed up fertilizer prices that were already high, made scarce supplies rarer still and squeezed farmers, especially those in the developing world struggling to make a living.</description></item><item><title>Pentagon monitoring reports of possible Russian chemical weapons attack in Mariupol</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555e7974c7a3473dd87e2e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555e7974c7a3473dd87e2e/</guid><description>If Russia were to have used chemical weapons, it would signal a major escalation of its botched invasion of Ukraine, which has stalled after more than a month.
Highlights If Russia were to have used chemical weapons in Mariupol, it would represent a major escalation of the conflict. British Foreign Secretary Liz Truss also says her government is working &amp;ldquo;urgently&amp;rdquo; to verify details of alleged attack. The original report was in the form of a Telegram message posted by the Azov Regiment, an ultra-nationalist part of the Ukrainian National Guard.</description></item><item><title>Russia has defaulted on its foreign debt, says S&amp;amp;P</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625462e469610c075b90044c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 17:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625462e469610c075b90044c/</guid><description>Russia has defaulted on its foreign debt because it offered bondholders payments in rubles, not dollars, credit ratings agency S&amp;amp;P has said.
Highlights Russia has defaulted on its foreign debt because it offered bondholders payments in rubles, not dollars, credit ratings agency S&amp;amp;P has said. Russia has a grace period of 30 days from April 4 to make the payments of capital and interest, but it does not expect it will convert them into dollars.</description></item><item><title>Chairman of Russian metals company calls for Bucha probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62522b1d9ecd65f4abcd34ab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62522b1d9ecd65f4abcd34ab/</guid><description>The board chairman of Russian metals company Rusal has called for an investigation into events in the Kyiv suburb of Bucha, where Ukrainian officials say Russian troops killed civilians
Highlights Board chairman of Russian metals company Rusal has called for an investigation into events in the Kyiv suburb of Bucha. Ukrainian forces and journalists discovered scores of bodies on streets and in mass graves after Russian troops withdrew. The Kremlin has said the deaths were staged by the Ukrainians to denigrate Russian forces.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainians shocked by 'crazy' scene at Chernobyl after Russian pullout reveals radioactive contamination</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251cd0e880d18b3a17a13ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251cd0e880d18b3a17a13ba/</guid><description>The sudden ear-piercing beep of a radiation meter fills the room as a Ukrainian soldier walks in. This is where Russian soldiers were living at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, and radiation levels are now higher than normal.
Highlights CNN was given exclusive access to Chernobyl nuclear power plant for the first time since it came back into Ukrainian control. Russian soldiers held Chernobyl for a month and are thought to have been operating in contaminated areas most of the time.</description></item><item><title>‘Russia Is Completely Depoliticized’ A sociologist from Moscow explains how the nation learned to deny reality.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62500b198d7dd62463ae9232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62500b198d7dd62463ae9232/</guid><description>A sociologist from Moscow explains how the nation learned to deny reality, in Ukraine and at home under Vladimir Putin.
Highlights Russian sociologist Greg Yudin says most people under Putin&amp;rsquo;s rule passively support his “special military operation” in Ukraine. He says two decades of authoritarian rule have made the Kremlin’s line easy to accept. If the war lasts longer than a few months, the mood may change, and Putin may be tempted to escalate, he says.</description></item><item><title>Netherlands seizes 14 yachts as Russia faces yet more sanctions over brutal war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dbd09717d73ea2c425130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dbd09717d73ea2c425130/</guid><description>The Dutch government said the &amp;quot;vessels cannot be delivered, transferred or exported&amp;quot; while their ownership is investigated for links to the Kremlin.
Highlights Dutch customs authorities impound 14 yachts in shipyards, including 12 still under construction. Vessels were being built in five different shipyards for &amp;ldquo;Russian beneficiaries,&amp;rdquo; the Dutch government says. The Netherlands has also frozen 516 million euros&amp;rsquo; worth of assets and 155 million euros in transactions, the minister says.</description></item><item><title>Russian embassy in Dublin short on fuel as companies refuse to deliver supplies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cbedcbf30eb6830749886/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 22:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cbedcbf30eb6830749886/</guid><description>EXCLUSIVE: The Irish Mirror also understands that Bank of Ireland have decided to suspend their accounts with the Russian Embassy in Ireland
Highlights The Russian Embassy in Ireland is running out of fuel for heating and hot water. It has written a letter to Foreign Affairs Minister Simon Coveney asking for help. Bank of Ireland also has decided to suspend their accounts with the Russian Embassy. A source said: “The embassy is struggling because no one wants to do business with them as a result of what’s happening in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Germany declares 'significant number' of Russian diplomats as undesirable</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b92cfd1f6beb3697589d9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b92cfd1f6beb3697589d9/</guid><description>Germany decided on Monday to declare undesirable a &amp;quot;significant number&amp;quot; of officials at the Russian embassy, Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock said, adding that Berlin would also boost its support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces.
Highlights Germany declares undesirable a &amp;ldquo;significant number&amp;rdquo; of officials at the Russian embassy. Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock says Berlin will also boost support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s armed forces. Baerbocks: &amp;ldquo;The images from Bucha testify to an unbelievable brutality on the part of the Russian leadership and those who follow its propaganda&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We will further tighten the existing sanctions against Russia,&amp;rdquo; she said.</description></item><item><title>Viktor Orban, Hungary's authoritarian leader, calls Zelensky an 'opponent' after winning reelection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a8d3873d0c22a5474ee06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 06:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a8d3873d0c22a5474ee06/</guid><description>Hungary&amp;rsquo;s authoritarian leader and longtime Russian ally, Viktor Orban, has declared victory in the country&amp;rsquo;s parliamentary elections, clinching a fourth consecutive term in power.
Highlights Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Fidesz party had a commanding lead with 71% of the votes counted. The election campaign was dominated by Moscow&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Hungary is heavily reliant on Russian energy and Orban has dodged opportunities to condemn Putin&amp;rsquo;s assault on its neighboring state. Opposition leader Peter Marki-Zay even failed to win in his own district, where he had served as mayor in the previous district.</description></item><item><title>US astronaut returns to Earth with Russian cosmonauts after record-breaking mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62458c72fdcced550645fedb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 11:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62458c72fdcced550645fedb/</guid><description>Mark Vande Hei rides back with Anton Shkaplerov and Pyotr Dubrov after 355 days at International Space Station, a US record
Highlights A Nasa astronaut caught a Russian ride back to Earth on Wednesday after a US record 355 days at the International Space Station. Despite escalating tensions between the US and Russia over Vladimir Putin’s war with Ukraine, the return followed customary procedures. A small Nasa team of doctors and other staff was on hand for the touchdown and planned to return immediately to Houston.</description></item><item><title>Russian oil tankers are vanishing off the map – transponders are turned off for hours at a time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245549b8dbd600257a6d926/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245549b8dbd600257a6d926/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine made the country a pariah in the global energy market. Since the war started, a de facto embargo on Russian oil has emerged, with oil companies, trading houses, shippers and banks backing away, all at the same time.
Highlights Dark activity among Russian-affiliated crude oil tankers is up by 600% compared with before the war began, a company says. Similar trends are playing out with other petroleum products, too.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops have accidentally shot down own aircraft and refused to carry out orders, UK spy chief to reveal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62453855b76e69931714b0bb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62453855b76e69931714b0bb/</guid><description>Sir Jeremy Fleming, the head of GCHQ, used the rare public speech to say it increasingly looks like Russia&amp;rsquo;s President Vladimir Putin &amp;quot;has massively misjudged the situation&amp;quot; in Ukraine.
Highlights He said: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve seen that we have seen that he looks to be taking it up a gear,&amp;rdquo; he said. He also added: &amp;ldquo;They are looking at the nature of the human body&amp;rdquo; as well as the physical condition of the body.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine Welcomes Home Soldier Who Told "Go F*** Yourself" To Russians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243848a9884d4361e564f43/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 22:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243848a9884d4361e564f43/</guid><description>A Ukrainian soldier who told a Russian warship to &amp;quot;go f*** yourself&amp;quot; before he was captured by the invading force has returned home, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Ministry tweeted.
Highlights Ukrainian soldier Roman Hrybov has returned home from Russian captivity, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Ministry tweeted. The soldier and his small squad had been defending a small island called Snake Island in the Black Sea during the early days of the Russian invasion in late February.</description></item><item><title>Mayor of Chernobyl workers town says Russian forces have left</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241c27f9e6ec78ee445e706/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 14:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241c27f9e6ec78ee445e706/</guid><description>Russian forces have left the Ukrainian town of Slavutych, home to workers at the defunct nuclear plant of Chernobyl, after completing their task of surveying it, the mayor said early on Monday.
Highlights Russian forces have left the Ukrainian town of Slavutych, home to workers at the defunct Chernobyl plant, after completing their task of surveying it. Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine has caused a major humanitarian crisis and displaced an estimated 10 million people, nearly a quarter of the population.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy: West needs more courage in helping Ukraine fight</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240d35a0e32defef8150f28/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 21:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240d35a0e32defef8150f28/</guid><description>LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy accused the West of cowardice Sunday as his country fights to stave off Russia’s invading troops, making an exasperated plea for fighter jets and tanks to sustain a defense as the war ground into a battle of attrition.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president calls for fighter jets and tanks to sustain a defense as the war ground into a battle of attrition. U.S. President Joe Biden said in a lacerating speech that Russian President Vladimir Putin could not stay in power.</description></item><item><title>UK says Russian sanctions could be lifted with Ukraine withdrawal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62400e4b8df569ee2d215fbc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62400e4b8df569ee2d215fbc/</guid><description>British foreign minister Liz Truss says sanctions imposed on Russian individuals and companies could be lifted if Russia withdraws from Ukraine and commits to end aggression, the Telegraph newspaper reported on Saturday.
Highlights British foreign minister says sanctions could be lifted if Russia withdraws from Ukraine. Britain and other nations are using economic sanctions to punish Russia for invading Ukraine. British government says it has imposed sanctions on Russian individuals and businesses with more than $650 million worth of assets in the region.</description></item><item><title>Missouri station offering Russian state radio to listeners - ABC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fd74f4451beeae6b46e21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fd74f4451beeae6b46e21/</guid><description>A radio station based in suburban Kansas City is facing criticism for airing Russian state-sponsored programming during the Ukrainian war
Highlights Radio Sputnik is funded by the Russian government. Peter Schartel runs a low-budget radio station in suburban Kansas City, Missouri. He says he&amp;rsquo;s standing up for free speech and alternative viewpoints. Critics say he&amp;rsquo;s promoting propaganda and misinformation by airing Russian state-sponsored programming. The National Association of Broadcasters issued a statement on March 1 calling on broadcasters to stop carrying Russian programming with ties to Russia or its agents.</description></item><item><title>UK to fund 2 mln pounds of food supplies for encircled Ukrainian cities</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f581fa21c546d4f77c41f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 18:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f581fa21c546d4f77c41f/</guid><description>Britain said on Saturday it would fund 2 million pounds ($2.6 million) worth of vital food supplies for areas of Ukraine which are encircled by Russian forces following a direct request from the Ukrainian government.
Highlights Britain said on Saturday it would fund 2 million pounds ($2.6 million) worth of vital food supplies for areas of Ukraine encircled by Russian forces. Britain said around 25 truckloads of dried food, tinned goods and water will be transported by road and rail from warehouses in Poland and Slovakia to the most at-risk Ukrainian towns and cities.</description></item><item><title>Russia reasserts right to use nuclear weapons in Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f2d8fcba1345c55860f54/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f2d8fcba1345c55860f54/</guid><description>Senior politician Dmitry Medvedev says Moscow’s nuclear doctrine does not require enemy state to use such weapons first
Highlights Russia threatens to use nuclear weapons against Ukraine, says Russian President Vladimir Putin. Russia has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest number of nuclear weapons, says Putin. Putin says Russia is prepared to use any nuclear weapons without the help of the U.S. military. Russia’s defence minister says he is ‘prepared to defend the sovereignty’ of the country and its allies in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says Moscow is forcibly taking civilians to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d7a2279b617c4551293a2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d7a2279b617c4551293a2/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine accused Moscow on Thursday of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians from shattered Ukrainian cities to Russia, where some may be used as “hostages” to pressure Kyiv to give up.
Highlights Ukraine says 402,000 people, including 84,000 children, have been taken to Russia. The Kremlin gave nearly identical numbers for those who have been relocated, but said they wanted to go to Russia. Ukraine’s rebel-controlled eastern regions are predominantly Russian-speaking, and many people there have supported close ties to Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Russia destroys Chernobyl radiation monitoring lab, says Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b7f910c6d79ac170ebd83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 20:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b7f910c6d79ac170ebd83/</guid><description>Russian forces have looted and destroyed a laboratory near the abandoned Chernobyl nuclear power plant that was used to monitor radioactive waste, the Ukrainian government said Wednesday.
Highlights The site of the world&amp;rsquo;s worst nuclear disaster fell into Russian hands in the first week of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion. The lab was part of a European Union-funded attempt to improve radioactive waste management. The government agency said it hoped Russia would use the samples to &amp;ldquo;harm itself, and not the civilized world&amp;rdquo; It is the latest scare at the infamous site in northern Ukraine, near the border with Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Navalny sentenced to 9 years in prison by Russian court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623aac2bf0e30c61d1634fbf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 05:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623aac2bf0e30c61d1634fbf/</guid><description>A Russian court has convicted top opposition leader Alexei Navalny of fraud and contempt of court, sentencing him to nine more years in prison in a move seen as an
Highlights Russian court convicts Alexei Navalny of fraud and contempt of court. Sentenced him to nine more years in prison in a move seen as an attempt to keep him behind bars for as long as possible. Navalny was convicted of contempt and fraud and sentenced to nine years behind bars.</description></item><item><title>Putin’s Russia looks increasingly desperate as Ukraine war nears stalemate, analysts say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623887d656193bdb34b59d07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 14:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623887d656193bdb34b59d07/</guid><description>Putin&amp;rsquo;s forces have exerted brutal force and destruction on much of Ukraine, but Russia has achieved few military victories.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine is nearing its fourth week, and analysts say it is showing increasing signs of desperation. Russia&amp;rsquo;s economy is creaking under the immense weight of international sanctions and the costs of war, having largely failed to achieve major military victories in Ukraine. Former U.S. ambassador to NATO: &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re bogged down.</description></item><item><title>Russian claims of bat bioweapon labs in Ukraine dismissed by US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236d3eb164a30f62ee6e9a5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 07:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236d3eb164a30f62ee6e9a5/</guid><description>Six countries with seats on the UN Security Council say Russia is spreading propaganda. They made the allegation at a meeting called at Russia&amp;rsquo;s request. Russia repeated its allegations that Ukraine has biological weapons program. The U.S. reiterated that Ukraine
Highlights Russia is using a UN Security Council meeting to spread its propaganda about its invasion of Ukraine, six Western members states say. The meeting was held at Russia&amp;rsquo;s request to discuss its allegations that Ukraine is developing biological weapons.</description></item><item><title>Vladimir Putin accused of war crimes as school and theatre are hit in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62340772f8d9aad8a7745fda/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62340772f8d9aad8a7745fda/</guid><description>British foreign secretary says there is ‘very strong evidence’, and France says Putin is only pretending to negotiate
Highlights UK, US, France, Albania, Ireland, Ireland and Norway accuse Russia of war crimes in Ukraine. UK foreign secretary Liz Truss says there is ‘very, very strong evidence’ of Russian war crimes. US secretary of state, Antony Blinken, said he agreed with Joe Biden that war crimes had been committed in Ukraine, adding that US experts were in the process of documenting and evaluating potential war crimes, according to the US.</description></item><item><title>Pregnant woman, baby die after Russia bombed maternity ward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</guid><description>MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned. Images of the woman being rushed to an ambulance on a stretcher had circled the world, epitomizing the horror of an attack on humanity’s most innocent.
Highlights A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned.</description></item><item><title>Biden to ban Russian oil imports over Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227aa473d8ef599a6bc2ef8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 19:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227aa473d8ef599a6bc2ef8/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden announced Tuesday the U.S. will ban all Russian oil imports , toughening the toll on Russia’s economy in retaliation for its invasion of Ukraine, but he acknowledged it will bring costs to Americans, particularly at the gas pump .
Highlights President Joe Biden announces a ban on Russian oil imports, toughening the toll on Russia’s economy in retaliation for its invasion of Ukraine. Biden acknowledged it will bring costs to Americans, particularly at the gas pump.</description></item><item><title>Russia Said It Has Blocked Facebook</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 22:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</guid><description>Russia’s communications regulator said it blocked Facebook because of “discrimination against Russian media and information resources.&amp;quot; Twitter was blocked shortly after.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator blocks access to Facebook and Twitter. The move comes amid President Vladimir Putin’s ongoing military invasion of Ukraine. Facebook&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Meta, says it will keep its apps, including Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp, available to Russians. Last week, Meta president Nick Clegg said Russia had restricted use of the company&amp;rsquo;s services.</description></item><item><title>Turn down heating by 1C to reduce need for Russian imports, Europeans told</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221d7f8f9305282b638de50/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221d7f8f9305282b638de50/</guid><description>IEA says reducing temperature could help wean consumers off fuel that Russia is using as a weapon in Ukraine war
Highlights The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s plan would reduce Russian gas imports by about a third before next winter. Red tape should be cut to bring forward the construction of more wind and solar power stations, the IEA said. The EU relies on Russia for about 40% of its gas consumption. The UK government is also understood to be urgently examining its exposure to gas market turbulence caused by Russia’s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russian commanders 'will be hunted down for war crimes', justice secretary warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220790dbc5a66d5a8ea76c9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 08:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220790dbc5a66d5a8ea76c9/</guid><description>The UK and 37 others countries referred Russia to the International Criminal Court on Wednesday for its &amp;quot;barbaric&amp;quot; invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Justice Secretary Dominic Raab said the UK is already planning to help identify and find fugitives suspected of war crimes. The UK and 37 other countries referred Russia to the International Criminal Court on Wednesday for its &amp;ldquo;barbaric&amp;rdquo; invasion of Ukraine. Justice Secretary Johnson said all 38 countries are &amp;ldquo;crystal clear that Mr Putin cannot commit these horrific acts with impunity&amp;rdquo; Mr Raab revealed more details to The Daily Telegraph.</description></item><item><title>Russian Police jail kids aged 7-11 for bringing flowers &amp;amp; “No to War” signs to Ukraine’s embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fc14b51949d11cab426fe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fc14b51949d11cab426fe/</guid><description>In an emergency session, the General Assembly voted 141-5 to condemn Russia and demand that it end its war in Ukraine. Also, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defense minister accused Russia of deploying “the criminal tactics of long-range shelling of peaceful cities,” and Moscow police jailed children who carried &amp;quot;No to War&amp;quot; signs.
Highlights Russia claims it has taken over the southern Ukrainian city of Kherson, but Ukrainian officials sharply dispute this. Russia shuts down two leading Russian media outlets over critical coverage of the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US expelling 12 Russian diplomats from UN mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9df2b7fd9ca46e8e2980/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9df2b7fd9ca46e8e2980/</guid><description>Russia’s United Nations ambassador said move ‘gross violation’ of UN agreement with US
Highlights US is expelling 12 Russian diplomats at the United Nations for engaging in activities not in accordance with their responsibilities and obligations as diplomats. Russia’s UN Ambassador Vassily Nebenzia described the move as ‘yet another hostile step undertaken by the host country’ He called the expulsions a ‘gross violation’ of the UN agreement with the US as the host of the Vienna Convention governing diplomatic relations.</description></item><item><title>A Ukrainian tried to sink a yacht owned by the head of a Russian state arms firm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d81da2984327dad9fa751/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 02:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d81da2984327dad9fa751/</guid><description>The man told a judge in Majorca that he had wanted to retaliate for the invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Ukrainian sailor admitted trying to sink a yacht owned by the head of a Russian arms firm. The man told a judge in Majorca that he had wanted to retaliate for the invasion of Ukraine. The sailor said he wanted to&amp;rsquo;retaliate&amp;rsquo; the yacht&amp;rsquo;s owner in retaliation for invasion of the country. The yacht was owned by head of Russian state arms firm, according to the judge.</description></item><item><title>IOC recommends Russian and Belarusian athletes should be banned from all international competitions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d48d1e03c5c25d4073b3c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 22:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d48d1e03c5c25d4073b3c/</guid><description>The International Olympic Committee has said it doesn&amp;rsquo;t wish to &amp;quot;punish&amp;quot; competitors for the &amp;quot;decisions of their government&amp;quot;, but a ban is needed to &amp;quot;protect the integrity of global sports competitions&amp;quot;.
Highlights International Olympic Committee says Russia and Belarusian athletes should not be allowed to compete in any international competitions. Committee says it doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to &amp;ldquo;punish&amp;rdquo; competitors for &amp;ldquo;decisions of their government&amp;rdquo; Russia&amp;rsquo;s attack on Ukraine entered its fifth day - with Moscow&amp;rsquo;s forces said to be 20 miles from Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Biden Administration Expands Sanctions Against Russia, Cutting Off U.S. Transactions With Central Bank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d030e588efbe3f6da1cca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 17:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d030e588efbe3f6da1cca/</guid><description>The new sanctions effectively prohibit Americans from doing any business with Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank as well as freezes its assets within the United States.
Highlights The Biden administration announced additional sanctions against Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank on Monday. The move prohibits Americans from doing any business with the bank as well as freezes its assets within the U.S. The new sanctions will also target the National Wealth Fund of the Russian Federation and the Ministry of Finance.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine army secures Kharkiv, expelling Russian troops – governor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621be931e85e399abf233274/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 21:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621be931e85e399abf233274/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces had secured full control of Kharkiv on Sunday following street fighting with Russian troops in the country&amp;rsquo;s second-biggest city, the local governor said.
Highlights Ukrainian forces secure full control of Kharkiv following street fighting with Russian troops. &amp;ldquo;Kharkiv is fully under our control,&amp;rdquo; head of the regional administration says. The army was expelling Russian forces during a &amp;ldquo;clean-up&amp;rdquo; operation, Oleg Sinegubov says. Russian forces were being expelled from the city during a clean-up operation, he said.</description></item><item><title>Poland and Sweden refuse to play Russia in World Cup qualifiers because of Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b6c116f6ca2b76e5c5d86/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b6c116f6ca2b76e5c5d86/</guid><description>Polish and Bayern Munich star Robert Lewandowski said he can&amp;rsquo;t &amp;quot;imagine playing&amp;quot; against Russia while its military continues to attack Ukraine.
Highlights Poland and Sweden will not play Russia in World Cup playoff qualifiers. Poland&amp;rsquo;s football association president Cezary Kulesza said in a tweet it is &amp;ldquo;time to act!&amp;rdquo; The decision comes days after FIFA President Gianni Infantino failed to condemn the actions of Russian President Vladimir Putin. Russia was set to play Poland on March 24 in a semifinal playoff game in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Anti-war sentiment grows in Russia despite govt crackdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ab3fc830a71de779bf75a/</guid><description>As Russian troops were closing in on the Ukrainian capital, more and more Russians at home were speaking out against the invasion even as the government&amp;rsquo;s official rhetoric grew increasingly harsher
Highlights At least 460 people in 34 cities were detained over anti-war protests on Saturday, including over 200 in Moscow. An online petition to stop the attack on Ukraine garnered over 780,000 signatures by Saturday evening. A prominent contemporary art museum in Moscow called Garage announced Saturday it was halting its work on exhibitions and postponing them “until the human and political tragedy that is unfolding in Ukraine has ceased&amp;quot; Dmitry Medvedev said Moscow may respond to Western sanctions by opting out of the last nuclear arms deal with the U.</description></item><item><title>Champions League final should not be held in Russia, says Foreign Secretary Liz Truss</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216792828c5450c89f05c57/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 18:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216792828c5450c89f05c57/</guid><description>European football&amp;rsquo;s yearly showpiece is due to be held in St Petersburg in May, but the match could now be moved to another host city due to the Ukraine crisis. Foreign Secretary Liz Truss tells Sky News the match &amp;quot;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;quot; be held in Russia.
Highlights Foreign Secretary Liz Truss tells Sky News the match &amp;ldquo;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rdquo; be held in Russia. European football&amp;rsquo;s yearly showpiece is due to be held on 28 May in St Petersburg.</description></item><item><title>U.S. has intel that Russian commanders have orders to proceed with Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</guid><description>The intelligence indicates that commanders on the ground making specific plans for how they would maneuver in their sector of the battlefield.
Highlights U.S. intelligence indicates Russian commanders have received orders to proceed with an invasion of Ukraine. Defense minister of Belarus announced Russia will be extending military drills near Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northern borders. Russia has massed roughly 150,000 troops, warplanes and equipment on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s three sides, escalating tensions with neighboring country.</description></item><item><title>U.S. and NATO say Russia is building up troops near Ukraine, not withdrawing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d769e093fc1e733d0e5ed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 22:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d769e093fc1e733d0e5ed/</guid><description>The United States and NATO said Russia was still building up troops around Ukraine on Wednesday despite Moscow&amp;rsquo;s insistence it was pulling back, questioning President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s stated desire to negotiate a solution to the crisis.
Highlights Russia says video shows tanks, infantry fighting vehicles, and self-propelled artillery units leaving Crimea. U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said key Russian units were moving towards the border, not away. Russia&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said its forces were pulling back after exercises in southern and western military districts near Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US accuses financial website Zero Hedge of spreading Russian propaganda</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c488b56e1c92fe7378875/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c488b56e1c92fe7378875/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. intelligence officials on Tuesday accused a conservative financial news website with a significant American readership of amplifying Kremlin propaganda and alleged five media outlets targeting Ukrainians have taken direction from Russian spies.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s Defense Ministry announced Tuesday that some units participating in military exercises would begin returning to their bases. In a response posted online Tuesday morning, the website said it “has never worked, collaborated or cooperated with Russia, nor are there any links to spy agencies” Zero Hedge has been sharply critical of Biden and posted stories about allegations of wrongdoing by his son Hunter.</description></item><item><title>Russia’s Central Bank Steps In to Halt Ruble Slide as Markets in Freefall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eff47a0bfa5d73aa0496bf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 13:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eff47a0bfa5d73aa0496bf/</guid><description>Russia’s Central Bank was forced to halt foreign currency purchases in a bid to stop a dramatic slide in the value of the ruble.
Summary Russia’s Central Bank was forced to halt foreign currency purchases Monday in a bid to stop a dramatic slide in the value of the ruble. The Russian currency was down 2.3% by Monday afternoon against the U.S. dollar — a significant move in the foreign currency markets — trading at 79.</description></item><item><title>Hactivists say they hacked Belarus rail system to stop Russian military buildup</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef75f1039fc967d4775ae1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef75f1039fc967d4775ae1/</guid><description>If confirmed, the attack would be one of the first times ransomware has been used this way.
Summary 🔺Preventing the presence of Russian troops on the territory of #Belarus. For technical reasons, reference web-resources of the Belarusian Railways and services for issuing electronic travel documents are temporarily unavailable. Belarusian Railways apologizes for the inconvenience caused. According to reports, Russia has been sending military equipment and personnel by rail into Belarus, which shares a border with Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Biden Considers Sending Thousands of Troops, Including Warships and Aircraft, to Eastern Europe and Baltics Amid Fears of Russian Attack on Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee5c9b135932fdb2bf832c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee5c9b135932fdb2bf832c/</guid><description>The president is also considering deploying warships and aircraft to NATO allies, in what would be a major shift from its restrained stance on Ukraine.
Summary Thinning out staff at American embassies is a common precaution when conflicts or other crises arise that could put American diplomats in harm’s way. In his news conference last week, Mr. Biden said he had cautioned Mr. Putin that a Russian invasion of Ukraine would prompt Washington to send more troops to the region.</description></item><item><title>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</guid><description>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine
Summary In response to the increasing Russian threat around Ukraine, the Netherlands is sending two F-35 fighter aircraft to Bulgaria. The two F-35s will participate in a NATO mission that has been ongoing for years to monitor the skies of Eastern Europe. The Netherlands also offers an amphibious transport ship (including landing craft and helicopters) and two ‘land-bound units’ (Ollongren does not specify which) for the NATO Response Force.</description></item><item><title>US President Biden predicts Russia will invade Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e979074defe592b9b65ea2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 15:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e979074defe592b9b65ea2/</guid><description>President Joe Biden predicted Wednesday that Russia will invade Ukraine, just as the United States launched a fresh effort to resolve the standoff.
Summary President Joe Biden predicted Wednesday that Russia will invade Ukraine, just as the United States launched a fresh effort to resolve the standoff and Moscow continued to mass troops on its neighbor&amp;rsquo;s doorstep. Biden said Putin “will be held accountable” and has “never have seen sanctions like the ones I promised will be imposed” if Russia makes further moves against Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia moves more troops westward amid Ukraine tensions | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is a sending an unspecified number of troops from the country’s far east to Belarus for major war games, officials said Tuesday, a deployment that will further beef up Russian military presence near Ukraine amid Western fears of a planned invasion.
Summary Russia has concentrated an estimated 100,000 troops with tanks and other heavy weapons near Ukraine in what the West fears could be a prelude to an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Canada deploys special forces to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</guid><description>Global News has learned that a small contingent of Canadian special forces soldiers sent to aid Ukrainian government, plan for potential embassy evacuation should Russia invade.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailCanadian special forces operators have been deployed to Ukraine amid rising tensions between the NATO military alliance and Russia, Global News has learned. Sources told Global News that the Canadian special operations presence is part of an attempt by NATO allies to deter Russian aggression in Ukraine, and to identify ways to assist the Ukrainian government.</description></item><item><title>Russia cannot 'tolerate' NATO's 'gradual invasion' of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;quot;tolerate&amp;quot; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;quot;gradual invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine.
Summary Russian President Vladimir Putin Vladimir Vladimirovich PutinRussia cannot &amp;rsquo;tolerate&amp;rsquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;gradual invasion&amp;rsquo; of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says Fears of Russian invasion of Ukraine rise despite US push for diplomacy Overnight Defense &amp;amp; National Security — US says Russia prepping &amp;lsquo;false flag&amp;rsquo; operation MORE&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;ldquo;tolerate&amp;rdquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;ldquo;gradual invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US claims Russia planning ‘false-flag’ operation to justify Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e21ccb3d1b05d76fae2d3d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e21ccb3d1b05d76fae2d3d/</guid><description>Officials say Moscow has already positioned saboteurs in Ukraine, on day Ukraine hit by ‘massive’ cyber-attack
Summary Moscow has persistently portrayed the crisis as a military threat from Ukraine against Russia, without providing any evidence. “We have information that indicates Russia has already pre-positioned a group of operatives to conduct a false flag operation in eastern Ukraine,” Jen Psaki, the White House spokeswoman, said. The hackers left a message on the foreign ministry website, according to reports.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine hit by ‘massive’ cyber-attack on government websites</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1c858146ceffe00e659d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1c858146ceffe00e659d9/</guid><description>Suspected Russian hackers leave message warning: ‘Ukrainians … be afraid and expect worse’
Summary Ukraine has been hit by a “massive” cyber-attack, with the websites of several government departments including the ministry of foreign affairs and the education ministry knocked out. Suspected Russian hackers left a message on the foreign ministry website, according to reports. NEWS IN KYIV: Several Ukrainian government websites down due to a major a cyberattack. But we can imagine.</description></item><item><title>Russia sees 'no grounds' for more security talks with US, NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</guid><description>Russia says it sees &amp;quot;no grounds&amp;quot; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine.
Summary Russia says it sees &amp;ldquo;no grounds&amp;rdquo; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine. “There is, to a certain extent, a dead end or a difference in approaches,” Ryabkov said, according to the Post.</description></item><item><title>Undersea Cable Connecting Norway With Arctic Satellite Station Has Been Mysteriously Severed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</guid><description>The cables run through a highly strategic stretch of water near where the Barents and Norwegian Sea meet.
Summary Bjoertvedt/Wikimedia Commons The Svalbard Satellite Station atop the mountain of Platåberget on the island of Spitsbergen in Svalbard, Norway. Known as the Svalbard Undersea Cable System, the dual communication cable runs between Longyearbyen and Andøya in northern Norway, each stretching more than 800 miles. Nsandel/Wikimedia Commons The Cable Innovator was one of the cable-laying vessels involved in laying the Svalbard Undersea Cable System.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>Blinken to Kazakhstan government: It's hard to get Russians to leave once they're in your home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</guid><description>As Kazakh authorities invite Russian-dominated alliance to quell protests, US secretary of state says &amp;rsquo;not clear why they feel the need for any outside assistance'
Summary WASHINGTON — US Secretary of State Antony Blinken warned Friday that Kazakhstan will find it difficult to lower Russian influence after inviting in troops to quell unrest. “I think one lesson in recent history is that once Russians are in your house, it’s sometimes very difficult to get them to leave,” Blinken told reporters.</description></item><item><title>Russian submarines threatening undersea network of internet cables, says UK defence chief Sir Tony Radakin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</guid><description>Any attempt to damage the underwater cables on which &amp;quot;predominantly all the world&amp;rsquo;s information and traffic travels&amp;quot; could be considered an &amp;quot;act of war&amp;quot;, the UK&amp;rsquo;s newly appointed head of the armed forces tells The Times.
Summary The head of Britain&amp;rsquo;s armed forces is warning Russian submarines are threatening a crucial network of underwater cables that carry information around the world. Admiral Sir Tony Radakin, who was appointed chief of the defence staff in October, said the undersea cables that transmit internet data are &amp;ldquo;the world&amp;rsquo;s real information system&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Satellite images show Russia still building up forces near Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</guid><description>New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.
Summary Dec 24 (Reuters) - New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.</description></item></channel></rss>