<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russian on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russian/</link><description>Recent content in russian on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Undersea Cable Connecting Norway With Arctic Satellite Station Has Been Mysteriously Severed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</guid><description>The cables run through a highly strategic stretch of water near where the Barents and Norwegian Sea meet.
Summary Bjoertvedt/Wikimedia Commons The Svalbard Satellite Station atop the mountain of Platåberget on the island of Spitsbergen in Svalbard, Norway. Known as the Svalbard Undersea Cable System, the dual communication cable runs between Longyearbyen and Andøya in northern Norway, each stretching more than 800 miles. Nsandel/Wikimedia Commons The Cable Innovator was one of the cable-laying vessels involved in laying the Svalbard Undersea Cable System.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>Blinken to Kazakhstan government: It's hard to get Russians to leave once they're in your home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</guid><description>As Kazakh authorities invite Russian-dominated alliance to quell protests, US secretary of state says &amp;lsquo;not clear why they feel the need for any outside assistance&amp;rsquo;
Summary WASHINGTON — US Secretary of State Antony Blinken warned Friday that Kazakhstan will find it difficult to lower Russian influence after inviting in troops to quell unrest. “I think one lesson in recent history is that once Russians are in your house, it’s sometimes very difficult to get them to leave,” Blinken told reporters.</description></item><item><title>Russian submarines threatening undersea network of internet cables, says UK defence chief Sir Tony Radakin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</guid><description>Any attempt to damage the underwater cables on which &amp;quot;predominantly all the world&amp;rsquo;s information and traffic travels&amp;quot; could be considered an &amp;quot;act of war&amp;quot;, the UK&amp;rsquo;s newly appointed head of the armed forces tells The Times.
Summary The head of Britain&amp;rsquo;s armed forces is warning Russian submarines are threatening a crucial network of underwater cables that carry information around the world. Admiral Sir Tony Radakin, who was appointed chief of the defence staff in October, said the undersea cables that transmit internet data are &amp;ldquo;the world&amp;rsquo;s real information system&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Satellite images show Russia still building up forces near Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</guid><description>New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.
Summary Dec 24 (Reuters) - New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.</description></item></channel></rss>