<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russian on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russian/</link><description>Recent content in russian on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia moves more troops westward amid Ukraine tensions | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is a sending an unspecified number of troops from the country’s far east to Belarus for major war games, officials said Tuesday, a deployment that will further beef up Russian military presence near Ukraine amid Western fears of a planned invasion.
Summary Russia has concentrated an estimated 100,000 troops with tanks and other heavy weapons near Ukraine in what the West fears could be a prelude to an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Canada deploys special forces to Ukraine amid rising tensions with Russia - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 13:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6b9f555dc5ac0adb57837/</guid><description>Global News has learned that a small contingent of Canadian special forces soldiers sent to aid Ukrainian government, plan for potential embassy evacuation should Russia invade.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailCanadian special forces operators have been deployed to Ukraine amid rising tensions between the NATO military alliance and Russia, Global News has learned. Sources told Global News that the Canadian special operations presence is part of an attempt by NATO allies to deter Russian aggression in Ukraine, and to identify ways to assist the Ukrainian government.</description></item><item><title>Russia cannot 'tolerate' NATO's 'gradual invasion' of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5061e691a86d804bd6815/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;quot;tolerate&amp;quot; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;quot;gradual invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine.
Summary Russian President Vladimir Putin Vladimir Vladimirovich PutinRussia cannot &amp;lsquo;tolerate&amp;rsquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;gradual invasion&amp;rsquo; of Ukraine, Putin spokesman says Fears of Russian invasion of Ukraine rise despite US push for diplomacy Overnight Defense &amp;amp; National Security — US says Russia prepping &amp;lsquo;false flag&amp;rsquo; operation MORE&amp;rsquo;s spokesman said on Sunday that Russia began its military buildup along the Ukrainian border because it could no longer &amp;ldquo;tolerate&amp;rdquo; NATO&amp;rsquo;s eastward expansion and &amp;ldquo;gradual invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US claims Russia planning ‘false-flag’ operation to justify Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e21ccb3d1b05d76fae2d3d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e21ccb3d1b05d76fae2d3d/</guid><description>Officials say Moscow has already positioned saboteurs in Ukraine, on day Ukraine hit by ‘massive’ cyber-attack
Summary Moscow has persistently portrayed the crisis as a military threat from Ukraine against Russia, without providing any evidence. “We have information that indicates Russia has already pre-positioned a group of operatives to conduct a false flag operation in eastern Ukraine,” Jen Psaki, the White House spokeswoman, said. The hackers left a message on the foreign ministry website, according to reports.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine hit by ‘massive’ cyber-attack on government websites</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1c858146ceffe00e659d9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1c858146ceffe00e659d9/</guid><description>Suspected Russian hackers leave message warning: ‘Ukrainians … be afraid and expect worse’
Summary Ukraine has been hit by a “massive” cyber-attack, with the websites of several government departments including the ministry of foreign affairs and the education ministry knocked out. Suspected Russian hackers left a message on the foreign ministry website, according to reports. NEWS IN KYIV: Several Ukrainian government websites down due to a major a cyberattack. But we can imagine.</description></item><item><title>Russia sees 'no grounds' for more security talks with US, NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</guid><description>Russia says it sees &amp;quot;no grounds&amp;quot; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine.
Summary Russia says it sees &amp;ldquo;no grounds&amp;rdquo; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine. “There is, to a certain extent, a dead end or a difference in approaches,” Ryabkov said, according to the Post.</description></item><item><title>Undersea Cable Connecting Norway With Arctic Satellite Station Has Been Mysteriously Severed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</guid><description>The cables run through a highly strategic stretch of water near where the Barents and Norwegian Sea meet.
Summary Bjoertvedt/Wikimedia Commons The Svalbard Satellite Station atop the mountain of Platåberget on the island of Spitsbergen in Svalbard, Norway. Known as the Svalbard Undersea Cable System, the dual communication cable runs between Longyearbyen and Andøya in northern Norway, each stretching more than 800 miles. Nsandel/Wikimedia Commons The Cable Innovator was one of the cable-laying vessels involved in laying the Svalbard Undersea Cable System.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>Blinken to Kazakhstan government: It's hard to get Russians to leave once they're in your home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db691a7dfdd13a529d95e8/</guid><description>As Kazakh authorities invite Russian-dominated alliance to quell protests, US secretary of state says &amp;lsquo;not clear why they feel the need for any outside assistance&amp;rsquo;
Summary WASHINGTON — US Secretary of State Antony Blinken warned Friday that Kazakhstan will find it difficult to lower Russian influence after inviting in troops to quell unrest. “I think one lesson in recent history is that once Russians are in your house, it’s sometimes very difficult to get them to leave,” Blinken told reporters.</description></item><item><title>Russian submarines threatening undersea network of internet cables, says UK defence chief Sir Tony Radakin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da5deff184b5fb463af579/</guid><description>Any attempt to damage the underwater cables on which &amp;quot;predominantly all the world&amp;rsquo;s information and traffic travels&amp;quot; could be considered an &amp;quot;act of war&amp;quot;, the UK&amp;rsquo;s newly appointed head of the armed forces tells The Times.
Summary The head of Britain&amp;rsquo;s armed forces is warning Russian submarines are threatening a crucial network of underwater cables that carry information around the world. Admiral Sir Tony Radakin, who was appointed chief of the defence staff in October, said the undersea cables that transmit internet data are &amp;ldquo;the world&amp;rsquo;s real information system&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Satellite images show Russia still building up forces near Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</guid><description>New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.
Summary Dec 24 (Reuters) - New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.</description></item></channel></rss>