<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>led on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/led/</link><description>Recent content in led on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 06:17:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/led/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arthur D. Riggs, Ph.D., the world-renowned diabetes expert who developed the technology that led to the first human synthetic insulin for the treatment of diabetes, has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624152b662dbb2c4cba21f0c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 06:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624152b662dbb2c4cba21f0c/</guid><description>Arthur D. Riggs, Ph.D., the world-renowned diabetes expert who developed the technology that led to the first human synthetic insulin for the treatment of diabetes, died March 23 after battling cancer. A biotechnology pioneer and a longtime leader at City of Hope, Riggs served as director emeritus of Beckman Research Institute of City of Hope and the Arthur Riggs Diabetes &amp;amp; Metabolism Research Institute at City of Hope.
Highlights Arthur D.</description></item><item><title>Arrest made in homicide investigation that led to Amir Locke shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62034d48125f980ef139c31c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62034d48125f980ef139c31c/</guid><description>A Minneapolis SWAT team serving a warrant that led to an officer shooting Amir Locke was looking for his teenage cousin and two others in connection with a homicide investigation, according to the court documents released Tuesday.
Highlights Police were looking for the cousin of Amir Locke and two others in connection with a homicide investigation, court documents say. Locke&amp;rsquo;s cousin Mekhi Speed was among three people wanted in the case, court records show.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Ninjas, company that led Arizona GOP election 'audit,' is shutting down</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d98aefe16bf8cde2335d33/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d98aefe16bf8cde2335d33/</guid><description>Cyber Ninjas, the company that helped steer an extraordinarily partisan audit of 2020 presidential election ballots in Arizona, is shutting down, a spokesperson told NBC News Thursday.
Summary &amp;ldquo;Cyber Ninjas is shutting down. A reporter for The Guardian earlier Thursday reported Cyber Ninjas&amp;rsquo; plans to shut down. Jack Wilenchik, a lawyer for Cyber Ninjas, did not immediately respond to a request for comment. It concluded that nearly 80 claims made by Cyber Ninjas were misleading or false.</description></item></channel></rss>