<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crash on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crash/</link><description>Recent content in crash on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:14:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US skateboarder, 22, among four people killed in Iceland plane crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62035bb5ce5b329f1bbc3da4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62035bb5ce5b329f1bbc3da4/</guid><description>US skateboarder and filmmaker Josh Neuman was one of four people killed in a plane crash in Iceland, local authorities confirmed.
Highlights Four bodies found at bottom of Lake Thingvallavik, Iceland. US skateboarder, 22-year-old known for skydiving videos, killed in plane crash. Neuman was in Iceland to shoot commercial content for Belgian brand Suspicious Antwerp. He produced videos that attracted more than 106 million views on YouTube and had more than 1.</description></item><item><title>Tesla driver charged with vehicular manslaughter over fatal Autopilot crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7ef531b69bf02ce1152b4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7ef531b69bf02ce1152b4/</guid><description>Misuse of autopilot, which can control steering, speed and braking, is the subject of investigations by two federal agencies
Summary California prosecutors have filed two counts of vehicular manslaughter against the driver of a Tesla on Autopilot who ran a red light, slammed into another car and killed two people in 2019. The filing of charges in the California crash could serve notice to drivers who use systems like Autopilot that they cannot rely on them to control vehicles.</description></item></channel></rss>