<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crash on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crash/</link><description>Recent content in crash on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 22:10:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 people were killed and at least 19 injured when vehicles crashed into pedestrians in Lincoln, Nebraska</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629540be92eeb4df5f3f994a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 22:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629540be92eeb4df5f3f994a/</guid><description>Two people are dead and at least 19 others injured after a two-car crash struck multiple pedestrians in Lincoln, Nebraska, according to authorities.
Highlights At least one of the 19 injured is in critical condition. Two women who were in one vehicle were killed, while the driver of the other vehicle is receiving treatment at a hospital. A vehicle was traveling westbound near 52nd and O streets, Lincoln Police Captain Max Hubka says.</description></item><item><title>Juveniles Crash Stolen Car into White House Security Barrier: Secret Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d2020b2d62a0e0bbd5325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 18:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d2020b2d62a0e0bbd5325/</guid><description>Two juveniles were injured Monday after crashing a stolen car into a concrete security barrier near the White House, the U.S. Secret Service said.
Highlights The car slammed into a concrete barrier and a telephone pole at 17th Street and Pennsylvania Avenue NW, officials said. Video shows a silver sedan partly crumpled in the front across the street from a Secret Service guard post. The two juveniles were taken to a hospital and are now in stable condition.</description></item><item><title>YouTuber who jumped from plane has pilots license revoked</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264b5f464a967818f802ddf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 02:29:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264b5f464a967818f802ddf/</guid><description>A YouTuber who parachuted from a small airplane over California mountains last year after claiming engine trouble purposely caused the aircraft to crash so he could record it, the FAA said in a recent letter.
Highlights Trevor Jacob parachuted from a small airplane over California mountains last year. He claimed engine trouble caused the plane to crash so he could record it, the FAA says. Jacob&amp;rsquo;s private pilot certificate, or license, has been revoked.</description></item><item><title>Woman arrested after crashing car, fleeing on foot showed signs of intoxication before bribing deputy with sex to let her go, Pct. 4 says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62644f470d537231b2b9d013/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 19:11:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62644f470d537231b2b9d013/</guid><description>As Ortiz was being taken to jail, she attempted to bribe the deputy by offering him “sexual acts and cash in exchange to be let go,” authorities reported.
Highlights Dulce Ortiz was arrested after crashing car, fleeing on foot, and showing signs of intoxication before bribing deputy with sex to let her go, authorities say. Ortiz was charged with Failure to Stop and Give Information. As Ortiz was being taken to jail, she attempted to bribe the deputy by offering him “sexual acts and cash in exchange to be let go,” authorities report.</description></item><item><title>South Dakota attorney general Jason Ravnsborg impeached over fatal crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62564ed6fa847101609a9aab/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 04:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62564ed6fa847101609a9aab/</guid><description>Ravnsborg struck and killed a pedestrian on the shoulder of a highway in September 2020.
Highlights South Dakota House impeached state Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg over 2020 fatal crash in which he initially told authorities he thought he had struck a deer or another large animal. On Monday night, he sent lawmakers a pair of defiant letters urging them to vote against impeachment. The South Dakota Legislature had never investigated impeachment for an elected official, and only once, in 1917, launched an impeachment inquiry into a circuit judge.</description></item><item><title>No survivors found after China's worst air disaster in more than a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b0035cf2c01a01c74d42c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b0035cf2c01a01c74d42c/</guid><description>No survivors of a China Eastern Airlines plane crash have been found after a second day of search efforts, Chinese investigators said late Tuesday.
Highlights Chinese investigators say no survivors have been found after second day of search efforts. Boeing 737-800 carrying 132 people crashed Monday afternoon in a remote, mountainous region in the south of the country. The cause of the crash is not yet clear, an official from the Civil Aviation Administration of China (CAAC) said.</description></item><item><title>Police helicopter goes down in California's Newport Bay, 2 pilots hospitalized</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621269317d8d5afb54b6fced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621269317d8d5afb54b6fced/</guid><description>One officer has died and another was critically injured when the police department helicopter they were in crashed into shallow water in Southern California&amp;rsquo;s N
Highlights Nicholas Vella, 44, a died of his injuries from the crash, Huntington Beach Police Chief Eric Parra said Saturday night. The helicopter was responding to a report of a fight in Newport Beach when it crash-landed around 6:30 p.m. The second officer, whose identity has not been released, was hospitalized in critical but stable condition.</description></item><item><title>US skateboarder, 22, among four people killed in Iceland plane crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62035bb5ce5b329f1bbc3da4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62035bb5ce5b329f1bbc3da4/</guid><description>US skateboarder and filmmaker Josh Neuman was one of four people killed in a plane crash in Iceland, local authorities confirmed.
Highlights Four bodies found at bottom of Lake Thingvallavik, Iceland. US skateboarder, 22-year-old known for skydiving videos, killed in plane crash. Neuman was in Iceland to shoot commercial content for Belgian brand Suspicious Antwerp. He produced videos that attracted more than 106 million views on YouTube and had more than 1.</description></item><item><title>Tesla driver charged with vehicular manslaughter over fatal Autopilot crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7ef531b69bf02ce1152b4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 11:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7ef531b69bf02ce1152b4/</guid><description>Misuse of autopilot, which can control steering, speed and braking, is the subject of investigations by two federal agencies
Summary California prosecutors have filed two counts of vehicular manslaughter against the driver of a Tesla on Autopilot who ran a red light, slammed into another car and killed two people in 2019. The filing of charges in the California crash could serve notice to drivers who use systems like Autopilot that they cannot rely on them to control vehicles.</description></item></channel></rss>