<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>young on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/young/</link><description>Recent content in young on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 06:18:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/young/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police teargas Paris protestors after Macron re-elected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62663d2d06fe5ea2ed6e776a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 06:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62663d2d06fe5ea2ed6e776a/</guid><description>Riot police charged and sprayed teargas on demonstrators in central Paris protesting after President Emmanuel Macron was re-elected on Sunday, footage from social media showed.
Highlights Police charged and sprayed teargas on demonstrators in central Paris protesting after President Emmanuel Macron was re-elected on Sunday. Police sought to break up a crowd of mostly young people who had gathered in the central neighborhood of Chatelet to protest, images on Twitter showed.</description></item><item><title>Two cousins, 12 and 14, killed while playing with gun on Instagram Live, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242a44733c2f2f0a74a6761/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242a44733c2f2f0a74a6761/</guid><description>Two young cousins from Missouri were livestreaming when one fatally shot the other before killing herself, police and a relative of the victims said.
Highlights Paris Harvey, 12, and her cousin Kuaron Harvey, 14, were livestreaming when one fatally shot the other before she killed herself, police say. Police classified the incident as a murder-suicide, but family members say it was a tragic accident. Paris’ mother, Shinise Harvey, says she let her daughter go to the apartment for a family party celebrating March birthdays.</description></item><item><title>Florida woman used PPP loan to hire hit man to kill young mother in front of her daughter, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e65f926b8af585e410b93/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 15:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e65f926b8af585e410b93/</guid><description>A Florida woman is accused of using some of her Covid-19 relief loan to hire a hit man to kill another woman, police said.
Highlights Le’Shonte Jones, 24, was shot multiple times on May 3 as she walked home with her 3-year-old daughter. Suspect Jasmine Martinez is accused of using some of her Covid-19 relief loan to hire a hit man to kill Jones, police say. She is alleged to have withdrawn about $10,000 from a federal Paycheck Protection Program loan she received for a single-employment beauty salon.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine's growing reserve army 'getting ready' amid fears of Russian attack | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcf2e6f76291a3b787a8ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcf2e6f76291a3b787a8ec/</guid><description>An increasing number of Ukrainians are joining territorial defence groups designed to support the regular armed forces in the event of a Russian offensive - such as by protecting key locations like council buildings and bridges.
Summary &amp;ldquo;The &amp;lsquo;young blood&amp;rsquo; … are people who didn&amp;rsquo;t serve in the armed forces for different reasons but they passed our combat training&amp;hellip; His group, 130 Battalion of Territorial Defence of Kyiv, comprises some 320-330 reservists, aged between 21 and 56.</description></item></channel></rss>