<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>unmarked on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unmarked/</link><description>Recent content in unmarked on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 10:13:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unmarked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dozens more graves found at former residential school sites</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e1fa125bbfbde8467d546/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 10:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e1fa125bbfbde8467d546/</guid><description>Indigenous-led investigations have discovered more than 1,100 unmarked graves in recent months.
Highlights Indigenous-led investigations have discovered more than 1,100 unmarked graves in recent months. Indigenous-lead investigations have found more than a million unmarked graves. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a very tough time,&amp;rdquo; says one of the people at the site of the unmarked graves, the man said. &amp;ldquo;We walk every day, drive every day,&amp;rdquo; says the man who led the investigation, who said it was a &amp;ldquo;very tough time&amp;rdquo; for his community to find the graves in the community.</description></item><item><title>93 Unmarked Graves Found at Residential School That Targeted Indigenous Children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0d56e8c68a1875fc2c366/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 05:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0d56e8c68a1875fc2c366/</guid><description>The investigation also uncovered testimonies of brutal treatment, including starvation and sexual assault, that non-Indigenous authorities repeatedly ignored.
Summary Cariboo Indian Residential School, also known as St. Joseph’s Mission Residential School, at Williams Lake in 1949. It was run in part by the same Catholic order that ran the former Kamloops Indian Residential School, where about 200 unmarked graves were detected in May 2021. Last May, Tk&amp;rsquo;emlúps te Secwépemc confirmed hundreds of unmarked graves at the Catholic-run Kamloops Indian Residential School grounds.</description></item></channel></rss>