<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>scene on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/scene/</link><description>Recent content in scene on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 17:14:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Four people are dead after a driver crashed a vehicle into Salem, Oregon, encampment of unhoused people</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62409b5406eaa744d5558b60/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 17:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62409b5406eaa744d5558b60/</guid><description>Four people died early Sunday morning after a motorist crashed a vehicle into an encampment of unhoused people in Salem, Oregon, according to a news release from the Salem Police Department.
Highlights Two people died at the scene of the crash, while two others died after being taken to a hospital, police say. The driver of the vehicle was also taken by ambulance to hospital. Road closures will remain in effect Sunday morning while the incident is investigated, police said.</description></item><item><title>Germany: Several injured at Heidelberg University after student opens fire in lecture hall; then kills himself.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eef754befb8041d1cd3d53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eef754befb8041d1cd3d53/</guid><description>The attacker entered the theatre in the Neuenheimer Feld area, opened fire and then fled the scene, police said.
Summary Germany: Lone gunman dead after shooting four people at university in HeidelbergGermany: Lone gunman dead after shooting four people at university in Heidelberg The attacker entered the theatre in the Neuenheimer Feld area, opened fire and then fled the scene, police said. Pic: APA lone gunman has shot four people at a university lecture hall in Germany - some of whom are seriously injured.</description></item><item><title>Bob Saget is dead at 65</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dba14f0e3f78f96fee79ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dba14f0e3f78f96fee79ed/</guid><description>Bob Saget has died. TMZ first reported the comedian and actor&amp;rsquo;s death, suggesting he died Sunday at the Ritz-Carlton in Orlando. First responders were called to his hotel room Sunday afternoon, but the actor was pronounced dead at the scene. He was 65. No cause of death has been reported.Saget has [&amp;hellip;]
Summary First responders were called to his hotel room Sunday afternoon, but the actor was pronounced dead at the scene.</description></item></channel></rss>