<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>georgia on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/georgia/</link><description>Recent content in georgia on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 15:13:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/georgia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lawsuit seeks to block 'insurrectionist' Marjorie Taylor Greene from reelection bid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ddc1206616fb7f6cb3755/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ddc1206616fb7f6cb3755/</guid><description>A group of Georgia voters on Thursday asked state officials to block Republican U.S. Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene from running for reelection, alleging she is unfit for office because of her support of rioters who attacked the U.S. Capitol.
Highlights Georgia voters want to block Republican U.S. Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene from running for reelection. The voters claim Greene has violated a provision of the Constitution known as the &amp;ldquo;Insurrectionist Disqualification Clause&amp;rdquo; The clause prohibits politicians from running if they have engaged in &amp;ldquo;insurrection or rebellion&amp;rdquo; against the United States.</description></item><item><title>"Mega" iceberg releases 152 billion tons of fresh water into ocean</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef2f93dffb0db4d8023292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef2f93dffb0db4d8023292/</guid><description>The iceberg was once one of the largest on record. Now it&amp;rsquo;s melting, and scientists are waiting to see how it&amp;rsquo;s going to impact South Georgia&amp;rsquo;s marine life.
Summary When the massive A68A iceberg snapped off its ice shelf in July 2017, it was the sixth-largest iceberg on record. The iceberg once measured roughly 5,719 square kilometers — nearly half the size of Connecticut — but it started to disintegrate once it arrived to the South Georgia island in the Atlantic Ocean.</description></item></channel></rss>