<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wants on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wants/</link><description>Recent content in wants on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 21:14:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EU wants to remove Russia's largest bank from SWIFT system and ban state-owned broadcasters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272ec88341644d39f769c5f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 21:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272ec88341644d39f769c5f/</guid><description>In addition to proposing a ban on Russian oil, the European Union is taking several other measures against Moscow over its war in Ukraine, EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said Wednesday.
Highlights EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen called on the 27-nation bloc to ban oil imports from Russia in a sixth package of sanctions targeting Moscow for its war in Ukraine. In addition to proposing a ban on Russian oil, the EU is taking several other measures against Moscow over its war.</description></item><item><title>French President Emmanuel Macron said he “really wants to piss off” the unvaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d517e13adecc797b78cc9c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d517e13adecc797b78cc9c/</guid><description>French President Emmanuel Macron raised eyebrows and provoked a fair amount of shock on Tuesday when he warned people in France not yet vaccinated against Covid-19 that he would annoy them by limiting access to key aspects of life in the country.
Summary “I don’t want to piss the French people off… But as for the non-vaccinated, I really want to piss them off (emmerder). You will no longer be able to go for a coffee, you will no longer be able to go to the theatre.</description></item><item><title>Germany to Allow Sale of Cannabis ‘for Pleasure Purposes’, Opponents Outraged</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61caa7fe173ae941b42f870d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 06:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61caa7fe173ae941b42f870d/</guid><description>Summary Berlin, December 14th, 2021 (The Berlin Spectator) — In Berlin, almost everyone seems to be an expert on cannabis and joints. Pot ‘for Pleasure Purposes’At this point, consuming marijuana is legal, but owning or selling it is not, in most cases. According to its coalition agreement, Chancellor Olaf Scholz’ government wants to allow what it calls “controlled sales to adults for pleasure purposes at licensed shops”. American Study on Cannabis UseThe proponents might be right, in a way, but so are the opponents.</description></item></channel></rss>