<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>took on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/took/</link><description>Recent content in took on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 14:09:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/took/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>"First Time In History": Cancer Vanishes For Every Patient In Drug Trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f5c0ccaa4a16d6258a673/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 14:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f5c0ccaa4a16d6258a673/</guid><description>A small group of people with rectal cancer just experienced something of a miracle as their cancer simply vanished after an experimental treatment.
Highlights A small group of people with rectal cancer just experienced something of a miracle as their cancer simply vanished after an experimental treatment. In a small clinical trial, 18 patients took a drug called Dostarlimab for around six months, and in the end, every one of them saw their tumours disappear.</description></item><item><title>More than 30 people, including children, killed in stampede at church event in Nigeria</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295e99707e815f4036a39c5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 10:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295e99707e815f4036a39c5/</guid><description>More than 30 people were killed and others injured when a stampede broke out at a church event in the southeastern Nigerian city of Port Harcourt on Saturday, according to police and security officials.
Highlights The incident took place at a local polo club, where the nearby Kings Assembly Church had organized a gift donation drive. Most of the casualties were children, police say. The drive had not yet started when the stampede took place, a spokeswoman for the state police says.</description></item><item><title>Intel shareholders reject executive pay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62835a5e22d92d210a9e193a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 08:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62835a5e22d92d210a9e193a/</guid><description>The vote won&amp;rsquo;t immediately affect the compensation of Intel&amp;rsquo;s executives.
Highlights Intel shareholders voted against its executive compensation package last week. The vote is advisory, and won&amp;rsquo;t immediately affect the compensation of Intel&amp;rsquo;s executives. CEO Pat Gelsinger took over as CEO of Intel in Feb. 2021, and received a compensation package worth $178.59 million. The actual payouts depend on the performance of Intel stock over five years, Intel said in its proxy filing.</description></item><item><title>Burial sites found at 53 Native American boarding schools: Interior Dept</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c992ba64a7397161ee61f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c992ba64a7397161ee61f/</guid><description>A U.S. government investigation into the dark history of Native American boarding schools has found &amp;quot;marked or unmarked burial sites&amp;quot; at 53 of them, Interior Secretary Deb Haaland said on Wednesday.
Highlights Interior Secretary Deb Haaland announced the investigation last year into the dark history of Native American boarding schools in the United States. The schools used education to change culture so tribal land could be taken. Many children were abused at the schools, and tens of thousands were never heard from again, activists and researchers say.</description></item><item><title>Yuri Madvedev: Russian troops drive tank over own commander amid anger at high casualties</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fb5cec8981f2647a1505f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fb5cec8981f2647a1505f/</guid><description>Yuri Madvedev: Russian troops drive tank over own commander amid anger at high casualties
Highlights Colonel Yuri Medvedev is said to have suffered severe leg injuries in the attack. Almost half the troops in his brigade of 1,500 either died, or were wounded, in a series of clashes in the early weeks of the war. Chechen leader Ramzan Kadyrov appears to show the colonel being medically evacuated. He was airlifted to Belarus for emergency treatment and awarded a Russian military honour.</description></item><item><title>Abortions in Texas fell 60% in 1st month under new limits</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205e29f7152236a20460ba4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 04:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205e29f7152236a20460ba4/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Abortions in Texas fell by 60% in the first month under the most restrictive abortion law in the U.S. in decades, according to new figures that for the first time reveal a full accounting of the immediate impact.
Highlights Abortions in Texas fell by 60% in the first month under the most restrictive abortion law in the U.S. in decades. That&amp;rsquo;s according to the fist figures released by Texas health officials since the law known as Senate Bill 8 took effect in September.</description></item></channel></rss>