<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>old on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/old/</link><description>Recent content in old on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 08:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FDA authorizes Pfizer Covid booster dose for kids ages 5 to 11 years old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284ab81bdb402c784425edc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284ab81bdb402c784425edc/</guid><description>The FDA determined that a third shot can help boost protection for children in this age group and the benefits outweigh the risks.
Highlights Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Covid vaccine for children ages 5 to 11 at least five months after their two-dose primary series. CDC has final say on whether health-care providers should start administering the boosters. The FDA determined that a third shot can help boost protection for children in this age group and the benefits outweigh the risks, the FDA says.</description></item><item><title>19-year-old could become the youngest African American law school graduate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62760ed4074b07ecd97af0ad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 06:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62760ed4074b07ecd97af0ad/</guid><description>Haley Taylor Schlitz was accepted to nine different law schools when she was only 16.
Highlights Haley Taylor Schlitz is set to graduate May 13 at Southern Methodist University&amp;rsquo;s Dedman School of Law. At 19 years old, she is the youngest African American to graduate law school. Her path to law school wasn&amp;rsquo;t conventional when she was just 13 years old. She hopes to work on education policy issues for an elected official or nonprofit organization.</description></item><item><title>Army report finds horses that carry the coffins of America's heroes live in 'unsatisfactory' conditions, after 2 die</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625042c77211b14eee386296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 14:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625042c77211b14eee386296/</guid><description>The military horses that carry America&amp;rsquo;s heroes to their final resting place in Arlington National Cemetery are living in unsanitary and potentially life-threatening conditions, according to a US Army report reviewed exclusively by CNN, consuming poor-quality feed, suffering from parasites and standing in their own excrement in tiny mud lots scattered with gravel and construction waste.
Highlights A US Army report reviewed exclusively by CNN found a host of systemic problems with the living conditions of the horses in the 3rd Infantry Regiment, also called the Old Guard, best known for guarding the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier.</description></item><item><title>Construction crew finds mummified body in wall at old Oakland convention center</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b20f8a58b16540ef2ad44/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 10:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b20f8a58b16540ef2ad44/</guid><description>A construction crew discovered what authorities described Wednesday as a mummified body in the wall of a historic building undergoing a remodel in Oakland.
Highlights A worker noticed what appeared to be a human body in a wall that was being deconstructed. Authorities plan on obtaining fingerprints to determine who the person is, how they got there and how long they&amp;rsquo;ve been there. The Henry J. Kaiser Convention Center opened in 1914 and was shuttered nearly a century later.</description></item></channel></rss>