<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suspended on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspended/</link><description>Recent content in suspended on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 22:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspended/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Georgia students sue over blocked protest against rebel flag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62841e4fe20491d33c91ccef/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62841e4fe20491d33c91ccef/</guid><description>ATLANTA (AP) — Several Black students who were suspended for trying to protest Confederate flag displays at their school in Georgia have filed a federal lawsuit against their school district and its board members, accusing them of allowing an extensive pattern of racism including “overt bigotry and animosity by some white students and teachers against African American students.”
Highlights Lawsuit filed against school district and its board members in Georgia. Accuses them of allowing an extensive pattern of racism including “overt bigotry and animosity by some white students and teachers against African American students’ students.</description></item><item><title>Kanye West Barred From Performing at Grammys, His Rep Confirms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623679dab9d8585295dd0692/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 00:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623679dab9d8585295dd0692/</guid><description>Kanye West&amp;rsquo;s planned performance at the 2022 Grammy Awards has been scrapped following his online posts, his rep has confirmed to E! News.
Highlights Kanye West was supposed to perform at the 2022 Grammy Awards. His rep confirmed a March 18 report from &amp;ldquo;The Blast&amp;rdquo; that the rapper has been canceled. The Recording Academy had never confirmed a planned performance by Kanye. The rapper is nominated for five Grammys for the 2022 show, which is set to take place on April 3.</description></item><item><title>UPS and FedEx halting shipments to Russia and Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d11141a4753b50838d0ce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 18:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d11141a4753b50838d0ce/</guid><description>U.S.-based United Parcel Service Inc and FedEx Corp , two of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest logistics companies, have said they are halting delivery service to Russia and Ukraine in light of the Russian invasion of its neighbor.
Highlights U.S.-based United Parcel Service Inc and FedEx Corp halt delivery service to Russia and Ukraine. Both inbound and outbound services have been suspended to Ukraine, as well as deliveries to destinations in Russia, UPS and FedEx said in online statements.</description></item><item><title>Two Denver police officers suspended for excessive force for using pepper spray, baton on peaceful protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 12:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</guid><description>Two Denver police officers will serve unpaid suspensions for using excessive force on demonstrators during two separate protests in 2020.
Highlights Officer Jesse Trudel twice used pepper spray on people peacefully protesting the murder of George Floyd. Body camera video shows the people he targeted were not posing any threat, police disciplinary letter says. Another officer, Daniel Veith, will serve a five-day unpaid suspension for using his baton to hit a person who was protesting the forced removal of an encampment of people experiencing homelessness on Aug.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Corbyn barred from rejoining UK Labour party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f19a519d4c7d986087968b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 19:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f19a519d4c7d986087968b/</guid><description>The opposition leader for the better part of the 2010s was suspended by the party in October 2020 after his party was accused of systematic antisemitism.
Summary Jeremy Corbyn, a Labour Party MP and the United Kingdom’s former opposition leader from 2015-2020, was not reinstated as an MP in the party following a vote on Tuesday, international media reports. Today’s NEC vote and Keir Starmer’s ongoing decision to bar me from sitting as a Labour MP is disappointing.</description></item></channel></rss>