<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nations on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nations/</link><description>Recent content in nations on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:09:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs the nation’s strictest abortion ban</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f89f3cd3741808d78f4c8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f89f3cd3741808d78f4c8/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt on Wednesday signed into law the nation’s strictest abortion ban, making the state the first in the nation to effectively end availability of the procedure.
Highlights The law takes effect immediately upon Stitt’s signature and prohibits all abortions with few exceptions. The ban enforced by civil lawsuits rather than criminal prosecution, similar to a Texas law that was passed last year. The only exceptions in the Oklahoma law are to save the life of a pregnant woman or if the pregnancy is the result of rape or incest that has been reported to law enforcement.</description></item><item><title>Oil prices ease as nations agree to tap reserves</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249ab0c63c8d6984c519258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249ab0c63c8d6984c519258/</guid><description>Both Brent and US crude benchmarks settled down around 13 percent.
Highlights Both Brent and US crude benchmarks settled down around 13 percent in their biggest weekly falls in two years. US President Joe Biden announced the release of one million barrels per day (bpd) of crude oil for six months from May, which at 180 million barrels is the largest release ever from the US Strategic Petroleum Reserve (SPR) Member countries of the IEA did not agree on volumes or commitments of each country at their emergency meeting.</description></item><item><title>US expelling 12 Russian diplomats from UN mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9df2b7fd9ca46e8e2980/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9df2b7fd9ca46e8e2980/</guid><description>Russia’s United Nations ambassador said move ‘gross violation’ of UN agreement with US
Highlights US is expelling 12 Russian diplomats at the United Nations for engaging in activities not in accordance with their responsibilities and obligations as diplomats. Russia’s UN Ambassador Vassily Nebenzia described the move as ‘yet another hostile step undertaken by the host country’ He called the expulsions a ‘gross violation’ of the UN agreement with the US as the host of the Vienna Convention governing diplomatic relations.</description></item><item><title>Red Cross declares first-ever national blood crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddf002a38635dfa71251c9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddf002a38635dfa71251c9/</guid><description>The historic shortage is forcing doctors to make tough decisions on who should get blood and who has to wait until there is more supply.
Summary The nation&amp;rsquo;s blood supply is dangerously low, prompting the Red Cross to announce a national blood crisis for the first time. The COVID-19 pandemic has caused a decline in donor turnout, the cancellation of blood drives and staffing challenges, leading to the worst blood shortage in more than a decade, the Red Cross said.</description></item></channel></rss>