<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>banks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/banks/</link><description>Recent content in banks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:56:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/banks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Credit Suisse faces US probe after telling investors to 'destroy documents' linked to oligarch yacht loans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242591daecc02c922eada32/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242591daecc02c922eada32/</guid><description>The House Oversight Committee launched a probe Monday into Credit Suisse, demanding documents linked to the bank&amp;rsquo;s compliance with sanctions on Russian oligarchs.
Highlights House Oversight Committee asks for documents related to sanctions on Russian oligarchs. House Democrats say it is concerned that the deal may be &amp;ldquo;disguarded&amp;rdquo; by the U.S. Congress. The Committee says it wants to know if Russian investors are complying with the sanctions imposed by the West.</description></item><item><title>EU considering SWIFT exclusion for Belarus banks - official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220db11b54319ca4326b78b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220db11b54319ca4326b78b/</guid><description>The European Union is considering excluding banks in Belarus from the SWIFT messaging system that underpins the global financial transactions, as it has already done for seven Russian banks, an EU official said on Thursday.
Highlights EU considering excluding banks in Belarus from the SWIFT messaging system that underpins the global financial transactions. EU official: &amp;ldquo;SWIFT is not as strategically important in the Belarus economy as it is in the Russian side&amp;rdquo; EU has already done for seven Russian banks, an EU official said on Thursday.</description></item></channel></rss>