<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>unlimited on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unlimited/</link><description>Recent content in unlimited on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 17:16:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unlimited/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colorado Springs to pay nearly $3 mln to family of Black man shot dead by police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</guid><description>A Colorado city has agreed to pay $2.9 million to settle a civil rights lawsuit filed by the family of a 19-year-old Black man who was fatally shot in the back by police in 2019, both sides in the litigation said on Tuesday.
Highlights De&amp;rsquo;Von Bailey was shot four times after he bolted from two Colorado Springs policemen who were questioning him about an armed robbery in August 2019. Police said they retrieved a handgun from Bailey after he was shot.</description></item><item><title>Brazil will stop monitoring deforestation in the Cerrado, the world's most species-rich savanna, a government researcher said on Thursday, days after data showed destruction hitting a 6-year high in 2021.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbcb88e7e972b0314f62fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 06:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbcb88e7e972b0314f62fa/</guid><description>Brazil will stop monitoring deforestation in the Cerrado, the world&amp;rsquo;s most species-rich savanna, a government researcher said on Thursday citing a lack of funds, days after data showed destruction hitting a 6-year high in 2021.
Summary REUTERS/Roberto JaymeSAO PAULO, Jan 6 (Reuters) - Brazil will stop monitoring deforestation in the Cerrado, the world&amp;rsquo;s most species-rich savanna, a government researcher said on Thursday citing a lack of funds, days after data showed destruction hitting a 6-year high in 2021.</description></item><item><title>UAE to ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan. 10</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d22e8c3e1379b736c3ed73/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d22e8c3e1379b736c3ed73/</guid><description>The United Arab Emirates will ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan. 10, the state news agency WAM reported on Saturday, citing the foreign ministry and the National Emergency Crisis and Disaster Management Authority.
Summary A family walks at Dubai International Airport, as Emirates airline resumed limited outbound passenger flights amid outbreak of the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Dubai, UAE April 27, 2020. REUTERS/Ahmed JadallahCAIRO, Jan 1 (Reuters) - The United Arab Emirates will ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>