<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>unlimited on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unlimited/</link><description>Recent content in unlimited on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:15:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unlimited/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sweden's ruling party backs joining NATO, paving way for bid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62815f419889176b513ea0b5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62815f419889176b513ea0b5/</guid><description>Sweden&amp;rsquo;s ruling Social Democrats said on Sunday they backed the country joining NATO, abandoning decades of opposition in the wake of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine and creating a large parliament majority in favour of membership.
Highlights Sweden&amp;rsquo;s ruling Social Democrats said on Sunday they backed the country joining NATO. With neighboring Finland already set to hand in its application, Prime Minister Magdalena Andersson is now all but certain to launch a formal application within days.</description></item><item><title>New York subway shooting suspect indicted on terrorism charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277b5c61855fe506386caa8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 12:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277b5c61855fe506386caa8/</guid><description>If convicted on the terrorism charge, James could be sentenced to life in prison.
Highlights Grand jury indicts Frank James, 62, for terrorism and other charges stemming from April 12 attack. James, a Bronx native, is accused of setting off smoke bombs and opening fire inside a New York City subway car in Brooklyn. If convicted on the terrorism charge, James could be sentenced to life in prison. The motive of the attack has not been determined but the suspect has been linked to several violent incidents in New York&amp;rsquo;s public transportation system in the past.</description></item><item><title>Amazon to reimburse U.S. employees who travel for abortions, other treatments</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270d635c4226b840c2355ee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 07:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270d635c4226b840c2355ee/</guid><description>Amazon.com Inc , the second-largest U.S. private employer, told its staff on Monday it will pay up to $4,000 in travel expenses annually for non-life threatening medical treatments including abortions, according to a message seen by Reuters.
Highlights Amazon.com will pay up to $4,000 in travel expenses annually for non-life threatening medical treatments including abortions. The online retailer is the latest company after Citigroup Inc (C.N), Yelp Inc (YELP.N) and others to respond to Republican-backed state laws curbing abortion access, helping employees bypass them.</description></item><item><title>IAEA says Ukraine carried out first staff rotations at Chornobyl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62542c6cad32ae1f2639a0ab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 13:26:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62542c6cad32ae1f2639a0ab/</guid><description>Ukraine informed the International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA) on Sunday that it had carried out the first staff rotation at the Chornobyl Nuclear Power Plant in three weeks, IAEA Director General Rafael Mariano Grossi said, adding the agency would send a mission there soon to assist in returning in to normality.
Highlights Russia occupied the defunct power station north of Kyiv soon after invading Ukraine on Feb. 24 but Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s state nuclear energy company said in early April they had left the plant and were heading towards the border with Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Syria's air defences confront 'Israeli aggression', state media report | Reuters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252d9796b3070546000ca04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 13:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252d9796b3070546000ca04/</guid><description>Syrian air defences confronted an &amp;quot;Israeli air aggression&amp;quot; on Saturday in the country&amp;rsquo;s central region, Syrian state media reported.
Highlights Syrian air defences confronted an &amp;ldquo;Israeli air aggression&amp;rdquo; in the country&amp;rsquo;s central region, state media reported. Israel&amp;rsquo;s military declined to comment on the reported air strikes in Syria. Syria state media: &amp;ldquo;The Israeli enemy launched an air aggression from the north of Lebanon, targeting some points in the central region,&amp;rdquo; state media said citing a military source.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Congressman Fortenberry found guilty of lying to FBI about funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623df8e25df3ce3b3788be8f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623df8e25df3ce3b3788be8f/</guid><description>A U.S. jury on Thursday convicted U.S. Congressman Jeff Fortenberry, a Republican from Nebraska, of lying to FBI investigators about illegal contributions to his 2016 re-election campaign.
Highlights U.S. Congressman Jeff Fortenberry, a Republican from Nebraska, found guilty of scheming to falsify and conceal material facts. Federal law prohibits foreign nationals from donating to federal election campaigns. Federal prosecutors alleged that he lied about $30,000 in campaign contributions he received in 2016 from Nigerian billionaire Gilbert Chagoury.</description></item><item><title>Russian navy commander killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237a6cbdf7fd557a009c592/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237a6cbdf7fd557a009c592/</guid><description>A senior naval commander in Russia&amp;rsquo;s Black Sea Fleet has been killed in Ukraine, the governor of Sevastopol said on Sunday.
Highlights A senior naval commander in Russia&amp;rsquo;s Black Sea Fleet has been killed in Ukraine. The deputy commander of the fleet died during fighting in the eastern Ukrainian port city of Mariupol. The Russian navy did not respond to a request for comment. Russia annexed Crimea from Ukraine in 2014, which is located on the Crimean peninsula, which Moscow annexed from Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russian central bank decides not to reopen stock market trading next week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233ec2c5694c25a4df0abfa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 02:19:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233ec2c5694c25a4df0abfa/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank on Saturday said it has decided not to reopen stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange from March 14-18, with the exception of some non-open-market transactions an transactions using the SPFI payment system.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank has decided not to reopen stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange from March 14-18. The foreign exchange market, money market and repo market would open at 0700 GMT on those days.</description></item><item><title>India says it accidentally fired missile into Pakistan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c5675b17ba5fd473a5da4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 08:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c5675b17ba5fd473a5da4/</guid><description>India said on Friday it accidentally fired a missile into Pakistan because of a &amp;quot;technical malfunction&amp;quot; during routine maintenance.
Highlights India says it accidentally fired a missile into Pakistan because of a &amp;ldquo;technical malfunction&amp;rdquo; during routine maintenance. The government said the missile landed in an area of Pakistan. The incident is &amp;ldquo;deeply regrettable&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;relieved that there has been no loss of life due to the accident,&amp;rdquo; the government said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Minneapolis school teachers call a strike; classes canceled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62287dcd67fc0059580cec29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62287dcd67fc0059580cec29/</guid><description>Minneapolis public school teachers called a strike on Monday, their first for more than 50 years, leading the school district to cancel classes for 30,000 students beginning Tuesday until the work stoppage is resolved.
Highlights Some 4,500 teachers and support staff plan to form picket lines at school buildings on Tuesday morning and hold a rally and march in the afternoon. Teachers are demanding better wages, mental health support and limits on class sizes.</description></item><item><title>Canada prepared to welcome an unlimited number of Ukrainians fleeing war, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622248ec8170757842306465/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 17:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622248ec8170757842306465/</guid><description>Immigration Minister Sean Fraser announced Thursday the federal government has created two new pathways for Ukrainians fleeing their war-torn country to come to Canada — part of a plan to accept an &amp;quot;unlimited number&amp;quot; of people who want to leave.
Highlights Immigration Minister Sean Fraser announced Thursday the federal government has created two new pathways for Ukrainians fleeing their war-torn country to come to Canada. Some critics, including NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh, have called on the government to drop the visa requirement altogether to allow all Ukrainians to travel to Canada unencumbered.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine to receive more missiles and Turkish drones, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220a2353dc68f7988b0834c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 11:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220a2353dc68f7988b0834c/</guid><description>Ukrainian Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Wednesday the country was set to receive Stinger and Javelin missiles from abroad, as well as another shipment of Turkish drones.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Wednesday the country was set to receive Stinger and Javelin missiles from abroad, as well as another shipment of Turkish drones. Western countries have pledged to supply Ukraine with weapons to fend off a Russian invasion.</description></item><item><title>Moscow Exchange won't resume stock trading on Wednesday - cenbank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fb43e61b0b7aaa278d207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fb43e61b0b7aaa278d207/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank kept stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange suspended for a third day in a row on Wednesday, but said it would allow a limited range of operations for the first time this week.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank kept stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange suspended for a third day in a row on Wednesday. The central bank said it would allow a limited range of operations for the first time this week.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Springs to pay nearly $3 mln to family of Black man shot dead by police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</guid><description>A Colorado city has agreed to pay $2.9 million to settle a civil rights lawsuit filed by the family of a 19-year-old Black man who was fatally shot in the back by police in 2019, both sides in the litigation said on Tuesday.
Highlights De&amp;rsquo;Von Bailey was shot four times after he bolted from two Colorado Springs policemen who were questioning him about an armed robbery in August 2019. Police said they retrieved a handgun from Bailey after he was shot.</description></item><item><title>Brazil will stop monitoring deforestation in the Cerrado, the world's most species-rich savanna, a government researcher said on Thursday, days after data showed destruction hitting a 6-year high in 2021.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbcb88e7e972b0314f62fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 06:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbcb88e7e972b0314f62fa/</guid><description>Brazil will stop monitoring deforestation in the Cerrado, the world&amp;rsquo;s most species-rich savanna, a government researcher said on Thursday citing a lack of funds, days after data showed destruction hitting a 6-year high in 2021.
Summary REUTERS/Roberto JaymeSAO PAULO, Jan 6 (Reuters) - Brazil will stop monitoring deforestation in the Cerrado, the world&amp;rsquo;s most species-rich savanna, a government researcher said on Thursday citing a lack of funds, days after data showed destruction hitting a 6-year high in 2021.</description></item><item><title>UAE to ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan. 10</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d22e8c3e1379b736c3ed73/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d22e8c3e1379b736c3ed73/</guid><description>The United Arab Emirates will ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan. 10, the state news agency WAM reported on Saturday, citing the foreign ministry and the National Emergency Crisis and Disaster Management Authority.
Summary A family walks at Dubai International Airport, as Emirates airline resumed limited outbound passenger flights amid outbreak of the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Dubai, UAE April 27, 2020. REUTERS/Ahmed JadallahCAIRO, Jan 1 (Reuters) - The United Arab Emirates will ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>