<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lock on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lock/</link><description>Recent content in lock on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teacher Closed Propped-Open Door Before Uvalde School Shooting: Police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296dc96ec3c53a05746ae29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296dc96ec3c53a05746ae29/</guid><description>New details are emerging about the door the Uvalde gunman used to gain access to the elementary school.
Highlights A Texas elementary school teacher propped the door open with a rock, police say. She then closed the door shut when she realized there was a shooter on campus, an official says. Investigators are still trying to interview the police chief who was the commander of the school shooting scene. 19 students and two teachers were killed in a classroom in Uvalde, Texas, on May 24.</description></item><item><title>Man, 21, arrested a week after 3 killed at Georgia gun range</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bb0be25355fae30fb333c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 06:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bb0be25355fae30fb333c/</guid><description>GRANTVILLE, Ga. (AP) — A 21-year-old man has been arrested in connection with a fatal armed robbery at a Georgia gun range that left three members of a family dead last week. Jacob Christian Muse, of College Park, is charged with three counts of malice murder, the Georgia Bureau of Investigation said in a news release Friday.
Highlights Jacob Christian Muse, of College Park, is charged with three counts of malice murder.</description></item></channel></rss>