<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>energy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/energy/</link><description>Recent content in energy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:10:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India's richest man is pouring more than $80 billion into green energy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1f29352ca7e76cd3ad3c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1f29352ca7e76cd3ad3c5/</guid><description>Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani is going big on green energy.
Summary Hong Kong (CNN Business) Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani is going big on green energy. The bulk of that money — about $67.7 billion — will go toward a new power plant and hydrogen system, the company said in a stock exchange filing . Reliance plans to make the massive investment over a 10-to-15-year period, and has already begun scouting for land for the 100-gigawatt capacity site.</description></item><item><title>Czech Republic to end coal use by 2033, boost nuclear power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8e22fe146efa5c4b73ba9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8e22fe146efa5c4b73ba9/</guid><description>Summary PRAGUE (AP) — The new Czech government aims to phase out coal in energy production by 2033 while increasing the country&amp;rsquo;s reliance on nuclear and renewable sources, its policy program published on Friday said. Coal-fired power plants currently generate almost 50% of total Czech electricity output. “It must accelerate the plan.”The European Union member plans to become more reliant on nuclear power, which neighboring Germany has decided to phase out by the end of 2022.</description></item></channel></rss>