<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>energy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/energy/</link><description>Recent content in energy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 16:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Turkey’s inflation soars to 73%, a 23-year high, as food and energy costs skyrocket</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a32e2543aa6618f383dc0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 16:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a32e2543aa6618f383dc0/</guid><description>Economic analysts expect Turkey&amp;rsquo;s inflation will only get worse as the country grapples with President Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s unorthodox strategy on monetary policy.
Highlights Turkey&amp;rsquo;s inflation for the month of May rose by an eye-watering 73.5% year on year. Food prices in the country of 84 million rose 91.6% in May. President Erdogan has for years refused to meaningfully raise rates to cool the resulting inflation. He instructed the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank to repeatedly slash borrowing rates last year even as inflation continued to rise.</description></item><item><title>Consumer prices rose 8.5% in March, slightly hotter than expected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625588ec6bc4da7578a98836/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 14:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625588ec6bc4da7578a98836/</guid><description>The consumer price index for March was expected to increase 8.4% from a year ago, according to Dow Jones estimates.
Highlights Consumer price index jumped 8.5% from a year ago on an unadjusted basis. Core inflation was the hottest since August 1982. The data reflected price rises not seen in the U.S. since the stagflation days of the late 1970s and early &amp;rsquo;80s. However, core inflation appeared to be ebbing, rising 0.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds of thousands of Puerto Rico's homes and businesses still without power after outage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251da32d481959242f3d509/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 19:11:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251da32d481959242f3d509/</guid><description>Hundreds of thousands of homes and businesses in Puerto Rico still were without power Saturday, more than two days after the start of an island-wide outage that began with a fire at a power plant.
Highlights Power has been restored to more than 1 million of Puerto Rico&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 million utility customers, the grid operator says. That leaves about 500,000 homes and businesses without power. An unspecified failure led to a fire at the plant outside the town of Guayanilla on the southwest coast around 8:45 p.</description></item><item><title>India's richest man is pouring more than $80 billion into green energy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1f29352ca7e76cd3ad3c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1f29352ca7e76cd3ad3c5/</guid><description>Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani is going big on green energy.
Summary Hong Kong (CNN Business) Indian billionaire Mukesh Ambani is going big on green energy. The bulk of that money — about $67.7 billion — will go toward a new power plant and hydrogen system, the company said in a stock exchange filing . Reliance plans to make the massive investment over a 10-to-15-year period, and has already begun scouting for land for the 100-gigawatt capacity site.</description></item><item><title>Czech Republic to end coal use by 2033, boost nuclear power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8e22fe146efa5c4b73ba9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8e22fe146efa5c4b73ba9/</guid><description>Summary PRAGUE (AP) — The new Czech government aims to phase out coal in energy production by 2033 while increasing the country&amp;rsquo;s reliance on nuclear and renewable sources, its policy program published on Friday said. Coal-fired power plants currently generate almost 50% of total Czech electricity output. “It must accelerate the plan.”The European Union member plans to become more reliant on nuclear power, which neighboring Germany has decided to phase out by the end of 2022.</description></item></channel></rss>