<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>positive on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/positive/</link><description>Recent content in positive on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 22:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/positive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Michigan says it won't follow CDC's more relaxed COVID-19 quarantine recommendations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61ce2bfb7e28cc2bb7b6ae30/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61ce2bfb7e28cc2bb7b6ae30/</guid><description>Michigan health officials say they won&amp;rsquo;t adopt shorter federal COVID-19 isolation/quarantine guidelines until the review
Summary Michigan says it won&amp;rsquo;t follow CDC&amp;rsquo;s more relaxed COVID-19 quarantine recommendationsShow Caption Hide Caption CDC shortens COVID-19 isolation and quarantine guidelines CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the changes were made based on &amp;ldquo;two years of science&amp;rdquo; about the virus. Rather, Michigan health leaders say they will continue to recommend previous, longer quarantine and isolation guidelines, including those for K-12 schools and congregate care settings.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds in Australia mistakenly told coronavirus test result was negative when they were positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61ca53a553ad5f95139afabc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61ca53a553ad5f95139afabc/</guid><description>The Sydney lab responsible blamed human error after hundreds with coronavirus were told they were negative amid record case numbers.
Summary A major laboratory in Australia incorrectly told 400 people their coronavirus test result was negative on Christmas Day, when they had actually tested positive for the virus. The lab responsible, based at St. Vincent&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Sydney, sent incorrect text messages on the evening of Christmas Day telling people they did not have the virus.</description></item></channel></rss>