<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>second on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/second/</link><description>Recent content in second on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/second/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First baby formula shipment arrives from Europe on U.S. military plane</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b33d9a5124cbf494c0190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b33d9a5124cbf494c0190/</guid><description>A military cargo plane carrying the first shipment of infant formula from Europe to help address a critical shortage in the United States landed in Indianapolis on Sunday, and the White House said a second flight had been arranged.
Highlights A military cargo plane carrying the first shipment of infant formula from Europe landed in Indianapolis on Sunday. The White House said a second flight carrying formula would leave from Ramstein Air Base in Germany in coming days.</description></item><item><title>US military confirms an interstellar meteor collided with Earth in 2014</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258651e2ba2db304919bd9d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258651e2ba2db304919bd9d/</guid><description>A meteor crashed into the Pacific Ocean in 2014, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until Harvard scientists researched its velocity and trajectory five years later that they learned it came from outside our solar system.
Highlights Researchers discovered the first known interstellar meteor to hit Earth. Amir Siraj identified the object as an interstellar meteor in a study co-authored by Harvard University. The meteor was moving at a high speed of about 28 miles per second (45 kilometers per second) relative to the sun.</description></item><item><title>SpaceX launches 3 visitors to space station for $55M each</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625454e407609d45b9b2b054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625454e407609d45b9b2b054/</guid><description>SpaceX has launched three rich businessmen and their astronaut escort to the International Space Station for more than a week’s stay
Highlights SpaceX launches three rich businessmen and their astronaut escort to the International Space Station. They&amp;rsquo;re paying $55 million apiece for the rocket ride and accommodations, all meals included. SpaceX&amp;rsquo;s first private charter flight to the orbiting lab after two years of carrying astronauts there for NASA. The three businessmen are the latest to take advantage of the opening of space to those with deep pockets.</description></item><item><title>Oil prices ease as nations agree to tap reserves</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249ab0c63c8d6984c519258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 14:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249ab0c63c8d6984c519258/</guid><description>Both Brent and US crude benchmarks settled down around 13 percent.
Highlights Both Brent and US crude benchmarks settled down around 13 percent in their biggest weekly falls in two years. US President Joe Biden announced the release of one million barrels per day (bpd) of crude oil for six months from May, which at 180 million barrels is the largest release ever from the US Strategic Petroleum Reserve (SPR) Member countries of the IEA did not agree on volumes or commitments of each country at their emergency meeting.</description></item><item><title>‘Long-overdue’: all-Black, female WWII battalion to receive Congressional Gold Medal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234a1b51f10fb9d0216a94f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234a1b51f10fb9d0216a94f/</guid><description>Known as the ‘six triple eight’, the battalion was the only group of African American women to serve overseas during second world war
Highlights The 6888th central post directory battalion, also known as the ‘six triple eight’, was the only group of African American women to serve overseas during second world war. Created in 1944, it included 824 enlisted Black women and 31 officers from the women’s army corps, the army service forces and the army air forces.</description></item><item><title>North Korea says it conducted second 'important' spy satellite test</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224b3ea4a2a3561105a87a4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224b3ea4a2a3561105a87a4/</guid><description>North Korea said it conducted &amp;quot;another important&amp;quot; test for reconnaissance satellite systems, state news agency KCNA reported on Sunday, a day after regional military authorities reported the launch of a ballistic missile from the country for the second time in a week.
Highlights North Korea said it conducted &amp;ldquo;another important&amp;rdquo; test for reconnaissance satellite systems. It was the second such launch in a week to test satellite equipment, and the ninth missile launch this year.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer CEO says two Covid vaccine doses aren’t ‘enough for omicron’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dde1f3795b81724024aa32/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dde1f3795b81724024aa32/</guid><description>Bourla said the two-dose vaccine has lost its protective power against infection and its ability to prevent hospitalization has also dropped.
Summary John Thys | AFP | Getty ImagesPfizer CEO Albert Bourla on Monday said two doses of the company&amp;rsquo;s vaccine may not provide strong protection against infection from the Covid omicron variant, and the original shots have also lost some of their efficacy at preventing hospitalization. Bourla, in an interview at J.</description></item></channel></rss>