<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>second on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/second/</link><description>Recent content in second on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 15:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/second/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Long-overdue’: all-Black, female WWII battalion to receive Congressional Gold Medal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234a1b51f10fb9d0216a94f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234a1b51f10fb9d0216a94f/</guid><description>Known as the ‘six triple eight’, the battalion was the only group of African American women to serve overseas during second world war
Highlights The 6888th central post directory battalion, also known as the ‘six triple eight’, was the only group of African American women to serve overseas during second world war. Created in 1944, it included 824 enlisted Black women and 31 officers from the women’s army corps, the army service forces and the army air forces.</description></item><item><title>North Korea says it conducted second 'important' spy satellite test</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224b3ea4a2a3561105a87a4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224b3ea4a2a3561105a87a4/</guid><description>North Korea said it conducted &amp;quot;another important&amp;quot; test for reconnaissance satellite systems, state news agency KCNA reported on Sunday, a day after regional military authorities reported the launch of a ballistic missile from the country for the second time in a week.
Highlights North Korea said it conducted &amp;ldquo;another important&amp;rdquo; test for reconnaissance satellite systems. It was the second such launch in a week to test satellite equipment, and the ninth missile launch this year.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer CEO says two Covid vaccine doses aren’t ‘enough for omicron’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dde1f3795b81724024aa32/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dde1f3795b81724024aa32/</guid><description>Bourla said the two-dose vaccine has lost its protective power against infection and its ability to prevent hospitalization has also dropped.
Summary John Thys | AFP | Getty ImagesPfizer CEO Albert Bourla on Monday said two doses of the company&amp;rsquo;s vaccine may not provide strong protection against infection from the Covid omicron variant, and the original shots have also lost some of their efficacy at preventing hospitalization. Bourla, in an interview at J.</description></item></channel></rss>