<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trading on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trading/</link><description>Recent content in trading on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 07:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Citigroup causes a "flash crash" in European stock markets; one index loses nearly 8% in minutes.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627227940c76dff91dac4205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627227940c76dff91dac4205/</guid><description>Inputting mistake led to suspension of trading on several markets after sudden steep falls
Highlights Trading was briefly suspended in several European markets after sudden steep declines. Europe Stoxx 600 index of leading shares lost as much as 3% before closing down 1.5%. One of the hardest hit was Sweden’s benchmark OMX 30 index, which fell by nearly 8%, but recouped most of the losses and ended the day 1.9% lower.</description></item><item><title>World's top oil trader will stop buying Russian crude</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62591b1ce54fe8adfc3b47df/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 07:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62591b1ce54fe8adfc3b47df/</guid><description>Vitol Group, the world&amp;rsquo;s top independent oil merchant, will stop trading Russian crude oil and products by the end of the year, a source with knowledge of the situation told CNN.
Highlights Vitol Group will stop trading Russian crude oil and products by the end of the year. The Dutch energy and commodities trading company will also not enter into any new Russian crude and product transactions. The U.S., UK, Canada and Australia have all announced bans on Russian oil since Russia invaded Ukraine in February.</description></item></channel></rss>