<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>americans on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/americans/</link><description>Recent content in americans on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/americans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Americans seeking to renounce their citizenship are stuck with it for now</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2a6d6c5e9a68ea4682554/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2a6d6c5e9a68ea4682554/</guid><description>As many as 30,000 citizens living abroad have been unable to secure a ‘loss of nationality’ interview during the pandemic
Highlights He discovered that along with thousands of other US citizens living abroad, he was caught in a Kafkaesque trap. Grant, 30, feels ready to acquire German citizenship, but under German law he must let go of his US passport. “The US appears intent on preventing its citizens from exercising their natural and fundamental right to voluntarily renounce their citizenship,” it says.</description></item><item><title>US had 5 rabies deaths last year, highest total in a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</guid><description>Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade
Summary Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decadeNEW YORK &amp;ndash; Five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade — and health officials said Thursday that some of the people didn&amp;rsquo;t realize they had been infected or refused life-saving shots.</description></item><item><title>Local officials call on Idaho sheriff to resign after he allegedly made disparaging comments about Native Americans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</guid><description>Members of a southeastern Idaho youth church group were being driven around by their chaperone last month,delivering Thanksgiving cards in the neighborhood to those they were thankful for when they decided last-minute to stop at the home of the county sheriff&amp;rsquo;s house, according to a probable cause affidavit later in court.
Summary What happened next outside the home of Bingham County Sheriff Craig Rowland has put the small Idaho community in the national spotlight.</description></item></channel></rss>