<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>oil on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oil/</link><description>Recent content in oil on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 17:23:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US oil refineries spewing cancer-causing benzene into communities, report finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e9406d6569dff2cd0b5a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 17:23:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e9406d6569dff2cd0b5a4/</guid><description>Analysis shows alarming level of benzene at fence-line of facilities in Texas, Louisiana, Pennsylvania, Indiana and US Virgin Islands
Highlights A dozen US oil refineries last year exceeded the federal limit on average benzene emissions. Five were in Texas, four in Louisiana, and one each in Pennsylvania, Indiana and the US Virgin Islands. EPA estimates 6.1 million people in the US live within three miles of a refinery, with low-income people and people of color represented at rates nearly twice that of the general population.</description></item><item><title>Exxon signals record quarterly profit from oil and gas prices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c5cbd71a1faba7d6a1e58/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 15:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c5cbd71a1faba7d6a1e58/</guid><description>Exxon Mobil Corp on Monday said its first-quarter results could top a seven-year quarterly record, with operating profits from pumping oil and gas alone of up to $9.3 billion.
Highlights Exxon Mobil Corp on Monday said its first-quarter results could top a seven-year quarterly record. Operating profits from pumping oil and gas alone of up to $9.3 billion. Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine pushed up oil by 45% last quarter over the final period of 2021, to an average of $114 per barrel, the highest in seven years.</description></item><item><title>Russian market cracks 17% as Ukraine tensions intensify</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62155feede8b75074051dd03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 22:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62155feede8b75074051dd03/</guid><description>Russia warned there were no firm plans for a summit between US President Joe Biden and Putin. In another development, reports emerged that Russian forces killed a group of five saboteurs who breached the country&amp;rsquo;s southwest border from Ukraine on Monday.
Highlights Russian stock market sank 17 per cent in Monday&amp;rsquo;s trade as President Vladimir Putin said his country was mulling recognising the independence of east Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s two separatist republics. Russia is one of the biggest producers of Crude oil, and the status can lead to a sharp spike of more than $100 and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Community in Ecuador punished for trying to stop alleged palm oil pollution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201a76333ed1612be4736dd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 23:13:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201a76333ed1612be4736dd/</guid><description>A legal loophole allowed palm oil companies in Ecuador to establish plantations on ancestral land that belongs to small communities. This is the first in a two-part series.
Highlights A legal loophole allowed palm oil companies in Ecuador to establish plantations on ancestral land that belongs to small communities. Residents say that agricultural chemicals and waste from plantations and palm oil processing mills is polluting the water sources on which they depend.</description></item></channel></rss>