<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shooting on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooting/</link><description>Recent content in shooting on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:23:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alex Jones' Infowars files for bankruptcy in wake of defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook massacre was a hoax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:23:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</guid><description>Jones was found liable in at least two defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.
Highlights Infowars and two other companies owned by radio host Alex Jones have filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in light of several defamation lawsuits. The filings were made in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas. A judge has ruled that Jones get back $75,000 in fines he paid to a Connecticut court for failing to appear at a deposition last month in a lawsuit over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in road rage shooting calls police on victim, gets arrested for attempted murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3f44ffcee691824663e0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 22:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3f44ffcee691824663e0/</guid><description>A man was arrested in North Charleston after a road rage incident turned into a shooting on Thursday. Jeremy Langworthy, 22, was arrested after allegedly shooting at a woman in a car near Ingleside Boulevard. North Charleston Police Department responded to the scene after receiving multiple calls, including one from the suspect, about a shooting. When they arrived, Langworthy told officers he threw a Mt. Dew can at a vehicle after the driver cut him off in traffic.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting suspect has been arrested, law enforcement officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</guid><description>Suspected Brooklyn subway shooter Frank James was arrested by patrol officers in the East Village in New York City on Wednesday, three law enforcement officials tell CNN.
Highlights Images captured by people at the scene of the shooting show chaos and chaos. People can be heard rushing off the train after it pulled into the 36th Street subway station. The bullet hit one man in the back of his knee and came out the other side, he says.</description></item><item><title>Police: Sacramento shooting was gunfight among gang rivals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ec70e2e06ece726611935/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 11:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ec70e2e06ece726611935/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The mass killing that left six people dead and 12 wounded outside bars just blocks from California’s Capitol last weekend was a gunfight involving at least five shooters from rival gangs, Sacramento police said Wednesday.
Highlights NEW: Police say at least two gangs were involved in the shooting that left six people dead and 12 wounded. NEW: Experts say if gangs were to blame, it would mark an unusually bloody feud.</description></item><item><title>Parkland school shooting: jury selection to begin in death penalty trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bcffba8213bd998bd328d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 05:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bcffba8213bd998bd328d/</guid><description>Jury will decide whether Nikolas Cruz faces life in prison or the death penalty after pleading guilty to the murders of 17 people
Highlights Jury selection in the death penalty trial of Nikolas Cruz began on Monday after years of delay due to Covid-19 pandemic. 1,500 candidates or more could be brought before circuit judge Elizabeth Scherer, prosecutors and Cruz’s public defenders for initial screening over the next several weeks.</description></item><item><title>2 killed, 2 injured in shooting near San Francisco's Alice Chalmers Playground, police say.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ba8ece40d3391a6e38bd4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ba8ece40d3391a6e38bd4/</guid><description>Police are investigating a shooting that left two dead and two injured near the Alice Chalmers Playground in San Francisco Sunday afternoon.
Highlights Police are investigating a shooting that left two dead and two injured near the Alice Chalmers Playground in San Francisco Sunday afternoon. The incident happened at around 4:39 p.m. on the 600 block of Brunswick Avenue. Police say they located four adult male victims with gunshot wounds.</description></item><item><title>UFC Fighter Kevin Holland Helps Stop Gunman In Houston Restaurant Shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231d62b4737427c172c88b0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:21:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231d62b4737427c172c88b0/</guid><description>The 29-year-old and two other men reportedly stopped a dangerous situation late Monday night.
Highlights UFC fighter Kevin Holland, 29, and two other men reportedly stopped a dangerous situation at a Houston-area restaurant late Monday night. The incident took place around 11:30 p.m. local time when a panic alarm went off at Ra Sushi in Highland Village, Texas. Police say 40-50 people were inside the restaurant when the suspect pulled out a gun and fired one time into the air.</description></item><item><title>Man ‘playing with gun’ kills pregnant teen, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</guid><description>Deputies allege the suspect was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back.
Highlights Chad Blackard faces several charges, including negligent homicide, third-degree feticide and illegal use of weapons. 17-year-old Karrington Smith was 25 weeks pregnant at the time, and her unborn child also died. Deputies say Blackard was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back. Blackard told deputies when he tried to reposition the gun, it “went off.</description></item><item><title>Shootings targeting homeless men in New York and Washington, DC are linked, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f1575fe7d1eee65919de9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f1575fe7d1eee65919de9/</guid><description>A series of shootings targeting homeless men in New York City and Washington, DC, were carried out by the same suspect, officials said Sunday.
Highlights Five shootings targeting homeless men in New York City and Washington, DC, were carried out by the same suspect, police say. The five shootings left two men dead and took place over a nine-day period this month. The mayors of both cities issued a joint statement Sunday night saying a &amp;ldquo;cold-blooded killer on the loose&amp;rdquo; Authorities are offering a total of $55,000 for information leading to the arrest of the suspect, with the MPD offering a reward of up to $10,000 to $20,000, leading to up to a $25,000.</description></item><item><title>Man kills 3 daughters, 1 other, himself at California church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e9a517842b39f085c053d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e9a517842b39f085c053d/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — A man shot and killed his three daughters, their chaperone and himself during a supervised visit with the girls Monday at a church in Sacramento, California, authorities said.
Highlights Deputies responding to reports of gunfire around 5 p.m. found five people dead, including the shooter, at the church in the Arden-Arcade neighborhood. Shooter was estranged from his daughters’ mother, who had a restraining order against him, sheriff says.</description></item><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families settle with gun maker in historic first</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</guid><description>Nine Sandy Hook Elementary School families have announced a settlement with Remington Arms, maker of the AR-15 used in the massacre.
Highlights Remington Arms agrees to pay families $73 million in settlement. Settlement comes seven years after families sued the maker of the Bushmaster XM15-E2S semiautomatic rifle. Remington&amp;rsquo;s version of the AR-15 is substantially similar to the standard issue M16 military service rifle used by the U.S. Army and other nations’ armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Bus driver shot in the head while transporting kids in north Minneapolis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</guid><description>Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis.
Highlights Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot in the head Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis. Police say they have not apprehended any suspects. Three children younger than 10 were on board the bus at the time of the shooting. Minneapolis Public Schools released a statement in response to the school bus shooting as well as a separate shooting in which a student was shot, which read, in part: “… We recognize the deep impact this has on our students, staff and families.</description></item><item><title>Mother of Michigan school shooting suspect pleaded to keep her job hours after the shooting, boss says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</guid><description>The text exchange was revealed in court Tuesday during a preliminary hearing for Jennifer and James Crumbley, who are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring clear warning signs that he was a threat to others.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley, 15, opened fire with a 9mm handgun at his Michigan high school, killing four students and injuring seven. His parents are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring warning signs that he was a threat to others.</description></item></channel></rss>