<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shooting on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooting/</link><description>Recent content in shooting on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families settle with gun maker in historic first</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</guid><description>Nine Sandy Hook Elementary School families have announced a settlement with Remington Arms, maker of the AR-15 used in the massacre.
Highlights Remington Arms agrees to pay families $73 million in settlement. Settlement comes seven years after families sued the maker of the Bushmaster XM15-E2S semiautomatic rifle. Remington&amp;rsquo;s version of the AR-15 is substantially similar to the standard issue M16 military service rifle used by the U.S. Army and other nations’ armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Bus driver shot in the head while transporting kids in north Minneapolis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</guid><description>Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis.
Highlights Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot in the head Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis. Police say they have not apprehended any suspects. Three children younger than 10 were on board the bus at the time of the shooting. Minneapolis Public Schools released a statement in response to the school bus shooting as well as a separate shooting in which a student was shot, which read, in part: “… We recognize the deep impact this has on our students, staff and families.</description></item><item><title>Mother of Michigan school shooting suspect pleaded to keep her job hours after the shooting, boss says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</guid><description>The text exchange was revealed in court Tuesday during a preliminary hearing for Jennifer and James Crumbley, who are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring clear warning signs that he was a threat to others.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley, 15, opened fire with a 9mm handgun at his Michigan high school, killing four students and injuring seven. His parents are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring warning signs that he was a threat to others.</description></item></channel></rss>