<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shooting on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooting/</link><description>Recent content in shooting on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:07:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alleged 'boogaloo' extremist sentenced to 41 years in murder of federal officer | The former Air Force staff sergeant pleaded guilty in the May 2020 murder of David Patrick Underwood.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bad4edb568a82743be61f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bad4edb568a82743be61f/</guid><description>Former Air Force staff Steven Carrillo sergeant pleaded guilty earlier this in the May 2020 murder of David Patrick Underwood.
Highlights Steven Carrillo, 33, pleaded guilty earlier this year to a federal murder charge in the killing of David Patrick Underwood and the attempted murder of Underwood’s colleague. Carrillo admitted to posting messages on Facebook a day before the shooting asking anyone if they were “down to boogaloo” Carrillo also admitted firing 19 rounds from a homemade AR-15 rifle from the back of a white van being driven by a man he connected with online.</description></item><item><title>Father and son craft 19 custom caskets for the Uvalde shooting victims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a15dbebefacfc4bf0b0e2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a15dbebefacfc4bf0b0e2/</guid><description>Each caskets is carefully handpainted and decorated to relect the child&amp;rsquo;s interests and personality.
Highlights Trey Ganem, 50, and his son Billy, 25, have been working around the clock to craft a custom casket for each of the children killed in last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting in Uvalde, Texas. Each casket is carefully handpainted and decorated to relect the child&amp;rsquo;s interests and personality. Ganem has donated the caskets to the families, making sure they have one less thing to think about.</description></item><item><title>CNN reporter threatened with trespassing after grilling Uvalde police chief over his actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629943361042e4a25eada900/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629943361042e4a25eada900/</guid><description>Shimon Prokupecz had earlier been grilling police chief Pedro Arredondo about his actions during the Uvalde shooting
Highlights CNN reporter was threatened with charges of trespassing if he and his crew didn’t leave the school district’s offices. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Simon Prokupecz shared a video of a confrontation with Uvalde Police Chief Pedro “Pete” Arredondo outside the school building where he had retreated behind earlier. The Texas Department of Public Safety maintains that the chief of the school police chief is not cooperating with investigators.</description></item><item><title>Florida fifth grader arrested after threatening a mass shooting, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295988d850718b5c5c3018c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 04:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295988d850718b5c5c3018c/</guid><description>A fifth grade student in Florida was arrested over the weekend and charged with sending a text message threatening to carry out a mass shooting, authorities
Highlights The Lee County Sheriff’s Office said it had learned earlier that day of a &amp;ldquo;threatening text message&amp;rdquo; sent by a student at an elementary school. It said its local school threat enforcement team was immediately notified and started investigating. The 10-year-old boy was interviewed and charged later with &amp;ldquo;making a written threat to conduct a mass shooting,&amp;rdquo; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said.</description></item><item><title>Chattanooga Mayor Tim Kelly says Saturday night shooting began with disagreement among teens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294ecc9cbe65c6d1b22a8f9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294ecc9cbe65c6d1b22a8f9/</guid><description>After the Saturday night shooting in downtown Chattanooga that left six young people injured, two of whom were in critical condition, Chattanooga Mayor Tim Kelly is asking parents to take action to help prevent more such incidents.
Highlights Six teens injured in shootings that left six injured downtown Chattanooga. Police chief: Gun battle appeared to break out between two groups of young people. Mayor Tim Kelly: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m heartbroken for the families and the victims whose lives were upended last night by gunfire&amp;rdquo; The shootings came less than a week after an 18-year-old opened fire at a Uvalde, Texas elementary school, killing 19 students and 2 teachers.</description></item><item><title>A 9-year-old describes escaping through a window during the Uvalde school massacre as anger mounts over police response | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294de629a989c9ad3c29768/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294de629a989c9ad3c29768/</guid><description>As a gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, and started firing, one student said his wounded teacher texted 911 for help.
Highlights Gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, and started firing, one student said. Daniel, 9, said he survived by hiding under a table next to the wall. &amp;ldquo;I could see him staring at people in front of me,&amp;rdquo; Daniel said. The deadly rampage at Robb Elementary marked at least the 30th shooting at a K-12 school in just the first five months of this year.</description></item><item><title>Fugitive suspect in Sacramento mass shooting found in Nevada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62948a52bc6af03120b9c490/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62948a52bc6af03120b9c490/</guid><description>Mtula Payton arrested in Las Vegas after being on the run since April 3 shooting in Sacramento. Police believe he was one of the alleged gang members who opened fire in downtown Sacramento. Six people were killed, including three men alleged to be
Highlights Mtula Payton was one of the alleged gang members who opened fire in downtown Sacramento on April 3. He was taken into custody at an apartment complex in Las Vegas, police say.</description></item><item><title>1-year-old child shot, killed in downtown Pittsburgh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62947c7723b214aba81cd7e8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62947c7723b214aba81cd7e8/</guid><description>The boy has been identified as DeAery Thomas. The shooting happened at around 2:44 p.m. on Saturday afternoon. The child was not the intended target, but a passenger in the car was. Officials said that residents
Highlights A 1-year-old boy was shot and killed in downtown Pittsburgh on Saturday afternoon. The boy has been identified as DeAery Thomas. The shooting happened at around 2:44 p.m. and a bullet went right through the window of a Jeep, hitting the child.</description></item><item><title>Police inaction moves to center of Uvalde shooting probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292819bd9f230e6013767f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292819bd9f230e6013767f9/</guid><description>The actions — or more notably, the inaction — of a school district police chief and other law enforcement officers have become the center of the investigation into this week&amp;rsquo;s shocking school shooting in Uvalde, Texas.
Highlights The actions of a school district police chief and other law enforcement officers have become the center of the investigation into this week’s shocking school shooting in Uvalde, Texas. The delay in confronting the shooter — who was inside the school for more than an hour — could lead to discipline, lawsuits and even criminal charges against police.</description></item><item><title>3 high school graduations across the U.S. end with gunfire in less than 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629199529bcc774208de3f22/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 03:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629199529bcc774208de3f22/</guid><description>Three high school graduation ceremonies ended with shots fired in separate incidents in Louisiana, Michigan and Tennessee within the span of 24 hours this week.
Highlights Three high school graduation ceremonies ended with shots fired in separate incidents in Louisiana, Michigan and Tennessee within the span of 24 hours this week. At least one person was killed and seven others injured in collective shootings that resulted in the arrest of a 17-year-old gunman in Tennessee.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde school police chief identified as commander who decided not to breach classroom</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62918b67c7239b3eba9f1372/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62918b67c7239b3eba9f1372/</guid><description>At a news conference Friday, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Col. Steven McCraw said the person who made the decision not to breach the Uvalde elementary school classroom where a gunman was shooting children and teachers was the school district police chief, calling it the “wrong decision” to not engage the gunman sooner.
Highlights Pedro “Pete” Arredondo is identified on the Uvalde School District website as the police chief. At a news conference Friday, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Col.</description></item><item><title>Victims' families urged armed police officers to charge into Uvalde school while massacre carried on for upwards of 40 minutes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f5fb153bb8489e43ce645/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f5fb153bb8489e43ce645/</guid><description>A mass shooting at a Texas elementary school left 19 children and two adults dead, adding to a gruesome series of mass killings in America.
Highlights Gunman killed at least 19 fourth-graders and two teachers in Uvalde, Texas. Salvador Ramos, 18, crashed his truck into a ditch outside the school, grabbed his AR-15-style semi-automatic rifle and shot at two people outside a nearby funeral home who ran away uninjured. Ramos then fired on two arriving police officers who were outside the building, a Texas Department of Public Safety spokesperson said.</description></item><item><title>Dallas Koreatown hair salon shooting suspect had 'delusional fear of Asians,' police records say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287a110643c452b8397ccf9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 14:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287a110643c452b8397ccf9/</guid><description>The arrest warrant affidavit says Jeremy Smith admitted he was in the area on the day of the shooting. His girlfriend told investigators he has panic attacks around people of Asian descent ever since a car crash with an Asian man two years ago.
Highlights Jeremy Smith, 36, was arrested for shooting three women at a Dallas Koreatown hair salon. Police say he was in the area on the day of the shooting and admitted he was looking for a business to repair a panel of broken glass for a garage door.</description></item><item><title>Multiple People Hit in Shooting at Laguna Woods Church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281892ae15ab0452fcce0a6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 23:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281892ae15ab0452fcce0a6/</guid><description>Multiple people were hit in a shooting at Geneva Presbyterian Church in the Laguna Woods area of Orange County. A suspected shooter is in custody and a gun has&amp;hellip;
Highlights At least five people have been injured in a shooting at a church in Laguna Woods, Orange County. The suspected shooter is in police custody, but the motive for the shooting is not yet known. Thirty to 40 witnesses will need to be interviewed, including people who were inside the church at the time.</description></item><item><title>1 dead, several injured in shooting at Mississippi Mudbug Festival, sheriff says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f067a09b1d93aa6366652/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 22:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f067a09b1d93aa6366652/</guid><description>One person has died and five others have been injured at the Mississippi Mudbug Festival, Hinds County Sheriff Tyree Jones said on Twitter late Saturday.
Highlights One person died and five others were injured at the Mississippi Mudbug Festival in Jackson, authorities say. The person who died is suspected to have been one of the shooters, officials say. Two juveniles have been detained, but no charges have been filed in the incident.</description></item><item><title>Stolen pizza, Pokémon cards lead to deadly deputy shooting in Osceola County, records show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e25d0f923710d95bca9c5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 06:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e25d0f923710d95bca9c5/</guid><description>Two men stealing a pizza and several packs of Pokémon cards from a Target lead to a deadly deputy shooting Wednesday night, records released Thursday revealed.
Highlights Two men were seen stealing a pizza and packs of Pokémon cards from a Target. Two deputies opened fire, killing one man, according to Osceola County Sheriff Marcos Lopez. In addition to the man who was killed, another person was hit in the hand by bullet shrapnel.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones' Infowars files for bankruptcy in wake of defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook massacre was a hoax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:23:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</guid><description>Jones was found liable in at least two defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.
Highlights Infowars and two other companies owned by radio host Alex Jones have filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in light of several defamation lawsuits. The filings were made in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas. A judge has ruled that Jones get back $75,000 in fines he paid to a Connecticut court for failing to appear at a deposition last month in a lawsuit over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in road rage shooting calls police on victim, gets arrested for attempted murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3f44ffcee691824663e0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 22:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3f44ffcee691824663e0/</guid><description>A man was arrested in North Charleston after a road rage incident turned into a shooting on Thursday. Jeremy Langworthy, 22, was arrested after allegedly shooting at a woman in a car near Ingleside Boulevard. North Charleston Police Department responded to the scene after receiving multiple calls, including one from the suspect, about a shooting. When they arrived, Langworthy told officers he threw a Mt. Dew can at a vehicle after the driver cut him off in traffic.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting suspect has been arrested, law enforcement officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</guid><description>Suspected Brooklyn subway shooter Frank James was arrested by patrol officers in the East Village in New York City on Wednesday, three law enforcement officials tell CNN.
Highlights Images captured by people at the scene of the shooting show chaos and chaos. People can be heard rushing off the train after it pulled into the 36th Street subway station. The bullet hit one man in the back of his knee and came out the other side, he says.</description></item><item><title>Police: Sacramento shooting was gunfight among gang rivals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ec70e2e06ece726611935/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 11:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ec70e2e06ece726611935/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The mass killing that left six people dead and 12 wounded outside bars just blocks from California’s Capitol last weekend was a gunfight involving at least five shooters from rival gangs, Sacramento police said Wednesday.
Highlights NEW: Police say at least two gangs were involved in the shooting that left six people dead and 12 wounded. NEW: Experts say if gangs were to blame, it would mark an unusually bloody feud.</description></item><item><title>Parkland school shooting: jury selection to begin in death penalty trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bcffba8213bd998bd328d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 05:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bcffba8213bd998bd328d/</guid><description>Jury will decide whether Nikolas Cruz faces life in prison or the death penalty after pleading guilty to the murders of 17 people
Highlights Jury selection in the death penalty trial of Nikolas Cruz began on Monday after years of delay due to Covid-19 pandemic. 1,500 candidates or more could be brought before circuit judge Elizabeth Scherer, prosecutors and Cruz’s public defenders for initial screening over the next several weeks. Cruz, 23, has already pled guilty to the murders at the Marjory Stoneman Douglas high school, meaning a jury will decide whether he faces life in prison or death penalty.</description></item><item><title>2 killed, 2 injured in shooting near San Francisco's Alice Chalmers Playground, police say.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ba8ece40d3391a6e38bd4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 02:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ba8ece40d3391a6e38bd4/</guid><description>Police are investigating a shooting that left two dead and two injured near the Alice Chalmers Playground in San Francisco Sunday afternoon.
Highlights Police are investigating a shooting that left two dead and two injured near the Alice Chalmers Playground in San Francisco Sunday afternoon. The incident happened at around 4:39 p.m. on the 600 block of Brunswick Avenue. Police say they located four adult male victims with gunshot wounds. One of the victims was grazed in the head with the bullet, before succumbing to their injuries.</description></item><item><title>UFC Fighter Kevin Holland Helps Stop Gunman In Houston Restaurant Shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231d62b4737427c172c88b0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:21:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231d62b4737427c172c88b0/</guid><description>The 29-year-old and two other men reportedly stopped a dangerous situation late Monday night.
Highlights UFC fighter Kevin Holland, 29, and two other men reportedly stopped a dangerous situation at a Houston-area restaurant late Monday night. The incident took place around 11:30 p.m. local time when a panic alarm went off at Ra Sushi in Highland Village, Texas. Police say 40-50 people were inside the restaurant when the suspect pulled out a gun and fired one time into the air.</description></item><item><title>Man ‘playing with gun’ kills pregnant teen, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</guid><description>Deputies allege the suspect was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back.
Highlights Chad Blackard faces several charges, including negligent homicide, third-degree feticide and illegal use of weapons. 17-year-old Karrington Smith was 25 weeks pregnant at the time, and her unborn child also died. Deputies say Blackard was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back. Blackard told deputies when he tried to reposition the gun, it “went off.</description></item><item><title>Shootings targeting homeless men in New York and Washington, DC are linked, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f1575fe7d1eee65919de9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f1575fe7d1eee65919de9/</guid><description>A series of shootings targeting homeless men in New York City and Washington, DC, were carried out by the same suspect, officials said Sunday.
Highlights Five shootings targeting homeless men in New York City and Washington, DC, were carried out by the same suspect, police say. The five shootings left two men dead and took place over a nine-day period this month. The mayors of both cities issued a joint statement Sunday night saying a &amp;ldquo;cold-blooded killer on the loose&amp;rdquo; Authorities are offering a total of $55,000 for information leading to the arrest of the suspect, with the MPD offering a reward of up to $10,000 to $20,000, leading to up to a $25,000.</description></item><item><title>Man kills 3 daughters, 1 other, himself at California church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e9a517842b39f085c053d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e9a517842b39f085c053d/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — A man shot and killed his three daughters, their chaperone and himself during a supervised visit with the girls Monday at a church in Sacramento, California, authorities said.
Highlights Deputies responding to reports of gunfire around 5 p.m. found five people dead, including the shooter, at the church in the Arden-Arcade neighborhood. Shooter was estranged from his daughters’ mother, who had a restraining order against him, sheriff says.</description></item><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families settle with gun maker in historic first</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</guid><description>Nine Sandy Hook Elementary School families have announced a settlement with Remington Arms, maker of the AR-15 used in the massacre.
Highlights Remington Arms agrees to pay families $73 million in settlement. Settlement comes seven years after families sued the maker of the Bushmaster XM15-E2S semiautomatic rifle. Remington&amp;rsquo;s version of the AR-15 is substantially similar to the standard issue M16 military service rifle used by the U.S. Army and other nations’ armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Bus driver shot in the head while transporting kids in north Minneapolis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</guid><description>Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis.
Highlights Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot in the head Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis. Police say they have not apprehended any suspects. Three children younger than 10 were on board the bus at the time of the shooting. Minneapolis Public Schools released a statement in response to the school bus shooting as well as a separate shooting in which a student was shot, which read, in part: “… We recognize the deep impact this has on our students, staff and families.</description></item><item><title>Mother of Michigan school shooting suspect pleaded to keep her job hours after the shooting, boss says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</guid><description>The text exchange was revealed in court Tuesday during a preliminary hearing for Jennifer and James Crumbley, who are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring clear warning signs that he was a threat to others.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley, 15, opened fire with a 9mm handgun at his Michigan high school, killing four students and injuring seven. His parents are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring warning signs that he was a threat to others.</description></item></channel></rss>