<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>webbs on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/webbs/</link><description>Recent content in webbs on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 12:24:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/webbs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The James Webb Space Telescope is fully aligned and ready to observe the universe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bd8d3ed0c20530c00c7ce/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 12:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bd8d3ed0c20530c00c7ce/</guid><description>By Ashley Strickland, CNN
Highlights Webb&amp;rsquo;s mirrors are directing focused light from space into each instrument and those instruments are capturing images. The first high-resolution images Webb collects of the cosmos aren&amp;rsquo;t expected until the end of June. The observatory&amp;rsquo;s instruments still need to be calibrated to capture high-quality images of the universe. Together, Webb&amp;rsquo;s images share the telescope&amp;rsquo;s full field of view with each other. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope: Sun shield is fully deployed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4b5719dc7edbace949c41/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4b5719dc7edbace949c41/</guid><description>The unfurling of the observatory&amp;rsquo;s giant sun shade is a major milestone for the $10bn mission.
Summary Its shield is deployed but its mirrors are still stowedThe new James Webb telescope has passed a major milestone in its quest to image the first stars to shine in the cosmos. &amp;ldquo;Unfolding Webb&amp;rsquo;s sun shield in space is an incredible milestone, crucial to the success of the mission,&amp;rdquo; said Greg Robinson, Webb&amp;rsquo;s program director at Nasa Headquarters.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope unfurls massive sunshield in major deployment milestone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d06c8cacf2f5060ba904d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d06c8cacf2f5060ba904d6/</guid><description>The $10 billion James Webb Space Telescope unfolded its huge sunshield on Friday (Dec. 31), pulling the five-layer structure out by sequentially deploying two booms.
Summary The sunshield of NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope is seen here fully unfurled during prelaunch testing on Earth. One of the James Webb Space Telescope&amp;rsquo;s most nail-biting deployment steps is safely in the books. Live updates: NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope missionRelated: How the James Webb Space Telescope works in picturesShine bright like a diamond 💎With the successful deployment of our right sunshield mid-boom, or “arm,” Webb’s sunshield has now taken on its diamond shape in space.</description></item></channel></rss>