<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hits on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hits/</link><description>Recent content in hits on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 07:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California's average gas price hits new record high with $5.28 a gallon, AAA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227020bc87880fdf0b7dea2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 07:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227020bc87880fdf0b7dea2/</guid><description>California hit another record for the average price of regular unleaded gas this weekend, at $5.28 a gallon as of Sunday.
Highlights California hit another record for the average price of regular unleaded gas this weekend. Napa, Marin, and Sonoma counties are the most expensive for gas. California&amp;rsquo;s already record-high gas prices are expected to get even more expensive in the coming months, fueled by the crisis in Ukraine. Long lines could be seen at the Costco in South San Francisco where the price of gasoline continues to surge.</description></item><item><title>US death toll from COVID-19 hits 900,000, sped by omicron</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdeae253c56b08f40a36d8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 03:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdeae253c56b08f40a36d8/</guid><description>Propelled in part by the wildly contagious omicron variant, the U.S. death toll from COVID-19 has hit 900,000, less than two months after eclipsing 800,000
Highlights The U.S. death toll from COVID-19 has hit 900,000, less than two months after eclipsing 800,000. The two-year total is greater than the population of Indianapolis, San Francisco, or Charlotte, North Carolina. The milestone comes more than 13 months into a vaccination drive that has been beset by misinformation and political and legal strife, though the shots have proved safe and highly effective at preventing serious illness and death.</description></item><item><title>Omicron hits all 50 states less than a month after entering U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</guid><description>With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was
Summary With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was first detected in the U.S., according to an NBC News tally. A day later, multiple states and territories set records for seven-day averages, including New York, Maine, Washington, D.</description></item></channel></rss>