<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sources on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sources/</link><description>Recent content in sources on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde police, school district no longer cooperating with Texas probe of shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296a0263f416bb99a7370bf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296a0263f416bb99a7370bf/</guid><description>Uvalde police and school district police are no longer cooperating with the Texas Dept. of Public Safety&amp;rsquo;s probe into the Robb Elementary School shooting, sources say.
Highlights Uv.C. police say they are no longer cooperating with the state&amp;rsquo;s response to the school shooting. The decision to stop cooperating occurred soon after the attack. The school was one of the worst school shootings in U.S. history, killing two people. The attack is believed to have been the result of a school shooting in Texas that took place at a school in May 2012, killing three people, including two children and two adults.</description></item><item><title>Twitter set to accept ‘best and final offer’ of Elon Musk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266acba63a9d45c947a6449/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266acba63a9d45c947a6449/</guid><description>Twitter Inc is poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, the price the chief executive of Tesla Inc has called his &amp;quot;best and final&amp;quot; offer for the social media company, people familiar with the matter said.
Highlights Twitter poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, people familiar with the matter said. Twitter may announce the $54.20-per-share deal later on Monday once its board has met to recommend the transaction to Twitter shareholders.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn Subway Shooting: Multiple Shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255974d1ff65f9627ad4b56/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 15:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255974d1ff65f9627ad4b56/</guid><description>It happened in Sunset Park, near 4th Avenue and 36th Street. The suspect is said to be a man in a gas mask.
Highlights At least five people were shot Tuesday on a moving Brooklyn subway by a man in a gas mask and orange construction vest who may have tossed a smoke canister on the platform to distract the rush hour crowd, according to NYPD officials and senior law enforcement officials.</description></item><item><title>U.S. seeks new lithium sources as demand for clean energy grows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62436874c68b093770803a5d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62436874c68b093770803a5d/</guid><description>The element is critical to the development of lithium-ion batteries, which are rechargeable batteries seen as critical to reducing the carbon emissions created by cars and other forms of transportation.
Highlights The U.S. will need far more lithium to achieve its clean energy goals. The element is critical to development of rechargeable lithium-ion batteries that are seen as key to reducing climate-changing carbon emissions created by cars and other forms of transportation.</description></item><item><title>Representative Matt Gaetz's ex-girlfriend granted immunity in sex trafficking probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</guid><description>The woman testified in front of a federal grand jury last week hearing evidence in the Gaetz investigation.
Summary Gaetz has been under investigation to determine if he violated sex trafficking laws and obstructed justice in that probe. Gaetz has previously denied all wrongdoing, and has said he has never paid for sex nor had sex with an underage girl. One of the sources said she has information related to the investigation of both the sex trafficking and obstruction allegations.</description></item><item><title>Russian mercenaries deploy to eastern Ukraine – sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c51baa07a8b73cad605b98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c51baa07a8b73cad605b98/</guid><description>By Maria Tsvetkova and Anton Zverev MOSCOW (Reuters) - Russian mercenaries have deployed to separatist-controlled eastern Ukraine in recent weeks to b&amp;hellip;
Summary The fighter said he was planning to join up with fellow mercenaries on the Russian side of the border with the separatist-held Luhansk region in eastern Ukraine. One of the sources, a contractor who has taken part in Russian operations abroad and had already arrived in eastern Ukraine, said the deployment was for defensive purposes.</description></item></channel></rss>