<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fighting on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fighting/</link><description>Recent content in fighting on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 17:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fighting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine accuses Russia of 'war crimes' targeting civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bb11aaf65ae32a734ab78/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bb11aaf65ae32a734ab78/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin ordered his country&amp;rsquo;s deterrence forces &amp;ndash; which include nuclear arms &amp;ndash; onto their highest state of alert on Sunday, as Ukrainian forces engaged in fierce fighting with Russian troops in multiple cities across Ukraine.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin orders his country&amp;rsquo;s deterrence forces on combat alert. Putin says Western sanctions against Russia are unlawful. Fighting breaks out in Kharkiv, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second largest city, after Russian forces enter the city.</description></item><item><title>Guardsman says not being ‘feminine’ cost her a job. The government is fighting her lawsuit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218d6bf7e9858a2a49bfc87/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 13:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218d6bf7e9858a2a49bfc87/</guid><description>“I’m not done wearing the uniform. I feel that I have more to do,” said Kristin Kingrey, a technical sergeant and civilian employee in the West Virginia Air National Guard.
Highlights A West Virginia Air National Guard airman says she lost out on a job due to discrimination over her sexual orientation and her appearance. Kristin Kingrey is a masculine-presenting lesbian who wears her hair short and doesn’t bother with makeup.</description></item><item><title>Explosions in Kyiv as UK reports ‘fierce resistance’ across the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218abe0d07b0625b40728bb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 10:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218abe0d07b0625b40728bb/</guid><description>Public urged to report Russian troop movements and prepare molotov cocktails, with heavy gunfire heard in residential district
Highlights US secretary of state, Antony Blinken, said Russia intends to “incircle and threaten” the city. Russian forces have vowed to stay in the capital in Ukraine. Russian president, Volodymyr Zelenskiy, accused Vladimir Putin of targeting civilian as well as military sites. “Russia will have to talk to us sooner or later about how to end hostilities and stop this invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>