<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sandy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sandy/</link><description>Recent content in sandy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:32:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sandy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandy Hook families defamed by Alex Jones want him to pay their legal fees fighting his ‘sham’ bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1f640b048304815a9edad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1f640b048304815a9edad/</guid><description>Families of victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting say they want to be reimbursed for fighting Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; &amp;quot;sham&amp;quot; bankruptcy.
Highlights Sandy Hook families won three defamation cases against Alex Jones in Connecticut, Texas. They say Jones&amp;rsquo; bankruptcy filing was a &amp;ldquo;calculated stunt&amp;rdquo; to avoid jury trials. The families want state judges to make Jones pay their legal costs for the 45 days they had to fight his &amp;ldquo;sham&amp;rdquo; filing in federal court.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones back on the hook for damages after bankruptcy judge sends Sandy Hook cases to Texas court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62886660069aa21ece71281f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 04:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62886660069aa21ece71281f/</guid><description>The bankruptcy judge’s ruling means the Texas trial to determine what Alex Jones owes&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; defamation cases are sent back to state court in Texas, where the parents of two boys slain in the Sandy Hook massacre await jury trials to see how much Jones owes them. Jones&amp;rsquo; bankruptcy filing put on hold the two trials in Texas and the third in Connecticut, since federal court trumps state proceedings.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook lawsuits against Alex Jones on track to resume</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f0240eacf0b6bd5438856/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 01:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f0240eacf0b6bd5438856/</guid><description>The Sandy Hook families’ lawsuits against Infowars host and conspiracy theorist Alex Jones for calling the 2012 Newtown school shooting in Connecticut a hoax appear poised to resume soon
Highlights The Sandy Hook families’ lawsuits against Alex Jones for calling the 2012 Newtown school shooting a hoax appear poised to resume soon. The families of eight of the victims and an FBI agent sued Jones, Infowars and others. Lawyers in the bankruptcy case said the families will be removed as creditors.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones after CT deposition in Sandy Hook defamation case: ‘I could have done a better job’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f622a41d64e74d5897f29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 22:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f622a41d64e74d5897f29/</guid><description>Alex Jones sat for depositions on Tuesday and Wednesday in the Sandy Hook case, ending&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones sat for a second day of questioning under oath in the Sandy Hook defamation case on Wednesday. Jones said in a video that he was being demonized for falsely reporting that the worst crime in modern Connecticut history never happened. Jones flew to Connecticut this week from the Texas headquarters of his “Infowars” internet program.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones skips Sandy Hook deposition again after judge rules 2nd doctor’s note doesn’t excuse him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cdecfff8f0c2d93c6deeb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 21:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cdecfff8f0c2d93c6deeb/</guid><description>This marks the second time this week Jones has failed to appear for his deposition, with&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones failed to comply with a court order requiring his deposition in a successful defamation lawsuit brought by families of Sandy Hook shooting victims. Law firms representing the families of the victims alerted the media that Jones did not arrive for the in-person questioning. The no-show marks the second time this week Jones has failed to appear for his deposition, with his defense attorneys arguing to the court that an unnamed “medical condition” should excuse him.</description></item></channel></rss>