<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>game on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/game/</link><description>Recent content in game on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 17:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandy Hook shooting: The unprecedented $73M settlement with gunmaker Remington</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293a9e4932dd87f36af2b73/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 17:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293a9e4932dd87f36af2b73/</guid><description>A lawsuit against an industry viewed by many as protected from liability over gun violence used a novel legal strategy, and accomplished the unthinkable: the largest payout ever by a gun company to victims of a mass shooting.
Highlights In 2013, four months after the Sandy Hook shooting, Francine Wheeler made an impassioned plea: &amp;ldquo;Please help us do something before our tragedy becomes your tragedy&amp;rdquo; The Wheelers, and eight other Sandy Hook families, sued the gunmaker, Remington Arms, and in February they settled the lawsuit for $73 million.</description></item><item><title>‘Hate is alive and well’: Burnley fan arrested for apparent Nazi salute at Spurs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62834b24cb7ae7e4d9bcca07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 07:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62834b24cb7ae7e4d9bcca07/</guid><description>Three Burnley supporters were arrested on suspicion of discriminatory behaviour after Sunday’s match at Tottenham, the Lancashire club has said
Highlights Three Burnley supporters arrested on suspicion of discriminatory behaviour after Sunday&amp;rsquo;s match at Tottenham Hotspur. Video appears to show a fan performing a Nazi salute at the game. Tottenham said they would support the police with their investigation. Two Brentford players said they had been racially abused at Everton on Sunday.</description></item><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item></channel></rss>