<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mariupol on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mariupol/</link><description>Recent content in mariupol on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:43:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mariupol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine: 200 bodies found in basement in Mariupol's ruins</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628da5d03f2bc72094e1eef3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628da5d03f2bc72094e1eef3/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Workers digging through the rubble of an apartment building in Mariupol found 200 bodies in the basement, Ukrainian authorities said Tuesday, as more horrors come to light in the ruined city that has seen some of the worst suffering of the 3-month-old war .
Highlights The town of Bakhmut has been coming under increasing artillery strikes, particularly over the last week, as Russian forces try to press forward to encircle the city of Sieverodonetsk.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says 400,000 citizens have been forcibly taken to Russia | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f04bd01220c9f7da9856f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 12:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f04bd01220c9f7da9856f/</guid><description>Ukraine accused Moscow on Thursday of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians from shattered Ukrainian cities to Russia, while the Kremlin has said the people relocated from Ukraine wanted to go to Russia.
Highlights Ukraine accuses Moscow of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians to Russia. The Kremlin gave nearly identical numbers for those who have been relocated, but it said they wanted to go to Russia. Some have reported shortages of food and water there.</description></item><item><title>These journalists filmed the agony in Mariupol and escaped while being hunted down by Russian forces</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623941058b2588270a92c953/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 03:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623941058b2588270a92c953/</guid><description>Associated Press video journalist Mstyslav Chernov and photographer Evgeniy Maloletka arrived in Mariupol, Ukraine, in the early hours of Feb. 24. An hour later, Russia&amp;rsquo;s war on its neighbour started. Chernov recounts what he and his colleague witnessed and how they escaped from the city as Russians were hunting them down.
Highlights Mstyslav Chernov and photographer Evgeniy Maloletka were the only international journalists left in Mariupol. They had been documenting the siege of the Ukrainian city by Russian troops for more than two weeks.</description></item></channel></rss>