<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>near on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/near/</link><description>Recent content in near on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/near/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia moves more troops westward amid Ukraine tensions | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is a sending an unspecified number of troops from the country’s far east to Belarus for major war games, officials said Tuesday, a deployment that will further beef up Russian military presence near Ukraine amid Western fears of a planned invasion.
Summary Russia has concentrated an estimated 100,000 troops with tanks and other heavy weapons near Ukraine in what the West fears could be a prelude to an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine warns Russia has 'almost completed' build-up of forces near border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</guid><description>Ukraine has warned that Russia has &amp;quot;almost completed&amp;quot; its build-up of forces that could be used for an offensive against the country, compounding fears that Moscow could launch an invasion at any time.
Summary The assessment called the situation &amp;ldquo;difficult,&amp;rdquo; and said Ukraine believes Russia is &amp;ldquo;trying to split and weaken the European Union and NATO.&amp;rdquo; Ukrainian military intelligence said Russia has deployed troops from its central and eastern regions to its western border &amp;ldquo;on a permanent basis.</description></item><item><title>Russia sees 'no grounds' for more security talks with US, NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</guid><description>Russia says it sees &amp;quot;no grounds&amp;quot; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine.
Summary Russia says it sees &amp;ldquo;no grounds&amp;rdquo; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine. “There is, to a certain extent, a dead end or a difference in approaches,” Ryabkov said, according to the Post.</description></item></channel></rss>