<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>near on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/near/</link><description>Recent content in near on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 09:09:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/near/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 adults, 3 kids found dead inside home, escaped Texas inmate may be connected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299cfac5aa952df53c41468/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 09:09:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299cfac5aa952df53c41468/</guid><description>A Texas inmate suspected of murdering five people after he escaped from a prison bus was killed by authorities on Thursday, officials said.
Highlights A 46-year-old convicted murderer Gonzalo Lopez was killed in a police shootout in Jourdanton, Texas, on June 2, 2022. Lopez allegedly killed an adult and four children while on the run, authorities said. Lopez, a convicted murderer, was added to Texas&amp;rsquo; 10 Most Wanted Fugitives List and a $50,000 reward was issued for his capture.</description></item><item><title>Fox caught on U.S. Capitol grounds euthanized; tests positive for rabies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e4bf16cdbf9b3fd66dd12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 02:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e4bf16cdbf9b3fd66dd12/</guid><description>WASHINGTON - A mother red fox captured Tuesday on the grounds of the U.S. Capitol has&amp;hellip;
Highlights A mother red fox has been euthanized and tested positive for rabies, a spokeswoman for the Humane Rescue Alliance says. The Washington, D.C., public health lab &amp;ldquo;has confirmed the fox tested positive&amp;rdquo; for the rabies virus. Rep. Ami Bera, D-Calif., said he was among those attacked, about 5 p.m. Monday while he was walking near the Russell Senate Office Building, across the street from the Capitol.</description></item><item><title>Biden admin warns that serious Russian combat forces have gathered near Ukraine in last 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f35c6774ec6a42b43d18ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f35c6774ec6a42b43d18ae/</guid><description>Asked about a timeline, Kirby said: &amp;lsquo;We have always said and said for quite some time, another incursion by Russia could be imminent &amp;ndash; and imminent means imminent.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights AdvertisementPresident Joe Biden reportedly told Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Thursday to brace his country for a certain Russian invasion. &amp;lsquo;President Biden reaffirmed the readiness of the United States along with its allies and partners to respond decisively if Russia further invades Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia moves more troops westward amid Ukraine tensions | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is a sending an unspecified number of troops from the country’s far east to Belarus for major war games, officials said Tuesday, a deployment that will further beef up Russian military presence near Ukraine amid Western fears of a planned invasion.
Summary Russia has concentrated an estimated 100,000 troops with tanks and other heavy weapons near Ukraine in what the West fears could be a prelude to an invasion.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine warns Russia has 'almost completed' build-up of forces near border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7b7173efe27f800aa5797/</guid><description>Ukraine has warned that Russia has &amp;quot;almost completed&amp;quot; its build-up of forces that could be used for an offensive against the country, compounding fears that Moscow could launch an invasion at any time.
Summary The assessment called the situation &amp;ldquo;difficult,&amp;rdquo; and said Ukraine believes Russia is &amp;ldquo;trying to split and weaken the European Union and NATO.&amp;rdquo; Ukrainian military intelligence said Russia has deployed troops from its central and eastern regions to its western border &amp;ldquo;on a permanent basis.</description></item><item><title>Russia sees 'no grounds' for more security talks with US, NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 11:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e157edac398ef45f13db98/</guid><description>Russia says it sees &amp;quot;no grounds&amp;quot; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine.
Summary Russia says it sees &amp;ldquo;no grounds&amp;rdquo; for continued talks with the U.S. and NATO as the alliance seeks to avert a second Moscow invasion of Ukraine. “There is, to a certain extent, a dead end or a difference in approaches,” Ryabkov said, according to the Post.</description></item></channel></rss>