<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>employees on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employees/</link><description>Recent content in employees on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meta employees left to do their own laundry as perks get cut | Silicon Valley | The Guardian</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</guid><description>Facebook parent company tells workers they will no longer receive free valet service and meals will be delayed
Highlights Facebook parent company tells employees it will be cutting down on onsite perks including free laundry, dry cleaning and valet service. The daily free dinner will be pushed back from 6pm to 6.30pm due to company cutbacks. Employees will now have to decide between a free meal or a free ride home.</description></item><item><title>McDonald's will temporarily close 850 restaurants in Russia, nearly 2 weeks after Putin invaded Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia after the company took heat for staying silent on the war in Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s says it will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia. The decision comes nearly two weeks after Russian forces invaded Ukraine. PepsiCo, Starbucks and Coco-Cola also announced similar step-backs from the country. McDonald&amp;rsquo;s restaurants in Russia and Ukraine account for 2% of its systemwide sales, 9% of revenue and 3% of operating income.</description></item><item><title>Houston doctor suing Chase bank for denying service: 'They didn't respect my credentials'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61faf363f73789a8176a8eb7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61faf363f73789a8176a8eb7/</guid><description>A Houston doctor is suing a Chase Bank in Sugar Land after she says she was discriminated against and denied service because of the color of her skin.
Highlights Dr. Malika Mitchell-Stewart says she had just finished her residency. She went to Chase&amp;rsquo;s First Colony Bank to open an account and deposit a $16,000 check. She says staff at the bank asked peculiar questions about the validity of her check and her employment as a doctor.</description></item><item><title>United CEO says vaccine mandate appears to have ended weekly deaths of employees from Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</guid><description>A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday.
Summary A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday. &amp;ldquo;Prior to our vaccine requirement, tragically, more than one United employee on average per week was dying from COVID,&amp;rdquo; Kirby wrote.</description></item><item><title>Grocers pressured to bring back 'hero pay' amid Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</guid><description>The head of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union says the refusal by the country&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;quot;hero pay&amp;quot; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;quot;about greed, period.&amp;quot;
Summary The failure of Canada&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;ldquo;hero pay&amp;rdquo; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;ldquo;about greed, period,&amp;rdquo; the head of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union said Friday. While each chain has sporadically reintroduced either wage bonuses or other incentives, it appears none have offered workers pay premiums as a result of the Omicron surge.</description></item><item><title>Tech Company Bolt Permanently Enacts 4 Day Workweek</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d65b58e28cd6e8b0e6765f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d65b58e28cd6e8b0e6765f/</guid><description>San Francisco-based tech firm Bolt said it has seen an increase in productivity, as well as better work-life balance for its employees.
Summary A four-day workweek is now a permanent perk for employees of tech unicorn Bolt. The San Francisco-based e-commerce developer piloted the program last fall, and the results were overwhelmingly positive, said founder and CEO Ryan Breslow. The idea is not to necessarily take on more work hours but to work more efficiently.</description></item></channel></rss>