<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>employees on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employees/</link><description>Recent content in employees on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Victims, parents of Oxford school shooting victims sue school employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628de4e0c5f62b4bdd93e509/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628de4e0c5f62b4bdd93e509/</guid><description>The lawsuit against Oxford Community School District and administrators
Highlights Plaintiffs and families of victims of November shooting in Michigan file lawsuit against school district, school administrators. Lawsuit accuses administrators of failing to notify law enforcement of the actions of the accused shooter leading up to the shooting. Justin Shilling and Tate Myre, who were killed in the shooting, and representatives for four minors who were injured in shooting. The lawsuit claims other students saw Ethan Crumbley with shell casings and live ammunition rounds one day before shooting.</description></item><item><title>Store employees fight off hammer-swinging thieves during Newport Beach smash-and-grab robbery: video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c5e378c4c6350ebf7787f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 04:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c5e378c4c6350ebf7787f/</guid><description>A smash-and-grab robbery at a Huntington Beach jewelry store ended with store workers fighting back against the hammer-swinging thieves.
Highlights A smash-and-grab robbery at a jewelry store in Huntington Beach ended with an employee counterpunch. The incident happened at about noon at the Princess Bride Jewelry store in the Bella Terra Mall. Four hooded individuals entered the jewelry store, the first suspect smashes the front jewelry case with a hammer. The employees successfully fought off all four robbers, and the suspects fled the area before police arrived.</description></item><item><title>Yelp, other companies take stance on abortion rights with travel benefit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277c44928d516adc649175a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277c44928d516adc649175a/</guid><description>Yelp, Amazon, and Citigroup are among a small but growing number of companies rolling out policies to cover costs for American employees who need to travel out of state for an abortion.
Highlights Yelp, Amazon.com, Citigroup, Levi Strauss &amp;amp; Co and Amazon have all pledged to pay for employees&amp;rsquo; travel to obtain abortions. The issue has gained urgency now that 31 states have introduced abortion bans this year, according to policy analysis by research group Guttmacher Institute.</description></item><item><title>Apple store in Maryland becomes third to launch union drive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717ea261fb248308b43d1f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717ea261fb248308b43d1f/</guid><description>Employees at the Towson Mall store say they want a voice on coronavirus safety, scheduling, pay and other topics.
Highlights Workers at the Towson Mall store near Baltimore have been drumming up support for nearly a year. They say they have signatures from more than 65 percent of employees who are likely to be eligible, giving them a “supermajority” that would be difficult for the company to overcome. The union drive is the latest sign of a reinvigorated labor movement.</description></item><item><title>Apple retail union organizers want workers to be paid at least $30 per hour</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e6ffb74e64f466f7b57a2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 08:17:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e6ffb74e64f466f7b57a2/</guid><description>An Apple employee-led union organizing committee is collecting authorization cards, which determines the level of unionization support at the workplace.
Highlights Workers at Apple&amp;rsquo;s Grand Central Terminal want workers to be paid a minimum of $30 per hour. Apple employees are seeking representation with Workers United, an affiliate of the Service Employees International Union. An Apple employee-led union organizing committee is collecting authorization cards that will determine the level of unionization support at the store.</description></item><item><title>Apple workers at New York's Grand Central store take steps to unionize</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625df010eb1bf025bee91249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 23:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625df010eb1bf025bee91249/</guid><description>Apple workers at the company&amp;rsquo;s Grand Central store in Manhattan have begun collecting signatures from workers, according to a website created by organizers.
Highlights Workers at Apple&amp;rsquo;s flagship Grand Central Terminal retail store in New York City are taking steps to unionize. Organizers are in the process of collecting signatures from workers, according to a website. Apple says it offers &amp;ldquo;very strong compensation and benefits&amp;rdquo; for full-time and part-time employees. Amazon workers at a Staten Island warehouse voted in the company&amp;rsquo;s first U.</description></item><item><title>Verizon raises minimum wage to $20 an hour for U.S employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625db7ca064c58d74cc9ca17/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 19:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625db7ca064c58d74cc9ca17/</guid><description>U.S. wireless carrier Verizon Communications Inc said on Monday it would raise the minimum wage of its new and existing customer service, retail and inside sales employees to $20 an hour amid a tight labor market and rising inflation.
Highlights Verizon Communications Inc (VZ.N) said on Monday it would raise the minimum wage of its new and existing customer service, retail and inside sales employees to $20 an hour. In recent months, U.</description></item><item><title>Disney employees across the U.S. are walking out today:"We have been forced into an impossible and unsustainable position," LBGTQ employees said in a statement.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ad74186e032c93e672c2c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 08:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ad74186e032c93e672c2c/</guid><description>Walt Disney Co. employees at corporate locations across the U.S. got up from their desks and headed to the exits Tuesday to protest CEO Bob Chapek&amp;rsquo;s response
Highlights Disney employees protest CEO Bob Chapek&amp;rsquo;s response to Florida&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rdquo; bill. The bill would prohibit instruction about &amp;ldquo;sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;rdquo; in kindergarten through the third grade in Florida. Disney CEO apologized for not taking a more forceful stand against the bill.</description></item><item><title>Disney employees and former judge among 108 arrested in human trafficking sting, Florida police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232c333d74c613709eebc2e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 05:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232c333d74c613709eebc2e/</guid><description>Authorities arrested 108 people, including alleged child sexual predators and those seeking prostitutes.
Highlights Authorities arrested 108 people during a six-day undercover human trafficking operation. Among those taken into custody were four Disney employees and a retired judge, police said. Detectives found prostitutes who had posted online advertisements through various websites and social media platforms to identify people who were seeking them out. They also identified adults who they thought were inappropriately communicating with children.</description></item><item><title>Meta employees left to do their own laundry as perks get cut | Silicon Valley | The Guardian</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d3eb7b2c230b067f3accc/</guid><description>Facebook parent company tells workers they will no longer receive free valet service and meals will be delayed
Highlights Facebook parent company tells employees it will be cutting down on onsite perks including free laundry, dry cleaning and valet service. The daily free dinner will be pushed back from 6pm to 6.30pm due to company cutbacks. Employees will now have to decide between a free meal or a free ride home.</description></item><item><title>McDonald's will temporarily close 850 restaurants in Russia, nearly 2 weeks after Putin invaded Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227d507b51f4a0cf4293df0/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia after the company took heat for staying silent on the war in Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s says it will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia. The decision comes nearly two weeks after Russian forces invaded Ukraine. PepsiCo, Starbucks and Coco-Cola also announced similar step-backs from the country. McDonald&amp;rsquo;s restaurants in Russia and Ukraine account for 2% of its systemwide sales, 9% of revenue and 3% of operating income.</description></item><item><title>Houston doctor suing Chase bank for denying service: 'They didn't respect my credentials'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61faf363f73789a8176a8eb7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61faf363f73789a8176a8eb7/</guid><description>A Houston doctor is suing a Chase Bank in Sugar Land after she says she was discriminated against and denied service because of the color of her skin.
Highlights Dr. Malika Mitchell-Stewart says she had just finished her residency. She went to Chase&amp;rsquo;s First Colony Bank to open an account and deposit a $16,000 check. She says staff at the bank asked peculiar questions about the validity of her check and her employment as a doctor.</description></item><item><title>United CEO says vaccine mandate appears to have ended weekly deaths of employees from Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</guid><description>A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday.
Summary A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday. &amp;ldquo;Prior to our vaccine requirement, tragically, more than one United employee on average per week was dying from COVID,&amp;rdquo; Kirby wrote.</description></item><item><title>Grocers pressured to bring back 'hero pay' amid Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</guid><description>The head of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union says the refusal by the country&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;quot;hero pay&amp;quot; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;quot;about greed, period.&amp;quot;
Summary The failure of Canada&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;ldquo;hero pay&amp;rdquo; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;ldquo;about greed, period,&amp;rdquo; the head of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union said Friday. While each chain has sporadically reintroduced either wage bonuses or other incentives, it appears none have offered workers pay premiums as a result of the Omicron surge.</description></item><item><title>Tech Company Bolt Permanently Enacts 4 Day Workweek</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d65b58e28cd6e8b0e6765f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d65b58e28cd6e8b0e6765f/</guid><description>San Francisco-based tech firm Bolt said it has seen an increase in productivity, as well as better work-life balance for its employees.
Summary A four-day workweek is now a permanent perk for employees of tech unicorn Bolt. The San Francisco-based e-commerce developer piloted the program last fall, and the results were overwhelmingly positive, said founder and CEO Ryan Breslow. The idea is not to necessarily take on more work hours but to work more efficiently.</description></item></channel></rss>