<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>united on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/united/</link><description>Recent content in united on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 19:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/united/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. lawyer Avenatti sentenced to four years prison for defrauding Stormy Daniels</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62990aa5f3ebe74dd5886a42/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62990aa5f3ebe74dd5886a42/</guid><description>Michael Avenatti, the brash California lawyer who once took on then-President Donald Trump, was sentenced to four years in prison on Thursday for defrauding his best-known former client, the porn actress Stormy Daniels.
Highlights Michael Avenatti, the brash California lawyer who once took on then-President Donald Trump, was sentenced to four years in prison on Thursday. He was sentenced for defrauding his best-known former client, the porn actress Stormy Daniels. Avenatti took on the president of the United States in a bid to get a settlement from the White House.</description></item><item><title>More than 100 confirmed or suspected cases of monkeypox have been reported in 12 countries, including the US - CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b6b39695a67b92a49b0a9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b6b39695a67b92a49b0a9/</guid><description>More cases of a rare disease have been reported worldwide, including in the United States &amp;ndash; where one health official said he expects more cases in the days ahead.
Highlights 92 confirmed cases and 28 suspected cases of monkeypox are under investigation in 12 countries, WHO says. The White House Covid-19 response coordinator says he expects &amp;ldquo;a few more&amp;rdquo; cases in the coming days. The United States had between one and five confirmed monkeypox cases as of Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Airline ticket prices have risen 40 percent since the beginning of 2022</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626843d0cc32197ea53d7c8e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 19:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626843d0cc32197ea53d7c8e/</guid><description>Surging demand, high fuel prices and an ongoing pilot shortage have combined to create&amp;hellip;
Highlights Average cost of airfare for U.S. travelers in April rose to $330 for a single domestic round-trip ticket. Hopper expects prices to increase a further 10 percent by the end of May. Air carriers excitedly eyeing current &amp;ldquo;strong revenue environment&amp;rdquo; brought about by high fuel prices, increased labor costs and a shortage of pilots in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Covid-19 was third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, CDC reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6263734f7a7e5d2e375dd940/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 03:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6263734f7a7e5d2e375dd940/</guid><description>Covid-19 was the third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, following heart disease and cancer, for the second year in a row, according to provisional data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Highlights Covid-19 was the third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, following heart disease and cancer. The data was published Friday in the CDC&amp;rsquo;s Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin says "nothing terrible will happen" if Russia is expelled from G20</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e3036bddc611cab4d4066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 21:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e3036bddc611cab4d4066/</guid><description>The Kremlin said on Friday that nothing terrible will happen if the United States and its allies succeed in expelling Russia from the Group of Twenty (G20) major economies because many of the G20&amp;rsquo;s members are at economic war with Moscow anyway.
Highlights Russia and its allies are at a state of war with each other, says U.S. President Vladimir Putin. Putin says some countries are taking a more sober approach towards Russia and not trying to isolate it.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks Workers United wins first store election outside of Buffalo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a4362f71a86f9ef39c979/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 15:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a4362f71a86f9ef39c979/</guid><description>Restaurant news
Highlights Starbucks Workers United won representation at a store in Mesa, Arizona, on Friday. This marks the second election in the ongoing union drive, and the first outside of Buffalo. Starbucks has reached public organizing drives in more than 100 stores. Organizers around the country say the spread of the union drive may have caught the company off guard. Starbucks still opposes the union and believes workers should vote as a regional market rather than on a store-by-store basis, a spokesperson for the coffee chain said.</description></item><item><title>'Every indication' Putin plans force by mid-February: US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</guid><description>The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday.
Summary The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;I have no idea whether he&amp;rsquo;s made the ultimate decision, but we certainly see every indication that he is going to use military force sometime perhaps (between) now and the middle of February,&amp;rdquo; Deputy Secretary of State Wendy Sherman told a forum.</description></item><item><title>Germany urges 'prudence' in potential sanctions against Russia over Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee78bf52b2999c47989444/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee78bf52b2999c47989444/</guid><description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s leader has urged Europe and the United States to think carefully when considering sanctions against Russia for any aggression against Ukraine in a crisis pitting Berlin&amp;rsquo;s main gas supplier against its biggest security allies. Among a range of possible Western sanctions against President Vladmir Putin&amp;rsquo;s government, Germany could halt the Nord Stream 2 pipeline from Russia if it invades Ukraine.
Summary BERLIN (Reuters) - Germany&amp;rsquo;s leader has urged Europe and the United States to think carefully when considering sanctions against Russia for any aggression against Ukraine in a crisis pitting Berlin&amp;rsquo;s main gas supplier against its biggest security allies.</description></item><item><title>Russia warns Japan to stay out of Ukraine crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee08403d4bf3a5db09fae7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee08403d4bf3a5db09fae7/</guid><description>The Russian foreign minister&amp;rsquo;s team warned Japan to stay out of the brewing Ukraine crisis after U.S. officials touted a “close alignment” with Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida in the lead-up to a potential eruption of violence in Eastern Europe.
Summary The Russian foreign minister&amp;rsquo;s team warned Japan to stay out of the brewing Ukraine crisis after U.S. officials touted a “close alignment” with Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida in the lead-up to a potential eruption of violence in Eastern Europe.</description></item><item><title>Nurses across the U.S. strike against COVID working conditions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4170a9c53b73c2c122f05/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4170a9c53b73c2c122f05/</guid><description>Nurses &amp;quot;are enraged to see that, for our government &amp;hellip; it’s all about what’s good for business, not what’s good for public health.&amp;quot;
Summary National Nurses United, a labor union with more than 175,000 members nationwide, organized several strikes across the country Thursday, calling on the hospital industry to &amp;ldquo;invest in safe staffing.&amp;rdquo; Why it matters: The health care industry has struggled against the backdrop of heightened health risks, worker shortages and burnout, largely exacerbated by the onslaught of the coronavirus.</description></item><item><title>Alabama woman who joined Islamic State stuck in refugee camp</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0147423285a11aff0d008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 12:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0147423285a11aff0d008/</guid><description>BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (AP) — Attorneys for a woman who left her Alabama home to join the Islamic State terror group plan to continue fighting for her and her young son even though the Supreme Court declined to consider her lawsuit seeking to re-enter the United States, one of the lawyers said Wednesday.
Summary FILE - This undated photo provided by attorney Hassan Shibly shows Hoda Muthana, who was born in New Jersey in 1994 and grew up in Alabama.</description></item><item><title>Australia spends $3.5billion to purchase 120 military tanks from the United States as tensions soar with China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd7f918524169ecd9dc143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd7f918524169ecd9dc143/</guid><description>Australia will spend more than $3.5billion to purchase 120 tanks and other armoured vehicles from the United States as China continues to gain a military advantage over the Western world.
Summary Australia will spend more than $3.5billion to purchase 120 tanks and other armoured vehicles from the United States. The upgrade could see the Australian Army gain up to 75 Abrams tanks, 29 assault breacher vehicles, 17 joint assault bridge vehicles, and six armoured recovery vehicles.</description></item><item><title>FBI: Cyber criminals are mailing out USB drives that install ransomware</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd636684d5880e99a4c7cf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd636684d5880e99a4c7cf/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t insert USB drives from unknown sources, even if they&amp;rsquo;re addressed to you in the post.
Summary The USB drives contain so-called &amp;lsquo;BadUSB&amp;rsquo; attacks. One type contained a message impersonating the US Department of Health and Human Services and claimed to be a COVID-19 warning. According to The Record, the FBI warned that the new BadUSB attacks were shipped on LILYGO-branded devices. The USB drives were configured to register as a keyboard device after being plugged in.</description></item></channel></rss>