<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>united on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/united/</link><description>Recent content in united on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 12:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/united/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alabama woman who joined Islamic State stuck in refugee camp</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0147423285a11aff0d008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 12:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0147423285a11aff0d008/</guid><description>BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (AP) — Attorneys for a woman who left her Alabama home to join the Islamic State terror group plan to continue fighting for her and her young son even though the Supreme Court declined to consider her lawsuit seeking to re-enter the United States, one of the lawyers said Wednesday.
Summary FILE - This undated photo provided by attorney Hassan Shibly shows Hoda Muthana, who was born in New Jersey in 1994 and grew up in Alabama.</description></item><item><title>Australia spends $3.5billion to purchase 120 military tanks from the United States as tensions soar with China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd7f918524169ecd9dc143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd7f918524169ecd9dc143/</guid><description>Australia will spend more than $3.5billion to purchase 120 tanks and other armoured vehicles from the United States as China continues to gain a military advantage over the Western world.
Summary Australia will spend more than $3.5billion to purchase 120 tanks and other armoured vehicles from the United States. The upgrade could see the Australian Army gain up to 75 Abrams tanks, 29 assault breacher vehicles, 17 joint assault bridge vehicles, and six armoured recovery vehicles.</description></item><item><title>FBI: Cyber criminals are mailing out USB drives that install ransomware</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd636684d5880e99a4c7cf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd636684d5880e99a4c7cf/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t insert USB drives from unknown sources, even if they&amp;rsquo;re addressed to you in the post.
Summary The USB drives contain so-called &amp;lsquo;BadUSB&amp;rsquo; attacks. One type contained a message impersonating the US Department of Health and Human Services and claimed to be a COVID-19 warning. According to The Record, the FBI warned that the new BadUSB attacks were shipped on LILYGO-branded devices. The USB drives were configured to register as a keyboard device after being plugged in.</description></item></channel></rss>