<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tells on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tells/</link><description>Recent content in tells on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:13:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tells/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twitter CEO tells employees company not 'held hostage' by Musk offer -source</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62597d5e3243983fec29462b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62597d5e3243983fec29462b/</guid><description>Twitter Chief Executive Officer Parag Agrawal sought to reassure employees during an all-hands meeting on Thursday that the company was not being &amp;quot;held hostage&amp;quot; by news of Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s offer to buy the company, a source familiar with the matter told Reuters.
Highlights Twitter Chief Executive Officer Parag Agrawal sought to reassure employees during an all-hands meeting on Thursday that the company was not being &amp;ldquo;held hostage&amp;rdquo; by news of Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s offer to buy Twitter.</description></item><item><title>The U.S. has a C-minus on infrastructure</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230ad074a5b6f65fec365a5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 15:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230ad074a5b6f65fec365a5/</guid><description>How did the U.S. end up with a C-minus grade on infrastructure? “You get what you pay for,” Sec. Pete Buttigieg tells Anderson Cooper. “And for pretty much as long as I’ve been alive, our country has been under-investing in public things.” https://cbsn.ws/3tToWx5
Highlights The U.S. has a C-minus grade on infrastructure. “You get what you pay for,” Sec. Pete Buttigieg tells Anderson Cooper. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Full-scale invasion 'likely' within 24 hours - Australia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621608cf92fc37af895449d4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 10:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621608cf92fc37af895449d4/</guid><description>The government is also conscripting reservists into the regular military as it braces for a possible invasion.
Highlights The EU is on the cusp of confirming its initial sanctions package. It follows a frantic 24 hours of talks between ambassadors, officials and foreign ministers. Final sign off hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened, but final sign-off hasn’t happened. The EU’s foreign policy chief Josep Borrell Fontelles tweeted last night that, for some, there’d now be no more shopping in Milan, partying in Saint-Tropez or diamonds in Antwerp!</description></item></channel></rss>