<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hours on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hours/</link><description>Recent content in hours on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 05:12:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hours/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine minister says the Ukrainian Military has regained control of ‘whole Kyiv region’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62492ca59ce80d90a36246ec/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62492ca59ce80d90a36246ec/</guid><description>Russia-Ukraine news from April 2: Ukraine’s president says retreating Russian forces creating ‘catastrophic’ situation.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s top negotiator in peace talks with Russia says Moscow&amp;rsquo;verbally&amp;rsquo; agreed to key Ukrainian proposals. Red Cross to make new attempt to evacuate civilians from besieged city of Mariupol. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president says retreating Russian troops are leaving behind land mines creating a “catastrophic” situation. Ukraine has regained control of ‘whole Kyiv region’ after invading Russian forces retreated from some key towns near the Ukrainian capital, deputy defence minister Ganna Maliar has said.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi fire chief dies hours after legal win allowing use of Ivermectin to treat COVID</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62053a81c1761200de2c8037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62053a81c1761200de2c8037/</guid><description>Wayne Doyle died Tuesday afternoon at North Mississippi Medical Center in Tupelo.
Highlights Wayne Doyle died Tuesday afternoon at North Mississippi Medical Center in Tupelo. He was given Ivermectin, which is not approved to treat the virus. Doyle died after he was moved out of the hospital to receive the drug. The drug has been at the center of attention during the pandemic of the virus in the U.S. Some used it for treatment, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not approved by the federal government and some use it to treat parasites in humans and animals.</description></item><item><title>Government official swims 12 hours to shore after helicopter crash off Madagascar: "My time to die hasn't come yet"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2cd05f199143caea32f00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 07:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2cd05f199143caea32f00/</guid><description>Description The helicopter was flying Serge Gelle and others to inspect the site of a deadly shipwreck off the northeastern coast.
Summary A Madagascan minister was one of two survivors to have swum some 12 hours to shore Tuesday after their helicopter crashed off the island&amp;rsquo;s northeastern coast, authorities said. A search was still ongoing for two other passengers after the crash Monday, whose cause was not immediately clear, police and port authorities said.</description></item></channel></rss>