<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prison on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prison/</link><description>Recent content in prison on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 16:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prison/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Woman gets 15 months in prison for punching flight attendant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62924984d5f7053850373fa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62924984d5f7053850373fa9/</guid><description>SAN DIEGO (AP) — A California woman who punched a Southwest Airlines flight attendant in the face during a flight, breaking her teeth, has been sentenced to 15 months in federal prison. Vyvianna Quinonez was also ordered Tuesday by the federal judge in San Diego to pay nearly $26,000 in restitution and a $7,500 fine for the assault on a May 23, 2021, Southwest flight between Sacramento and San Diego.</description></item><item><title>Man who stormed Capitol in caveman costume gets prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275e8464a15320a7d2c0cfc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 03:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275e8464a15320a7d2c0cfc/</guid><description>A New York City judge&amp;rsquo;s son who stormed the U.S. Capitol wearing a furry “caveman&amp;quot; costume was sentenced on Friday to eight months in prison. U.S.
Highlights Aaron Mostofsky, the son of a New York judge, was sentenced on Friday, May 6, 2022, to eight months in prison. U.S. District Judge James Boasberg said he was “literally on the front lines” of the mob’s attack on Jan. 6, 2021. He also sentenced him to one year of supervised release and ordered him to perform 200 hours of community service and pay $2,000 in restitution.</description></item><item><title>US brothers freed after 25 years in prison for murder they did not commit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b70c86b5152a731ff761b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 19:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b70c86b5152a731ff761b/</guid><description>Judge issues apology to George and Melvin DeJesus, wrongfully convicted of 1995 murder of Margaret Midkiff in Michigan
Highlights George and Melvin DeJesus were convicted in the 1995 killing of Margaret Midkiff. A judge set aside their convictions early Tuesday. The brothers later embraced family members – and met some for the first time – at a restaurant in Lansing. Brandon Gohagen was convicted of second-degree murder and first-degree criminal sexual conduct in the case in 1997.</description></item><item><title>Wrongfully convicted Kansas man who spent 23 years in prison sues for $93m | Kansas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62365574f50e5672cd589afd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 22:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62365574f50e5672cd589afd/</guid><description>Lamonte McIntyre spent two decades in prison for a double murder he did not commit and says a former detective framed him
Highlights Lamonte McIntyre spent 23 years in prison for a double murder he did not commit. He is seeking $93m in damages from the county where he was convicted and a former detective he says framed him. McIntyre was freed in 2017 after a prosecutor asked the court to vacate his convictions and drop all charges.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin kicks off new trial against opposition leader Navalny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621de38684d1b6badecfa96e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621de38684d1b6badecfa96e/</guid><description>Investigators accuse Navalny of stealing more than $4.8m of public donations from the organisations he founded.
Highlights Russian opposition leader Alexey Navalny is accused of stealing more than $4.8m of public donations. He is currently serving a two and a half year sentence on old fraud charges. If found guilty, his sentence could extend up to 10 years. Amnesty International described the hearing as a “sham trial, attended by prison guards rather than the media’s.</description></item><item><title>Waffle House shooter who killed four people sentenced to life in prison without parole</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff6739d314bf883a7367a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 06:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff6739d314bf883a7367a9/</guid><description>Travis Reinking, who killed four people in 2018 when he opened fire with an assault-style rifle at a Waffle House in Tennessee, was sentenced Saturday to life in prison without parole.
Highlights Jurors heard from relatives of the four people who were killed in the shooting. The prosecution asked for life without parole, calling Reinking a mass murderer whose bullets were ripping apart the lives of the victims&amp;rsquo; relatives. Reinking, 33, was found guilty Friday of all 16 counts, including eight first-degree murder charges.</description></item><item><title>Auschwitz: Dutch tourist fined over Nazi salute at former death camp</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee6aa75901fbbda8bbbb32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 09:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee6aa75901fbbda8bbbb32/</guid><description>A 29-year-old woman - who says it was a bad joke - is charged with engaging in Nazi propaganda.
Summary It is not the first time foreigners have been detained for promoting Nazi propaganda in Poland - a charge that can carry up to two years in prison. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>