<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>support on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/support/</link><description>Recent content in support on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 07:14:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Hate is alive and well’: Burnley fan arrested for apparent Nazi salute at Spurs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62834b24cb7ae7e4d9bcca07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 07:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62834b24cb7ae7e4d9bcca07/</guid><description>Three Burnley supporters were arrested on suspicion of discriminatory behaviour after Sunday’s match at Tottenham, the Lancashire club has said
Highlights Three Burnley supporters arrested on suspicion of discriminatory behaviour after Sunday&amp;rsquo;s match at Tottenham Hotspur. Video appears to show a fan performing a Nazi salute at the game. Tottenham said they would support the police with their investigation. Two Brentford players said they had been racially abused at Everton on Sunday.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine win Eurovision with UK in second</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62810a59db3813eb5c2d34ea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62810a59db3813eb5c2d34ea/</guid><description>Ukraine wins the final of the Song Contest, followed by the UK, Spain, Sweden and then Serbia.
Highlights Kalush Orchestra wins the Song Contest, followed by the UK, Spain, Sweden and then Serbia. Ukraine fans flocked to Telegram to share their excitement at the news. Many people have been describing the country&amp;rsquo;s win as a &amp;ldquo;victory&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;glory to the heroes&amp;rdquo; Others have thanked friendly countries for voting and sharing their support for the country.</description></item><item><title>‘Troll factory’ spreading Russian pro-war lies online, says UK</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e89cec6b3aeae30d8a412/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e89cec6b3aeae30d8a412/</guid><description>St Petersburg outfit hijacks discussions on Twitter, TikTok, world leaders’ social accounts and media websites, as well as manipulating opinion polls
Highlights Research funded by the UK government found operatives were ordering followers to target western media outlets and politicians. The St Petersburg outfit hijacks discussions on Twitter, TikTok, world leaders’ social accounts and media websites. The research said TikTok influencers were being paid to amplify pro-Kremlin narratives. The troll farm is said to recruit and hire salaried workers openly, justifying the work as ‘patriotic activity’ in support of the “special military operation” in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Missouri high school bans LGBTQ support stickers and cards</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62695deaaabc7f02d509426a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 15:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62695deaaabc7f02d509426a/</guid><description>The school board of suburban Kansas City high school has told its teachers to remove cards and stickers that show they are allies of LGBTQ students.
Highlights School board of suburban Kansas City high school has told teachers to remove cards and stickers that show they are allies of LGBTQ students. The directive came after members received “a concern” about the cards. The email said the district remains committed to helping create a safe and inclusive environment, but the cards were “not appropriate at this time.</description></item><item><title>Man who paid $2.9m for NFT of Jack Dorsey’s first tweet set to lose almost $2.9m</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b07f15a279f85d9ece8d9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 18:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b07f15a279f85d9ece8d9/</guid><description>‘This is the Mona Lisa of the digital world’, says crypto entrepreneur Sina Estavi who bought the NFT in March 2021
Highlights Sina Estavi bought the NFT of Jack Dorsey’s first tweet in March 2021 for $2.9m. The initial purchase was at the time among the most expensive sales of a non-fungible token. Estavi put the tweet up for resale on the popular NFT marketplace OpenSea last week, initially asking for $48m.</description></item><item><title>Tesla to pay Ukrainian employees for up to 3 months if they are conscripted to fight</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a69a4a4121c4ac6acba7f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 21:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a69a4a4121c4ac6acba7f/</guid><description>Ukrainian Tesla employees who are asked to return to defend their country will receive pay for at least three months, according to an e-mail the company sent Mo
Highlights Ukrainian Tesla employees who are asked to return to defend their country will receive pay for at least three months. Tesla employees were also praised for helping SpaceX, the aerospace venture also led by Tesla CEO Elon Musk, to bring its Starlink satellite internet service to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher pledge to match up to $3 million in aid for Ukrainian refugees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222f0feb7170ee61678538f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 05:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222f0feb7170ee61678538f/</guid><description>Actors Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher have pledged to match up to $3 million in aid to displaced Ukrainians.
Highlights Actors Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher have pledged to match up to $3 million in aid to displaced Ukrainians. More than 1 million people have already fled Ukraine in a rapid exodus more than a week after Russia invaded and bombarded key cities across the country. Kunis: &amp;ldquo;The events that have unfolded in Ukraine are devastating.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau promises to support Ukraine as Canadian warship departs for Black Sea</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e995286dc41a7a20015e9b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e995286dc41a7a20015e9b/</guid><description>A Canadian warship departed for Europe and the Black Sea near Russia on Wednesday, as Prime Minister Justin Trudeau admitted to fears of a Russian invasion in Ukraine.
Summary HALIFAX - A Canadian warship departed for Europe and the Black Sea near Russia on Wednesday, as Prime Minister Justin Trudeau admitted to fears of a Russian invasion in Ukraine. “We&amp;rsquo;re looking at many different factors when we make decisions on how to best support the people of Ukraine,” he said.</description></item><item><title>NATO won't create '2nd-class' allies to soothe Russia, alliance head says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8c60fcac41dd3e6c7be29/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8c60fcac41dd3e6c7be29/</guid><description>NATO has said it is ready for talks on reciprocal arms control with Moscow, but added that the alliance is united against the &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; risk of Russian aggression against Ukraine.
Summary NATO foreign ministers met by video conference Friday to discuss Russia&amp;rsquo;s military presence on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s borders, as alliance Secretary-General Jens Stoltenberg said the troop buildup continues. &amp;ldquo;We are ready to engage in arms control with Russia, conventional and nuclear, but that has to be reciprocal,&amp;rdquo; Stoltenberg said.</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump golf resorts claimed at least £3.3m in UK furlough support: Former US president’s two Scottish resorts claimed emergency support during Covid pandemic.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cafc7a09274a986eb67dee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 12:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cafc7a09274a986eb67dee/</guid><description>Former US president’s two Scottish resorts claimed emergency support during Covid pandemic
Summary Donald Trump’s loss-making Scottish golf resorts claimed in excess of £3.3m in emergency support from the UK government, to help furlough staff during the Covid pandemic. Other government data shows Trump Turnberry and Trump International Scotland in Aberdeenshire then made further claims this year while the UK government’s job retention scheme was still in force. Global controls on air travel, particularly from the US golfing visitors; the impacts on staffing, supply chains and costs from Brexit; and general inflation, had all hit the Trump businesses, he added.</description></item></channel></rss>