<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kyiv on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kyiv/</link><description>Recent content in kyiv on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kyiv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine rules out territorial concessions, as Russia steps up attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bb50b28d5e7b260085460/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bb50b28d5e7b260085460/</guid><description>Kyiv revealed its worst military losses from a single attack of the Ukraine war on Monday, saying 87 people had been killed last week when Russian forces struck a barracks housing troops at a training base in the north.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president says 87 people were killed when Russian forces struck barracks housing troops at a training base in the north last week. The disclosure that scores had been killed in the attack demonstrated Russia&amp;rsquo;s ability to inflict huge losses, even far from the front.</description></item><item><title>Kyiv: Video shows Russian soldiers killing 2 civilians before they ransack a business</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d16a15e342270e8ee26f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 14:16:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d16a15e342270e8ee26f1/</guid><description>CNN has obtained surveillance video showing two men being shot in the back, in an incident now being investigated as a war crime by Ukrainian prosecutors.
Highlights Russian soldiers shot two unarmed civilians as they walked away after an encounter in the Ukrainian capital of Kyiv. CNN has obtained surveillance video of what is now being investigated as a war crime by Ukrainian prosecutors. One was the owner of the vehicle dealership that was looted, whose family does not want to be named.</description></item><item><title>Police: More than 900 civilian bodies found in Kyiv region</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b14bf6cb27277aae31e57/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:11:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b14bf6cb27277aae31e57/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of more than 900 civilians have been discovered in the region surrounding the Ukrainian capital following Russia&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal — most of them fatally shot, police said Friday, an indication that many people were &amp;quot;simply executed.”
Highlights More than 900 civilians have been discovered in the region surrounding the Ukrainian capital following Russia’s withdrawal, police say. Police data indicates 95% died from gunshot wounds, an indication many people were “simply executed” Police: More bodies are being found every day under rubble and in mass graves, with the largest number found in Bucha, where there were more than 350.</description></item><item><title>Mariupol mayor says siege has killed more than 10K civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625499e1fcb75036ac08b36e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 21:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625499e1fcb75036ac08b36e/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The mayor of the Ukrainian port city of Mariupol said Monday that more than 10,000 civilians have died in the Russian siege of his city, and that the death toll could surpass 20,000, with corpses that were “carpeted through the streets.”
Highlights Mariupol Mayor Vadym Boychenko says more than 10,000 civilians have died in the Russian siege of his city. He says corpses have been “carpeted through the streets” and the death toll could surpass 20,000.</description></item><item><title>Dozens of Ukrainians found in grave near Kyiv as battle looms in east | Reuters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252cb5b6889ec91e9ab6d18/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252cb5b6889ec91e9ab6d18/</guid><description>Ukraine said on Sunday it was seeking another round of European Union sanctions against Moscow and more military aid from its allies as it braces for a major Russian offensive in the east of the country.
Highlights Ukraine says it is seeking more sanctions against Moscow and more military aid from its allies. President Volodymyr Zelenskiy renews appeal for a total ban on Russian energy products and more weapons for Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine says Moscow is forcibly taking civilians to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d7a2279b617c4551293a2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d7a2279b617c4551293a2/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine accused Moscow on Thursday of forcibly taking hundreds of thousands of civilians from shattered Ukrainian cities to Russia, where some may be used as “hostages” to pressure Kyiv to give up.
Highlights Ukraine says 402,000 people, including 84,000 children, have been taken to Russia. The Kremlin gave nearly identical numbers for those who have been relocated, but said they wanted to go to Russia. Ukraine’s rebel-controlled eastern regions are predominantly Russian-speaking, and many people there have supported close ties to Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Russian forces shoot and kill 10 people queuing for bread in Chernihiv - US embassy says | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231fe9c2437ef6503213ae2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 15:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231fe9c2437ef6503213ae2/</guid><description>The US embassy in Kyiv says it is &amp;quot;considering all available options to ensure accountability for any atrocity crimes in Ukraine&amp;quot;.
Highlights 10 people shot and killed in Chernihiv, northern Ukraine, US embassy in Kyiv says. US embassy: &amp;ldquo;Such horrific attacks must stop. We are considering all available options to ensure accountability for atrocity crimes&amp;rdquo; UK Ministry of Defence says Ukraine exploiting Russia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;lack of manoeuvre&amp;rdquo; and inflicting heavy losses. Russian troops are continuing to fire missiles at Ukrainian targets, and rockets are hitting civilian buildings and infrastructure, an adviser says.</description></item><item><title>Young Ukrainian volunteer killed delivering aid to dog shelter near Kyiv: ‘She was a hero’ - National</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245ec44c82d9f4715952c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62245ec44c82d9f4715952c9/</guid><description>A young Ukrainian volunteer was shot and killed near Kyiv after delivering supplies to a dog shelter. Her friends say she was targeted at close-range by Russian troops.
Highlights Anastasiia Yalanskaya, a young volunteer in Ukraine, was shot and killed while delivering food to a dog shelter in Bucha, 30 kilometres outside Kyiv, on Friday. Friends and family say her car was deliberately targeted at close-range by Russian troops. Russian troops are increasingly killing civilians at random as a way to scare the population into submission, friends say.</description></item><item><title>Europe's largest nuclear power plant on fire after Russian attack, says local mayor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62219fbcbba8a070e4f92cb3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 05:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62219fbcbba8a070e4f92cb3/</guid><description>A fire broke out in a training building at the largest nuclear power plant in Europe during intense fighting between Russian and Ukrainian forces, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s state emergency service said on Friday.
Highlights U.S. Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm said there was no indication of elevated radiation levels at the Zaporizhzhia plant. A video feed from the plant verified by Reuters showed shelling and smoke rising near a building at the plant compound.</description></item><item><title>Russia's 40-mile convoy has stalled on its way to Kyiv, a U.S. official says : NPR</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ee111d2f020d9d3bb14da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ee111d2f020d9d3bb14da/</guid><description>The convoy is apparently being hampered by fuel and food shortages, the official says. The news comes as Russia continues to concentrate attacks on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s largest cities: Kyiv and Kharkiv.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s 40-mile convoy has stalled on its way to Kyiv, a U.S. official says. The convoy is apparently being hampered by fuel and food shortages. Some elements within the military column are &amp;ldquo;literally out of gas&amp;rdquo; and having difficulty feeding their troops.</description></item><item><title>Explosions in Kyiv as UK reports ‘fierce resistance’ across the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218abe0d07b0625b40728bb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 10:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218abe0d07b0625b40728bb/</guid><description>Public urged to report Russian troop movements and prepare molotov cocktails, with heavy gunfire heard in residential district
Highlights US secretary of state, Antony Blinken, said Russia intends to “incircle and threaten” the city. Russian forces have vowed to stay in the capital in Ukraine. Russian president, Volodymyr Zelenskiy, accused Vladimir Putin of targeting civilian as well as military sites. “Russia will have to talk to us sooner or later about how to end hostilities and stop this invasion.</description></item><item><title>‘Say no to Putin’: Ukrainians support protests in Kazakhstan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</guid><description>Demonstrators in Kyiv fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots.
Summary Demonstrators in Kyiv and Kharkov fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots. Kyiv, Ukraine – With their country’s fate being discussed at this week’s US-Russia talks, Ukrainians took to the streets over the weekend to defend their independence and champion an additional cause – that of Kazakhstan’s protests.</description></item></channel></rss>