<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prosecutors on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prosecutors/</link><description>Recent content in prosecutors on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 21:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prosecutors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A doctor claimed he had a ‘miracle cure’ for covid. He’s going to prison.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296840cdc710408731507bd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296840cdc710408731507bd/</guid><description>San Diego doctor Jennings Staley pleaded guilty to attempting to smuggle in a barrel of hydroxychloroquine powder with the help of a Chinese supplier.
Highlights Jennings Ryan Staley was sentenced last week to 30 days in prison and a year of home confinement for the scheme. He pleaded guilty last year to trafficking in hydroxychloroquine, a drug used to treat the coronavirus. The drug was touted by President Donald Trump, starting in the early days of the pandemic, as a “game changer’s game changer.</description></item><item><title>Internet troll faces trial after Capitol riot plea fizzles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628215e80b4a877dec42b83c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628215e80b4a877dec42b83c/</guid><description>A federal judge scheduled a trial next year for a far-right internet troll after the man, known to his social media followers as “Baked Alaska,” balked at pleading guilty on Wednesday to a criminal charge stemming from the U.S.
Highlights U.S. District Judge Emmet Sullivan refused to accept a guilty plea by Anthime Gionet after he professed his innocence at the start of what was scheduled to be a plea agreement hearing.</description></item><item><title>Florida family Makarenkos allegedly beat, blinded gay man after he 'made' their son gay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62631a67743e163aaeb2b5f5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62631a67743e163aaeb2b5f5/</guid><description>“Unfortunately, your son’s gay,” the 31-year-old Florida man told the Makarenkos, including his alleged lover, as they allegedly attacked him last year, according to records obtained by The Washington Post.
Highlights A Florida man was brutally beaten and blinded by members of his boyfriend’s family because they believed the man “made” their son gay, according to court documents. Prosecutors allege that Inna Makarenko, 44; Yevhen Makarenkos, 43; and two of their adult sons, Oleh, 21, and Vladyslav, 25, ambushed the man at his apartment in Pompano Beach last August and beat him so badly that they left him severely injured in a pool of his own blood for about 14 hours.</description></item><item><title>US charges Russian oligarch, dismantles cybercrime operation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e9ded19710f7e5b98381f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 08:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e9ded19710f7e5b98381f/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration has charged a Russian oligarch linked to the Kremlin with violating U.S. government sanctions, and disrupted a cybercrime operation that was launched by a Russian military intelligence agency, officials said Wednesday.
Highlights The Biden administration has charged a Russian oligarch linked to the Kremlin with violating U.S. government sanctions, and disrupted a cybercrime operation that was launched by a Russian military intelligence agency, officials said Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Black man grabbing tea from car shot by New Jersey police and paralyzed, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62354a47f05cf05715d21fc8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62354a47f05cf05715d21fc8/</guid><description>Jajuan R. Henderson, 29, was unarmed and grabbing an iced tea before he was paralyzed by Trenton police on Feb. 12, a lawsuit alleges.
Highlights Jajuan R. Henderson, 29, was getting the drink from a Saturn Ion parked outside of his home shortly after midnight on Feb. 12 in Trenton, New Jersey. A group of men in dark clothing and masks driving an unidentified vehicle boxed in the Saturn, which was parallel parked, according to the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Mexico finds 17 bodies buried in backyards, patios</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230c983a8d7e5f566e21889/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 17:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230c983a8d7e5f566e21889/</guid><description>MEXICO CITY (AP) — Volunteer searchers in northern Mexico led authorities to a series of grisly finds: 17 bodies or skeletal remains buried in the backyards and patios of houses in a low-income housing development, prosecutors in the northern border state of Sonora said late Sunday.
Highlights Bodies found at abandoned houses in the city of Ciudad Obregon. Bodies had apparently been killed between six months and a year ago, prosecutors say.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 delays trial in plot to abduct Mich. Gov. Whitmer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622eeafbbedc213f9a384880/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 07:14:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622eeafbbedc213f9a384880/</guid><description>The trial for four men accused of plotting to kidnap Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer that was scheduled to resume Monday has been postponed at least until Thursday because an essential participant tested positive for COVID-19
Highlights Trial for four men accused of plotting to kidnap Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer has been postponed at least until Thursday. Undercover FBI agents and informants were expected to testify in the coming weeks. Jurors heard for the first time a recording of one of the defendants specifically talk about kidnapping the Democratic governor.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas officer accused of robbing casino with department-issued gun</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d512f7eeb81165eefd88d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 02:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d512f7eeb81165eefd88d/</guid><description>An off-duty Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Officer accused of robbing a casino with his department-issued gun and suspected in two other robberies has been charged with federal crimes, officials announced Thursday.
Highlights Caleb Rogers, 33, has been charged with interference with commerce by robbery and brandishing a firearm during a crime of violence. He was arrested Feb. 27 after reportedly robbing the Rio All-Suite Hotel &amp;amp; Casino at gunpoint and attempting to abscond with $78,898.</description></item><item><title>US far-right podcaster charged after machine guns found in basement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083eb1f56717984e2c4926/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083eb1f56717984e2c4926/</guid><description>Joseph Paul Berger and his father, Joseph Raymond Berger, arrested last week and charged with multiple firearms offenses
Highlights Joseph Paul Berger, 32, and Joseph Raymond Berger, 67, charged with multiple firearms offenses. Federal prosecutors claim they found cache of weapons in locked basement at home in Bethlehem, Pennsylvania. Prosecutors claim he espouses strong anti-government and anti-law enforcement views. Joseph Berger goes by the moniker “GlockDoctor1488” – 1488 being a popular coded signal among neo-Nazi neo-Nazis, with “14” referencing the slogan “We must secure the existence of our people and a future for white children” and “Heil Hitler” in the Alt-Right Armory podcast.</description></item><item><title>Man found alive in Scotland after faking his death to evade U.S. sex assault charges, official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</guid><description>A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities
Summary A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities said Thursday. Utah County Attorney David O. Leavitt admitted that had Rossi not contracted Covid and needed medical care, he would still probably be living &amp;ldquo;off the grid&amp;rdquo; successfully.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keepers leader and 10 others charged with 'seditious conspiracy' related to US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0af18e4592ec744bbf895/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 23:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0af18e4592ec744bbf895/</guid><description>The Justice Department escalated its January 6 investigation by bringing seditious conspiracy charges against 11 defendants, including the leader of the Oath Keepers, Stewart Rhodes.
Summary (CNN) The Justice Department escalated its January 6 investigation by bringing seditious conspiracy charges against 11 defendants, including the leader of the Oath Keepers, Stewart Rhodes. JUST WATCHED Inside America&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;militias&amp;rsquo; - from the KKK to the Oath Keepers Replay More Videos &amp;hellip; MUST WATCH Inside America&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;militias&amp;rsquo; - from the KKK to the Oath Keepers 11:47&amp;quot;We aren&amp;rsquo;t going through this without civil war.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioters’ tears, remorse don’t spare them from jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1da39b41e6d4d720586bc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1da39b41e6d4d720586bc/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Florida business owner Robert Palmer cheered on the violence at the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 before he joined the fray. Screaming obscenities, he hurled a wooden plank and a fire extinguisher at police officers trying to ward off the mob.
Summary The Justice Department has undertaken the largest investigation in its history with the probe into rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6. The Justice Department has undertaken the largest investigation in its history with the probe into rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan.</description></item><item><title>Michigan woman won’t be charged for outing anti-mask nurses on Twitter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd914e20fa07a434457363/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd914e20fa07a434457363/</guid><description>A conservative sheriff in Michigan who wanted charges to be filed against a Howell woman for calling out anti-maskers on Twitter won’t get his way&amp;hellip;.
Summary click to enlarge ShutterstockIn a series of tweets earlier this month, Kasey Helton took aim at anti-mask nurses who spread misinformation about COVID-19. This evening I was notified by my attorney that the Livingston County prosecutor’s office WILL NOT seek felony charges for a dubious criminal complaint brought against me by the @LCSOMI related to my tweets exposing nurses for publicly spreading COVID #misinfo at gov’t meetings.</description></item></channel></rss>