<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>noknock on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/noknock/</link><description>Recent content in noknock on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 15:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/noknock/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minneapolis mayor suspends no-knock warrants after police killing of Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fe93406340e3e7a144d3dc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fe93406340e3e7a144d3dc/</guid><description>Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey announced on Friday a moratorium on no-knock warrants after police fatally shot a 22-year-old Black man during a raid on an apartment.
Highlights Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey announced on Friday a moratorium on no-knock warrants after police fatally shot a 22-year-old Black man during a raid on an apartment. Video shows the man, Amir Locke, holding a gun as he twisted around beneath a blanket after being roused by officers who entered the apartment on Wednesday to carry out a search warrant.</description></item><item><title>Body camera video shows Minneapolis officers shooting Black man during no-knock warrant. Attorneys say he wasn't the target</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd41fac083c07eb133b322/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd41fac083c07eb133b322/</guid><description>In the early morning hours Wednesday, Minneapolis police officers gently placed a key in a city apartment door before bursting through the doorway yelling &amp;quot;Police! Search warrant!,&amp;quot; according to body camera footage released by city officials Thursday night.
Highlights Minneapolis police officers placed a key in a door before bursting through the doorway yelling &amp;ldquo;Police! Search warrant!&amp;rdquo; The man was shot and killed in the early morning hours Wednesday morning. He was not named in any search warrants before the entry, police say.</description></item></channel></rss>