<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>east on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/east/</link><description>Recent content in east on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 12:15:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/east/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Heat wave engulfs East Coast with temperatures approaching 100 degrees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288d7c2d7ec14d665fd2b8f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 12:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288d7c2d7ec14d665fd2b8f/</guid><description>The earliest heat advisories on record are in effect for New York and Boston.
Highlights Heat advisories are in effect for much of the Acela Corridor in the Northeast, including Philadelphia, Newark, parts of the New York City metro, Hartford and Providence, R.I., and Boston. A few locations could register their highest temperature ever observed during May and their hottest weather recorded so early in the calendar year. The abnormally hot weather is an ominous signal of the effects of human-caused climate change, which is increasing the intensity, frequency and duration of heat waves and extending summerlike conditions deeper into both spring and fall.</description></item><item><title>Dozens of Ukrainians found in grave near Kyiv as battle looms in east | Reuters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252cb5b6889ec91e9ab6d18/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 12:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252cb5b6889ec91e9ab6d18/</guid><description>Ukraine said on Sunday it was seeking another round of European Union sanctions against Moscow and more military aid from its allies as it braces for a major Russian offensive in the east of the country.
Highlights Ukraine says it is seeking more sanctions against Moscow and more military aid from its allies. President Volodymyr Zelenskiy renews appeal for a total ban on Russian energy products and more weapons for Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine has retaken towns 35km east of Kyiv, UK says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623deb52c4f242fe8b959ced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 16:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623deb52c4f242fe8b959ced/</guid><description>Ukraine has retaken towns and defensive positions up to 35 kilometres east of Kyiv, helped by Russian forces falling back on overextended supply lines, Britain&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said on Friday.
Highlights Ukraine retaken towns and defensive positions up to 35 kilometres east of Kyiv, UK defence ministry says. Russia forces falling back on overextended supply lines, British defence ministry said. Russia says it has fallen back on over-stretched supply lines. Ukraine retaking towns helped by Russian forces, Britain&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry has said.</description></item></channel></rss>