<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>abu on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abu/</link><description>Recent content in abu on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 03:38:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AP News: Independent probe points to Israeli fire in journalist death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281c6e961192b99ec3c8a89/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 03:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281c6e961192b99ec3c8a89/</guid><description>JERUSALEM (AP) — As Israel and the Palestinians wrangle over the investigation into the killing of Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh, several independent groups have launched their own probes.
Highlights Shireen Abu Akleh was shot and killed while covering an Israeli raid in the occupied West Bank. She was a household name across the Arab world, known for documenting the hardship of Palestinian life under Israeli rule. Israel and Palestinians are locked in a war of narratives that already has put Israel on the defensive.</description></item><item><title>US condemns Israel’s attack on Shireen Abu Aqleh’s funeral</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f6598617654d9e4454578/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 08:18:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f6598617654d9e4454578/</guid><description>Antony Blinken says US ‘deeply troubled’ after police stormed procession for Palestinian American journalist
Highlights Antony Blinken says US &amp;lsquo;deeply troubled&amp;rsquo; by Israeli police attack on funeral procession. Police burst through gates of St Joseph’s Hospital to beat pallbearers with batons and kick mourners. Dozens of Palestinians were packed around the coffin, some waving Palestinian flags and chanting, “with our soul and blood we will redeem you Sh.Aqleh” at the scene of her death.</description></item></channel></rss>