<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suit on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suit/</link><description>Recent content in suit on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 22:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mom suing TikTok after 10-year-old daughter dies from dangerous "Blackout Challenge"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ed839cc648bb44c345e3c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 22:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ed839cc648bb44c345e3c/</guid><description>Tawainna Anderson said in December 2021 that her daughter Nylah was rushed to the hospital after attempting the challenge, which encourages users to choke themselves.
Highlights Tawainna Anderson said in December 2021, her daughter Nylah was rushed to the hospital after attempting the challenge. She was in the intensive care unit for several days before she died. Anderson is suing TikTok for multiple counts including wrongful death, strict products liability and negligence.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families who won defamation suit against Alex Jones subpoena Facebook as trial nears</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1903629059753f4d85456/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1903629059753f4d85456/</guid><description>The Sandy Hook families who won a defamation suit against extremist Alex Jones in&amp;hellip;
Summary NEWTOWN — The Sandy Hook families who won a defamation suit against extremist Alex Jones in Connecticut want to know whether the “Infowars” host used Facebook to amplify conspiracy theories as both sides prepare for a trial to establish damages. But since Facebook deactivated Jones’ accounts in 2018, his lawyers said they had no access to the social media data the families seek, according to court records.</description></item><item><title>Greenland permanently bans all oil and gas exploration</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5dcbfa5bc3e7975f5909e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5dcbfa5bc3e7975f5909e/</guid><description>Hopefully Greenland&amp;rsquo;s actions will inspire other countries to follow suit and accelerate their divestment from fossil fuels.
Summary In exciting news for the planet and environmentalists, Greenland has announced it is permanently halting all new oil and gas exploration in the country. Despite the recent discovery of potentially significant oil reserves off the island’s east coast, the country’s government says the costs for our planet far outweigh any potential financial gains: “The future does not lie in oil.</description></item></channel></rss>