<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vehicle on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vehicle/</link><description>Recent content in vehicle on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 19:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vehicle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Washington state plans to ban most non-electric vehicles by 2030</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240b6a5c0e8628efc2f035e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 19:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240b6a5c0e8628efc2f035e/</guid><description>Washington state plans to ban most non-electric vehicles by 2030, according to a newly signed bill by Gov. Jay Inslee.
Highlights Washington state plans to ban most non-electric vehicles by 2030. Gov. Jay Inslee signed a bill that covers a lot of transportation issues in the state. The bill is part of a larger $16.9 billion transportation package called “Move Ahead Washington&amp;quot; The bill includes funding for four new hybrid-electric ferries, thousands of electric vehicle charging stations, 25 transit electrification projects across the state, as well as free fares for riders 18 and younger on public transportation systems, Inslee wrote on Friday in a Medium post.</description></item><item><title>Houston gas station claims thieves stole over 1,000 gallons of diesel fuel from underground storage tanks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f9336f47a0e96928dc77c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f9336f47a0e96928dc77c/</guid><description>A family-owned gas station in southwest Houston claims thousands of dollars’ worth of diesel fuel was stolen from their underground storage tanks by alleged thieves.
Highlights Jerry Thayil, the manager at the Fuqua Express gas station, said he noticed a dark-colored van parking over the store’s storage tanks on multiple occasions. His family&amp;rsquo;s business was hit three times for about 350 gallons of diesel per day. He has filed a police report with the Houston Police Department and notified them of what he believes took place.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas woman who pushed elderly man off bus, leading to his death, gets prison sentence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211334a682d8ea3a435733d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211334a682d8ea3a435733d/</guid><description>A Las Vegas woman who admitted to pushing an elderly man off a public transit bus in 2019 was sentenced to prison Friday as part of a plea bargain.
Highlights Cadesha Bishop, 25, received a sentence of eight to 20 years for abuse of an older person resulting in death. On March 21, 2019, Bishop was captured on bus surveillance video arguing with Serge Fournier, 74. Bishop was seen pushing him, causing him to fall onto the sidewalk below.</description></item><item><title>Pa. Supreme Court says warrantless searches not justified by cannabis smell alone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfa7b627c20b2654f045ce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfa7b627c20b2654f045ce/</guid><description>On Dec. 29, Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s highest court confirmed a decision by a trial court that said the smell of cannabis cannot be the sole basis of&amp;hellip;
Summary On Dec. 29, Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s highest court confirmed a decision by a trial court that said the smell of cannabis cannot be the sole basis of a warrantless search by police officers. Then a trooper smelled the odor of burnt marijuana through the open window of the vehicle, wrote Chief Justice Max Baer in the majority opinion .</description></item><item><title>Protesters call for firing of officer in fatal Florida dirt bike traffic stop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd3ced4379b3f93d073956/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd3ced4379b3f93d073956/</guid><description>Demonstrators outside the Boynton Beach, Florida police headquarters also demanded transparency about how Stanley David Jr. died.
Summary Demonstrators outside police headquarters in Boynton Beach, Florida, Tuesday night called for the firing of the officer involved in the death of a 13-year old boy on a dirt bike during an attempted traffic stop Sunday, CBS West Palm Beach affiliate WPEC-TV reports. Demonstrators outside Boynton Beach, Florida police headquarters on night of December 29, 2021 pressed for the firing of the officer in a fatal attempted dirt bike traffic stop two days before.</description></item></channel></rss>