<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>supply on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supply/</link><description>Recent content in supply on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:11:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supply/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Marijuana violations have taken over 10,000 truck drivers off the road this year, adding more supply chain disruptions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289f009b321671c04f3045a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289f009b321671c04f3045a/</guid><description>The first quarter of 2022 saw a nearly 33% increase year over year in marijuana violations among commercial vehicle drivers. Stacker looks at the rise in truckers being pulled from the road and the potential effects on the supply chain.
Highlights As of April 1, 2022, 10,276 commercial vehicle drivers have tested positive for marijuana use. That’s a 32.6% increase year over year. Truck drivers who travel cross-country face inconsistent state regulations as 19 states have legalized recreational marijuana and 37 states permit it for medicinal purposes.</description></item><item><title>More human remains found at Lake Mead as reservoir's water level plunges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62795ad0b0abf73599607b72/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 18:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62795ad0b0abf73599607b72/</guid><description>More human remains were found at Lake Mead over the weekend, days after a body was found in a barrel.
Highlights The West&amp;rsquo;s megadrought is already at &amp;lsquo;critically low levels&amp;rsquo; and the dry season is just starting. The Colorado River irrigates farms, powers electric grids and provides drinking water for 40 million people. Experts say the term &amp;lsquo;drought&amp;rsquo; may be insufficient to capture what is happening in the West. More human remains were found at Lake Mead over the weekend, days after a body was found in a barrel.</description></item><item><title>Biden to require US-made steel, iron for infrastructure</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d9e06074170249a8f2e32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d9e06074170249a8f2e32/</guid><description>New guidance being issued Monday will require material for projects like bridges, highways and broadband internet funded by last year’s infrastructure package be produced in the U.S. President Joe Biden hopes to create more jobs, ease supply chain strains
Highlights Biden to require US-made steel, iron for infrastructure for infrastructure projects. New guidance being issued Monday will require material for projects like bridges, highways and broadband internet funded by last year’s infrastructure package be produced in the U.</description></item><item><title>Cadbury faces fresh accusations of child labour on cocoa farms in Ghana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249f13e2e230952f74004c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249f13e2e230952f74004c9/</guid><description>A new TV documentary alleges that children as young as 10 are using machetes to harvest pods
Highlights Children as young as 10 are allegedly being forced to work long hours on cocoa farms in Ghana. Children were also filmed using sharp knives to open cocoa pods and swinging long sticks with blades tied to them to harvest the pods from the cocoa trees. Mondelēz International owns Cadbury, which made global profits last year of more than £3.</description></item><item><title>U.S. home sales tumble; higher prices, mortgage rates eroding affordability</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237cb804c9af8b7f4b860e4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237cb804c9af8b7f4b860e4/</guid><description>U.S. home sales fell by the most in a year in February as a perennial shortage of houses and double-digit price growth continued to squeeze first-time buyers out of the market.
Highlights Housing inventory drops 15.5% to 870,000 from year ago, down 155% from a year ago. Sales fell 7.2% to a seasonally adjusted annual rate of 6.02 million units last month. Mortgage rates are set to increase further after the Federal Reserve on Wednesday raised its policy interest rate by 25 basis points.</description></item><item><title>Mariupol under siege: 'We are being completely cut off'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62212f29183110b42cb8a023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62212f29183110b42cb8a023/</guid><description>Residents of the south-eastern city tell the BBC they are being cut off by relentless Russian shelling.
Highlights Residents of south-eastern city say they are being cut off by relentless Russian shelling. &amp;ldquo;There is still some bread at the shop near us, but we don&amp;rsquo;t know when the food supply will end,&amp;rdquo; one resident says. &amp;ldquo;What will happen when we run out of our water? What will happen to my phone battery die?</description></item><item><title>Americans should get ready for $5 a gallon gas, analyst warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220b2b5d6af769c0d7c69af/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 12:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220b2b5d6af769c0d7c69af/</guid><description>The cost of filling up your car is soaring across much of the U.S as the Ukraine crisis further drives up oil prices.
Highlights The cost of filling up your car is soaring across much of the U.S. as the Ukraine crisis further drives up oil prices. Oil prices continue to rise as the war with Ukraine intensifies, experts say. The current national average price of gas is $3.61 per gallon, up 26 cents from February and roughly a dollar from a year ago.</description></item><item><title>Intel and AMD suspended product deliveries to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b245ffc189aecd980ec06/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b245ffc189aecd980ec06/</guid><description>AMD and Intel have suspended deliveries of their products to Russia. This can lead to a shortage of computers, servers and other products, which will lead to higher prices. The Chinese office of Intel notified partners about introduction of a ban on the
Highlights AMD and Intel have suspended deliveries of their products to Russia. This is reported by RBC citing own sources. This can lead to a shortage of computers, servers and other products, which will lead to higher prices.</description></item><item><title>Texas says supply chain issues have limited the number of voter registration forms it can give out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e835b990b2251d6cee8128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 16:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e835b990b2251d6cee8128/</guid><description>The Texas League of Women Voters says this shortage is disproportionately affecting the thousands of newly naturalized citizens they usually register each year.
Summary The Texas Secretary of State’s office is having more trouble than usual getting enough voter registration cards to groups who help Texans register to vote. Either way, the League and their volunteers often ask for thousands of voter registration forms ahead of these ceremonies. Taylor said the Secretary of State’s office has been forced to limit each group to 1,000 to 2,000 registration forms per request.</description></item><item><title>Russian Jets Knock Out Water Supply In Syria's Idlib: "Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water..."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</guid><description>Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.
Summary Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.</description></item></channel></rss>