<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>homeless on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/homeless/</link><description>Recent content in homeless on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 04:16:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/homeless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mayor orders New York’s homeless camps dismantled ‘within two weeks’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fe51114fbb0e5908645e6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 04:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fe51114fbb0e5908645e6/</guid><description>Eric Adams says officials will place people in ‘healthy living conditions with wraparound services’ as homelessness debate swirls
Highlights Eric Adams says homeless people will be placed in &amp;lsquo;healthy living conditions&amp;rsquo; with wraparound services, he says. The number of people living in parks and on the streets is estimated at around 1,100. The issue of homelessness in New York has arisen amid a crime spike in the city and a series of high-profile violent attacks, though advocates point out that the city – and its homeless population – has been caught in a crisis over inadequate mental health services for many years.</description></item><item><title>New York City will begin removing homeless people from subways at night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 09:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</guid><description>Mayor says public fear of subways is driving riders from the system and announces more mental health support to homeless
Highlights New York leaders released a plan to strictly enforce rules on the New York City subway as part of an aggressive effort to remove homeless people from the city’s sprawling transit system. The plan comes in light of an uptick in felony assaults in the subway which, while rare, were up 25% in 2021 compared with 2019.</description></item></channel></rss>