<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>air on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/air/</link><description>Recent content in air on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 19:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/air/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4 Air Force cadets may not graduate due to vaccine refusal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ffef2302eef9713711edf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 19:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ffef2302eef9713711edf/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Four cadets at the Air Force Academy may not graduate or be commissioned as military officers this month because they have refused the COVID-19 vaccine, and they may be required to pay back thousands of dollars in tuition costs, according to Air Force officials.
Highlights Four cadets at the Air Force Academy may not graduate or be commissioned as military officers in May 2022. They may be required to pay back thousands of dollars in tuition costs.</description></item><item><title>Slovakia says it has given S-300 air defence system to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251943fe7a27e8d2bb113ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 14:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251943fe7a27e8d2bb113ba/</guid><description>Prime Minister Eduard Heger says donation does not mean the NATO member joined the war.
Highlights Slovakia has donated S-300 air defence system to Ukraine to help it defend against Russian attacks. The donation does not mean the country has joined the conflict, says the Prime Minister. The US has agreed to send weapons to Ukraine in response to Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. The United States has also pledged to send more weapons to the region, including the US Patriot missile system, to help with the Russian invasion of Crimea.</description></item><item><title>Guardsman says not being ‘feminine’ cost her a job. The government is fighting her lawsuit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218d6bf7e9858a2a49bfc87/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 13:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218d6bf7e9858a2a49bfc87/</guid><description>“I’m not done wearing the uniform. I feel that I have more to do,” said Kristin Kingrey, a technical sergeant and civilian employee in the West Virginia Air National Guard.
Highlights A West Virginia Air National Guard airman says she lost out on a job due to discrimination over her sexual orientation and her appearance. Kristin Kingrey is a masculine-presenting lesbian who wears her hair short and doesn’t bother with makeup.</description></item></channel></rss>