<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>summer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/summer/</link><description>Recent content in summer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 21:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. abortion rights activists start 'summer of rage' with Saturday protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62801b553f6a9e6023db2c58/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 21:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62801b553f6a9e6023db2c58/</guid><description>Thousands of abortion rights supporters rallied across the United States on Saturday to express their anger over fears the Roe v. Wade case that legalized abortion nationwide will be overturned by the U.S. Supreme Court.
Highlights Protests held across the U.S. over fears the Roe v. Wade case that legalized abortion nationwide will be overturned. Large gatherings in New York, Washington, Los Angeles and Chicago with some smaller counter-protests. The court&amp;rsquo;s final ruling, which could give states the power to ban abortion, is expected in June.</description></item><item><title>New government maps show nearly all of the West is in drought and it's not even summer yet: "This is unprecedented"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e9558a2248a51edafc57f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e9558a2248a51edafc57f/</guid><description>The latest government maps show 95% of California is suffering severe or extreme drought.
Highlights Southern California officials ask residents to limit outdoor watering to once a week. Nearly all of the West is in drought, and 95% of California is suffering severe or extreme drought. Lake Mead, the largest reservoir in the nation formed by the Hoover Dam on the Colorado River, needs a new pump to ensure water can flow to Las Vegas.</description></item><item><title>Ground Temperatures Hit 129 Degrees as Argentina Suffers Blackouts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfdc44a8cbc3a0a3bcdd6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfdc44a8cbc3a0a3bcdd6e/</guid><description>The country is suffering through a heat wave that knocked out power in Buenos Aires and challenged all-time records.
Summary Ground temperatures climbed above 129 degrees Fahrenheit (54 degrees Celsius) in parts of Argentina this week as the country suffers through a shockingly hot start to summer. Those temperatures are different than air temperatures, which is our usual way of conveying how hot a place is. On Tuesday, temperatures rose to 106.</description></item></channel></rss>