<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>day on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/day/</link><description>Recent content in day on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:11:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Pay or surrender him’: Woman forced to give up puppy over $10,000 veterinary bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a21b8053268ed89936f838/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a21b8053268ed89936f838/</guid><description>A woman is pleading to get her puppy back after she was forced to surrender him due to a medical bill.
Highlights Rachel Mullen said her puppy, Jaxx, needed emergency surgery to save his life. The bill came to $10,000, an amount that she couldn’t afford. The clinic told her she had to pay or surrender him. A spokesperson from the clinic’s corporate owner, Rarebreed Veterinary Partners, said when a person surrenders a pet, it&amp;rsquo;s a legally binding contract.</description></item><item><title>Rosaries, bouquets and tiny caskets: Uvalde begins to bury its dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295f7758062616263523ef6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295f7758062616263523ef6/</guid><description>In a Texas town scarred by gun massacre, anger and grief gives way to a relentless cycle of mourning as two weeks of funerals begin.
Highlights Funeral home in U.S. reopens for mourners for victims of U.N. school shooting. “There’s going to be a lot of tears and sadness, but as we continue to celebrate their lives, they will turn into tears of joy,” priest says. Funeral director: “It&amp;rsquo;s okay to be angry.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky man, 22, shoots mom after dispute over Xbox controller on Mother’s Day, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a9fe136294392194c0e03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 17:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a9fe136294392194c0e03/</guid><description>A Kentucky man has been arrested after shooting his mother on Mother’s Day following a dispute over an Xbox controller he gave her as a gift, officials say.
Highlights Jacob R. Small, of Monticello, Kentucky, was charged with attempted murder, first-degree assault and second-degree criminal mischief. Small told authorities he got into a verbal dispute with his mother over an Xbox controller he gave her as a Mother’s Day gift. The mother was treated at the Wayne County Hospital and transferred to the University of Kentucky Hospital for further treatment.</description></item><item><title>Italy Reports 70,520 Coronavirus Cases Today, 143 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626522ee29182268e6847435/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 10:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626522ee29182268e6847435/</guid><description>Italy reported 70,520 COVID-19 related cases on Saturday, against 73,212 the day before, the health ministry said, while the daily number of deaths fell to 143 from 202.
Highlights Italy reported 70,520 COVID-19 related cases on Saturday, against 73,212 the day before. The daily number of deaths fell to 143 from 202, Italy has registered 162,609 deaths linked to the outbreak. The country has reported 16.1 million cases to date, with 43 new admissions to intensive care units, decreasing from 46 on Friday.</description></item><item><title>Minneapolis Public Schools cancels classes again as teachers enter tenth day of strike</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238b2ba3b4d0b79b5547718/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 17:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238b2ba3b4d0b79b5547718/</guid><description>Minneapolis Public Schools (MPS) will remain closed Monday, with classes canceled for more than 30,000 students for the tenth day, as teachers continue a strike over wages and class sizes, a district spokesperson said.
Highlights The strike began March 8 as The Minneapolis Federation of Teachers (MFT) and Education Support Professionals (ESP) want to raise wages and smaller class sizes. The offer includes increasing starting wages for 85% of them to at least $23 per hour.</description></item><item><title>Dozens more graves found at former residential school sites</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e1fa125bbfbde8467d546/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 10:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e1fa125bbfbde8467d546/</guid><description>Indigenous-led investigations have discovered more than 1,100 unmarked graves in recent months.
Highlights Indigenous-led investigations have discovered more than 1,100 unmarked graves in recent months. Indigenous-lead investigations have found more than a million unmarked graves. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a very tough time,&amp;rdquo; says one of the people at the site of the unmarked graves, the man said. &amp;ldquo;We walk every day, drive every day,&amp;rdquo; says the man who led the investigation, who said it was a &amp;ldquo;very tough time&amp;rdquo; for his community to find the graves in the community.</description></item><item><title>British transport aircraft are now in their third day of delivering “thousands” of anti-tank weapons to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e85fca633a60cf9f75804c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e85fca633a60cf9f75804c/</guid><description>Summary British transport aircraft are now in their third day of delivering “thousands” of anti-tank weapons to Ukraine in the face of a massive build-up of Russian troops. Minister James Heappey told Times Radio that the Ministry of Defence has given “thousands” of anti-armour weapons to Ukraine. We have taken the decision to supply Ukraine with light, anti-armour, defensive weapon systems. This is a screenshot of flight tracking software showing two British C-17s in flight at various part of their journeys to and from Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>The United States records an average of 700,000 new cases per day; Fauci says the nation could grow to 1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 12:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</guid><description>Summary The country reported about 4.91 million cases in the week ending Saturday. “I would not be surprised at all if we go over a million cases per day,” Dr. Anthony Fauci, the president’s chief medical adviser, told News 4 New York in an interview Saturday. But Fauci told the TV station the dismal numbers could start to decline by month’s end. 📈Today’s numbers: The U.S. has recorded more than 60 million confirmed COVID-19 cases and more than 837,000 deaths, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description></item><item><title>Kosovo bans cryptocurrency mining after blackouts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d63f382b3a4dcd352d28de/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 01:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d63f382b3a4dcd352d28de/</guid><description>The Balkan country is enforcing blackouts amid an electricity shortage caused by high global prices.
Summary Concerned about the environmental impact of the practice, other countries such as China and Iran have cracked down on crypto mining. Last year, Iran announce a four-month ban because it was draining more than 2GW from the grid each day. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>US children hospitalized with COVID in record numbers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</guid><description>The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers
Summary The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbersSEATTLE &amp;ndash; The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers, and experts lament that most of the youngsters are not vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Chinese officials admitted Wednesday they have faced challenges getting enough supplies to residents in locked-down Xi'an, after the city's inhabitants took to social media to complain they didn't have enough food and call for help</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdbb7b0bffccb9c59fac81/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 14:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdbb7b0bffccb9c59fac81/</guid><description>Chinese officials admitted Wednesday they have faced challenges getting enough supplies to residents in locked-down Xi&amp;rsquo;an, after the city&amp;rsquo;s inhabitants took to social media to complain they didn&amp;rsquo;t ha…
Summary Beijing has followed a strict &amp;ldquo;zero Covid&amp;rdquo; strategy involving tight border restrictions and targeted lockdowns since the virus first surfaced in a central city in late 2019. Xi&amp;rsquo;an official Chen Jianfeng told reporters that the local government has mobilised enterprises to step up community distribution, with cadres supervising wholesale markets and supermarkets.</description></item><item><title>UK DJ Dimension becomes New Zealand's first Omicron community case after breaking quarantine rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd2eed5b3a592ea0807b3d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd2eed5b3a592ea0807b3d/</guid><description>On social media, UK drum and bass artist Dimension told followers he had tested positive for the Omicron variant while in New Zealand.
Summary UK DJ Dimension posted images of himself at a Waiheke Beach on Christmas Day. In a social media post late on Wednesday night, Dimension confirmed he had tested positive for the Omicron variant while in New Zealand. On social media, Dimension posted images of himself at a Waiheke Island beach on Christmas Day.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6. The ruling Wednesday comes one day after he asked a federal judge in Florida for a temporary restraining order, and it&amp;rsquo;s the first quick response to a lawsuit from a House witness, after several went to court to try to invalidate the committee and block the House from pursuing their phone records.</description></item></channel></rss>