<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>admits on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/admits/</link><description>Recent content in admits on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/admits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shooter entered school through propped open door, had over 1,600 rounds of ammunition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62916f8eda334519cf99d403/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62916f8eda334519cf99d403/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — Nearly 20 officers stood in a hallway outside of the classrooms during this week&amp;rsquo;s attack on a Texas elementary school for more than 45 minutes before agents used a master key to open a door and confront a gunman, authorities said Friday. Caption: News Conference: Texas Department of Public Safety Director Steven McCraw.
Highlights Nearly 20 officers stood in hallway outside of classrooms during attack on Texas elementary school.</description></item><item><title>BLM co-founder admits she held parties at mansion bought with donor funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bd2eef1dbe204e3793f09/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bd2eef1dbe204e3793f09/</guid><description>Black Lives Matter Co-Founder Patrisse Cullors admitted in an Associated Press interview she spent overnights and hosted multiple personal events at the group’s controversial Malibu mansion. Cullors’sstatements come after she claimed to have “never misappropriated funds” related to the Black Lives Matter Global Network Foundation’s (BLMGNF) purchase of a $6 million Malibu home with donor funds.
Highlights Patrisse Cullors admitted in an Associated Press interview she spent overnights and hosted multiple personal events at the group&amp;rsquo;s controversial Malibu mansion.</description></item></channel></rss>