<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>port on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/port/</link><description>Recent content in port on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/port/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passengers scream as world’s longest cruise ship crashes into Jamaican pier</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295bf58be8e95faa111cf69/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295bf58be8e95faa111cf69/</guid><description>Investigation launched into alleged accident
Highlights The Harmony of the Seas crashed into a pier in Falmouth, Jamaica, on Thursday morning. The 227,000 tonne vessel was trying to dock at the busy port on the country&amp;rsquo;s northern shore. Video of the crash has attracted more than 500,000 views on social media. No injuries were reported - although the vessel sustained &amp;lsquo;cosmetic&amp;rsquo; damage. Port Authority of Jamaica has launched an investigation into the incident.</description></item><item><title>A Russian oligarch's superyacht is stuck in Norway because no one will sell it fuel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232a78c6ecb8dcdcd1bde27/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232a78c6ecb8dcdcd1bde27/</guid><description>The Ragnar is owned by Russian oligarch Vladimir Strzhalkovsky, a former KGB agent with deep ties to Russian President Vladimir Putin. Onboard amenities include an amphibious ATV and an island.
Highlights The Ragnar is owned by Russian oligarch Vladimir Strzhalkovsky, a former KGB agent. The yacht is stuck in a port city in northern Norway because no one will sell it fuel. The Ragnar was custom-built on the hull of a former service ship capable of pushing its way through ice.</description></item></channel></rss>