<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bankruptcy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bankruptcy/</link><description>Recent content in bankruptcy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:13:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bankruptcy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alex Jones' attorney Norm Pattis asks to be dropped from Sandy Hook defamation case as trial looms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62998a4eedcb1dfda076937f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62998a4eedcb1dfda076937f/</guid><description>A Connecticut judge rejected a request that Alex Jones’ New Haven-based attorney be dropped from the defamation case he lost to Sandy Hook families.
Highlights Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; attorneys want to be dropped from a defamation case involving Sandy Hook families. Jones lost two defamation cases to Sandy Hook parents last year. Jones is seeking to forestall a similar damages award trial in Texas where he lost two other defamation cases. Jones has spent $10 million on attorneys fees and lost at least $20 million because of the Sandy Hook lawsuits, his representatives say.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families’ defamation damages trial against Alex Jones to move forward in CT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628daebfb0b099bc309dc2b2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:21:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628daebfb0b099bc309dc2b2/</guid><description>Representatives for Alex Jones and the Sandy Hook families reached an agreement in&amp;hellip;
Highlights A federal judge clears the way for Sandy Hook families to have the defamation lawsuit they won against Alex Jones released from bankruptcy protection. The families&amp;rsquo; target will be Jones himself and his parent company Free Speech Systems. A trial to determine the damages Jones must pay for calling the worst crime in Connecticut history “staged,’ “synthetic,” “manufactured,“ and “a giant hoax” A federal bankruptcy judge in Texas released Jones from Chapter 11 protection and sent his defamation cases back to state court in Texas.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families drop 3 Alex Jones companies from lawsuit and ask judge to return their case to trial court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270bae4eac07e9fb6d032f2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 05:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270bae4eac07e9fb6d032f2/</guid><description>An FBI agent and eight Sandy Hook families that won a defamation lawsuit against Alex&amp;hellip;
Highlights The families of two boys slain in the Sandy Hook massacre have dropped three defamation cases against Alex Jones. The families hope the cases will be returned to state court in Connecticut. Jones&amp;rsquo; Free Speech Systems did not file for bankruptcy, but his cases have been removed from state courts while a federal bankruptcy judge in Texas weighs the three cases.</description></item><item><title>Puerto Rico formally exits bankruptcy following largest public debt restructuring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230e520159c830fd7b4a0fe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 19:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230e520159c830fd7b4a0fe/</guid><description>Puerto Rico’s government formally exited bankruptcy Tuesday, completing the largest public debt restructuring in U.S. history.
Highlights Puerto Rico’s government will resume payments to bondholders for the first time in several years. Puerto Rico accumulated more than $70 billion in public debt through decades of corruption, mismanagement and excessive borrowing. The bankruptcy led to widely criticized austerity measures on an island that paid some $1 billion in fees to consultants and lawyers.</description></item></channel></rss>