<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wheat on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wheat/</link><description>Recent content in wheat on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 19:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wheat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lebanon faces food crisis with ‘no wheat orders since Ukraine war began’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62362ab5d61fcd74f8a3a478/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 19:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62362ab5d61fcd74f8a3a478/</guid><description>As global prices soar, millers tell ‘The National’ that suppliers have no interest in selling to cash-strapped Lebanon
Highlights Wheat prices have soared since the start of the war in Ukraine, one of the world’s largest producers. Lebanon normally buys 96 per cent of its wheat from Russia and Ukraine. Importers are struggling to get dollars from a subsidy programme to buy wheat from new suppliers. The cost of the country&amp;rsquo;s largely imported food increased by 2,076 per cent between 2018 and 2021 due to the crash of the local currency.</description></item><item><title>Arctic Seed Vault to Receive Rare Deposits</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a487c92e353c0dbaf25ae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 12:18:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a487c92e353c0dbaf25ae/</guid><description>A vault built on an Arctic mountainside to preserve the world&amp;rsquo;s crop seeds from catastrophes will receive new deposits, including one from the first organisation that made a withdrawal from the facility.
Highlights Svalbard facility is global back-up for seed banks designed to safeguard biodiversity of crops. Facility is on Spitsbergen island halfway between mainland Norway and the North Pole. On Monday, gene banks from Sudan, Uganda, New Zealand, Germany and Lebanon will deposit seeds.</description></item></channel></rss>