<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>users on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/users/</link><description>Recent content in users on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 04:17:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/users/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EU deal will push Google, Facebook, others to police platforms against hate speech, disinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264cf41f8f06fb43bfff2e1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264cf41f8f06fb43bfff2e1/</guid><description>European Union officials clinched the agreement in principle on the Digital Services Act after lengthy final negotiations that began Friday. The law will also force tech companies to make it easier for users to flag problems, ban online ads aimed at kids and empower regulators to punish noncompliance with billions in fines.
Highlights NEW: The Digital Services Act is one half of an overhaul for the 27-nation bloc’s digital rulebook. Big tech companies like Google and Facebook parent Meta will have to police their platforms more strictly to better protect European users from hate speech, disinformation and other harmful online content.</description></item><item><title>Twitch and OnlyFans block all users from Russia due to sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b94fc3eaadef89329f81b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 15:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b94fc3eaadef89329f81b/</guid><description>The Brother HL-L2375DW “4-star” printer at €129.99 (-16%) Aliexpress is already crushing the price of the Redmi Note 11. The Philips 3000 series XD3110
Highlights The Brother HL-L2375DW “4-star” printer at €129.99 (-16%) Aliexpress is already crushing the price of the Redmi Note 11. Windows 11 on incompatible PCs, Macs in anticipation and better photos at Samsung. The Philips 3000 series XD3110/09/09 vacuum cleaner with bag with bag is €84.99 - a good deal – The Philips 3/5/9/10 vacuum cleaner is €85.</description></item><item><title>Spotify stocks fall as executives seek to reassure amid Rogan controversy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc373f065a117e1de4baea/</guid><description>Subscriber outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter earnings as the company’s shares fell nearly 18% in late trading
Highlights Spotify forecast current-quarter subscribers lower than Wall Street expectations. Company&amp;rsquo;s shares fell as much as 18% in late trading after Spotify reported the subscriber outlook. The outlook overshadowed fourth-quarter revenue, which came in higher than analysts’ estimates. CEO Daniel Ek acknowledged the Joe Rogan controversy at the outset of the earnings conference call. He said he was proud of the steps Spotify took following the concerns raised by the medical and scientific communities and he said policies were developed with input from external and internal and external exports.</description></item><item><title>Meta shares plunge as Facebook owner misses on earnings, forecast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb72ede85b942e7d365927/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 06:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb72ede85b942e7d365927/</guid><description>Facebook owner Meta Platforms Inc&amp;rsquo;s shares plunged more than 20% late on Wednesday after the social media company posted a weaker-than-expected forecast, blaming Apple&amp;rsquo;s privacy changes and increased competition for users from rivals like TikTok.
Highlights Facebook owner Meta Platforms Inc&amp;rsquo;s (FB.O) shares plunged more than 20% late on Wednesday after the social media company posted a weaker-than-expected forecast. Facebook’s global daily active users declined from the previous quarter for the first time, to 1.</description></item><item><title>Thieves Steal Gallery Owner’s Multimillion-Dollar NFT Collection: 'All my apes gone'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7ad676d0d55e9b2c21d31/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 03:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7ad676d0d55e9b2c21d31/</guid><description>Dealer Ross Kramer said thieves had stolen his $2.2 million NFT collection.
Summary This just sold please help me,” wrote gallery owner Todd Kramer, of New York’s Ross + Kramer Gallery, in a since-deleted tweet posted on December 30. A phishing scam had drained his Ethereum wallet of 15 NFTs valued at a total of $2.2 million, including four apes from the “Bored Ape Yacht Club” collection. With the help of the buyers and the NFT platform OpenSea, Kramer was able to get back several of his NFTs.</description></item></channel></rss>