<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mexico on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mexico/</link><description>Recent content in mexico on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:11:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mexico/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mexico totally bans sales of e-cigarettes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62978185c8506c666b17fb73/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 15:11:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62978185c8506c666b17fb73/</guid><description>Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador has signed a decree outlawing the sale of e-cigarettes, continuing the government&amp;rsquo;s anti-vaping policy
Highlights Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador has signed a decree outlawing the sale of e-cigarettes. Mexico had already prohibited imports of the devices since at least October. Despite Tuesday’s decree, many Mexicans import or buy vaping cartridges or fluid under the table or online domestically. Assistant Health Secretary calls industry claims that vaping is safer than smoking &amp;ldquo;a big lie&amp;rdquo; The government estimates that at least 5 million Mexicans have tried vaping at least once, government&amp;rsquo;s own figures say 5 million have tried the device at the very hands of 5 million people in the country.</description></item><item><title>U.S. arrests 210,000 migrants at Mexico border in March, rivaling record highs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c142936b98669dd78eab0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 13:21:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c142936b98669dd78eab0/</guid><description>It is the highest monthly total in two decades, underscoring challenges for U.S. President Joe Biden.
Highlights March total is a 24% increase from the same month a year earlier, when 169,000 migrants were picked up at the border. It is the highest monthly total in two decades, underscoring challenges in the coming months for U.S. President Biden. More than half of the migrants encountered in March were from the traditional sending countries of Mexico, Guatemala, Honduras and El Salvador, according to a court filing on Friday night.</description></item><item><title>US allows Ukrainians fleeing war into the country through Mexico</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62343f956f77017bc65592e1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 08:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62343f956f77017bc65592e1/</guid><description>Mexican official says at least 310 Ukrainians have reached the northern border city of Tijuana by air this month.
Highlights Mexican official says at least 310 Ukrainians have reached the northern border city of Tijuana by air this month. The US-Mexico border has been closed to most asylum seekers under a pandemic-era policy known as Title 42. A US citizen who travelled to Ukraine to retrieve her cousin and her cousin’s child got them into the US after a trek that took them through Poland, Croatia, Hungary, Amsterdam, Mexico City and then Tijuana.</description></item><item><title>Mexico deports 'El Huevo,' suspected drug gang leader, to U.S. after arrest sparks attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623252b8a80217b45bfb32b1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 21:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623252b8a80217b45bfb32b1/</guid><description>Mexico deported the suspected leader of a drug gang to the U.S., authorities said on Tuesday, after an arrest that spurred armed attacks by his organization on almost two dozen military installations and a U.S. consulate.
Highlights Juan Trevino, also known as “El Huevo” or “The Egg,” was arrested on Sunday in the northern Mexican border state of Tamaulipas. He was wanted in connection with crimes that included drug trafficking and money laundering.</description></item><item><title>New Mexico's governor just signed a bill to make college tuition-free</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227b900ba42a6509c3b5bf5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 20:19:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227b900ba42a6509c3b5bf5/</guid><description>For most New Mexico residents, college will now be officially tuition-free after Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham signed Senate Bill 140. Many states across the country have moved to provide some sort of tuition-free college education.
Highlights Gov. Michelle Lujan Grisham signed on Friday Senate Bill 140, otherwise known as the New Mexico Opportunity Scholarship Act. The plan will waive tuition for students attending any in-state public school or tribal college, including community colleges.</description></item><item><title>All 21 people who were trapped in New Mexico tramway overnight have been rescued</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2046b619783975541b952/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2046b619783975541b952/</guid><description>Officials have rescued 21 people who were trapped on the Sandia Peak Tramway in Albuquerque, New Mexico for more than 12 hours during icy conditions Friday night.
Summary (CNN) Officials have rescued 21 people who were trapped on the Sandia Peak Tramway in Albuquerque, New Mexico for more than 12 hours during icy conditions Friday night. &amp;ldquo;We are happy to report that at this time all people needing rescue from the Tram cars have been rescued and are safely at base,&amp;rdquo; the Bernalillo County Fire Department said on Twitter.</description></item></channel></rss>