<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prince on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/prince/</link><description>Recent content in prince on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/prince/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge slaps down attempt to halt Prince Andrew's sexual assault case</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d0f92f04a163ebd72ac347/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d0f92f04a163ebd72ac347/</guid><description>A JUDGE in the US has denied a motion from lawyers for the Duke of York to halt proceedings in a civil lawsuit against Prince Andrew while an issue…
Summary A JUDGE in the US has denied a motion from lawyers for the Duke of York to halt proceedings in a civil lawsuit against Prince Andrew while an issue of where his accuser lives is dealt with. Earlier this week Andrew’s lawyers had called for the case against the royal in the US to be stopped because Virginia Giuffre is “actually domiciled in Australia”.</description></item><item><title>Man killed in front of his 3 kids, girlfriend in potential Christmas Eve road rage shooting</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c8e5fbdb916eb1f48dca84/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c8e5fbdb916eb1f48dca84/</guid><description>A man was driving with his girlfriend and three kids, heading to a Christmas Eve gathering, when he was shot dead in a possible road rage incident.
Summary A man was driving with his girlfriend and three kids, heading to a Christmas Eve gathering, when he was shot dead in a possible road rage incident, police in Maryland said. The suspect&amp;rsquo;s car apparently pulled up next to Kelly&amp;rsquo;s SUV and someone in the suspect&amp;rsquo;s car fired, police said.</description></item></channel></rss>