<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>neil on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/neil/</link><description>Recent content in neil on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 02:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/neil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spotify Agrees to Pull Neil Young’s Music After His Criticism of Joe Rogan’s Podcast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1fcbc90c7cdece1b33f4a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1fcbc90c7cdece1b33f4a/</guid><description>Young accused Spotify of “spreading fake information about vaccines” by hosting The Joe Rogan Experience
Summary Now, Spotify has agreed to pull Young’s work from streaming, according to a statement from a Spotify spokesperson. “Spotify has recently become a very damaging force via its public misinformation and lies about COVID,” Young wrote. These young people believe Spotify would never present grossly unfactual information. In his original letter, Young accused Spotify of “potentially causing death to those who believe the disinformation being spread by them.</description></item><item><title>Neil Young Wants His Music Off Spotify Over Joe Rogan Vaccine Misinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 07:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</guid><description>Neil Young demanded that Spotify remove his music, citing its spread of vaccine misinformation via &amp;quot;The Joe Rogan Experience&amp;quot; podcast.
Summary Neil Young wants his music pulled from Spotify, citing the spread of vaccine misinformation on the popular Joe Rogan Experience podcast as the cause. “They can have Rogan or Young. Not both,” Young wrote in an open letter to his management team and record label posted to his Neil Young Archives website, according to Rolling Stone.</description></item></channel></rss>