<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>israel on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/israel/</link><description>Recent content in israel on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 16:20:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/israel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israel denounced Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov for suggesting that Nazi leader Adolf Hitler had Jewish roots, and demanded an apology from Moscow</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627004ad3a8ef829637c910f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 16:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627004ad3a8ef829637c910f/</guid><description>Israel lambasted Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov on Monday for claiming that Adolf Hitler had Jewish origins, saying it was an &amp;quot;unforgivable&amp;quot; falsehood that debased the horrors of the Nazi Holocaust.
Highlights Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov says Adolf Hitler had Jewish origins. Israeli foreign ministry summons Russian ambassador and demands apology. Claims were made in a signal of sharply deteriorating relations with Moscow. Ukraine says Russia is &amp;ldquo;full of hatred&amp;rdquo; for other nations.</description></item><item><title>Israel settler opens fire at Palestine primary school in West Bank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230747b0743f306954a0180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 11:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230747b0743f306954a0180/</guid><description>An armed Israeli Jewish settler opened gunfire at a Palestinian girls&amp;rsquo; primary school in the occupied West Bank city of Bethlehem. Hundreds of students were evacuated and classes were cancelled following the attack. Violence and vandalism by Israeli settlers is commonplace in the
Highlights An armed Israeli Jewish settler opened gunfire at a Palestinian girls&amp;rsquo; primary school in the occupied West Bank city of Bethlehem. Hundreds of students were evacuated and classes were cancelled in the aftermath of the attack.</description></item><item><title>Health Ministry formally bans LGBTQ+ conversion therapy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b1a1794b30a60a7c155f8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b1a1794b30a60a7c155f8/</guid><description>While the Health Ministry has recommended against conversion therapy for years, this is the first formal ban.
Highlights Health Ministry issues circular banning medical professionals in Israel from providing conversion therapy. Licensed professionals who do so will face sanctions, including severe disciplinary proceedings and the revocation of their licenses. The circular stresses the risks to mental health posed by conversion therapy and prohibits all professionals from the offering, publicizing, or providing such &amp;ldquo;therapies&amp;rdquo; The circular defines conversion therapy as any therapy given in consultation or consultation which has the goal of changing the identity or sexual identity of a person.</description></item><item><title>Israel to open first LGBT shelter for Arab youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201dfc784df80ceb5249e0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201dfc784df80ceb5249e0d/</guid><description>Lawmaker hopes move will ‘break taboos’ * Two centers for LGBT Arab Israeli adults to open in Haifa
Highlights Israel is set to open its first shelter designated for LGBT Arab Israeli youth, in a move hailed as “historic” by one of the lawmakers who led the initiative. The new shelter will be established in an area with a large Arab population, though the exact location has not yet been decided.</description></item></channel></rss>