<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>business on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/business/</link><description>Recent content in business on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 08:21:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goldman Sachs is the 1st major Wall Street bank to pull out of Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b065fdef8228ac39d2442/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 08:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b065fdef8228ac39d2442/</guid><description>Goldman Sachs says it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;winding down its business in Russia in compliance with regulatory and licensing requirements,&amp;quot; two weeks after the country first invaded Ukraine.
Highlights Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan Chase are pulling out of Russia. Goldman Sachs is &amp;ldquo;winding down its business in compliance with regulatory and licensing requirements,&amp;rdquo; a spokesperson says. JPMorgan Chase continues to conduct limited business in the country. Western Union says it&amp;rsquo;s suspending operations in Russia and Belarus &amp;ldquo;in light of the ongoing tragic impact of Russia&amp;rsquo;s prolonged assault on Ukraine&amp;rdquo; The move comes a year after Citi announced that it would exit its consumer banking business in Russia, a dozen other countries, and other financial services companies say they&amp;rsquo;re working on exit strategies.</description></item><item><title>Two top Russian billionaires speak out against invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</guid><description>Oleg Deripaska and Ukrainian-born Mikhail Fridman call for peace, as activities come under threat from sanctions
Highlights Russian billionaires Mikhail Fridman and Oleg Deripaska speak out against Moscow’s invasion of Ukraine. In a letter to his employees he called for an end to the “bloodshed” in an email to staff at LetterOne. He joins a small group of prominent Russians – including popular actors, musicians and television presenters – who have called on President Vladimir Putin stop the military operation in Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>