<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>business on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/business/</link><description>Recent content in business on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 09:15:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business owner and sons charged for zip-tying, kidnapping and assaulting alleged thief for 45 minutes before law enforcement arrived</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ca0edeecd2d29d339818f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 09:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ca0edeecd2d29d339818f/</guid><description>A 50-year-old business owner and his two sons were arrested after they turned themselves in for an incident that happened in late April in which the Kern County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said they assaulted a burglary suspect from the father&amp;rsquo;s northwest Bakersfield business. On April 27, around 3 a. m. deputies were called to the area of Meany Avenue and Alken Street for a report of a business burglary at Sparks Custom Pools.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba lays off 40% of AliExpress Russia staff amid Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280e0192bfbb6f009e7a3ec/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280e0192bfbb6f009e7a3ec/</guid><description>AliExpress Russia, a joint venture launched in 2019 by Alibaba and Russian partners, operates domestic and cross-border transactions.
Highlights Alibaba Group Holding laid off about 40% of staff in Russian joint venture. China e-commerce giant could not be immediately reached for comment. Company depends on cross-border sales for more than three-quarters of its business. It has been slower to benefit from a pandemic-led ecommerce boom as supply chains adjust to new travel curbs.</description></item><item><title>Barclays avoids almost £2bn in tax via Luxembourg scheme</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279763f019e4dd2789c4945/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 20:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279763f019e4dd2789c4945/</guid><description>Exclusive: Arrangement has allowed bank to earn billions of pounds nearly tax-free for over 12 years
Highlights Barclays has avoided nearly £2bn in tax via a lucrative arrangement in Luxembourg that allowed it to pay less than 1% on profits in the tax haven for more than a decade. Labour MP Margaret Hodge: &amp;lsquo;These revelations that Barclays is using a scheme in an infamous tax haven leaves the British-headquartered bank with important questions to answer&amp;rsquo; The bank has 46,000 staff in the UK and nearly 10,000 in the US.</description></item><item><title>New Mexico launches cannabis sales, within Texans' reach.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246fea128559aa6b6799c4f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 13:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246fea128559aa6b6799c4f/</guid><description>SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — New Mexico is bringing sales of recreational marijuana to the doorstep of Texas, the largest prohibition state, as the movement toward broad legalization sweeps up even more of the American West.
Highlights New Mexico is bringing sales of recreational marijuana to the doorstep of Texas, the largest prohibition state, as the movement toward broad legalization sweeps up even more of the American West. “It’s going to be like getting a cup of joe at Starbucks,” said Henson, a former real estate agent who says his affection for marijuana was a burden in the past.</description></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs is the 1st major Wall Street bank to pull out of Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b065fdef8228ac39d2442/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 08:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b065fdef8228ac39d2442/</guid><description>Goldman Sachs says it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;quot;winding down its business in Russia in compliance with regulatory and licensing requirements,&amp;quot; two weeks after the country first invaded Ukraine.
Highlights Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan Chase are pulling out of Russia. Goldman Sachs is &amp;ldquo;winding down its business in compliance with regulatory and licensing requirements,&amp;rdquo; a spokesperson says. JPMorgan Chase continues to conduct limited business in the country. Western Union says it&amp;rsquo;s suspending operations in Russia and Belarus &amp;ldquo;in light of the ongoing tragic impact of Russia&amp;rsquo;s prolonged assault on Ukraine&amp;rdquo; The move comes a year after Citi announced that it would exit its consumer banking business in Russia, a dozen other countries, and other financial services companies say they&amp;rsquo;re working on exit strategies.</description></item><item><title>Two top Russian billionaires speak out against invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</guid><description>Oleg Deripaska and Ukrainian-born Mikhail Fridman call for peace, as activities come under threat from sanctions
Highlights Russian billionaires Mikhail Fridman and Oleg Deripaska speak out against Moscow’s invasion of Ukraine. In a letter to his employees he called for an end to the “bloodshed” in an email to staff at LetterOne. He joins a small group of prominent Russians – including popular actors, musicians and television presenters – who have called on President Vladimir Putin stop the military operation in Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>