<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukrainians on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukrainians/</link><description>Recent content in ukrainians on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:21:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukrainians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US decries ‘disturbing’ accounts of Ukrainians deported to Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62386dbb33af1d4c46869b8b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:21:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62386dbb33af1d4c46869b8b/</guid><description>US ambassador to the UN says it would be ‘unconscionable for Russia to force Ukrainian citizens into Russia’.
Highlights US ambassador to the UN says it would be ‘unconscionable’ for Russia to force Ukrainian citizens into Russia’ Linda Thomas-Greenfield: Accounts that thousands of residents of Ukraine’s besieged port city of Mariupol have been forcibly deported to Russia are ‘disturbing’ and “unconscusable” if true, if true. The US supports efforts to mediate a ceasefire in Ukraine, which has led to more than 900 civilian deaths and nearly 1,500 injuries.</description></item><item><title>Canada prepared to welcome an unlimited number of Ukrainians fleeing war, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622248ec8170757842306465/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 17:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622248ec8170757842306465/</guid><description>Immigration Minister Sean Fraser announced Thursday the federal government has created two new pathways for Ukrainians fleeing their war-torn country to come to Canada — part of a plan to accept an &amp;quot;unlimited number&amp;quot; of people who want to leave.
Highlights Immigration Minister Sean Fraser announced Thursday the federal government has created two new pathways for Ukrainians fleeing their war-torn country to come to Canada. Some critics, including NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh, have called on the government to drop the visa requirement altogether to allow all Ukrainians to travel to Canada unencumbered.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: UK will stand 'shoulder to shoulder' with Kyiv but 'extremely unlikely' to send troops, deputy PM Dominic Raab says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee40740dc840c9ca99bd5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 06:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee40740dc840c9ca99bd5c/</guid><description>Russian troops are mounting on the Ukraine border and the Foreign Office has accused Moscow of plotting to install a puppet leader in Kyiv. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to the UK has vowed to &amp;quot;fight to the death&amp;quot;.
Summary The UK will stand &amp;ldquo;shoulder to shoulder&amp;rdquo; with Ukraine but it is &amp;ldquo;extremely unlikely&amp;rdquo; British troops will be sent to the Russian border, Dominic Raab has said. The deputy prime minister said the UK and other nations will enforce economic and financial sanctions on Moscow if Russia invades Ukraine - as troops mount at the border.</description></item></channel></rss>