<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>employee on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employee/</link><description>Recent content in employee on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 03:43:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/employee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Report: Elon Musk exposed himself to SpaceX flight attendant, according to documents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870e2f0fa7953f0335d28d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 03:43:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870e2f0fa7953f0335d28d/</guid><description>The billionaire tech mogul allegedly offered a severance package worth $250,000 to a&amp;hellip;
Highlights Business Insider obtained documents from a flight attendant. They say Musk allegedly offered her $250,000 to pay for an erotic massage. Musk has yet to respond to the allegations. The publication reached out to the media for comment. The payment included non-disclosure clauses that barred the attendant from mentioning the incidents or disclosing information about SpaceX or Musk&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the alleged incident, the report says.</description></item><item><title>Home Depot employee arrested for swapping store cash with counterfeit bills for years, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff3cc3973cad27de13f433/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 03:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff3cc3973cad27de13f433/</guid><description>A Tempe, Arizona, Home Depot employee is facing a federal charge, after authorities said he repeatedly took cash from the store and replaced it with counterfeit currency before depositing it in the bank, according to a criminal complaint.
Highlights Adrian Jean Pineda, a vault employee at the store, was responsible for counting cash and preparing it for deposit. He is accused of ordering counterfeit bills from Amazon, swapping them with money taken from store cash registers and sealing them in bags for transfer to the bank.</description></item><item><title>Ontario spent $133,866 trying to fire employee over alleged $2.99 theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd6c818dd457b34b3e027d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd6c818dd457b34b3e027d/</guid><description>The city of Ontario spent almost $134,000 in legal fees in its failed attempt to fire a civilian police records specialist. Gricelda Perez was accused of stealing a $2.99 energy bar from a convenience store in 2018.
Highlights Ontario spent almost $134,000 in legal fees in its failed attempt to fire a civilian police records specialist. Gricelda Perez was accused of stealing a $2.99 energy bar from a convenience store in 2018.</description></item></channel></rss>