<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ford on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ford/</link><description>Recent content in ford on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:18:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ford/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ford, GM to halt production at two Michigan plants due to parts shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624733bbd66db14bbfec9a70/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624733bbd66db14bbfec9a70/</guid><description>Ford Motor Co and General Motors will each halt production next week at a Michigan plant due to parts shortages, the two companies said separately on Thursday.
Highlights Ford Motor Co and General Motors will each halt production next week at a Michigan plant due to parts shortages. The auto industry is grappling with a global chip shortage triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic, forcing companies to cut production. Ford said it would suspend production at its Flat Rock Assembly Plant next week, where it builds the Mustang, due to the global semiconductor shortage.</description></item><item><title>Auburn man arrested for leaving flowers at fiancé's grave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057fa87d384d8a5f85ebf5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057fa87d384d8a5f85ebf5/</guid><description>An arrest warrant for Winchester Hagans is signed by his fiancés father Tom Ford. The charge: littering.
Highlights Winchester Hagans lost his fiancé, Hannah Ford, in a car crash in January 2021. She died one month after he proposed to her. Hagans built a flower box filled with her favorite flowers and decorated it with pictures of the two of them to put by her grave. Last month, Hagans was arrested for littering after putting the box of flowers on her grave.</description></item><item><title>Chip shortage forces Ford to cut production of F-150, Bronco and other important vehicles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff58ba9fc01e3cd1cc393f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 05:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff58ba9fc01e3cd1cc393f/</guid><description>The cuts come a day after Ford significantly missed Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s earnings expectations due to supply chain issues, sending shares to tumble 9.7% on Friday.
Highlights Ford Bronco, Explorer, F-150, Ranger, Mustang Mach-E, Lincoln Aviator SUV among key products. Production downtime is due to an ongoing global shortage of semiconductor chips. The cuts come a day after Ford significantly missed Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s earnings expectations due to lower-than-expected production caused by the supply chain issues, causing shares to tumble 9.</description></item><item><title>Ford recalls nearly 185,000 F-150s for defect that can cause drivers to lose control of the vehicle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</guid><description>A new recall affects close to 185,000 F-150 pickups from the 2021 and 2022 model years.
Summary Ford Motor Company is recalling nearly 185,000 F-150s from the 2021 and 2022 model years for a defect that can cause a fractured driveshaft. Ford reports that insulators on the underbody of the trucks can loosen and contact the aluminum driveshaft, rubbing and scoring it. Operators may observe a loose underbody insulator, or hear a rattling, clicking or clunking noise due to a loose underbody insulator contacting the driveshaft.</description></item></channel></rss>