<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>custody on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/custody/</link><description>Recent content in custody on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 23:14:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/custody/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multiple People Hit in Shooting at Laguna Woods Church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281892ae15ab0452fcce0a6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 23:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281892ae15ab0452fcce0a6/</guid><description>Multiple people were hit in a shooting at Geneva Presbyterian Church in the Laguna Woods area of Orange County. A suspected shooter is in custody and a gun has&amp;hellip;
Highlights At least five people have been injured in a shooting at a church in Laguna Woods, Orange County. The suspected shooter is in police custody, but the motive for the shooting is not yet known. Thirty to 40 witnesses will need to be interviewed, including people who were inside the church at the time.</description></item><item><title>Wife filled husband’s phone with child porn in attempt to get custody of children, Oklahoma police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d8717b400df1050cc609c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 22:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d8717b400df1050cc609c/</guid><description>Police say Lacey Hucks, 33, the wife, and Angel Moore, 44, are alleged to have worked together to frame her husband. Hucks allegedly drove Moore to the police station and had her turn the phone in and file
Highlights Police say they found hundreds of images of child pornography in the home of Lacey Hucks and her husband. They say they planned to frame the husband in order to get him out of the picture.</description></item><item><title>Young mother killed after accidentally shot by toddler playing with gun; father in custody</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f40d05104a89dd8c1315d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 13:19:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f40d05104a89dd8c1315d/</guid><description>Police said a 3-year-old boy got hold of a gun in the back seat of his parent&amp;rsquo;s car and began playing with the weapon when it discharged.
Highlights Police say a 3-year-old boy got hold of a gun in the back seat of his parent&amp;rsquo;s car and began playing with the weapon. It discharged, hitting his mother, Dejah Bennet, 22, in the neck. She died a short time later. The boy&amp;rsquo;s father, who was also present at the time of the shooting, is now in custody as police determine whether there are any charges to be filed against him.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated New Brunswick dad loses custody of at-risk child</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fddd6474a012ed43774f97/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 02:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fddd6474a012ed43774f97/</guid><description>A New Brunswick father who is refusing to be vaccinated against COVID-19 has lost his right to see his immunocompromised child in person.
Highlights A New Brunswick father has lost his right to see his immunocompromised child and his two other children in person. He refused to be vaccinated against the deadly virus COVID-19 vaccine. The parents and the children are not named in the 26-page court ruling. The decision is the first written ruling of its kind in the province and will serve as a precedent for other cases.</description></item></channel></rss>