<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>patrol on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/patrol/</link><description>Recent content in patrol on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 17:14:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/patrol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spain intercepts fishing boat with 3 metric tons of cocaine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c4af182101fb879718d90/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 17:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c4af182101fb879718d90/</guid><description>MADRID (AP) — Spanish police have detained a fishing boat loaded with nearly three metric tons (3.3 short tons) of cocaine south of the Canary Islands, authorities said Sunday. The police intercepted the 20-meter-long (65-foot-long) vessel called the AKT 1 on Wednesday around 300 nautical miles (555 kilometers) south of the Spanish archipelago located in the Atlantic Ocean off west Africa.
Highlights Police intercepted the 20-meter-long (65-foot-long) vessel called the AKT 1 on Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>On-duty police officer accused of selling cocaine from patrol car, DEA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e0f79c3c4ea5693f6f939/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 12:20:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e0f79c3c4ea5693f6f939/</guid><description>According to the Drug Enforcement Administration, Kevin Rodriguez, 33 with the Raleigh Police Department, allegedly met with a confidential source for a drug exchange on Jan. 24, 2022.
Highlights Kevin Rodriguez, 33, with the Raleigh Police Department, allegedly met with a confidential source for a drug exchange on Jan. 24, 2022. The DEA said the confidential source gave Rodriguez $2,600 in cash for about 56 grams of cocaine. Rodriguez faces a mandatory minimum penalty of 5 years in prison if convicted, and a maximum of life in prison.</description></item></channel></rss>