<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>minister on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/minister/</link><description>Recent content in minister on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 17:17:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/minister/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trudeau makes surprise visit to Kyiv as Russia readies ‘Victory Day’ show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277fafcf12bbf65c4cda410/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277fafcf12bbf65c4cda410/</guid><description>During the visit, he is expected to meet in person with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy as Ukrainian forces continue to push back Russian soldiers.
Highlights Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has just made a surprise visit to the Ukrainian capital of Kyiv. The brief trip was supposed to be kept under wraps until after Trudeau left. During the visit, he is expected to meet in person with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy as Ukrainian forces continue to push back Russian soldiers in a stunning show of courage and defiance that has galvanized supporters around the world.</description></item><item><title>Northern Ireland election results: Sinn Féin wins most seats in historic election</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627789c4e1afacbeb0c28fbe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 09:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627789c4e1afacbeb0c28fbe/</guid><description>The party has won 27 seats in the Stormont assembly election, while the DUP returned with 25.
Highlights The party has won 27 seats in the Stormont assembly election. The DUP won the election with 25 seats, while the DUP won 25 seats. The party won 27 of the 27 seats, with the DUP winning 25, in the poll. It is now incumbent on all political parties and elected representatives to deliver on their mandate.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy urges Russian troops not to fight</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e7b88f638ac8553fbedbf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e7b88f638ac8553fbedbf/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine &amp;ndash; Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy switched into Russian in his nightly video address to urge Russian soldiers not to fight in Ukraine, saying even their generals expected that thousands of them would die.
Highlights Sweden says a Russian military plane has violated Swedish airspace. Up to 1,000 civilians are living beneath a Soviet-era steel plant in Mariupol, Ukrainian officials say. Russia has been recruiting new troops “with little motivation and little combat experience” for units gutted during the early weeks of the war.</description></item><item><title>Moldova officially applies for EU membership</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622176b0d5033dd467ff6d5a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 02:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622176b0d5033dd467ff6d5a/</guid><description>Russia’s invasion of Ukraine has triggered fears among ex-Soviet countries that they may be next.
Highlights Moldova and Georgia formally apply for membership of the European Union. Announcement comes a week after Russia’s invasion of Ukraine began. The West has expressed concerns that ex-Soviet nations risk becoming possible targets for the Kremlin after Ukraine. Efforts from the West to build closer ties with the West have long angered Russia. Moscow is fiercely opposed to the eastwards expansion of the EU and NATO, which it sees as a direct threat to Russia&amp;rsquo;s security.</description></item><item><title>Germany finally gives Estonia permission to send weapons to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ba3ce6e3272743c577ee3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ba3ce6e3272743c577ee3/</guid><description>Germany has granted Estonia permission to send weapons, formerly owned by the country, to Ukraine, media outlets Die Zeit and Deutsche Welle reported on Saturday. Prime Minister Kaja Kallas has confirmed the news.
Highlights Germany has granted Estonia permission to send weapons, formerly owned by the country, to Ukraine. Estonia sought permission from Germany and Finland more than a month ago. Prime Minister Kaja Kallas (Reform) confirmed the move on Saturday evening.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau ends use of Emergencies Act, says 'situation is no longer an emergency' | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62172276127997f9cadaffbb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 06:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62172276127997f9cadaffbb/</guid><description>Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is revoking the use of the Emergencies Act, the powerful legislative tool that was deployed in response to protests and blockades that erupted in Ottawa and at border crossings over recent weeks.
Highlights Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is revoking the use of the Emergencies Act. The act was used in response to protests and blockades that erupted in Ottawa and at border crossings over recent weeks. The Governor General signed off on the revocation on Wednesday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Israel's public security minister says attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank are 'organised terrorism'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efae34ea46e77b35f64bcf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 08:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efae34ea46e77b35f64bcf/</guid><description>Israel&amp;rsquo;s public security minister has described attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank as &amp;lsquo;organised terrorism&amp;rsquo;.
Summary Israel&amp;rsquo;s public security minister has described attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank as &amp;lsquo;organised terrorism&amp;rsquo;. An Israeli minister has described on Monday attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank as &amp;ldquo;organised terrorism&amp;rdquo;. Barlev sparked uproar last month when he criticised a wave of violence by West Bank settlers against Palestinians in the West Bank.</description></item><item><title>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</guid><description>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine
Summary In response to the increasing Russian threat around Ukraine, the Netherlands is sending two F-35 fighter aircraft to Bulgaria. The two F-35s will participate in a NATO mission that has been ongoing for years to monitor the skies of Eastern Europe. The Netherlands also offers an amphibious transport ship (including landing craft and helicopters) and two ‘land-bound units’ (Ollongren does not specify which) for the NATO Response Force.</description></item><item><title>Calls grow for UK PM to resign over lockdown ‘parties’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e30bd81755f9952bbfc7b4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e30bd81755f9952bbfc7b4/</guid><description>Staff at Downing Street held ‘wine-time Fridays’ during coronavirus lockdowns, according to new revelations.
Summary Calls are growing for British Prime Minister Boris Johnson to resign after more revelations came to light about regular parties organised at Downing Street that broke COVID-19 lockdown rules, with Labour party leader Keir Starmer saying Johnson was “unable to lead”. In response, a Downing Street spokeswoman said the government was awaiting Gray’s inquiry “to establish the facts around the nature of gatherings” during the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>