<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>minister on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/minister/</link><description>Recent content in minister on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 08:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/minister/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israel's public security minister says attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank are 'organised terrorism'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efae34ea46e77b35f64bcf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 08:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efae34ea46e77b35f64bcf/</guid><description>Israel&amp;rsquo;s public security minister has described attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank as &amp;lsquo;organised terrorism&amp;rsquo;.
Summary Israel&amp;rsquo;s public security minister has described attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank as &amp;lsquo;organised terrorism&amp;rsquo;. An Israeli minister has described on Monday attacks by Israeli settlers in the occupied West Bank as &amp;ldquo;organised terrorism&amp;rdquo;. Barlev sparked uproar last month when he criticised a wave of violence by West Bank settlers against Palestinians in the West Bank.</description></item><item><title>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</guid><description>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine
Summary In response to the increasing Russian threat around Ukraine, the Netherlands is sending two F-35 fighter aircraft to Bulgaria. The two F-35s will participate in a NATO mission that has been ongoing for years to monitor the skies of Eastern Europe. The Netherlands also offers an amphibious transport ship (including landing craft and helicopters) and two ‘land-bound units’ (Ollongren does not specify which) for the NATO Response Force.</description></item><item><title>Calls grow for UK PM to resign over lockdown ‘parties’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e30bd81755f9952bbfc7b4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e30bd81755f9952bbfc7b4/</guid><description>Staff at Downing Street held ‘wine-time Fridays’ during coronavirus lockdowns, according to new revelations.
Summary Calls are growing for British Prime Minister Boris Johnson to resign after more revelations came to light about regular parties organised at Downing Street that broke COVID-19 lockdown rules, with Labour party leader Keir Starmer saying Johnson was “unable to lead”. In response, a Downing Street spokeswoman said the government was awaiting Gray’s inquiry “to establish the facts around the nature of gatherings” during the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>