<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>flight on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/flight/</link><description>Recent content in flight on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 04:19:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/flight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. agency refers 80 unruly airplane passengers for potential prosecution</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 04:19:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dcbc4e741cebc1f14b8f2/</guid><description>A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) said on Wednesday, as onboard disruptions rose sharply in 2021, many over COVID-19 mask requirements.
Highlights A total of 80 unruly airplane passengers have been referred to the FBI for potential criminal prosecution, the Federal Aviation Administration said on Wednesday. The Justice Department said Wednesday it was prosecuting a record number of passengers for interfering with flight crews.</description></item><item><title>A large Russian cargo plane took a lengthy, unexpected, and unexplained route over central and southern Finland on Saturday night, passing over Finland's Air Force headquarters and a military intelligence unit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7003a1a2afff60d9e9272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7003a1a2afff60d9e9272/</guid><description>The incident comes as political tensions continue to rise in the Baltic region.
Summary A large Russian cargo plane took an lengthy, unexpected and unexplained route over central and southern Finland on Saturday night, passing over Finland&amp;rsquo;s Air Force headquarters and a military intelligence unit. The cargo plane took off from Moscow at about 7.26pm Finnish time on Saturday evening and flew towards the city of Murmansk in northwestern Russia. The cargo plane also passed close to the Halli military airport in Jämsä, Central Finland.</description></item></channel></rss>