<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>daily on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/daily/</link><description>Recent content in daily on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/daily/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unvaccinated People Ordered to Stay Home or Face Jail in Philippines' Capital Manila</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4a76e739e6722aeed5579/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4a76e739e6722aeed5579/</guid><description>After weeks of its lowest caseloads in the pandemic, the Philippines’ capital region is seeing a frightening rise in coronavirus infections.
Summary Under the order, unvaccinated people must stay at home except to buy essential goods or for medical purposes. Some officials criticized the council’s stay-at-home order for unvaccinated people, noting that even vaccinated people can contract and transmit the virus. “The recent exponential COVID-19 surge in Metro Manila happened even when 102 percent of the target population is already vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Florida reports 46,923 new coronavirus cases, shattering state daily record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd6722f3238650c09f2f4f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd6722f3238650c09f2f4f/</guid><description>Florida&amp;rsquo;s 46,923 new daily coronavirus cases shattered the state record for residents and became the third state in the nation to pass 4 million infections, according to data submitted to the Centers for Disease Control. Also, hospitalizations have risen to 3,836, the highest in 2 1/2 months.
Summary The first cases were reported in Florida on March 1, 2020. Twice week a CDC revises new daily cases in data provided by the state.</description></item></channel></rss>