<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>selling on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/selling/</link><description>Recent content in selling on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 07:14:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/selling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etsy sellers protest fees by halting their sales for a week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625526a4dbb66051e0a6343f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 07:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625526a4dbb66051e0a6343f/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Some vendors on Etsy say they are halting sales of their items on the site for a week to protest a hike in the fees the crafts e-commerce marketplace charges them. Starting Monday, Etsy sellers must pay a 6.5% commission on each transaction, up from the 5% in place since 2018.
Highlights Etsy sellers say they are halting sales of their items on the site for a week to protest a hike in fees the crafts e-commerce marketplace charges them.</description></item><item><title>Man, 21, accused of selling fentanyl-laced cocaine to West Point spring breakers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e2616c01f0f9f41bf39f4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 17:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e2616c01f0f9f41bf39f4/</guid><description>Prosecutors accused a 21-year-old man of selling the fentanyl-laced cocaine that had spring breakers dependent on intensive care ventilators at a Broward County hospital.
Highlights Axel Giovany Casseus, 21, is accused of selling the fentany-laced cocaine that caused 7 overdoses. The tragedy on Thursday at a rental home in Wilton Manors included four cadets from the U.S. Military Academy at West Point. Four of the seven hospitalized voluntarily ingested the cocaine; the other three came into contact with it when they performed cardiopulmonary resuscitation.</description></item></channel></rss>