<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>remains on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/remains/</link><description>Recent content in remains on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:26:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/remains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nestlé remains silent on child deaths from contaminated pizzas in France</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eaa4e06616a1d9c21603e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eaa4e06616a1d9c21603e/</guid><description>The food giant is citing the ongoing preliminary investigation into its Buitoni pizzas to avoid making any statement.
Highlights An 8-year-old boy died in Paris after suffering from severe hemolytic uremic syndrome (HUS) A newborn baby died eight hours after birth. The children ate Buitoni&amp;rsquo;s Fraîch&amp;rsquo;Up pizzas produced in the same Nestlé factory in Caudry (northern France) Analyses have revealed that the pizzas were contaminated by Escherichia coli (E. coli) bacteria.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin disrespecting families as it stalls return of dead soldiers, says Zelenskiy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62427cfef063648fb8a5f1ff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 03:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62427cfef063648fb8a5f1ff/</guid><description>Ukrainian president criticises Russian authorities for not agreeing on scheme to have remains sent home
Highlights Ukrainian president accuses Russian authorities of disrespecting families of dead soldiers. Claims Kremlin was affording less respect to those killed during invasion of Ukraine than is usually given to dead pets. Russia has insisted on calling a “special military operation” in Ukraine. Nato last week estimated the Russian death toll to be between 7,000 and 15,000.</description></item><item><title>'Freedom Convoy' leader Pat King denied bail, remains in jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621977765b8589946b3687e1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621977765b8589946b3687e1/</guid><description>Leader of the so-called Freedom Convoy Pat King has been denied bail because of a &amp;quot;substantial likelihood&amp;quot; he would reoffend, according to Justice of the Peace Andrew Seymour.
Highlights Pat King has been denied bail because of a &amp;ldquo;substantial likelihood&amp;rdquo; he would reoffend, says Justice of the Peace Andrew Seymour. King, an Alberta resident who helped lead the three-week occupation in Ottawa, was arrested last Friday. He faces charges of counselling to commit mischief, counselling to disobey a court order, and counselling to obstruct police.</description></item></channel></rss>