<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vehicles on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vehicles/</link><description>Recent content in vehicles on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:12:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guns killed more youngsters than cars for the first time in 2020</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f989bf88db1e492adf3c4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f989bf88db1e492adf3c4/</guid><description>Guns killed more in 2021, too. The increase is driven by the number of Black youths killed by firearms.
Highlights The Washington Post analysis reviewed CDC death records for people ages 1 through 19 from 2011 through October 2021. The change was caused by a 30 percent increase in gun deaths for people 19 and younger in 2020. Non-Hispanic Black youths are the only group for whom guns are deadlier than cars.</description></item><item><title>Protesters for Amir Locke, a Black man killed by Minneapolis police, demand police chief's resignation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 07:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</guid><description>A caravan of vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke, the 22-year old Black man who was fatally shot by Minneapolis police as officers served a no-knock search warrant.
Highlights A caravan of about 50 vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke. The caravan was organized by the Racial Justice Network and other police accountability groups. Some in the caravan then gathered in a neighborhood outside what’s believed to be the home of interim Police Chief Amelia Huffman.</description></item><item><title>Australia spends $3.5billion to purchase 120 military tanks from the United States as tensions soar with China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd7f918524169ecd9dc143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd7f918524169ecd9dc143/</guid><description>Australia will spend more than $3.5billion to purchase 120 tanks and other armoured vehicles from the United States as China continues to gain a military advantage over the Western world.
Summary Australia will spend more than $3.5billion to purchase 120 tanks and other armoured vehicles from the United States. The upgrade could see the Australian Army gain up to 75 Abrams tanks, 29 assault breacher vehicles, 17 joint assault bridge vehicles, and six armoured recovery vehicles.</description></item></channel></rss>