<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attacks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attacks/</link><description>Recent content in attacks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 22:12:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Explosion Rocks Niger State As Boko Haram Launches Attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aa592bc270ab446ece7c8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 22:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aa592bc270ab446ece7c8/</guid><description>The explosion comes a few days after the first ever bomb blast occurred at the same Galadima Kogo.
Highlights The explosion comes a few days after the first ever bomb blast occurred at the same Galadima Kogo. The number of casualties is yet to be ascertained as the affected areas are not yet accessible due to fear of further possible explosions. The explosion was reported in a statement by co-convener, Concerned Shiroro Youths of Niger State, Sani Abubar Yusuf Kokki on Friday.</description></item><item><title>New York City to try installing subway barriers after attacks leave riders on edge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621802e703db442705631c6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 22:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621802e703db442705631c6e/</guid><description>New York City will experiment with installing barriers or doors on a few subway platforms, the city&amp;rsquo;s transit chief said on Wednesday, with residents on edge over a rise in violence against riders.
Highlights New York City will experiment with installing barriers or doors on a few subway platforms, transit chief says. Move comes five weeks after a 40-year-old woman, Michelle Go, was struck and killed by a train at the Times Square subway station.</description></item></channel></rss>