<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>war on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/war/</link><description>Recent content in war on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 13:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vatican documents show secret back channel between Pope Pius XII and Adolph Hitler</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0a52dcd8f076f1419bb39/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 13:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0a52dcd8f076f1419bb39/</guid><description>A series of recently opened Vatican archives are shedding new light on the relationship between Pope Pius XII and Adolph Hitler as he led Nazi Germany during World War II. A new book takes a deeper look at these revelations. Historian David Kertzer, author of “The Pope At War: The Secret History of Pope Pius XII, Mussolini, and Hitler,” joins Amna Nawaz to discuss.
Highlights A series of recently opened Vatican archives shed new light on the relationship between Pope Pius XII and Adolph Hitler as he led Nazi Germany during World War II.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine court jails Russian soldier for life in war crimes trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b959de21b1e4548374c15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 14:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b959de21b1e4548374c15/</guid><description>A Ukrainian court sentenced a Russian soldier to life in prison on Monday for killing an unarmed civilian in the first war crimes trial arising from Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion.
Highlights Ukrainian court sentences Russian tank commander Vadim Shishimarin to life in prison for killing unarmed civilian. 21-year-old tank commander pleaded guilty to killing Oleksandr Shelipov in the northeastern Ukrainian village of Chupakhivka on Feb. 28, four days after the invasion. Russia denies targeting civilians or involvement in war crimes while it carries out what it calls a &amp;ldquo;special military operation&amp;rdquo; in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>‘This can’t be real’: Grubhub promotion turns New York City restaurants into a ‘war zone’ | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628651ec068a4f4a3f2dfba6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 14:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628651ec068a4f4a3f2dfba6/</guid><description>The deal resulted in 6,000 New Yorkers placing an order every minute, overwhelming kitchens and delivery workers
Highlights Grubhub&amp;rsquo;s free lunch promotion went badly awry on Tuesday in New York City. The app was offering $15 off of any order made in the city between 11am and 2pm. The platform said 69% of working New Yorkers said they had skipped lunch. But many users never saw their food after spending money, with some kept hungry and waiting for hours by the app’s promises that the food would arrive.</description></item><item><title>Russian soldier pleads guilty at Ukraine war crimes trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62860965105208870f83676f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62860965105208870f83676f/</guid><description>A 21-year-old Russian soldier facing the first war crimes trial since Moscow invaded Ukraine has pleaded guilty to killing an unarmed civilian
Highlights Sgt. Vadim Shishimarin could get life in prison for allegedly shooting a 62-year-old Ukrainian man in the head. Shishhimarin was a captured member of a Russian tank unit. He was prosecuted under a section of the Ukrainian criminal code that addresses the laws and customs of war. Investigators are investigating allegations that Russian troops violated Ukrainian and international law by killing, torturing and abusing possibly thousands of Ukrainian civilians.</description></item><item><title>McDonald’s says it will sell its Russia business after previously pausing operations due to Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283675b4bfb41f007c69f11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 09:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283675b4bfb41f007c69f11/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s said it will sell its business in Russia, a little more than two months after it paused operations in the country due to its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s has more than 800 restaurants and 62,000 employees in Russia. Franchisees operate only 15% of its Russian locations, while the company owns the rest. &amp;ldquo;If you can&amp;rsquo;t go to America, come to McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in Moscow,&amp;rdquo; was a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s ad slogan at the time in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine wins battle for city of Kharkiv – reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fb8ea91f4e88b7d1dcc2e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 14:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fb8ea91f4e88b7d1dcc2e/</guid><description>Kharkiv&amp;rsquo;s mayor tells the BBC that people are now gradually coming back to the key Ukrainian city.
Highlights Dergachi&amp;rsquo;s Palace of Culture is one of the last buildings in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second city to be hit by artillery. It is not a turning point in the war for Ukraine, but it is still a major victory, says the mayor of Kharkiv. Russian tanks and armoured fighting vehicles have been eliminated by Ukrainian fighters.</description></item><item><title>Lithuania recognises war in Ukraine as genocide, Russia as terrorist state</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a5a32344d628e8556570e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 12:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a5a32344d628e8556570e/</guid><description>On Tuesday, the Lithuanian parliament voted unanimously to recognise Russia’s war against Ukraine as genocide.
Highlights Lithuanian parliament voted unanimously to recognise Russia’s war against Ukraine as genocide. The resolution passed with 128 votes in favour, none against and no abstentions. It states that Russia&amp;rsquo;s armed forces and mercenaries have committed mass war crimes on Ukrainian territory. The intent is to wholly or partially destroy the Ukrainian nation and break its spirit by killing entire families, including children, abducting and raping people, and mocking them and the bodies of the murdered, the document states.</description></item><item><title>Men and boys among alleged rape victims of Russian soldiers in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272b6d28740d75f9abcb471/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272b6d28740d75f9abcb471/</guid><description>UN chief on sexual violence warns dozens of cases under investigation are ‘tip of the iceberg’
Highlights UN special representative on sexual violence in war warns dozens of cases of rape by invading forces are already under investigation. UN envoy Pramila Patten urges survivors to come forward and report rape cases. Russian forces still hold swathes of territory in the south and east of the country. Victims range from men and women of all ages, from children to elderly people, UN says.</description></item><item><title>Russia says risks of nuclear war must be kept to minimum -TASS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626faf488c0cc630a82cf74f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 10:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626faf488c0cc630a82cf74f/</guid><description>Russia believes the risks of nuclear war should be kept to a minimum and that any armed conflict between nucle
Highlights Russia believes the risks of nuclear war should be kept to a minimum and that any armed conflict between nuclear powers should be prevented, TASS news agency quoted a foreign ministry official as saying on Saturday. Vladimir Yermakov, the foreign ministry&amp;rsquo;s head of nuclear non-proliferation, said all nuclear powers must stick to the logic laid out in official documents aimed at preventing nuclear war.</description></item><item><title>Spain's Queen Gifts Grenade Shipment To Ukraine, Adds Victory Message</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626da64341c21c5b918c1590/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626da64341c21c5b918c1590/</guid><description>The Queen of Spain put traditional sausages and a postcard wishing Ukraine victory over Russia in a shipment of grenades from her country. The gift was sent to Ukraine to give a boost to the fighting power of its army.
Highlights The Queen of Spain put traditional sausages and a postcard wishing Ukraine victory over Russia in a shipment of grenades from her country. The gift was sent to Ukraine to give a boost to the fighting power of its army against a numerically superior enemy.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops use rape as 'an instrument of war' in Ukraine, rights groups allege</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262c640d35e7b2c430daa1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 15:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262c640d35e7b2c430daa1c/</guid><description>When Russian troops invaded Ukraine and began closing in on its capital, Kyiv, Andrii Dereko begged his 22-year-old stepdaughter Karina Yershova to leave the suburb where she lived.
Highlights Karina Yershova&amp;rsquo;s stepfather says she was killed by Russian soldiers. Police told her family she had been killed by pro-Russian soldiers, he says. Human rights groups say they have been working around the clock to deal with a growing number of sexual abuse cases.</description></item><item><title>'The war for talent' continues. 40% of recent job switchers are again looking for a new position, survey finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62550a361fc32a12d31dc3ad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 05:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62550a361fc32a12d31dc3ad/</guid><description>Many recent job switchers may fuel the Great Resignation trend in the near term, a new survey suggests.
Highlights Survey: Two of every five workers who switched jobs over the past year are looking for work again. Of those recent job-switchers, 40% are already actively looking for another job. Employers may need to reconsider pay, benefits and other workplace issues. Almost 60% of those who recently took new jobs had two or more competing offers when they made their decision, the survey found.</description></item><item><title>Denmark stocks up on iodine pills to bolster nuclear emergency plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254fd1a5bcf24a56997c2c8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254fd1a5bcf24a56997c2c8/</guid><description>Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Health Agency, concerned by the war in Ukraine, will buy 2 million iodine tablets to protect people in the event of a nuclear accident close to the Nordic country, it said on Monday.
Highlights Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Health Agency will buy 2 million iodine tablets to protect people in the event of a nuclear accident close to the Nordic country. The first deliveries are expected within two to three months. Denmark is more than 900 kilometres from the nearest nuclear plants in Ukraine, according to the health agency.</description></item><item><title>‘Russia Is Completely Depoliticized’ A sociologist from Moscow explains how the nation learned to deny reality.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62500b198d7dd62463ae9232/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62500b198d7dd62463ae9232/</guid><description>A sociologist from Moscow explains how the nation learned to deny reality, in Ukraine and at home under Vladimir Putin.
Highlights Russian sociologist Greg Yudin says most people under Putin&amp;rsquo;s rule passively support his “special military operation” in Ukraine. He says two decades of authoritarian rule have made the Kremlin’s line easy to accept. If the war lasts longer than a few months, the mood may change, and Putin may be tempted to escalate, he says.</description></item><item><title>UN votes Russia out of human rights council citing Bucha killings - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ffcd7a38f10728a169aa3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 09:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ffcd7a38f10728a169aa3/</guid><description>An overwhelming majority of member countries in the United Nations General Assembly voted to suspend Russia from its human rights body following recent killings in Bucha.
Highlights The United Nations General Assembly voted to suspend Russia from its human rights body on Thursday over the war in Ukraine. Russia&amp;rsquo;s deputy UN Ambassador Gennady Kuzmin called the decision an “illegitimate and politically motivated step’ Russia has vehemently denied the allegations, despite the mounting evidence.</description></item><item><title>Red is dead: Russian anti-war protesters fly a new flag for peace</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ab6d3694adbf4ade88e50/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 09:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ab6d3694adbf4ade88e50/</guid><description>Seeing the tricolour as tainted, they took the ‘blood’ out to leave blue and white, then found others had done so too
Highlights When Putin’s forces invaded Ukraine, anti-war Russians joined protests around the world. Kai Katonina and his friends came up with a white, blue and white striped flag. It has since been embraced on social media as well as by Russian protesters on the streets. The new Russian flag has also drawn the ire of the Kremlin, and officials last week proposed banning it as an “extremist” symbol.</description></item><item><title>Chernihiv mayor says Russian attacks have increased despite Moscow saying it would reduce assault on city</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624689cf3cc8f2e5d4f42020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 05:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624689cf3cc8f2e5d4f42020/</guid><description>Ukrainian authorities are racing to evacuate civilians from several hard-hit cities, including besieged Mariupol, as Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion continues.
Highlights At least 197 Ukrainian children have been born in Polish hospitals since the war began. At least one woman survived an attack in her hometown of Buchad before being diagnosed with cervical cancer in Poland. At one of the hospitals in Warsaw, a psychiatrist says, &amp;ldquo;It’s unimaginable. For someone who hasn’t seen the war, I don&amp;rsquo;t think it&amp;rsquo;s possible to imagine such pain and such stress,&amp;rdquo; says psychiatrist Magda Dutsch.</description></item><item><title>After Russian forces pull back, a shattered town breathes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62433ebf6e2fa075ed2ab079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 17:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62433ebf6e2fa075ed2ab079/</guid><description>TROSTYANETS, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of two Russian soldiers lie abandoned in the woods.
Highlights Trostyanets, 400km (250 miles) east of capital Kyiv, Ukraine, has seized back control from Russian forces. The more than month-old war has killed thousands and driven more than 10 million Ukrainians from their homes including almost 4 million from their country. It is not clear where the Russian forces went, under what circumstances they fled or whether the town will remain free of them in the days ahead.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy: West needs more courage in helping Ukraine fight</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240d35a0e32defef8150f28/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 21:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240d35a0e32defef8150f28/</guid><description>LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy accused the West of cowardice Sunday as his country fights to stave off Russia’s invading troops, making an exasperated plea for fighter jets and tanks to sustain a defense as the war ground into a battle of attrition.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president calls for fighter jets and tanks to sustain a defense as the war ground into a battle of attrition. U.S. President Joe Biden said in a lacerating speech that Russian President Vladimir Putin could not stay in power.</description></item><item><title>300 dead in airstrike on theatre in Mariupol, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ecbb3b643fcf6f25fe0db/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ecbb3b643fcf6f25fe0db/</guid><description>In what could signal an important narrowing of Moscow&amp;rsquo;s military objectives, the U.S. said Russian forces appear to have halted, at least for now, their ground offensive aimed at capturing the capital, Kyiv, and are concentrating more on the fighting for control of the Donbas region in the country&amp;rsquo;s southeast &amp;ndash; a shift the Kremlin seemed to confirm.
Highlights NEW: U.S. official: Russian forces appear to have halted ground offensive aimed at capturing the capital, Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Poland refuses to pay for Russian gas in rubles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d963a40d88ec492998b32/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 10:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d963a40d88ec492998b32/</guid><description>Poland’s state energy company on Thursday said it would not pay for Russian gas in rubles, becoming the latest to reject Kremlin demands amid unprecedented
Highlights Poland&amp;rsquo;s state energy company on Thursday said it would not pay for Russian gas in rubles. The move is the latest to reject Kremlin demands amid unprecedented sanctions on Moscow over its war in Ukraine. President Vladimir Putin on Wednesday said Russia would only accept payments for gas deliveries to “unfriendly countries” after Moscow was hit by an avalanche of sanctions over the war.</description></item><item><title>Russian foreign minister praises Fox News coverage of war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623527b9f4ca64ee362fcd4d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623527b9f4ca64ee362fcd4d/</guid><description>Sergei Lavrov says only Fox is presenting an ‘alternative point of view’ rather than ‘information terrorism’
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister praises Fox News for its coverage of Ukraine. Sergei Lavrov says only Fox is presenting an ‘alternative point of view’ rather than ‘information terrorism’ in the US. Comments came as six western nations accused Moscow of using UN security council to launder disinformation and spread propaganda. Russian diplomats again raised allegations that the US was involved in biological weapons, which have been repeatedly denied by both Washington and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>‘They don’t believe it’s real’: how war has split Ukrainian-Russian families</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234b08b5aa9ec49b5dff267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234b08b5aa9ec49b5dff267/</guid><description>Ukrainians describe anger and frustration as they try to communicate invasion’s reality to relatives across the border
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s war in Ukraine is testing myriad familial cross-border ties that have endured for decades. While people in Ukraine can see with their own eyes what is happening to their country, people in Russia do so only through the house of mirrors that is state television. Russian television is pervasive and persuasive that even some people in eastern Ukraine who watch it were taken in by its version of events.</description></item><item><title>Russian TV Editor Who Disrupted News Show With Anti-War Poster Missing, Her Lawyers Claim</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62310fe021594345dc4df9f6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 22:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62310fe021594345dc4df9f6/</guid><description>The incident, a highly unusual breach of security at Channel One, took place during its flagship news show called &amp;lsquo;Time&amp;rsquo;.
Highlights Marina Ovsyannikova was taken to a police station after the breach. Human rights group OVD-Info has claimed she is missing. She is believed to be being held in a secret location. Incident took place during Channel One&amp;rsquo;s flagship 9:00pm news show called &amp;lsquo;Time&amp;rsquo; It is watched by millions around the country, particularly by older Russians.</description></item><item><title>U.S. estimates 2,000 to 4,000 Russian troops killed in Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62289b807562b419b4dd1c48/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62289b807562b419b4dd1c48/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I think Putin&amp;rsquo;s assumptions have turned out to be profoundly flawed.&amp;quot;
Highlights Between 2,000 and 4,000 Russian troops have been killed over the course of Putin&amp;rsquo;s 12-day war in Ukraine, U.S. intelligence officials say. Putin may turn to more brutal tactics in the coming days and weeks, intelligence officials testify. CIA Director Bill Burns says Putin is likely to &amp;ldquo;double down&amp;rdquo; and may escalate his assault on heavily populated civilian areas.</description></item><item><title>Criminal offence for any Russian plane to enter UK airspace, says transport secretary</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228535ed7f51eb6d8a1d9c4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 07:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228535ed7f51eb6d8a1d9c4/</guid><description>Under the new law, Russian owned or chartered planes can be detained and Russian-owned aircraft registered in the UK can have their licences cancelled.
Highlights Transport Secretary Grant Shapps sent a letter to all UK airports and airfields on Tuesday. Air traffic control now has the power to tell pilots not to enter UK airspace. New powers will also allow the government to remove aircraft belonging to designated Russian individuals and entities from the UK aircraft register.</description></item><item><title>War in Ukraine: Russian helicopter shot down by missile in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223c41f88bf8831307278f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 20:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223c41f88bf8831307278f9/</guid><description>The video, shared by Ukrainian armed forces, shows the helicopter being hit by a missile.
Highlights &amp;lsquo;Kherson is Ukraine&amp;rsquo;: Protests in city taken by Russia. Video, shared by Ukrainian armed forces, shows helicopter being hit by missile. Helicopter hit by a missile in video shared by Ukraine armed forces. Protests take place in the city of Kherson, which has been seized by Russia since 2008. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>President Zelensky says first wave of foreign fighters has arrived to assist Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221ae7a19a53b57effd14b7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 06:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221ae7a19a53b57effd14b7/</guid><description>The first foreign fighters have arrived in Ukraine to help defend the country against the Russian invasion, according to Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky.
Highlights First foreign fighters have arrived in Ukraine to help defend against Russian invasion. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky: &amp;ldquo;The first 16,000 are already on their way to protect freedom and life for us, and for all&amp;rdquo; He did not specify where the fighters have come from, but praised allies for sending weapons to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Moscow police detain children for laying flowers at Ukrainian embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 13:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</guid><description>Children aged seven to 11 with peace signs detained for hours while two women face trial on unspecified charges
Highlights Children aged seven to 11 were held with their mothers in a police van before being taken to a police station. They were released hours later and face trial and a fine on unspecified charges. Ukrainian foreign minister, Dmytro Kuleba, said it was another sign of the toll Putin’s war against Ukraine is taking on children.</description></item><item><title>Nations agree to release 60M barrels of oil amid Russian war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</guid><description>FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves — half of that from the United States — “to send a strong message to oil markets” that supplies won&amp;rsquo;t fall short after the Russian invasion of Ukraine .
Highlights The International Energy Agency’s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves.</description></item><item><title>Two top Russian billionaires speak out against invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</guid><description>Oleg Deripaska and Ukrainian-born Mikhail Fridman call for peace, as activities come under threat from sanctions
Highlights Russian billionaires Mikhail Fridman and Oleg Deripaska speak out against Moscow’s invasion of Ukraine. In a letter to his employees he called for an end to the “bloodshed” in an email to staff at LetterOne. He joins a small group of prominent Russians – including popular actors, musicians and television presenters – who have called on President Vladimir Putin stop the military operation in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Germany halts approval of gas pipeline Nord Stream 2 after Russia’s actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</guid><description>Germany on Tuesday halted the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring natural gas from Russia directly to Europe.
Highlights Germany halts certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline to bring gas to Europe. The pipeline is designed to bring natural gas directly to Europe from Russia. Germany&amp;rsquo;s president said the country would not accept the recognition of the two pro-Russian separatist regions in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky: Make potential sanctions on Russia public, before a possible invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 05:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said Saturday sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify. He told CNN&amp;rsquo;s Chief International Anchor Christiane Amanpour that he disagreed with the stance that sanctions should only be listed after a potential Russian invasion takes place.</description></item><item><title>Taliban announces a national suicide brigade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</guid><description>The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. These “martyrdom brigades”
Summary The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. Before sweeping into power in 2021, the Taliban used suicide bombers for 20 years to attack US, UK and Afghan troops. Japanese pilots used suicide tactics during the second world war, with the Japanese Kamikaze pilots crashing their aircraft into Allied naval vessels.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>Teen who urinated on WW2 memorial and posted video online is jailed for four years.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</guid><description>The 19-year-old male was found to have &amp;lsquo;desecrated&amp;rsquo; a portrait of a war veteran, and was deemed guilty under a strict new law introduced in March this year following a similar case
Summary A teenager has been sentenced to four years in prison after being seen urinating on a World War Two memorial. 19-year-old Matvey Yuferov actually recorded himself urinating on a portrait of a World War Two veteran on November 25, in the Moscow district of Izmailovo, and uploaded the footage online.</description></item></channel></rss>