<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>war on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/war/</link><description>Recent content in war on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 13:18:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moscow police detain children for laying flowers at Ukrainian embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 13:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</guid><description>Children aged seven to 11 with peace signs detained for hours while two women face trial on unspecified charges
Highlights Children aged seven to 11 were held with their mothers in a police van before being taken to a police station. They were released hours later and face trial and a fine on unspecified charges. Ukrainian foreign minister, Dmytro Kuleba, said it was another sign of the toll Putin’s war against Ukraine is taking on children.</description></item><item><title>Nations agree to release 60M barrels of oil amid Russian war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</guid><description>FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves — half of that from the United States — “to send a strong message to oil markets” that supplies won&amp;rsquo;t fall short after the Russian invasion of Ukraine .
Highlights The International Energy Agency’s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves.</description></item><item><title>Two top Russian billionaires speak out against invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c3e2382af79d0a5fce3c6/</guid><description>Oleg Deripaska and Ukrainian-born Mikhail Fridman call for peace, as activities come under threat from sanctions
Highlights Russian billionaires Mikhail Fridman and Oleg Deripaska speak out against Moscow’s invasion of Ukraine. In a letter to his employees he called for an end to the “bloodshed” in an email to staff at LetterOne. He joins a small group of prominent Russians – including popular actors, musicians and television presenters – who have called on President Vladimir Putin stop the military operation in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Germany halts approval of gas pipeline Nord Stream 2 after Russia’s actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</guid><description>Germany on Tuesday halted the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring natural gas from Russia directly to Europe.
Highlights Germany halts certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline to bring gas to Europe. The pipeline is designed to bring natural gas directly to Europe from Russia. Germany&amp;rsquo;s president said the country would not accept the recognition of the two pro-Russian separatist regions in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky: Make potential sanctions on Russia public, before a possible invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 05:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said Saturday sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify. He told CNN&amp;rsquo;s Chief International Anchor Christiane Amanpour that he disagreed with the stance that sanctions should only be listed after a potential Russian invasion takes place.</description></item><item><title>Taliban announces a national suicide brigade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</guid><description>The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. These “martyrdom brigades”
Summary The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. Before sweeping into power in 2021, the Taliban used suicide bombers for 20 years to attack US, UK and Afghan troops. Japanese pilots used suicide tactics during the second world war, with the Japanese Kamikaze pilots crashing their aircraft into Allied naval vessels.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>Teen who urinated on WW2 memorial and posted video online is jailed for four years.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</guid><description>The 19-year-old male was found to have &amp;lsquo;desecrated&amp;rsquo; a portrait of a war veteran, and was deemed guilty under a strict new law introduced in March this year following a similar case
Summary A teenager has been sentenced to four years in prison after being seen urinating on a World War Two memorial. 19-year-old Matvey Yuferov actually recorded himself urinating on a portrait of a World War Two veteran on November 25, in the Moscow district of Izmailovo, and uploaded the footage online.</description></item></channel></rss>