<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>war on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/war/</link><description>Recent content in war on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Taliban announces a national suicide brigade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</guid><description>The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. These “martyrdom brigades”
Summary The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. Before sweeping into power in 2021, the Taliban used suicide bombers for 20 years to attack US, UK and Afghan troops. Japanese pilots used suicide tactics during the second world war, with the Japanese Kamikaze pilots crashing their aircraft into Allied naval vessels.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: We will defend ourselves against Russia 'until the last drop of blood', says country's army chief | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddfe086393bf35ab875218/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Lieutenant General Valerii Zaluzhnyi says his forces are closely monitoring the activities of Russian forces close to the border.
Summary &amp;ldquo;But… my mission is to prepare and sustain the armed forces for their intended task - to defend the state.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;So I will repeat that our armed forces have been at war for eight years. What about whether his armed forces, which number some 260,000 servicemen and women, would be able to resist a large-scale Russian invasion?</description></item><item><title>Teen who urinated on WW2 memorial and posted video online is jailed for four years.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</guid><description>The 19-year-old male was found to have &amp;lsquo;desecrated&amp;rsquo; a portrait of a war veteran, and was deemed guilty under a strict new law introduced in March this year following a similar case
Summary A teenager has been sentenced to four years in prison after being seen urinating on a World War Two memorial. 19-year-old Matvey Yuferov actually recorded himself urinating on a portrait of a World War Two veteran on November 25, in the Moscow district of Izmailovo, and uploaded the footage online.</description></item></channel></rss>