<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>white on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/white/</link><description>Recent content in white on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/white/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fauci says U.S. should consider vaccine mandate for domestic air travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</guid><description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said in an interview on MSNBC that such a requirement should be &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot; considered.
Summary The federal government should consider requiring Covid-19 vaccines for domestic flights, the nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said Monday. &amp;ldquo;If you want to do that with domestic flights, I think that&amp;rsquo;s something that seriously should be considered.&amp;rdquo; There is no indication at this point that a vaccine mandate is on its way for U.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item></channel></rss>