<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>white on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/white/</link><description>Recent content in white on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/white/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Walmart, Kroger raise at-home Covid test prices after White House agreement expires</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d614fd7457ed8d5de65850/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d614fd7457ed8d5de65850/</guid><description>Walmart and Kroger raised the price of Abbott&amp;rsquo;s at-home Covid-19 test kit after an agreement with the White House to sell the tests at a reduced price expired.
Summary Walmart and Kroger raised the price of Abbott&amp;rsquo;s at-home Covid-19 test kit after an agreement with the White House to sell the tests at a reduced price expired, the companies said Tuesday. Kroger listed the tests for $23.99. Packages of Abbott Laboratories' BinaxNOW Covid-19 Antigen Self Test are stacked on a shelf in a store in N.</description></item><item><title>Cheney: January 6 committee has 'firsthand testimony' that Ivanka asked Trump to intervene during insurrection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</guid><description>Members of the House select committee investigating January 6 said Sunday that they have critical testimony about communications to former President Donald Trump on the day of the deadly attack.
Summary Wyoming Rep. Liz Cheney, the vice chair of the committee and one of its two Republican members, told ABC News that the panel has &amp;ldquo;firsthand testimony&amp;rdquo; that during the attack, Trump&amp;rsquo;s daughter and then-senior adviser Ivanka Trump asked him to intervene.</description></item><item><title>Fauci says U.S. should consider vaccine mandate for domestic air travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</guid><description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said in an interview on MSNBC that such a requirement should be &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot; considered.
Summary The federal government should consider requiring Covid-19 vaccines for domestic flights, the nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said Monday. &amp;ldquo;If you want to do that with domestic flights, I think that&amp;rsquo;s something that seriously should be considered.&amp;rdquo; There is no indication at this point that a vaccine mandate is on its way for U.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item></channel></rss>