<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>white on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/white/</link><description>Recent content in white on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 22:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/white/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Georgia students sue over blocked protest against rebel flag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62841e4fe20491d33c91ccef/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62841e4fe20491d33c91ccef/</guid><description>ATLANTA (AP) — Several Black students who were suspended for trying to protest Confederate flag displays at their school in Georgia have filed a federal lawsuit against their school district and its board members, accusing them of allowing an extensive pattern of racism including “overt bigotry and animosity by some white students and teachers against African American students.”
Highlights Lawsuit filed against school district and its board members in Georgia. Accuses them of allowing an extensive pattern of racism including “overt bigotry and animosity by some white students and teachers against African American students’ students.</description></item><item><title>Supermarket shooter sought Black neighborhood, official says | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628143bb3b525b137fdd74d5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628143bb3b525b137fdd74d5/</guid><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The white 18-year-old who shot and killed 10 people at a Buffalo supermarket had researched the local demographics while looking for places with a high concentration of Black residents, arriving there at least a day in advance to conduct reconnaissance, law enforcement officials said Sunday.
Highlights The shooter, identified as Payton Gendron, had previously threatened a shooting at his high school last June, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Judge orders man who defaced Pride mural to write essay on Pulse shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a2820aa5719f42701adb6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 05:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a2820aa5719f42701adb6/</guid><description>Judge says he needs more time to determine a punishment and orders Alexander Jerich to write 25-page essay on 2016 massacre
Highlights Alexander Jerich, 19, pleaded guilty to criminal mischief and reckless driving. Judge ordered Jerich to write 25-page essay about Pulse shooting victims. Judge says he needs more time to decide on punishment for Jerich. Jerich says he was just trying to fit in and be accepted at the time of the attack.</description></item><item><title>Vice President Kamala Harris tests positive for Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268606c938e436982988a0c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268606c938e436982988a0c/</guid><description>Vice President Kamala Harris tested positive for Covid-19 on Tuesday after returning from a weeklong trip to California.
Highlights Vice President Joe Biden last tested negative for Covid-19 on Monday, White House says. Vice President Harris tested positive for the disease on both rapid and rapid tests, official says. Democratic Sens. Chris Murphy and Ron Wyden also tested positive on Tuesday. Senate Democrats had hoped to confirm Lisa Cook and Alvaro Bedoya to the Federal Reserve Board.</description></item><item><title>White House to extend student loan pause through August</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cb0abaca20f0c20dc01a4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 21:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624cb0abaca20f0c20dc01a4/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration plans to freeze federal student loan payments through Aug. 31, extending a moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to postpone payments during the coronavirus pandemic, according to an administration official familiar with the White House&amp;rsquo;s decision-making.
Highlights The Biden administration plans to freeze federal student loan payments through Aug. 31, extending a moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to postpone payments during the coronavirus pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Biden signs bill making lynching a federal hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Presidents typically say a few words before they turn legislation into law. But Joe Biden flipped the script Tuesday when it came time to put his signature on the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act.
Highlights Biden signs the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act in the White House Rose Garden. Biden said it&amp;rsquo;s “a little unusual to do the bill signing, not say anything and then speak” Biden: “Racial hate isn’t an old problem — it’s a persistent problem.</description></item><item><title>City of Marquette closing road nightly to save salamanders</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62411f6e47eec6be204787ef/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62411f6e47eec6be204787ef/</guid><description>MARQUETTE, Mich. (AP) — An Upper Peninsula city is closing a portion of a road to vehicular traffic every night to protect migrating salamanders. The city of Marquette is closing a portion of Peter White Drive in Presque Isle Park from 8 p.m.
Highlights The city of Marquette is closing a portion of Peter White Drive in Presque Isle Park from 8 p.m. to 8 a.m., until April 15. Road barricades will be placed and removed daily to prevent vehicular traffic in the migration area.</description></item><item><title>Nashville firefighter who called council members white supremacists suspended for 16 days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237989535641d06cf41d77d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237989535641d06cf41d77d/</guid><description>NFD concluded that Lipscomb had violated department policy and, pending a\u00a0hearing, he should be suspended for 16 days.
Highlights Nashville firefighter Josh Lipscomb, who performs as a comedian under the name Josh Black, called some council members “white supremacists” in a Feb. 3 tweet. An NFD panel concluded he violated department policy and should be suspended for 16 days. The suspension will begin on his next scheduled shift Monday, records show.</description></item><item><title>Man arrested after allegedly masturbating in Florida Starbucks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f6aa4a03a6a2565a8053e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 16:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f6aa4a03a6a2565a8053e/</guid><description>A 27-year-old self-described model was arrested last week after allegedly masturbating in front of horrified onlookers inside a Starbucks cafe.A self-
Highlights Blake Reign, 27, was allegedly seen by several witnesses pleasuring himself at the Starbucks on Collins Ave and 29th Street in Miami Beach, Florida. He was charged with lewd and lascivious behaviour, disorderly conduct in an establishment, and resisting an officer without violence. Police used ‘closed fist distraction blows’ and kicked him in the lower back area as well, according to the arrest report.</description></item><item><title>Fort Lauderdale police chief fired over minority-first practices in hiring and promotions, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62247ad9d8c03a5aff85ba95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 09:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62247ad9d8c03a5aff85ba95/</guid><description>The city of Fort Lauderdale has fired its police chief Larry Scirotto, who has been in office for less than a year, following allegations of discriminatory practices for promotions.
Highlights Larry Scirotto was sworn-in as police chief in mid-August. The city of Fort Lauderdale had hired a law firm by November to investigate complaints of discrimination. The law firm&amp;rsquo;s report says he implemented an approach to hiring and promotion that was unfairly focused on minority candidates.</description></item><item><title>Video of police stopping fight at NJ mall sparks excessive force investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d4c6f3af054a299cb3af4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 19:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d4c6f3af054a299cb3af4/</guid><description>A video posted on social media of police breaking up a fight between a Black and white teen at Bridgewater Commons mall has prompted an investigation.
Highlights Video shows two male teens, one Black and the other white, having an argument before pointing fingers at each other. The video shows no sign of resistance from the Black teen. A female voice is heard saying, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s cause he&amp;rsquo;s Black, racially motivated,&amp;rdquo; a female voice heard saying in the video.</description></item><item><title>US will act ‘decisively’ if Russia deploys military to Cuba or Venezuela – White House</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e28d3ff7b48085346590e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e28d3ff7b48085346590e5/</guid><description>The American authorities would act “decisively” if Russia deployed its military to Latin America, the White House said on Thursday, following suggestions that Moscow could station some of its troops in Venezuela or Cuba.
Summary Moscow has refused to rule out sending military infrastructure to Venezuela or CubaThe American authorities would act “decisively” if Russia deployed its military to Latin America, the White House said on Thursday, following suggestions that Moscow could station some of its troops in Venezuela or Cuba.</description></item><item><title>Walmart, Kroger raise at-home Covid test prices after White House agreement expires</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d614fd7457ed8d5de65850/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d614fd7457ed8d5de65850/</guid><description>Walmart and Kroger raised the price of Abbott&amp;rsquo;s at-home Covid-19 test kit after an agreement with the White House to sell the tests at a reduced price expired.
Summary Walmart and Kroger raised the price of Abbott&amp;rsquo;s at-home Covid-19 test kit after an agreement with the White House to sell the tests at a reduced price expired, the companies said Tuesday. Kroger listed the tests for $23.99. Packages of Abbott Laboratories&amp;rsquo; BinaxNOW Covid-19 Antigen Self Test are stacked on a shelf in a store in N.</description></item><item><title>Cheney: January 6 committee has 'firsthand testimony' that Ivanka asked Trump to intervene during insurrection</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d274f5c3e27d699922db1d/</guid><description>Members of the House select committee investigating January 6 said Sunday that they have critical testimony about communications to former President Donald Trump on the day of the deadly attack.
Summary Wyoming Rep. Liz Cheney, the vice chair of the committee and one of its two Republican members, told ABC News that the panel has &amp;ldquo;firsthand testimony&amp;rdquo; that during the attack, Trump&amp;rsquo;s daughter and then-senior adviser Ivanka Trump asked him to intervene.</description></item><item><title>Fauci says U.S. should consider vaccine mandate for domestic air travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</guid><description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said in an interview on MSNBC that such a requirement should be &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot; considered.
Summary The federal government should consider requiring Covid-19 vaccines for domestic flights, the nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said Monday. &amp;ldquo;If you want to do that with domestic flights, I think that&amp;rsquo;s something that seriously should be considered.&amp;rdquo; There is no indication at this point that a vaccine mandate is on its way for U.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item></channel></rss>