<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>30 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/30/</link><description>Recent content in 30 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 13:38:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/30/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>McDonald's to exit Russia after 30 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628253b8c0286768a3ad7324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 13:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628253b8c0286768a3ad7324/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Corp on Monday became one of the biggest global names to exit Russia, laying out plans to sell all its restaurants after operating for more than 30 years in the country following its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s plans to sell all its restaurants in Russia after operating for more than 30 years in the country following its invasion of Ukraine. The world&amp;rsquo;s largest burger chain will take a related non-cash charge of up to $1.</description></item><item><title>UK inflation rises at fastest rate in almost 30 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e2d0d27149367a95e2356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 11:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e2d0d27149367a95e2356/</guid><description>Inflation in the United Kingdom has risen at the fastest rate in almost 30 years as increased costs for energy, housing and transportation squeezed household budgets
Highlights Consumer price index ticked up to 5.5% in the 12 months through January. Latest figure is the highest since March 1992, when inflation reached 7.2%. U.K. consumers are reeling from a surge in utility bills fueled by increased demand for energy worldwide. By comparison, U.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan rejects US CDC guidance on 5-day quarantine - Some Omicron cases still infectious up to 12 days after testing positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0eb30fcff74226b151d37/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0eb30fcff74226b151d37/</guid><description>Some Omicron cases still infectious up to 12 days after testing positive | 2021-12-30 18:59:00
Summary It also shortened the isolation period for vaccinated people who have been exposed to the virus to five days. During a press conference on Dec. 30, Philip Lo (羅一鈞), deputy head of the CECC’s medical response division, announced that a total of 59 imported Omicron cases have been detected in Taiwan. More than 80% of these cases were detected upon arrival in Taiwan, while the rest tested positive within six days after entering the country.</description></item></channel></rss>