<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>longer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/longer/</link><description>Recent content in longer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 19:18:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/longer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multiple airlines allowing passengers to go maskless following judge's ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f0ad58f990e57c936e6b4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 19:18:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f0ad58f990e57c936e6b4/</guid><description>Though customers are free to continue wearing masks if they choose, passengers will not be required to mask up on many carriers for the first time in years.
Highlights In the wake of a judge&amp;rsquo;s ruling, major U.S. airlines have made mask-wearing optional for both passengers and employees. Many airlines note that while their new policies apply on all domestic flights, masks may still be required to fly to some international destinations.</description></item><item><title>Nestlé remains silent on child deaths from contaminated pizzas in France</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eaa4e06616a1d9c21603e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eaa4e06616a1d9c21603e/</guid><description>The food giant is citing the ongoing preliminary investigation into its Buitoni pizzas to avoid making any statement.
Highlights An 8-year-old boy died in Paris after suffering from severe hemolytic uremic syndrome (HUS) A newborn baby died eight hours after birth. The children ate Buitoni&amp;rsquo;s Fraîch&amp;rsquo;Up pizzas produced in the same Nestlé factory in Caudry (northern France) Analyses have revealed that the pizzas were contaminated by Escherichia coli (E. coli) bacteria.</description></item><item><title>Indoor masking no longer necessary for most of the U.S, CDC says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 16:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</guid><description>Indoor mask mandates are not necessary to be safe now across most of the United States, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Friday.
Highlights Most Americans are safe going without a mask in indoor settings, including in schools, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says. The new guidance puts more than half of the nation&amp;rsquo;s counties at low or medium risk for Covid, meaning masks are no longer necessary.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau ends use of Emergencies Act, says 'situation is no longer an emergency' | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62172276127997f9cadaffbb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 06:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62172276127997f9cadaffbb/</guid><description>Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is revoking the use of the Emergencies Act, the powerful legislative tool that was deployed in response to protests and blockades that erupted in Ottawa and at border crossings over recent weeks.
Highlights Prime Minister Justin Trudeau is revoking the use of the Emergencies Act. The act was used in response to protests and blockades that erupted in Ottawa and at border crossings over recent weeks. The Governor General signed off on the revocation on Wednesday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Tax firm Mazars fires Trump Organization as client, says former president’s financial statements are unreliable</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b0b39cc2db0c898685899/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:09:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b0b39cc2db0c898685899/</guid><description>N.Y. Attorney General Letitia James&amp;rsquo; office for several years has been investigating Trump&amp;rsquo;s company, the Trump Organization.
Highlights Mazars, which for years prepared Trump&amp;rsquo;s income tax returns and financial statements used to obtain loans for his company, told the Trump Organization&amp;rsquo;s top lawyer Alan Garten that it would no longer represent the company. N.Y. Attorney General Letitia James&amp;rsquo; office asked a state judge to order the Trump organization to comply with subpoenas seeking documents and testimony.</description></item><item><title>Thousands of diesel vehicles will no longer be allowed to drive in Brussels</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb5ed94a7d38ad6db4171c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb5ed94a7d38ad6db4171c/</guid><description>Vehicles with Euro 4 diesel engines are responsible for one-quarter of nitrogen oxide emissions but account for only 12% of the region&amp;rsquo;s vehicles.
Summary Thousands of diesel vehicles will no longer be allowed to drive in BrusselsCredit: BelgaFrom 1 January, the Low Emissions Zone (LEZ) in Brussels will introduce a new restriction on Euro 4 diesel vehicles – effectively banning them from circulating in 19 Brussels communes. Approximately 25,000 of these are registered in Brussels itself, Belga News Agency reports.</description></item></channel></rss>