<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prime on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prime/</link><description>Recent content in prime on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:14:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US official: "We believe that Putin is being misinformed" about Russian military performance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244b9fb62c38fa98dfb97f9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244b9fb62c38fa98dfb97f9/</guid><description>The US believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin is being &amp;quot;misinformed&amp;quot; by his advisers about how badly the Russian military is performing in Ukraine and the impact of sanctions on Russia&amp;rsquo;s economy, a US official tells CNN.
Highlights Former British Prime Minister David Cameron says Russian President Vladimir Putin is “effectively a war criminal” Cameron urged the US, Britain, European countries and others not to attend the upcoming G20 summit in November in Bali, Indonesia, if Putin is invited and able to attend.</description></item><item><title>Swedish and Finnish PMs quiet on Nato plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224c0fe468a527a709adb3b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 14:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224c0fe468a527a709adb3b/</guid><description>Prime Minister Sanna Marin did not want to say on Saturday whether Finland and Sweden were seeking special non-Nato partner status with the United States.
Highlights Finland and Sweden say their countries are deepening cooperation in the wake of Russia&amp;rsquo;s assault on Ukraine. Prime Minister Sanna Marin says public opinion on Nato membership is shifting in both countries. PMs did not comment on whether Finland or Sweden were seeking special non-Nato partner status with the United States.</description></item><item><title>Justin Trudeau invokes Emergencies Act for the first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b28b3ecb531b6cb0c80ee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b28b3ecb531b6cb0c80ee/</guid><description>Canada&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says police will also be given &amp;quot;more tools&amp;quot; to imprison or fine demonstrators.
Highlights Canada&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says police will also be given &amp;ldquo;more tools&amp;rdquo; to imprison or fine demonstrators. Critics have noted that the prime minister voiced support for farmers in India who blocked major highways to New Delhi for a year in 2021. Canada will always be there to defend the right of peaceful protest, he said at the time, saying: Canada will always defend the rights to peaceful protest.</description></item><item><title>Calls grow for UK PM to resign over lockdown ‘parties’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e30bd81755f9952bbfc7b4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e30bd81755f9952bbfc7b4/</guid><description>Staff at Downing Street held ‘wine-time Fridays’ during coronavirus lockdowns, according to new revelations.
Summary Calls are growing for British Prime Minister Boris Johnson to resign after more revelations came to light about regular parties organised at Downing Street that broke COVID-19 lockdown rules, with Labour party leader Keir Starmer saying Johnson was “unable to lead”. In response, a Downing Street spokeswoman said the government was awaiting Gray’s inquiry “to establish the facts around the nature of gatherings” during the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>