<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mount on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mount/</link><description>Recent content in mount on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 10:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mount/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>18 Years Old Lucy Westlake Becomes Youngest American Woman to Summit Mt. Everest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280d2d17fd5a36afc9303ff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280d2d17fd5a36afc9303ff/</guid><description>18-year-old Lucy Westlake, from Chicago, summits Mt. Everest, the highest mountain, to become the youngest American woman to do so.
Highlights Lucy Westlake, 18, is the youngest American woman to have ever scaled the mighty Everest. The Naperville native has successfully climbed Denali in Alaska, Mount Elbrus in Europe, Mount Kilimanjaro in Africa, and Aconcagua in South America. Her next goal is to complete the Explorers Grand Slam, which includes the challenge of reaching both the north and the south poles and climbing each of the highest peaks in the seven continents.</description></item><item><title>Nepali Sherpa breaks his own record again by scaling Everest 26 times, official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62784072bd9dea7e451a3ef3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62784072bd9dea7e451a3ef3/</guid><description>A Nepali sherpa scaled Mount Everest for a record 26th time, beating his own previous record set last year, a government official said on Sunday.
Highlights Kami Rita Sherpa, 52, scaled the 8,848.86-meter (29,031.69-foot) mountain on Saturday. The climbing route used by the 52-year-old Sherpa was pioneered by Sir Edmund Hillary and Nepal&amp;rsquo;s Sherpa Tenzing Norgay in 1953. This year Nepal has issued 316 permits to climb Everest in the peak season, compared with 408 last year.</description></item><item><title>Qatar in talks with the US on supplying Europe with gas as Russia, Ukraine tensions mount</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee246320aee75c50cff906/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 04:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee246320aee75c50cff906/</guid><description>Summary More than 40% of Europe’s liquified natural gas (LNG) supply comes from Russia, and almost a third of the latter’s gas passes through Ukraine. Concerns over an invasion increased late last year as Russia was seen dispatching its troops on its border with Ukraine. Europe receives more than 40% of its gas supply from Russia whilst almost a third of its shipments pass through Ukraine. On 14 January, Reuters reported that the US State Department was in talks with energy companies to shift around gas supplies to Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>