<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>commander on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/commander/</link><description>Recent content in commander on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/commander/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A dying Uvalde teacher was on the phone with her husband -- a school police officer whose boss decided not to enter her classroom, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629975d9766eab870f824e13/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629975d9766eab870f824e13/</guid><description>Eva Mireles spent some of her final monents on the phone with her police officer husband, The New York Times reported. But he couldn&amp;rsquo;t save his wife and 20 others massacred at Robb Elementary. And a negotiator&amp;rsquo;s attempts to reach the gunman were futile.
Highlights Texas State Sen. Roland Gutierrez questions whether 911 calls from inside Texas elementary school were relayed properly to responders at the scene of the shooting. Gutierrez promised to share that information with media once received.</description></item><item><title>More than 4.5 million have fled war in Ukraine: UN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253106dea533b02023fdc6c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 17:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253106dea533b02023fdc6c/</guid><description>Russia turns to Alexander Dvornikov, who has a record of brutality against civilians in Syria, say US officials.
Highlights The death toll from Friday’s railway station bombing in Kramatorsk has risen to 52. Russia denies responsibility, saying missiles responsible for the attack were used by the attack only. Russia turns to Alexander Dvornikov, who has a record of brutality against civilians in Syria, officials in Kyiv said. The U.N. has updated the number of refugees fleeing Ukraine since the war started, bringing the total to some 4.</description></item><item><title>Yuri Madvedev: Russian troops drive tank over own commander amid anger at high casualties</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fb5cec8981f2647a1505f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fb5cec8981f2647a1505f/</guid><description>Yuri Madvedev: Russian troops drive tank over own commander amid anger at high casualties
Highlights Colonel Yuri Medvedev is said to have suffered severe leg injuries in the attack. Almost half the troops in his brigade of 1,500 either died, or were wounded, in a series of clashes in the early weeks of the war. Chechen leader Ramzan Kadyrov appears to show the colonel being medically evacuated. He was airlifted to Belarus for emergency treatment and awarded a Russian military honour.</description></item><item><title>Top Russian general killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</guid><description>Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky, the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division, was killed in fighting in Ukraine earlier this week.
Highlights Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky was the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division. His death was confirmed by a local officers’ organization in the Krasnodar region in southern Russia. The circumstances of his death were not immediately clear. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>