<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>approve on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/approve/</link><description>Recent content in approve on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 05:12:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/approve/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russians transiting Lithuania to be met with Ukraine war photos: ‘do you approve of this?’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ea09d181a4558dfa1a031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ea09d181a4558dfa1a031/</guid><description>Vilnius railway station has set up a photo exhibition, displaying images from the war in Ukraine to passengers on Russia&amp;hellip;
Highlights Vilnius railway station has set up a photo exhibition, displaying images from the war in Ukraine to passengers on Russian transit trains between Moscow and Kaliningrad. The photos, which show people injured during the war, mourning people, as well as destroyed buildings, also bear inscriptions in Russian: &amp;ldquo;Today, Putin is killing the peaceful population of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Florida lawmakers approve bill to restrict rooftop solar incentives</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62290a60047c33a7f9ded5b3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62290a60047c33a7f9ded5b3/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. &amp;ndash; Major changes could be coming to rooftop solar energy in the state of Florida. House Bill 741 was passed by both the Florida House and Senate this past week, and will now be sent to Governor DeSantis to sign. Caption: WEAR. The legislation would effect a process called net metering. Net metering is the process in which additional energy goes into what is called a grid and homeowners are then given dollar for dollar credit by power companies, such as Florida Power &amp;amp; Light.</description></item><item><title>Birds are real, a US government agency wants you to assure you</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9fb7a03ad2604cf64f8af/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 21:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9fb7a03ad2604cf64f8af/</guid><description>And the US Consumer Product Safety Commission flew off on a meme tangent to prove it.
Summary Ohio Division of WildlifeA parody movement claims birds aren&amp;rsquo;t real. Now, a government agency, the US Consumer Product Safety Commission, is jumping in to defend its feathered friends. Background: Peter McIndoe, 23, created the &amp;ldquo;Birds Aren&amp;rsquo;t Real&amp;rdquo; movement in 2017 as a parody of conspiracy theories, according to The New York Times, His storyline claimed birds are drones created by the government to spy on its citizens, although McIndoe says he&amp;rsquo;s done with the joke now.</description></item></channel></rss>