<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mayor on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mayor/</link><description>Recent content in mayor on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:12:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mayor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chattanooga Mayor Tim Kelly says Saturday night shooting began with disagreement among teens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294ecc9cbe65c6d1b22a8f9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294ecc9cbe65c6d1b22a8f9/</guid><description>After the Saturday night shooting in downtown Chattanooga that left six young people injured, two of whom were in critical condition, Chattanooga Mayor Tim Kelly is asking parents to take action to help prevent more such incidents.
Highlights Six teens injured in shootings that left six injured downtown Chattanooga. Police chief: Gun battle appeared to break out between two groups of young people. Mayor Tim Kelly: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m heartbroken for the families and the victims whose lives were upended last night by gunfire&amp;rdquo; The shootings came less than a week after an 18-year-old opened fire at a Uvalde, Texas elementary school, killing 19 students and 2 teachers.</description></item><item><title>Mariupol mayor says siege has killed more than 10K civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625499e1fcb75036ac08b36e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 21:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625499e1fcb75036ac08b36e/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The mayor of the Ukrainian port city of Mariupol said Monday that more than 10,000 civilians have died in the Russian siege of his city, and that the death toll could surpass 20,000, with corpses that were “carpeted through the streets.”
Highlights Mariupol Mayor Vadym Boychenko says more than 10,000 civilians have died in the Russian siege of his city. He says corpses have been “carpeted through the streets” and the death toll could surpass 20,000.</description></item><item><title>Portland mayor bans homeless encampments near highways over pedestrian deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff90ab1dad74c15a9988cf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 09:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff90ab1dad74c15a9988cf/</guid><description>The mayor of Oregon&amp;rsquo;s most populous city on Friday banned encampments near highways and high-traffic intersections, saying homeless people comprised the majority of pedestrians who were killed in Portland traffic incidents last year.
Highlights Portland Mayor Ted Wheeler&amp;rsquo;s emergency order enacting the ban is set to run at least until February 18. Wheeler cites a report from the city&amp;rsquo;s transportation bureau, which said 19 homeless pedestrians were killed in traffic incidents in Portland last year.</description></item><item><title>Kyiv's mayor decries Germany's offer of 5,000 helmets to Ukraine as a 'joke' and asks if 'pillows' are next</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f226f2180452bda9b3dace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f226f2180452bda9b3dace/</guid><description>Unlike other NATO members, Germany has declined to send weapons to Ukraine, renewing scrutiny of its motives.
Summary Germany is offering 5,000 helmets to Ukraine amid fears of a Russian invasion. &amp;ldquo;We will supply Ukraine with 5,000 helmets as a clear signal: We are at your side.&amp;rdquo; Nord Stream 2 bypasses Ukraine — depriving it of billions in gas transit fees. Even still, the Ukrainian government vehemently opposes Nord Stream 2.</description></item><item><title>Germany has 'betrayed' Ukraine, Kiev mayor Vitali Klitschko declares</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0e38eec650aed9f88b2c0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 06:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0e38eec650aed9f88b2c0/</guid><description>The ex-heavyweight champ today slated Germany for its &amp;lsquo;failure to provide assistance&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;betrayal of friends&amp;rsquo; as fears of a Russian invasion of Ukraine climb ever higher.
Summary Former world heavyweight boxing champion and Mayor of Kiev Vitali Klitschko has accused Germany of &amp;lsquo;betraying&amp;rsquo; Ukraine over its support of a Russian gas pipeline and refusal to export arms to his country. &amp;lsquo;There is huge disappointment in Ukraine that the federal government is sticking to Nord Stream 2 and that it does not want to supply defence weapons,&amp;rsquo; Klitschko wrote in Bild.</description></item></channel></rss>