<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rule on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rule/</link><description>Recent content in rule on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rule/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EPA moves to give states, tribes more power to protect water</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299b37f48cdab34b624630f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299b37f48cdab34b624630f/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Thursday proposed undoing a Trump-era rule that limited the power of states and Native American tribes to block energy projects like natural gas pipelines based on their potential to pollute rivers and streams.
Highlights The Biden administration on Thursday, June 2, 2022, proposed undoing a Trump-era rule that limited the power of states and Native American tribes to block energy projects like natural gas pipelines based on their potential to pollute rivers and streams.</description></item><item><title>Thailand to give away one million free cannabis plants, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627be21a3b5c0635fdd3500d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 16:20:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627be21a3b5c0635fdd3500d/</guid><description>The Thai government will distribute one million free cannabis plants to households across the nation in June to mark a new rule allowing people to grow cannabis at home, its health minister has said.
Highlights Thailand to distribute one million free cannabis plants to households across the nation in June. Health Minister Anutin Charnvirakul announced the move in a Facebook post on May 8. The move is the latest step in Thailand’s plan to promote cannabis as a cash crop.</description></item></channel></rss>