<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>platforms on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/platforms/</link><description>Recent content in platforms on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 16:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/platforms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An appeals court finds Florida's social media law unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d03c3e2cada4724b26a66/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d03c3e2cada4724b26a66/</guid><description>In a blow to Gov. Ron DeSantis, a three-judge panel of the 11th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals said social media companies&amp;rsquo; moderation and curation efforts were protected by the First Amendment.
Highlights An appeals court finds Florida&amp;rsquo;s social media law unconstitutional. The law would require large social media companies to publish standards on how it decides to &amp;ldquo;censor, deplatform, and shadow ban&amp;rdquo; The law was signed by GOP Gov. Ron DeSantis in 2021.</description></item><item><title>Twitter bans climate change propaganda ads as deniers target platforms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626569310e2d491eb6406cd7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 15:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626569310e2d491eb6406cd7/</guid><description>Twitter is banning advertisements that promote climate change denial in an effort to curb the reach of groups seeking to downplay the extent of the environmental crisis.
Highlights Twitter will be relying on reports from the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, a unit within the United Nations, to inform its decisions about which advertisements break its rules. Twitter’s Friday announcement is part of a larger trend by social media companies to address criticism from activists that they are doing too little to combat climate change disinformation campaigns.</description></item></channel></rss>