<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>secretary on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/secretary/</link><description>Recent content in secretary on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:18:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/secretary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NATO is no longer bound by commitments to Russia and will beef up Eastern Europe presence, says deputy secretary general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294fc331528a4330fdec89e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294fc331528a4330fdec89e/</guid><description>The NATO-Russia agreement signed 25 years ago no longer binds the Alliance because Russia itself violated the agreement &amp;hellip;
Highlights NATO-Russia agreement signed 25 years ago no longer binds the Alliance because Russia itself violated the agreement by invading Ukraine, says NATO Deputy Secretary General Mircea Geoană, visiting Vilnius. NATO pledged not to permanently deploy significant forces in central and eastern Europe, including the Baltic states. Russia has committed to refrain from aggression against its neighbours and is not complying, he says.</description></item><item><title>Disinformation Governance Board to tackle spread of misinformation in U.S., focusing on Russia and U.S.-Mexico border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d1962dbb68bb45dd6e9e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d1962dbb68bb45dd6e9e5/</guid><description>The immediate focus will be on misinformation from human smugglers, who spread falsehoods about border policy to migrants to help drum up business.
Highlights The Department of Homeland Security is setting up a Disinformation Governance Board to try to counter the spread of false information. The board will focus on misinformation coming from Russia as well as misleading messages about the U.S.-Mexico border. The immediate focus will be on misinformation from human smugglers, who spread false claims about border policy to migrants to help drum up business.</description></item><item><title>US Defense Secretary says allies don't have any time to waste" in providing help to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62687ccfd372ae8b275f0287/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 23:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62687ccfd372ae8b275f0287/</guid><description>US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin opened his news conference Tuesday by thanking the countries that have stepped up to help Ukraine noting, &amp;quot;We don&amp;rsquo;t have any time to waste.&amp;quot;
Highlights Diplomats return to Ukraine for the first time since Russia invaded the country. U.S. Secretary of State says it is not safe for anyone to be in Ukraine right now. Russia warned the US against arming Ukraine earlier this month in a diplomatic cable.</description></item><item><title>Russian commanders 'will be hunted down for war crimes', justice secretary warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220790dbc5a66d5a8ea76c9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 08:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220790dbc5a66d5a8ea76c9/</guid><description>The UK and 37 others countries referred Russia to the International Criminal Court on Wednesday for its &amp;quot;barbaric&amp;quot; invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Justice Secretary Dominic Raab said the UK is already planning to help identify and find fugitives suspected of war crimes. The UK and 37 other countries referred Russia to the International Criminal Court on Wednesday for its &amp;ldquo;barbaric&amp;rdquo; invasion of Ukraine. Justice Secretary Johnson said all 38 countries are &amp;ldquo;crystal clear that Mr Putin cannot commit these horrific acts with impunity&amp;rdquo; Mr Raab revealed more details to The Daily Telegraph.</description></item><item><title>Pope Benedict XVI knew of abusive priests when he ran Munich archdiocese, investigators say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea7637a83375790c39bf3e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 09:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea7637a83375790c39bf3e/</guid><description>Pope Benedict XVI knew about priests who abused children but failed to act when he was archbishop of Munich from 1977 to 1982, an inquest found Thursday, rejecting Benedict&amp;rsquo;s long-standing denials in a damning judgment.
Summary Berlin (CNN) Pope Benedict XVI knew about priests who abused children but failed to act when he was archbishop of Munich from 1977 to 1982, an inquest found Thursday, rejecting Benedict&amp;rsquo;s long-standing denials in a damning judgment.</description></item><item><title>Secretary Blinken: NATO Did Not Invade Georgia &amp;amp; Ukraine, Russia Did</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7833dc5dfa87b9e5f1602/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7833dc5dfa87b9e5f1602/</guid><description>Yesterday, US Secretary of State, Antony Blinken, and Minister of Foreign Affairs of Germany, Annalena Baerbock, held a joint press conference. During the conference, Secretary Blinken was asked about
Summary Secretary Blinken: NATO Did Not Invade Georgia &amp;amp; Ukraine, Russia Did - GeorgianJournal READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>