<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>chief on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/chief/</link><description>Recent content in chief on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 15:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/chief/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Don’t let people off if they steal food in desperation, minister tells police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62865e59d030b11ab95a5242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 15:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62865e59d030b11ab95a5242/</guid><description>Kit Malthouse says police watchdog’s suggestion that cost of living will trigger more crime is ‘old-fashioned’
Highlights Andy Cooke said cost of living crisis will trigger an increase in crime. Chief inspector of constabulary said officers should use their ‘discretion’ when deciding whether to prosecute people who steal in order to eat. Malthouse said people are challenged financially ‘doesn’t necessarily mean they’re going to turn to crime’ The policing minister has told police not to let shoplifters off if they are stealing food out of desperation during the cost-of-living crisis.</description></item><item><title>Beijing loyalist John Lee will be Hong Kong’s next leader</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277ed4c539db492c11ab390/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:18:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277ed4c539db492c11ab390/</guid><description>John Lee, the only candidate for Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s top post, has been elected to be Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s next Chief Executive.
Highlights The only candidate to be elected to be Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s next president was elected on Sunday. He is the only candidate for the job. The election was held under the &amp;ldquo;one country, two-nation&amp;rdquo; rule of Hong Kong. The city is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most populous and most populous countries.</description></item><item><title>FDA chief explains why misinformation is leading cause of death in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62776d95b35e022b05e65963/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 07:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62776d95b35e022b05e65963/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with CNN&amp;rsquo;s Pamela Brown, FDA chief Dr. Robert Califf explains why he says the leading cause of death in the US is misinformation.
Highlights FDA chief Dr. Robert Califf says the leading cause of death in the US is misinformation. Califf tells CNN&amp;rsquo;s Pamela Brown why he says the top cause of US death is death. The FDA chief says misinformation is leading to the death toll in the U.</description></item><item><title>US official: Russia appoints new Ukraine war commander</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253f14366b76509ed863537/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253f14366b76509ed863537/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Russia has tapped a new Ukraine war commander to take centralized control of the next phase of battle after its costly failures in the opening campaign and carnage for Ukrainian civilians.
Highlights Russia has appointed Gen. Alexander Dvornikov as commander of an armed campaign that Russian authorities still refer to as a “special military operation&amp;quot; U.S. officials don’t see one man making a difference in Moscow’s prospects. The White House national security adviser, Jake Sullivan, said “no appointment of any general can erase the fact that Russia has already faced a strategic failure in Ukraine” The decision to establish new battlefield leadership comes as Russia gears up for what is expected to be a large and more focused push to expand Russian control in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s east and south, including the Donbas, and follows a failed opening bid in the north.</description></item><item><title>Fort Lauderdale police chief fired over minority-first practices in hiring and promotions, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62247ad9d8c03a5aff85ba95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 09:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62247ad9d8c03a5aff85ba95/</guid><description>The city of Fort Lauderdale has fired its police chief Larry Scirotto, who has been in office for less than a year, following allegations of discriminatory practices for promotions.
Highlights Larry Scirotto was sworn-in as police chief in mid-August. The city of Fort Lauderdale had hired a law firm by November to investigate complaints of discrimination. The law firm&amp;rsquo;s report says he implemented an approach to hiring and promotion that was unfairly focused on minority candidates.</description></item></channel></rss>