<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fbi on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fbi/</link><description>Recent content in fbi on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fbi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu Resigns After FBI Reveals Anaheim Corruption Probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c7745216ed39f72f0727e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c7745216ed39f72f0727e/</guid><description>Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu abruptly resigns following FBI corruption probe into city hall. Mayor&amp;rsquo;s lawyer Paul Meyer issued a statement defending the mayor’s actions while in office. An FBI affidavit alleges that Sidhu shared city information with the
Highlights Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu abruptly resigns Monday. The resignation comes after an FBI corruption probe into Anaheim City Hall was revealed. Sidhu&amp;rsquo;s lawyer Paul Meyer issued a statement defending the mayor’s actions while in office.</description></item><item><title>Suspect arrested in Dallas salon shooting as FBI opens hate crime investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62840f6d512ad27954770942/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62840f6d512ad27954770942/</guid><description>Dallas police arrested a suspect in connection with the May 11 shooting of three Korean women at a hair salon. The FBI opened a hate crime probe into the incident.
Highlights Dallas police arrested a suspect in connection with the May 11 shooting of three women in a hair salon in the city&amp;rsquo;s Koreatown. The incident is being investigated as a hate crime and could be linked to a series of recent shootings at Asian-run businesses.</description></item><item><title>New FBI documents link Saudi spy in California to 9/11 attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623430e744fcd7fe5a34ebdc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 07:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623430e744fcd7fe5a34ebdc/</guid><description>A new batch of previously secret FBI documents confirms that US authorities knew that a Saudi man who helped 9/11 hijackers was, in fact, a Saudi spy.
Highlights New FBI documents link Saudi spy in California to 9/11 attacks. FBI concluded five years ago that there was a &amp;ldquo;50/50 chance&amp;rdquo; that this Saudi spy knew ahead of time that the two Islamists he befriended were about to join the plot to hijack commercial jetliners and crash them into buildings in what turned out to be America&amp;rsquo;s deadliest terrorist attack.</description></item></channel></rss>