<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>supremacist on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supremacist/</link><description>Recent content in supremacist on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 08:16:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supremacist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 men plead guilty in white supremacist terror plot to disrupt power grid, trigger race war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f27a1e607ca0d1aa20388/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f27a1e607ca0d1aa20388/</guid><description>Three men who plotted to attack electricity substations in a white supremacist bid to sow national unrest pleaded guilty to providing material support to
Highlights Three men plotted to attack electricity substations in a white supremacist bid to sow national unrest, prosecutors say. They planned to disrupt the electricity grid in order to sow civil unrest and economic uncertainty in furtherance of their white supremacist cohort, they say. The three had planned to kill themselves with &amp;ldquo;suicide necklaces&amp;rdquo; containing fentanyl, the powerful synthetic opioid, if law enforcement came upon them before they were successful.</description></item><item><title>Arbery killer shared racist messages, white supremacist song with friends</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dc22cd509ceed0084f029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dc22cd509ceed0084f029/</guid><description>The gunman convicted of murdering Ahmaud Arbery, a Black man in Georgia, repeatedly used racist language in text messages with friends, and also shared a music video of a white supremacist singer, jurors at his federal hate crimes trial heard on Wednesday.
Highlights Jurors in federal hate-crime trial of Georgia man convicted of murdering Black man Ahmaud Arbery in 2020. Gunman Travis McMichael repeatedly used racist language in text messages with friends, jurors heard on Wednesday.</description></item></channel></rss>