<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>depot on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/depot/</link><description>Recent content in depot on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:17:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/depot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Investors force Home Depot to review wood-sourcing policy over logging concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c6a2fffa2675311b3dfb1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 05:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c6a2fffa2675311b3dfb1/</guid><description>Environmental science and conservation news
Highlights Some of Home Depot&amp;rsquo;s plywood is allegedly sourced from vulnerable forests in Ecuador’s Chocó region and the Brazilian Cerrado. A proposal passed requiring the home improvement giant to reevaluate policies related to sustainability certifications of wood suppliers. Investors and conservationists have pressured Home Depot to clean up its supply chain. Home Depot has around 2,300 locations across North America and a significant wood importer. The company doesn’t offer specific figures on how much it imports from where wood comes from, but has no specific limits on where it buys it.</description></item><item><title>Home Depot employee arrested for swapping store cash with counterfeit bills for years, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff3cc3973cad27de13f433/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 03:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff3cc3973cad27de13f433/</guid><description>A Tempe, Arizona, Home Depot employee is facing a federal charge, after authorities said he repeatedly took cash from the store and replaced it with counterfeit currency before depositing it in the bank, according to a criminal complaint.
Highlights Adrian Jean Pineda, a vault employee at the store, was responsible for counting cash and preparing it for deposit. He is accused of ordering counterfeit bills from Amazon, swapping them with money taken from store cash registers and sealing them in bags for transfer to the bank.</description></item></channel></rss>