<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>st on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/st/</link><description>Recent content in st on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 11:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/st/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Red Power Ranger Actor Among 19 Accused in North Texas PPP Scheme – NBC 5 Dallas-Fort Worth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a199b8b0f2359b2dfebb3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a199b8b0f2359b2dfebb3/</guid><description>Nineteen people, including the actor who played the Red Power Ranger on television, are facing federal charges after being accused of conspiracy to commit wire&amp;hellip;
Highlights Austin St. John, whose real name is Jason Lawrence Geiger, was named in an indictment returned by a federal grand jury on May 12. The actor was best known for his role in the 1990s children&amp;rsquo;s children&amp;rsquo;s superhero show “Mighty Morphin’s Gold Ranger in the “Power Rangers Zeo” St John played the Red Power Ranger in 1996 in the TV show and recently, in 2020, wore the red ranger&amp;rsquo;s red suit again.</description></item><item><title>Drone carrying bag of handguns from United States to Canada intercepted by tree | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273a3a22e363130125b9264/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 10:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273a3a22e363130125b9264/</guid><description>Ontario Provincial Police are trying to figure out who sent a shopping bag full of handguns across the Canada-U.S. border via drone &amp;ndash; and who was supposed to receive the illegal package.
Highlights Ontario Provincial Police are trying to figure out who sent a shopping bag full of handguns across the Canada-U.S. border via drone. A large drone was found stuck in a tree along the St. Clair River near Port Lambton, a small village on the Canadian side of the river, about 40 km south of Sarnia, Ont.</description></item><item><title>Former sheriff gets 4 life sentences in rape, incest case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62156e20b59bc10d2da0c442/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 23:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62156e20b59bc10d2da0c442/</guid><description>Jack Strain was sentenced to serve the rest of his life in prison after being found guilty of rape and incest.
Highlights Jack Strain was sentenced to serve the rest of his life in prison after being found guilty of rape and incest. He was convicted in November on four counts of aggravated rape, two counts of incest, one count of indecent behavior with a juvenile, and five years for sexual battery.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutor won't charge reporter who uncovered database flaw</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208cb639b4b8b009fc335d1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 09:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208cb639b4b8b009fc335d1/</guid><description>A Missouri prosecutor will not charge a St. Louis Post-Dispatch journalist who exposed a state database flaw that allowed public access to thousands of teachers&amp;rsquo; Social Security numbers.
Highlights Cole County Prosecutor Locke Thompson says there is an argument to be made that there was a violation of law. A St. Louis Post-Dispatch reporter exposed a state database flaw that allowed public access to teachers&amp;rsquo; Social Security numbers. Republican Gov. Mike Parson announced the investigation in October after a reporter informed the state of a significant data issue that left the teachers&amp;rsquo; data vulnerable to public disclosure.</description></item></channel></rss>