<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bragg on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bragg/</link><description>Recent content in bragg on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 09:13:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bragg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suspect in New York City attacks on Asian women indicted on felony hate charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c083063745b28950cc1b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 09:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c083063745b28950cc1b1/</guid><description>A man arrested last month in a string of attacks on seven Asian women in New York City has been indicted on felony and misdemeanor hate crimes charges,
Highlights Steven Zajonc, 28, is charged with six felony counts of third-degree assault as a hate crime. Zajanc is accused in a three-hour string of attacks targeting Asian women on Feb. The district attorney&amp;rsquo;s office has 27 open cases related to anti-Asian hate crimes, prosecutors say.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutors resigned after New York DA said he wasn't prepared to move forward with indictment of Trump</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226915f3a4150fb2029b642/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 23:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226915f3a4150fb2029b642/</guid><description>Two top prosecutors in the Trump investigation into former President Donald Trump resigned last month. The resignations followed weeks of internal debate and discussion over the strength of the evidence against Trump. Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg said he wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared to
Highlights Two senior prosecutors on the team resigned last month after the Manhattan district attorney said he was not prepared to authorize an indictment against the former President. The resignations followed weeks of internal debate and discussion over the strength of the evidence against Trump.</description></item></channel></rss>