<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suspension on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspension/</link><description>Recent content in suspension on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 15:15:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspension/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Hell Week’ kidnapping, hazing allegations lead to LSU fraternity’s suspension</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625445d62bf3f4b92879eadf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625445d62bf3f4b92879eadf/</guid><description>The fraternity is suspended until May of 2023 and is barred from campus activities. It is also blocked from selecting or admitting new members during the suspension.
Highlights A letter reviewed by WAFB details “Hell Week” hazing between 2017 and 2020. In October of 2020, a “large” group of people reportedly kidnapped and assaulted an active fraternity member, LSU found. The fraternity is suspended until May of 2023 and is barred from campus activities.</description></item><item><title>YouTube permanently bans Fox News host Dan Bongino</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f23658373f3d0dddf913cb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f23658373f3d0dddf913cb/</guid><description>Fox News Channel host Dan Bongino on Wednesday became among the most-followed conservative personalities to be permanently banned from YouTube, a week after the Google-owned video service said he had posted COVID-19 misinformation.
Summary REUTERS/Jonathan ErnstJan 26 (Reuters) - Fox News Channel host Dan Bongino on Wednesday became among the most-followed conservative personalities to be permanently banned from YouTube, a week after the Google-owned (GOOGL.O) video service said he had posted COVID-19 misinformation.</description></item></channel></rss>