<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>japan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/japan/</link><description>Recent content in japan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 08:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Japan's Okinawa marks half century since U.S. handover as regional tensions grow.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628208d3d51777c04c4eb771/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 08:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628208d3d51777c04c4eb771/</guid><description>The Japanese island chain of Okinawa marked the 50th anniversary on Sunday of the end of U.S. occupation and its return to Japan with calls for more economic growth and fewer U.S. bases despite growing worries over its proximity to an increasingly assertive China.
Highlights The Japanese island chain of Okinawa marked the 50th anniversary on Sunday of the end of U.S. occupation and its return to Japan. The islands suffered massive devastation in World War Two and were finally returned to Japan in 1972.</description></item><item><title>10 found dead after Japan tour boat with 26 aboard sinks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62662e392042d02a34ceb4e7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 05:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62662e392042d02a34ceb4e7/</guid><description>The search for the others is still ongoing after the boat sent a distress call on Saturday afternoon saying it was sinking. The location, near the Kashuni Waterfall, is known as a difficult place to maneuver boats because of its rocky coastline and strong tide.
Highlights The search for the others is still ongoing after the boat sent a distress call on Saturday afternoon saying it was sinking. The Transport Ministry launches an investigation into the boat’s operator, which had two accidents last year.</description></item><item><title>Russia warns Japan to stay out of Ukraine crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee08403d4bf3a5db09fae7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee08403d4bf3a5db09fae7/</guid><description>The Russian foreign minister&amp;rsquo;s team warned Japan to stay out of the brewing Ukraine crisis after U.S. officials touted a “close alignment” with Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida in the lead-up to a potential eruption of violence in Eastern Europe.
Summary The Russian foreign minister&amp;rsquo;s team warned Japan to stay out of the brewing Ukraine crisis after U.S. officials touted a “close alignment” with Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida in the lead-up to a potential eruption of violence in Eastern Europe.</description></item><item><title>Japan bans facial recognition tech exports due to China's human rights abuses: Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</guid><description>Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions | 2022-01-03 16:53:00
Summary A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. Tokyo has deemed the new measures necessary to prevent technologies from being used in this way. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>