<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>traffic on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/traffic/</link><description>Recent content in traffic on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 22:15:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/traffic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Autopsy shows Patrick Lyoya shot in head by Michigan cop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f345da859788504e34923/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 22:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f345da859788504e34923/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A Michigan police officer who killed Patrick Lyoya after a traffic stop pressed the gun against his head when firing the fatal shot, an expert who performed an independent autopsy for the Black man&amp;rsquo;s family said Tuesday.
Highlights Forensic pathologist Dr. Werner Spitz performed the autopsy last weekend at a funeral home. The 95-year-old forensic pathologist participated in the assassination investigations of President John F. Kennedy and Martin Luther King Jr.</description></item><item><title>Possible Evidence of Russian Atrocities: German Intelligence Intercepts Radio Traffic Discussing the Murder of Civilians in Bucha</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f375e8dcf6be01d07d6d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 19:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f375e8dcf6be01d07d6d3/</guid><description>The images of the murdered civilians in Bucha shocked the world. DER SPIEGEL has learned that German intelligence intercepted radio traffic from suspected perpetrators. It appears that such atrocities were part of the strategy of Putin&amp;rsquo;s army.
Highlights DER SPIEGEL has learned that the BND has new satellite images and has intercepted incriminating radio traffic from Russian military personnel in the region north of Kyiv. Some of the intercepted traffic apparently matches the locations of bodies found along the main road through Bucha.</description></item><item><title>A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop for speeding and asked to see the officer's supervisor, video footage shows.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</guid><description>Video footage shows a Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who began recording his traffic stop, saying he was feeling unsafe
Highlights A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop, video footage shows. Delane Gordon began recording when the March 10 stop started to make him feel unsafe, attorney says. The man wound up facing additional charges of resisting arrest and obstruction of justice.</description></item><item><title>4th Kansas Rep. charged in a year, Suzi Carlson charged with two counts after DUI arrest last month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62213d62d4636e71e7d9be1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 22:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62213d62d4636e71e7d9be1c/</guid><description>Rep. Suzi Carlson, R-Clay Center, is charged with two counts in relation to an arrest for allegedly\u00a0driving under the influence earlier this year.
Highlights Rep. Suzi Carlson charged with two counts after DUI arrest last month. Carlson was arrested on suspicion of driving under the influence with a blood alcohol concentration above 0.08 and failure to maintain a single lane. Carlson, 69, is a retired municipal court judge. She is the fourth Kansas lawmaker arrested in the past year, with another scheduled hearing scheduled for May.</description></item></channel></rss>