<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>facility on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/facility/</link><description>Recent content in facility on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 22:13:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/facility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police shoot man being held for mental health at Florida hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624232fdc14d3fc2029a2743/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 22:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624232fdc14d3fc2029a2743/</guid><description>With no space available at a mental health facility, man was shot after brandishing scissors at medical hospital
Highlights 29-year-old man was being held under the Baker Act, which allows authorities to hold someone in a mental health facility for up to 72 hours if they are a threat to themselves or others. The man was among a number of people being held in the hospital because there were no beds at the local mental health facilities.</description></item><item><title>FDA warns consumers not to use certain Family Dollar products in 6 states after discovering more than 1,000 dead rodents at plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621124d6d524bb30f7191963/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 17:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621124d6d524bb30f7191963/</guid><description>The recall impacts stores in Alabama, Arkansas, Louisiana, Mississippi, Missouri and Tennessee, and products purchased between January 1, 2021, and today.
Highlights The FDA says it found more than 1,000 dead rodents after a fumigation at a distribution facility in Arkansas. Family Dollar says it is not aware of any reports of illness related to the recall. The FDA said it began an investigation into the West Memphis, Arkansas, distribution facility after receiving a consumer complaint in January.</description></item></channel></rss>