<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>philadelphia on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/philadelphia/</link><description>Recent content in philadelphia on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 08:17:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/philadelphia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Philadelphia becomes first major US city to reinstate indoor mask mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255356262381e5d718436ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 08:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255356262381e5d718436ec/</guid><description>Covid-19 cases have risen more than 50% in 10 days, the threshold at which city’s guidelines call for masking indoors
Highlights Philadelphia is first major US city to reinstate its indoor mask mandate after sharp increase in coronavirus infections. Health inspectors will begin enforcing the mask mandate at city businesses on 18 April. Health officials believe the recent wave is being driven by the highly transmissible BA.2 sub-variant of Omicron, which has spread rapidly throughout Europe and Asia.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Philadelphia Cop Charged In Beating Of Now-Exonerated Man Who Spent 11 Years In Prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226ba7d88098f836c2f1668/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 02:08:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226ba7d88098f836c2f1668/</guid><description>James Pitts, 51, is charged with three counts of obstructing administration of law and two counts of perjury. Pitts is accused of assaulting Obina Onyiah during an interrogation and then lying about the alleged assault. Ony
Highlights James Pitts, 51, is charged with three counts of obstructing administration of law and two counts of perjury. He is accused of beating Obina Onyiah during an interrogation and then lying about the alleged assault in 2010.</description></item></channel></rss>