<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>warning on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/warning/</link><description>Recent content in warning on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 12:16:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/warning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disney+ adds warning label to 'Obi-Wan Kenobi' following Uvalde school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294b57a30fe82cb548a1faf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 12:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294b57a30fe82cb548a1faf/</guid><description>Disney+ is the latest streaming service to add a warning label to some of its content in the wake of a mass shooting at a Texas elementary school.
Highlights Disney+ is the latest streaming service to add a warning label to some of its content in the wake of a mass shooting at a Texas elementary school. The warning is due to a scene that shows Stormtroopers and Imperial Inquisitors attacking the Jedi temple.</description></item><item><title>New Chinese hacking tool found, spurring U.S. warning to allies. “Chinese hacking tool that has been able to escape public attention for more than a decade.”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dba12870c7342f5be9657/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 06:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dba12870c7342f5be9657/</guid><description>Security researchers with U.S. cybersecurity firm Symantec said they have discovered a “highly sophisticated” Chinese hacking tool that has been able to escape public attention for more than a decade.
Highlights Security researchers with U.S. cybersecurity firm Symantec said they have discovered a “highly sophisticated” Chinese hacking tool. The tool, which it calls Daxin, has been able to escape public attention for more than a decade. The discovery was shared with the United States in recent months, who have shared the information with foreign partners.</description></item><item><title>S&amp;amp;P cuts Russia's rating to junk, Moody's issues junk warning</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a975947b839aaaac52f97/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 21:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a975947b839aaaac52f97/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine triggered a flurry of credit rating moves on Friday, with S&amp;amp;P lowering Russia&amp;rsquo;s rating to &amp;lsquo;junk&amp;rsquo; status, Moody&amp;rsquo;s putting it on review for a downgrade to junk, and S&amp;amp;P and Fitch swiftly cutting Ukraine on default worries.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine triggered flurry of credit rating moves on Friday. S&amp;amp;P lowered Russia&amp;rsquo;s long-term foreign currency credit rating to &amp;lsquo;BB+&amp;rsquo; from &amp;lsquo;BBB-&amp;rsquo; and warned it could lower ratings further.</description></item><item><title>Alcohol should have cancer warning labels, say doctors and researchers pushing to raise awareness of risk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db4ceec450f920d000aba5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db4ceec450f920d000aba5/</guid><description>Advocates of warning labels want Canadians to understand that alcohol is classified as a Group 1 carcinogen and one of the top causes of preventable cancer.
Summary Stockwell wants to change that, and he and other health experts are advocating for cancer warning labels on alcohol containers. Tim Stockwell, a senior scientist with the Canadian Institute for Substance Use Research at the University of Victoria, is among the researchers and doctors pushing for cancer warning labels on alcohol.</description></item></channel></rss>