<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dies on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dies/</link><description>Recent content in dies on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 11:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stephen Wilhite: Creator of the GIF dies from Covid-19 at age 74</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c51dfc94fc962429eab42/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 11:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c51dfc94fc962429eab42/</guid><description>Programmer once clarified that ‘jif’ was the correct pronunciation of his famous file format. Stephen Wilhite came up with Graphics Interchange Format.
Highlights Programmer once clarified that ‘jif’ was the correct pronunciation of his famous file format. Programmer Stephen Wilhite came up with Graphics Interchange Format in the 1980s. He worked for CompuServe at the time, which is now used for animated internet memes and jokes, when he worked for the company.</description></item><item><title>Deputy Sergeant dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 06:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</guid><description>A deputy sergeant has reportedly died as she worked to help those in the Eastland community evacuate the recent catastrophic wildfires happening in West Texas.
Highlights Deputy Sergeant Barbara Fenley dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents. Fenley was last heard from as she was headed to check on an elderly individual while massive flames continued to move across the area. She leaves behind her husband and three children.</description></item><item><title>Snow leopard dies at Illinois zoo after contracting Covid-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</guid><description>A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois.
Summary (CNN) A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois. before death, according to a Rilu, an 11-year-old snow leopard, struggled with Covid-19 induced pneumoniabefore death, according to a post on the Miller Park Zoo verified Instagram account. &amp;ldquo;Rilu arrived at the Miller Park Zoo in 2011 from the Oklahoma City Zoo,&amp;rdquo; the post said.</description></item><item><title>Harry Reid, former Senate majority leader and Democratic kingmaker, dies at 82 - The Nevada Independent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</guid><description>Over more than three decades of service in Congress, Reid earned a reputation for fighting relentlessly to protect his home state and everyday Americans. As Senate Democratic leader for a dozen years, he played an instrumental role in passing the Affordable Care Act and shepherding through Congress pivotal economic recovery legislation in the wake of the Great Recession.
Summary He also turned the Nevada State Democratic Party into a well-oiled political operation — nicknamed the Reid Machine — responsible for securing numerous Democratic victories in close races over the last decade.</description></item><item><title>John Madden, football legend, dies at 85</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbcf4c809e5182b7aa7d4b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbcf4c809e5182b7aa7d4b/</guid><description>Summary The NFL announced Madden’s passing today. Madden’s influence on the sport of football is impossible to overstate. But as great a coach as he was, he did more for the sport after he retired from coaching. The youngest generation of football fans that can’t even remember him as a broadcaster, let alone as a coach, is still influenced by Madden’s giant presence in the sport. John Madden may have been the single most influential person in the history of the sport of football.</description></item></channel></rss>