<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dies on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dies/</link><description>Recent content in dies on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:08:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prisma Health employee dies after mental patient strikes groin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0bb3ef5fe9a141ffbd445/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 15:08:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0bb3ef5fe9a141ffbd445/</guid><description>WIS has contacted Prisma Health for a statement.
Highlights A mental health technician was struck in the groin area by a patient on May 27. The patient, Imani Cox, 27, was trying to leave the hospital when she struck at least two staff members. Cox was charged with assault and battery-2nd degree and booked at the Sumter County Sheriff’s Office Detention Center. The detention center confirmed Cox is still in their custody.</description></item><item><title>2 adults, 3 kids found dead inside home, escaped Texas inmate may be connected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299cfac5aa952df53c41468/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 09:09:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299cfac5aa952df53c41468/</guid><description>A Texas inmate suspected of murdering five people after he escaped from a prison bus was killed by authorities on Thursday, officials said.
Highlights A 46-year-old convicted murderer Gonzalo Lopez was killed in a police shootout in Jourdanton, Texas, on June 2, 2022. Lopez allegedly killed an adult and four children while on the run, authorities said. Lopez, a convicted murderer, was added to Texas&amp;rsquo; 10 Most Wanted Fugitives List and a $50,000 reward was issued for his capture.</description></item><item><title>Yellowstone visitor dies after bison gores her, tosses her 10 feet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62976c95e0cecba2d87dedb2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 13:42:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62976c95e0cecba2d87dedb2/</guid><description>A woman visiting Yellowstone National Park died after a bison gored her and tossed her into the air, park officials said Tuesday.
Highlights The 25-year-old woman was visiting from Ohio. The woman approached the female bison Monday morning after it came close to a boardwalk at Black Sand Basin, near Old Faithful geyser. An estimated 2,300 to 5,500 bison live at the park, and they have injured more people than any other animal.</description></item><item><title>‘Goodfellas’ Star Ray Liotta Dies at 67</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fdedda65cf001017e21b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 20:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fdedda65cf001017e21b1/</guid><description>Ray Liotta has died. The &amp;lsquo;Goodfellas&amp;rsquo; star and &amp;lsquo;Field Of Dreams&amp;rsquo; actor was 67.
Highlights Actor Ray Liotta dies in his sleep in the Dominican Republic, where he was shooting the film Dangerous Waters. Liotta, 67, was engaged to be married to Jacy Nittolo. His career breakout came in the 1990 Martin Scorsese crime classic Goodfellas. He also starred with Taron Egerton in the Apple TV+ series Black Bird, recurred on Prime Video’s Hanna and starred opposite Jennifer Lopez in the 2016-18 NBC police drama Shades of Blue.</description></item><item><title>Vangelis, composer of Chariots of Fire and Blade Runner soundtracks, dies aged 79</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287af5644e9aa157e4a1917/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287af5644e9aa157e4a1917/</guid><description>Greek composer topped US charts and won an Oscar with Chariots of Fire’s uplifting piano-led theme
Highlights Vangelis won an Oscar for his 1981 Chariots of Fire soundtrack. Composer died in hospital in France where he was being treated for cancer. He was also composer to soundtrack the 2000 Olympic Games, the 2002 World Cup and the 2000 Sydney Olympics in Japan and South Korea. His score to Blade Runner is equally celebrated for its evocation of a sinister future Los Angeles, where “replicants and humans live awkwardly alongside one another, through the use of long, malevolent synth notes; saxophones and lush ambient passages enhance the film’s romantic and poignant moments.</description></item><item><title>Casey White manhunt ends in Indiana, accomplice Vicky White hospitalized, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279cc3fdd92052d282307db/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 02:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279cc3fdd92052d282307db/</guid><description>Vicky White, a former Alabama corrections officer, died of self-inflicted gunshot wound, authorities say. Casey White and his suspected accomplice, Vicky, have been on the run since April 29. They were captured after a
Highlights Vicky White, a former Alabama corrections officer, died Monday night from self-inflicted gunshot wounds. Casey White, the fugitive inmate awaiting trial for capital murder, was arrested in Evansville, Indiana. The pair had been on the run since April 29 when the 56-year-old jailer told the Alabama jailer that she was transporting the inmate for a mental evaluation.</description></item><item><title>Tourist dies after 250-foot fall from cliff on treacherous Hawaii trail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625205308323d2c4d0e8c515/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 22:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625205308323d2c4d0e8c515/</guid><description>Officials have tried to stop the spread of online videos luring people to the steep ridges of the mountain range.
Highlights The man fell 250 feet while hiking near the third peak of Mount Olomana. At least five others have died on the trail since 2011. The trail is a treacherous, narrow path that snakes along steep cliffs to a series of peaks. Local rescue crews have been dispatched to the trail five times this year and responded to 13 calls in 2021, a fire department spokesperson said.</description></item><item><title>Palestinian baby dies after treatment delayed by Israeli blockade of Gaza</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62480629b2eefebe79cfac36/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62480629b2eefebe79cfac36/</guid><description>Fatima al-Masri, a 19-month-old with a hole in her heart, waited five months for Israel to issue a permit to allow her to travel to Jerusalem for treatment
Highlights Fatima al-Masri, 19 months, died in Gaza after waiting for five months for a permit to leave the blockaded enclave for treatment. She was diagnosed last year with a hole in the heart and died on Friday. Human rights groups say Israel’s blockade of Gaza was responsible for her death.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Wilhite: Creator of the GIF dies from Covid-19 at age 74</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c51dfc94fc962429eab42/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 11:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c51dfc94fc962429eab42/</guid><description>Programmer once clarified that ‘jif’ was the correct pronunciation of his famous file format. Stephen Wilhite came up with Graphics Interchange Format.
Highlights Programmer once clarified that ‘jif’ was the correct pronunciation of his famous file format. Programmer Stephen Wilhite came up with Graphics Interchange Format in the 1980s. He worked for CompuServe at the time, which is now used for animated internet memes and jokes, when he worked for the company.</description></item><item><title>Deputy Sergeant dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 06:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</guid><description>A deputy sergeant has reportedly died as she worked to help those in the Eastland community evacuate the recent catastrophic wildfires happening in West Texas.
Highlights Deputy Sergeant Barbara Fenley dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents. Fenley was last heard from as she was headed to check on an elderly individual while massive flames continued to move across the area. She leaves behind her husband and three children.</description></item><item><title>Snow leopard dies at Illinois zoo after contracting Covid-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</guid><description>A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois.
Summary (CNN) A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois. before death, according to a Rilu, an 11-year-old snow leopard, struggled with Covid-19 induced pneumoniabefore death, according to a post on the Miller Park Zoo verified Instagram account. &amp;ldquo;Rilu arrived at the Miller Park Zoo in 2011 from the Oklahoma City Zoo,&amp;rdquo; the post said.</description></item><item><title>Harry Reid, former Senate majority leader and Democratic kingmaker, dies at 82 - The Nevada Independent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</guid><description>Over more than three decades of service in Congress, Reid earned a reputation for fighting relentlessly to protect his home state and everyday Americans. As Senate Democratic leader for a dozen years, he played an instrumental role in passing the Affordable Care Act and shepherding through Congress pivotal economic recovery legislation in the wake of the Great Recession.
Summary He also turned the Nevada State Democratic Party into a well-oiled political operation — nicknamed the Reid Machine — responsible for securing numerous Democratic victories in close races over the last decade.</description></item><item><title>John Madden, football legend, dies at 85</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbcf4c809e5182b7aa7d4b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbcf4c809e5182b7aa7d4b/</guid><description>Summary The NFL announced Madden’s passing today. Madden’s influence on the sport of football is impossible to overstate. But as great a coach as he was, he did more for the sport after he retired from coaching. The youngest generation of football fans that can’t even remember him as a broadcaster, let alone as a coach, is still influenced by Madden’s giant presence in the sport. John Madden may have been the single most influential person in the history of the sport of football.</description></item></channel></rss>