<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>union on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/union/</link><description>Recent content in union on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/union/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple store in Maryland becomes third to launch union drive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717ea261fb248308b43d1f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717ea261fb248308b43d1f/</guid><description>Employees at the Towson Mall store say they want a voice on coronavirus safety, scheduling, pay and other topics.
Highlights Workers at the Towson Mall store near Baltimore have been drumming up support for nearly a year. They say they have signatures from more than 65 percent of employees who are likely to be eligible, giving them a “supermajority” that would be difficult for the company to overcome. The union drive is the latest sign of a reinvigorated labor movement.</description></item><item><title>‘Monstrous, Monstrous Acts': Ex-Boston Police Union President Pleads Guilty to Child Rape</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626988a4dd8ada9810ac5526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 18:17:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626988a4dd8ada9810ac5526/</guid><description>A former head of Boston&amp;rsquo;s police union facing a total of 33 charges in connection with the rape and abuse of six children over various periods of time beginning&amp;hellip;
Highlights Patrick Rose pleads guilty to 21 counts of child rape and sexual assault over 27-year period. He was sentenced to 10 to 13 years in prison, plus 10 years probation following his release. Prosecutors said most of the charges date back to the 1990s, but at least one was within the last two years.</description></item><item><title>Apple workers at New York's Grand Central store take steps to unionize</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625df010eb1bf025bee91249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 23:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625df010eb1bf025bee91249/</guid><description>Apple workers at the company&amp;rsquo;s Grand Central store in Manhattan have begun collecting signatures from workers, according to a website created by organizers.
Highlights Workers at Apple&amp;rsquo;s flagship Grand Central Terminal retail store in New York City are taking steps to unionize. Organizers are in the process of collecting signatures from workers, according to a website. Apple says it offers &amp;ldquo;very strong compensation and benefits&amp;rdquo; for full-time and part-time employees. Amazon workers at a Staten Island warehouse voted in the company&amp;rsquo;s first U.</description></item><item><title>UK says Russian sanctions could be lifted with Ukraine withdrawal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62400e4b8df569ee2d215fbc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62400e4b8df569ee2d215fbc/</guid><description>British foreign minister Liz Truss says sanctions imposed on Russian individuals and companies could be lifted if Russia withdraws from Ukraine and commits to end aggression, the Telegraph newspaper reported on Saturday.
Highlights British foreign minister says sanctions could be lifted if Russia withdraws from Ukraine. Britain and other nations are using economic sanctions to punish Russia for invading Ukraine. British government says it has imposed sanctions on Russian individuals and businesses with more than $650 million worth of assets in the region.</description></item><item><title>Amazon warehouse workers on Staten Island refile union petition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 03:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</guid><description>The group, called Amazon Labor Union, is looking to organize workers across four company warehouses on Staten Island.
Summary A labor group seeking to organize Amazon warehouse workers on New York&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island has refiled a union petition with the National Labor Relations Board, the agency confirmed Wednesday. The group, known as the Amazon Labor Union, first filed its request for a union vote in late October with signatures from more than 2,000 employees.</description></item></channel></rss>