<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>union on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/union/</link><description>Recent content in union on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/union/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK says Russian sanctions could be lifted with Ukraine withdrawal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62400e4b8df569ee2d215fbc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62400e4b8df569ee2d215fbc/</guid><description>British foreign minister Liz Truss says sanctions imposed on Russian individuals and companies could be lifted if Russia withdraws from Ukraine and commits to end aggression, the Telegraph newspaper reported on Saturday.
Highlights British foreign minister says sanctions could be lifted if Russia withdraws from Ukraine. Britain and other nations are using economic sanctions to punish Russia for invading Ukraine. British government says it has imposed sanctions on Russian individuals and businesses with more than $650 million worth of assets in the region.</description></item><item><title>Amazon warehouse workers on Staten Island refile union petition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 03:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</guid><description>The group, called Amazon Labor Union, is looking to organize workers across four company warehouses on Staten Island.
Summary A labor group seeking to organize Amazon warehouse workers on New York&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island has refiled a union petition with the National Labor Relations Board, the agency confirmed Wednesday. The group, known as the Amazon Labor Union, first filed its request for a union vote in late October with signatures from more than 2,000 employees.</description></item></channel></rss>