<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>million on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/million/</link><description>Recent content in million on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/million/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DOJ moves to seize 2 planes worth more than $400 million from Russian oligarch Roman Abramovich</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eec052b1b9045d31665cb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629eec052b1b9045d31665cb/</guid><description>The planned seizure of jets belonging to Russian oligarch Roman Abramovich is the latest U.S. government response to the invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights The Boeing 787-8 Dreamliner and a Gulfstream G650ER are valued at more than $400 million. The Commerce Department&amp;rsquo;s Bureau of Industry is seeking penalties of up to twice the value of the aircraft. The move is the latest in a series of sanctions and economic attacks by the U.</description></item><item><title>Real estate agents got $3.9 billion in Covid relief PPP loans. The housing market boomed, but few repaid the loans.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629c190b83b4af82c20b3215/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 02:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629c190b83b4af82c20b3215/</guid><description>Real estate firms with one worker got $3.9 billion in government-approved Paycheck Protection Program (PPP) loans. But during Covid, the housing market boomed.
Highlights Gary Goldberg, a Santa Barbara, California, real estate agent, sold more than $27 million worth of luxury homes during the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s first year. Federal records show he also applied for and received two loans totaling $95,832 via the federal government’s Covid relief Paycheck Protection Program. So far $3.</description></item><item><title>Man mistakenly sent 46.3 mil. yen in COVID funds gambles it all away</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283cb2bdc47f448629ccd87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283cb2bdc47f448629ccd87/</guid><description>A 24-year-old man mistakenly sent 46.3 million yen ($360,000) in COVID-19 relief money by the western Japan town he resides in, says he gambled it all away on overseas casino sites, sources close to the matter say.
Highlights A 24-year-old man mistakenly sent 46.3 million yen ($360,000) in COVID-19 relief money by the western Japan town he resides in, says he gambled it all away on overseas casino sites. The man is unlikely to be able to return the money transferred to him in error by the town of Abu, Yamaguchi Prefecture, according to his lawyer.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717187170404dccf614c0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 18:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717187170404dccf614c0d/</guid><description>The US labor market remained on fire in March with a record 4.5 million workers quitting their jobs, new data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed Tuesday.
Highlights The number of quits increased most significantly in the professional and business services sector, as well as construction. The overall quits rate moved up to 3%, a level not seen since December 2021. The job openings rate inched back up to 7.</description></item><item><title>More than one million African children protected by first malaria vaccine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262f0d3fc1063078c022c5d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 18:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262f0d3fc1063078c022c5d/</guid><description>More than a million children in Ghana, Kenya and Malawi have now received at least one dose of the first anti-malaria vaccine, the World Health Organization said Thursday.
Highlights More than a million children in Ghana, Kenya and Malawi have now received at least one dose of the first anti-malaria vaccine. The &amp;ldquo;breakthrough&amp;rdquo; RTS,S vaccine was pioneered in Malawi in April 2019 and found to be safe and to substantially reduce severe cases of the disease.</description></item><item><title>U.S. to release 1 million barrels of oil per day from reserves to help cut gas prices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245e1ee567603ff5e9fa40c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245e1ee567603ff5e9fa40c/</guid><description>The White House on Thursday announced that the U.S. will release 1 million barrels of oil per day from strategic reserves.
Highlights President Joe Biden plans to tap the nation&amp;rsquo;s Strategic Petroleum Reserve for the next six months. Oil prices dropped Thursday after reports surfaced Wednesday evening suggesting such a move was imminent. The announcement comes as the White House looks for ways to combat a spike in energy prices caused by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>U.S. detects highly lethal bird flu in Wisconsin egg-laying chickens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fafbdfdd3f89325ee355e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 21:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fafbdfdd3f89325ee355e/</guid><description>A commercial flock of 2.75 million egg-laying chickens in Wisconsin will be culled to prevent the spread of a highly lethal form of avian flu after birds on the farm tested positive for the disease, state officials said on Monday.
Highlights A commercial flock of 2.75 million egg-laying chickens in Wisconsin will be culled to prevent the spread of a highly lethal form of avian flu. The Wisconsin culls would bring to about 6.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19: Surge in Hong Kong coronavirus cases pushes neighbouring Chinese city of Shenzhen into lockdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f32feacb8f0ef4095ee9c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f32feacb8f0ef4095ee9c/</guid><description>Although infection numbers on the mainland are relatively low, the authorities are enforcing a &amp;quot;zero tolerance&amp;quot; strategy to find and quarantine every infected person, and have imposed fresh restrictions in a number of areas.
Highlights Authorities reported 1,938 new cases on the Chinese mainland on Sunday, more than triple the previous day&amp;rsquo;s total. Hong Kong authorities are enforcing a &amp;lsquo;zero tolerance&amp;rsquo; strategy to find and isolate every infected person. Access to Shanghai has been restricted with bus services suspended and a negative test required from anyone wanting to enter.</description></item><item><title>Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher pledge to match up to $3 million in aid for Ukrainian refugees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222f0feb7170ee61678538f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 05:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222f0feb7170ee61678538f/</guid><description>Actors Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher have pledged to match up to $3 million in aid to displaced Ukrainians.
Highlights Actors Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutcher have pledged to match up to $3 million in aid to displaced Ukrainians. More than 1 million people have already fled Ukraine in a rapid exodus more than a week after Russia invaded and bombarded key cities across the country. Kunis: &amp;ldquo;The events that have unfolded in Ukraine are devastating.</description></item><item><title>$1 million bounty on Putin offered by Russian businessman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fa5e271132ab2a2f4f4d4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 17:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fa5e271132ab2a2f4f4d4/</guid><description>The Russian entrepreneur said the Russian president came to power by &amp;quot;blowing up apartment buildings in Russia.&amp;quot;
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin was offered to military officers by Russian entrepreneur Alex Konanykhin in a post he published on social media this week. &amp;ldquo;Putin is not the Russian president as he came to power as the result of a special operation of a. special operation in Russia, then violated the Constitution by.</description></item><item><title>Buffett's Berkshire bought about $1 billion worth of Activision shares before Microsoft deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b44db53730ab3b3948ad1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 06:15:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b44db53730ab3b3948ad1/</guid><description>Berkshire Hathaway jumped into Activision Blizzard after a state lawsuit alleging a sexist culture sent the stock price down.
Highlights Berkshire Hathaway purchased $1 billion worth of shares in Activision Blizzard in the fourth quarter. Microsoft agreed to buy the video-game publisher for $68.7 billion. The California Department of Fair Employment and Housing filed a suit alleging a sexist culture. Berkshire owns 14.66 million shares valued at $975 million as of the end of 2021, a regulatory filing shows.</description></item><item><title>Delta loses $408 million; 8,000 employees contract Covid over the last four weeks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0bd331bbfc302012403ef/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0bd331bbfc302012403ef/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines lost $408 million in the final quarter of 2021, dragged down by a Covid-19 surge that rocked the airline in December, and the carrier predicted Thursday that it will suffer one more quarterly loss before travel perks up in spring and summer.
Summary CEO Ed Bastian said 8,000 employees have contracted Covid-19 over the last four weeks. Earlier this week, United Airlines CEO Scott Kirby sent a letter to employees saying that 3,000 employees had tested positive for Covid-19.</description></item><item><title>Tim Cook earned over 1,400 times the average Apple worker in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d960bd299b7b512d0f9cfe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d960bd299b7b512d0f9cfe/</guid><description>Apple Inc boss Tim Cook&amp;rsquo;s pay in 2021 was 1,447 times that of the average employee at the tech giant, a filing on Thursday showed, fueled by stock awards that helped him earn a total of nearly $100 million.
Summary Apple CEO Tim Cook attends the premiere for season two of the television series &amp;ldquo;Ted Lasso&amp;rdquo; at Pacific Design Center in West Hollywood, California, U.S. July 15, 2021. In 2021, the median pay for employees was $68,254, Apple said, adding it had selected a new median employee for comparison due to changes in hiring and compensation.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis admits to finding 1 million stockpiled COVID-19 tests in warehouse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d759097b1c95286e64ad35/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d759097b1c95286e64ad35/</guid><description>The explosive allegation comes as thousands of people wait hours in long lines to receive a COVID-19 test.
Summary UPDATE, January 6, 10:55am:In a press conference Thursday morning, Governor DeSantis admitted state officials found 1 million unused COVID-19 tests in a warehouse. The admission came as DeSantis unveiled a plan to get 1 million COVID-19 tests to Florida’s seniors. ORIGINAL REPORT, January 5:LEE COUNTY, Fla. – Florida Commissioner of Agriculture Nikki Fried announced Wednesday in Lee County that she believes nearly one million COVID-19 tests have been stockpiled by the state’s executive branch of government.</description></item><item><title>$4 million worth of heroin seized by U.S. Navy in Arabian Sea</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cef0e0f536cbfc298016a0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cef0e0f536cbfc298016a0/</guid><description>United States navy vessels seized 849 pounds of heroin in the Arabian Sea worth some $4 million, in a major bust by the international maritime operation in the
Summary United States navy vessels seized 849 pounds of heroin in the Arabian Sea worth some $4 million, in a major bust by the international maritime operation in the region, officials said Thursday. The USS Tempest and USS Typhoon seized the drugs hidden aboard a stateless fishing vessel plying Mideast waters, the international task force said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Fossil of a giant millipede reveals 'the biggest bug that ever lived'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c891a24171aed7c52c0433/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c891a24171aed7c52c0433/</guid><description>A giant millipede, nearly as long as a small car, once crawled around what is now northern England.
Summary (CNN) A fossil of a giant millipede found on a beach in northern England has revealed the &amp;ldquo;biggest bug that ever lived,&amp;rdquo; paleontologists say. The fossil was discovered in January 2018 in a chunk of sandstone that had fallen from a cliff onto the beach at Howick Bay in Northumberland. &amp;ldquo;It was an incredibly exciting find, but the fossil is so large it took four of us to carry it up the cliff face,&amp;rdquo; said Davies in a news statement.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong police seize record 1.2 tonnes of ketamine worth HK $ 840 million in biggest single bust , 4 arrested in raid on pier</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8757dd8712ba5f5cc65b2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8757dd8712ba5f5cc65b2/</guid><description>Four suspects, aged 32 to 47, detained at Sam Ka Tsuen Ferry Pier in Yau Tong on Thursday morning.
Summary Police seized more than a tonne of ketamine in a single operation. Photo: Xiaomei Chen READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>