<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>missed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missed/</link><description>Recent content in missed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scotland missed 100% clean electricity consumption in 2020 by only 1.4%</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfdfedede570939739675d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfdfedede570939739675d/</guid><description>In 2011, Scotland set a target of reaching 100% gross clean electricity consumption in 2020, and it almost made it by reaching 98.6%.
Summary In 2011, Scotland set a target of reaching 100% clean electricity consumption in 2020. And last year, the country almost reached its target – 98.6% of gross electricity consumption came from renewable sources, according to the Scottish government’s December energy statement. The BBC notes:In 2019, Scotland met 90.</description></item><item><title>Woman runs onto Phoenix tarmac to stop plane she missed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccda7dfd57757688763a88/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccda7dfd57757688763a88/</guid><description>Instead of waiting for the next flight, police say she ran through the glass doors separating the passenger area and the secure airfield.
Summary PHOENIX (Gray News) – A woman is facing charges after running onto the tarmac at Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport. According to the police report, the door to the jetway was already secured when Vickie Meyers, of St. Louis, Missouri, tried to catch a flight Sunday afternoon.</description></item></channel></rss>