<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>biden on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/biden/</link><description>Recent content in biden on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/biden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biden to devote $2.1 bln of new funds to strengthen US food supply chain.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298730ace6e941a02e6aa8b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298730ace6e941a02e6aa8b/</guid><description>The Biden Administration on Wednesday will announce $2.1 billion in new funding to bolster food supply chains, including initiatives to expand small- and
Highlights The Biden Administration on Wednesday will announce $2.1 billion in new funding to bolster food supply chains. The funds will also be used to finance new infrastructure such as cold storage facilities and to assist farmers shifting to organic production. Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack plans to focus on the importance of moving US food supplies away from dominance by a few highly concentrated businesses.</description></item><item><title>Annadale man who allegedly called for ‘extermination’ of Biden supporters gets 3 years on gun charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628680e11b0f18d6d51254ea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 17:40:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628680e11b0f18d6d51254ea/</guid><description>Brian Maiorana, 55, was arrested late last year after allegedly calling for the ‘extermination’ of Democrats and their families. Authorities at the time discovered at the house a semiautomatic Glock pistol, two magazines
Highlights Brian Maiorana, 55, pleaded guilty to being a felon in possession of a firearm in April 2021. Authorities at the time discovered at the house a semiautomatic Glock pistol, two magazines of.45-caliber ammunition, parts for a.22-caliber firearm and additional ammunition.</description></item><item><title>Biden to require US-made steel, iron for infrastructure</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d9e06074170249a8f2e32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d9e06074170249a8f2e32/</guid><description>New guidance being issued Monday will require material for projects like bridges, highways and broadband internet funded by last year’s infrastructure package be produced in the U.S. President Joe Biden hopes to create more jobs, ease supply chain strains
Highlights Biden to require US-made steel, iron for infrastructure for infrastructure projects. New guidance being issued Monday will require material for projects like bridges, highways and broadband internet funded by last year’s infrastructure package be produced in the U.</description></item><item><title>Biden administration announces it will resume onshore oil and gas lease sales with higher royalty rate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b235f006fb22d490d16df/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 20:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b235f006fb22d490d16df/</guid><description>The Department of Interior announced Friday it planned to resume onshore oil and gas lease sales on federal land.
Highlights The new royalty rate is 18.75% instead of 12.5%. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time the rate has been increased. The increase comes after a plan to increase the rate was put on hold last year. The rate is higher than the previous rate that was used to calculate the amount of oil and gas per capita consumption in the U.</description></item><item><title>New federal rule requires serial numbers, background checks for ‘ghost gun’ kits</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254a82e3e45f1f08639f5d8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 22:14:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254a82e3e45f1f08639f5d8/</guid><description>The aim is to rein in privately made firearms without serial numbers. They&amp;rsquo;re increasingly cropping up at crime scenes across the U.S. The new rule requires homemade gun kits to be treated like other guns made and sold in the U
Highlights The Biden administration is expected to come out within days with its long-awaited ghost gun rule. The aim is to rein in privately made firearms without serial numbers. The rule requires homemade gun kits to be treated like other guns made and sold in the U.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Joe Biden, Hillary Clinton and senior White House officials banned from entering Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230f3844097207c39ce6940/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 20:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230f3844097207c39ce6940/</guid><description>Joining Joe Biden and Hillary Clinton on a Kremlin &amp;quot;stop list&amp;quot; are the president&amp;rsquo;s secretary of state Antony Blinken, CIA chief William Burns, the US defence secretary Lloyd Austin, and national security adviser Jake Sullivan.
Highlights Joe Biden has not visited Russia since 2011, when he was vice president to Barack Obama. Joining the 79-year-old on a Kremlin &amp;ldquo;stop list&amp;rdquo; are his secretary of state Antony Blinken, CIA chief William Burns, defence secretary Lloyd Austin, and national security adviser Jake Sullivan.</description></item><item><title>Biden Administration Expands Sanctions Against Russia, Cutting Off U.S. Transactions With Central Bank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d030e588efbe3f6da1cca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 17:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d030e588efbe3f6da1cca/</guid><description>The new sanctions effectively prohibit Americans from doing any business with Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank as well as freezes its assets within the United States.
Highlights The Biden administration announced additional sanctions against Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank on Monday. The move prohibits Americans from doing any business with the bank as well as freezes its assets within the U.S. The new sanctions will also target the National Wealth Fund of the Russian Federation and the Ministry of Finance.</description></item><item><title>Biden says it's possible U.S. would sanction Putin personally if he invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 02:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden,&amp;hellip;
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden, speaking to reporters in Washington, said there would be &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; for Putin if there is a Russian invasion. Earlier Tuesday, U.S. officials said Washington is prepared to impose sanctions and export controls on critical sectors of the Russian economy if Putin invades Ukraine, the Wall Street Journal reported.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian President pushes back on Biden: 'There are no minor incursions'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea05be5207a8818afc9f3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 01:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea05be5207a8818afc9f3d/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky publicly pushed back Thursday on US President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments that a &amp;quot;minor incursion&amp;quot; by Russia into Ukraine would prompt a lesser response than a full-scale invasion, in an implicit rebuke of Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments.
Summary (CNN) Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky publicly pushed back Thursday on US President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments that a &amp;ldquo;minor incursion&amp;rdquo; by Russia into Ukraine would prompt a lesser response than a full-scale invasion, in an implicit rebuke of Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments.</description></item><item><title>Walmart, Kroger raise at-home Covid test prices after White House agreement expires</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d614fd7457ed8d5de65850/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d614fd7457ed8d5de65850/</guid><description>Walmart and Kroger raised the price of Abbott&amp;rsquo;s at-home Covid-19 test kit after an agreement with the White House to sell the tests at a reduced price expired.
Summary Walmart and Kroger raised the price of Abbott&amp;rsquo;s at-home Covid-19 test kit after an agreement with the White House to sell the tests at a reduced price expired, the companies said Tuesday. Kroger listed the tests for $23.99. Packages of Abbott Laboratories&amp;rsquo; BinaxNOW Covid-19 Antigen Self Test are stacked on a shelf in a store in N.</description></item><item><title>Putin threatened Biden with a complete collapse of US-Russia relations if he launches more sanctions over Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf7d7fe65e7e680657d79c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf7d7fe65e7e680657d79c/</guid><description>Putin told Biden in their call that sanctions over Ukraine &amp;quot;could lead to a complete breakdown in ties between our countries,&amp;quot; a Kremlin aide said.
Summary Putin told Biden that sanctions over Ukraine could mean a total rupture in US-Russia relations. Biden urged Putin to ease tensions but said the US would respond if Russia invades. The Kremlin aide Yuri Ushakov said after the call that Putin told Biden that sanctions &amp;ldquo;could lead to a complete breakdown in ties between our countries,&amp;rdquo; Reuters reported.</description></item><item><title>Pause on student loan payments is extended through May 1</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</guid><description>Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1.
Summary WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;ndash; The Biden administration is extending a student loan moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to put off debt payments during the pandemic. Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1. Interest rates will remain at 0% during that period, and debt collection efforts will be suspended.</description></item></channel></rss>