<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>biden on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/biden/</link><description>Recent content in biden on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 22:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/biden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Putin threatened Biden with a complete collapse of US-Russia relations if he launches more sanctions over Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cf7d7fe65e7e680657d79c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cf7d7fe65e7e680657d79c/</guid><description>Putin told Biden in their call that sanctions over Ukraine &amp;quot;could lead to a complete breakdown in ties between our countries,&amp;quot; a Kremlin aide said.
Summary Putin told Biden that sanctions over Ukraine could mean a total rupture in US-Russia relations. Biden urged Putin to ease tensions but said the US would respond if Russia invades. The Kremlin aide Yuri Ushakov said after the call that Putin told Biden that sanctions &amp;ldquo;could lead to a complete breakdown in ties between our countries,&amp;rdquo; Reuters reported.</description></item><item><title>Pause on student loan payments is extended through May 1</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</guid><description>Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1.
Summary WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;ndash; The Biden administration is extending a student loan moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to put off debt payments during the pandemic. Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1. Interest rates will remain at 0% during that period, and debt collection efforts will be suspended.</description></item></channel></rss>