<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>firearms on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/firearms/</link><description>Recent content in firearms on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:19:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/firearms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Federal operation nabs nearly 43,000 illegal gun silencers shipped from China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f57d8adfa582f8c16d02a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:19:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f57d8adfa582f8c16d02a/</guid><description>Operation Silent Night has led to the arrest of felons and domestic extremists who were found with illegal firearm silencers bought from China, officials say.
Highlights Operation Silent Night has seized 42,888 illegal imported silencers and 4,868 firearms, ICE says. The operation has led to 204 arrests, including felons and domestic extremists, officials say. Chinese websites targeted by this operation don’t require buyers to go through the lengthy background check process.</description></item><item><title>More guns are being stolen out of cars in alarming trend across the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a6c3c9148e73e81069aa2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 13:45:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a6c3c9148e73e81069aa2/</guid><description>More guns are being stolen out of vehicles in many U.S. cities, according to a new data analysis, which was first obtained and independently verified by NBC New
Highlights Everytown for Gun Safety analyzed FBI crime data from 2011 to 2020. At least 180 cities saw a rise in gun thefts from vehicles, the nonprofit says. It&amp;rsquo;s an alarming trend as shootings rise nationwide, propelled in large part by firearms obtained illegally.</description></item><item><title>Police seize over 60 guns linked to man accused of making untraceable firearms in Salem</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235f2fe435ad0ddd64485d2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 15:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235f2fe435ad0ddd64485d2/</guid><description>SALEM, Ore. — A Salem man was indicted for distributing counterfeit prescription pills containing fentanyl and running the state’s largest homemade firearm or &amp;quot;ghost gun&amp;quot; workshop out of his basement. Tyler Ray Harnden, 29, was indicted on multiple felony charges, including drug possession and illegally possessing a gun as a convicted felon. Investigators served a search warrant at Harnden’s south Salem home on February 16 and found a large firearm manufacturing operation.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keeper pleads guilty to seditious conspiracy for Jan. 6 attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622032c56c05a31a2b20e9f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622032c56c05a31a2b20e9f1/</guid><description>Joshua James, 34, of Arab, Alabama, pleaded guilty to seditious conspiracy charges on Wednesday as part of deal with prosecutors contingent on his cooperation.
Highlights Joshua James, 34, pleads guilty to seditious conspiracy charges in exchange for reduced offense level. Plea deal is the first of its kind for a Jan. 6 defendant. James admitted he and others collected firearms at hotels on the outskirts of Washington, D.C., and were ready to use them to prevent Biden from becoming president.</description></item><item><title>13 states have backed the Mexican government's lawsuit against a group of US gun manufacturers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fff44eec5861ae80dfcf13/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 16:16:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fff44eec5861ae80dfcf13/</guid><description>The attorneys general of 13 states and Washington DC this week expressed support for a federal lawsuit by the Mexican government that accuses a group of American gun manufacturers of facilitating the trafficking of weapons to criminals in Mexico, fueling gun violence.
Highlights The AGs say a federal law protecting gun manufacturers does not apply in this case. The gunmakers, along with a distributor, use &amp;ldquo;reckless and corrupt gun dealers and dangerous and illegal sales practices that the cartels rely on to get their guns,&amp;rdquo; the lawsuit claims.</description></item></channel></rss>