<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>victims on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/victims/</link><description>Recent content in victims on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 09:10:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/victims/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wray: FBI blocked planned cyberattack on children's hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62987e5a543e99ca166906d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62987e5a543e99ca166906d3/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The FBI thwarted a planned cyberattack on a children&amp;rsquo;s hospital in Boston that was to have been carried out by hackers sponsored by the Iranian government, FBI Director Christopher Wray said Wednesday.
Highlights FBI Director Christopher Wray says his agents thwarted a planned cyberattack on a Boston children&amp;rsquo;s hospital that was to have been carried out by hackers sponsored by the Iranian government. Wray told a Boston College cybersecurity conference that his agents learned of the planned digital attack from an unspecified intelligence partner and got Boston Children’s Hospital the information it needed last summer to block what would have been “one of the most despicable cyberattacks I’ve seen” The speech took place as the FBI continues to combat ransomware attacks from criminal gangs, a continuing concern for U.</description></item><item><title>Multiple people shot in Tennessee, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629363abfe557847be52d29e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 12:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629363abfe557847be52d29e/</guid><description>Multiple people were shot on Saturday night during an exchange of gunfire in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, police said.
Highlights At least six people were injured in an exchange of gunfire in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, police said. Police officers were patrolling downtown at about 10:48 p.m. local time when they &amp;ldquo;observed multiple parties exchanging gunfire and numerous people fleeing the area&amp;rdquo; Most of the victims were in their teens or early 20s.</description></item><item><title>Nine Shot, One Dead in San Bernardino County</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628986272d7363eecf2511da/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628986272d7363eecf2511da/</guid><description>One person was killed and eight others were injured Friday night when shots were fired at a large party in Highland. Here are updates on the investigation in&amp;hellip;
Highlights One person was killed and eight others were injured Friday night when shots were fired at a large party at a strip mall hookah lounge in the San Bernardino County community of Highland. The shooting in the city east of San Bernardino was reported just before midnight in the 3600 block of East Highland Avenue.</description></item><item><title>A 17-year-old boy died by suicide hours after being scammed. The FBI says it's part of a troubling increase in 'sextortion' cases.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ac448f30216d66222fa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288ac448f30216d66222fa9/</guid><description>Ryan Last received a message on a school night in February from someone he believed to be a girl.
Highlights A 17-year-old California teen was targeted by a cybercriminal posing as a young girl. The FBI says there were over 18,000 sextortion-related complaints in 2021, with losses in excess of $13 million. Experts say young males are especially vulnerable to the scams. Parents should be aware of the scams and talk to their kids about what they&amp;rsquo;re doing online, experts say.</description></item><item><title>San Jose police officer faces charges for masturbating during disturbance call: D.A.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ea106b350a098a158bb22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 18:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ea106b350a098a158bb22/</guid><description>A San Jose police officer faces indecent exposure charges for allegedly masturbating at a family&amp;rsquo;s home while responding to a disturbance call last month, officials say.
Highlights Matthew Dominguez, 32, was arrested on Thursday, Santa Clara County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s office said. The incident took place April 21, when he and two other officers were sent to a home on a call that a family member, who is mentally ill, was being violent.</description></item><item><title>Colombia court says 5,733 people killed, disappeared in campaign against left-wing party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626621a4a8618f5dd51b323d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 04:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626621a4a8618f5dd51b323d/</guid><description>Some 5,733 people were killed or disappeared in Colombia as part of a campaign against the left-wing Patriotic Union (UP) party between 1984 and 2016, acts linked to paramilitaries with military backing, the country&amp;rsquo;s transitional justice tribunal said on Friday.
Highlights Some 5,733 people were killed or disappeared in Colombia as part of a campaign against the left-wing Patriotic Union (UP) party between 1984 and 2016. The attacks were often carried out by right-wing paramilitary gunmen, although there was also evidence of involvement of state agents.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in South Carolina mall shooting on house arrest after judge sets $25,000 bond</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</guid><description>The suspect in a South Carolina mall shooting in which nine people were wounded has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor after
Highlights Nine people were injured in a shooting in South Carolina early Sunday morning. The victims are ages 15 to 73. The suspect has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor. Police say no deaths have been reported in the shooting in Hampton County, South Carolina.</description></item><item><title>'You got rich off our dead bodies' opioid victims tell Purdue's Sacklers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ada1d06819d4181840eb5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ada1d06819d4181840eb5/</guid><description>Victims of America&amp;rsquo;s opioid epidemic confronted members of the Sackler family that owns Purdue Pharma on Thursday with wrenching stories of suffering they said was caused by the painkillers that built the company fortune.
Highlights Victims of U.S. opioid epidemic confronted Sackler family that owns Purdue Pharma on Thursday with wrenching stories of suffering they said was caused by the painkillers that built the company fortune. &amp;ldquo;You got rich off our dead bodies and told us it was our own fault for dying,&amp;rdquo; Ryan Hampton told Richard Sackler, a former board member.</description></item><item><title>Deputies: 3 arrested following violent outbreak at Neo-Nazi rally in Orlando</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fe3f0af0e31e22f2dd3325/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 09:11:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fe3f0af0e31e22f2dd3325/</guid><description>The Orange County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office arrested three people for an attack at an anti-Semitic rally in Central Florida.
Highlights Orange County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office arrested three people for an attack at an anti-Semitic rally in Central Florida. Joshua Terrell, 46, and Burt Colucci, 45, are facing charges of battery with a hate crime enhancement. Jason Brown, 47, is facing a charge of grand theft. The suspects are known members of the National Socialist Movement, according to deputies.</description></item><item><title>New York governor declares racism 'public health emergency' amid new anti-discrimination legislation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0b2e33dc16f8fc2f3f50e/</guid><description>New York Gov. Kathy Hochul declared racism a public health emergency and has implemented new laws to combat discrimination.
Summary Kathy Hochul has declared racism a &amp;ldquo;public health crisis,&amp;rdquo; signing an entire package of legislation Dec. 23 aimed at addressing discrimination and racial injustice in the state. &amp;ldquo;For far too long, communities of color in New York have been held back by systemic racism and inequitable treatment,&amp;rdquo; Hochul said in a statement last week.</description></item></channel></rss>