<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bail on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bail/</link><description>Recent content in bail on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 15:13:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Freedom Convoy’ leader says he just wants to go home after spending night in jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62110908c184c05d9ba9f847/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 15:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62110908c184c05d9ba9f847/</guid><description>‘My organizing days are over,’ Chris Barber said Friday, when he was granted bail.
Highlights ‘Freedom Convoy’ leader says he just wants to go home after spending night in jail. ‘My organizing days are over,’ Chris Barber said Friday, when he was granted bail. Barber agreed with the bail conditions that he can no longer support the protest verbally, on TV or online. Barber is charged with mischief, counselling to commit the offence of disobey court order.</description></item><item><title>Local BLM chapter posts bail for man charged with attempted murder of mayoral candidate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f398145d88ce574f204e9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f398145d88ce574f204e9/</guid><description>LOUISVILLE, Ky. (TND) — A man who is charged with the attempted murder of a mayoral candidate in Louisville is no longer in jail after a local Black Lives Matter chapter teamed up with a community bail fund to post his bail. Quintez Brown, 21, who is said to be a &amp;quot;social justice activist&amp;quot; running as a candidate for Louisville&amp;rsquo;s metro council, allegedly tried to assassinate Democrat mayoral candidateCraig Greenberg.</description></item><item><title>4 Alberta border protesters charged with conspiring to murder RCMP officers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d14abe3b73fe54fc2fbe8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d14abe3b73fe54fc2fbe8/</guid><description>The first 11 protesters to be arrested in connection to the Coutts, Alta., border blockade made their first court appearance Tuesday afternoon on charges that include conspiracy to murder, mischief and possession of a weapon.
Highlights At least 13 people have been arrested at the Coutts, Alta., border crossing in southern Alberta. Most face charges of mischief to property over $5,000 and possession of a weapon. A total of 13 have been charged with conspiracy to murder in relation to a protest against pandemic restrictions near the main U.</description></item></channel></rss>