<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>night on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/night/</link><description>Recent content in night on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 02:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/night/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Foo Fighters' Taylor Hawkins had 10 different substances in his system at the time of his death, Colombian official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fca50ca672241161dfff4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 02:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fca50ca672241161dfff4/</guid><description>Hawkins, 50, died in his hotel room in Bogotá, Colombia, on Friday, shortly before the Foo Fighters were set to perform.
Highlights Foo Fighters drummer Taylor Hawkins had 10 different substances in his system, Colombia&amp;rsquo;s attorney general says. Hawkins, 50, was found dead in his hotel room in Bogotá, Colombia, on Friday night. An exact cause of death was not announced, and the National Institute of Forensic Medicine continues to investigate.</description></item><item><title>New York City will begin removing homeless people from subways at night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 09:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</guid><description>Mayor says public fear of subways is driving riders from the system and announces more mental health support to homeless
Highlights New York leaders released a plan to strictly enforce rules on the New York City subway as part of an aggressive effort to remove homeless people from the city’s sprawling transit system. The plan comes in light of an uptick in felony assaults in the subway which, while rare, were up 25% in 2021 compared with 2019.</description></item></channel></rss>