<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>force on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/force/</link><description>Recent content in force on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 16:20:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/force/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thailand to give away one million free cannabis plants, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627be21a3b5c0635fdd3500d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 16:20:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627be21a3b5c0635fdd3500d/</guid><description>The Thai government will distribute one million free cannabis plants to households across the nation in June to mark a new rule allowing people to grow cannabis at home, its health minister has said.
Highlights Thailand to distribute one million free cannabis plants to households across the nation in June. Health Minister Anutin Charnvirakul announced the move in a Facebook post on May 8. The move is the latest step in Thailand’s plan to promote cannabis as a cash crop.</description></item><item><title>NATO Scrambling More Often in Response to Russian Jets Near Poland</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b4d87133f23fc29cb8fc5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 23:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b4d87133f23fc29cb8fc5/</guid><description>Russia is increasingly harassing NATO aircraft near Polish air space, reinforcing the need for both Polish and NATO air policing
Highlights Polish Air Force official: Russia is increasingly harassing NATO aircraft near Polish air space. Russian Su-35s, Su-27s, and MiG-29s from Belarus have approached air space multiple times since Ukraine invasion. Poland has taken on tremendous risk, hosting 10,500 allied troops in addition to 24/7 air patrol and surveillance. Poland also has a border with Ukraine to its southeast, but Russian jets battling Ukraine have yet to venture so close to NATO airspace.</description></item><item><title>China makes semi-secret delivery of missiles to Serbia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62531eadfc76d8c7af9149c4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 18:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62531eadfc76d8c7af9149c4/</guid><description>BELGRADE, Serbia (AP) — Russian ally Serbia took the delivery of a sophisticated Chinese anti-aircraft system in a veiled operation this weekend, amid Western concerns that an arms buildup in the Balkans at the time of the war in Ukraine could threaten the fragile peace in the region.
Highlights Six Chinese Air Force Y-20 transport planes landed at Belgrade’s commercial airport early Saturday, reportedly carrying HQ-22 surface-to-air missile systems for the Serbian military.</description></item><item><title>DA declines to charge Alameda police for death of Mario Gonzalez. Coroner ruled death a homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250ee01fcaee5df204566fc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 02:23:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250ee01fcaee5df204566fc/</guid><description>The Alameda County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office on Thursday determined there would be no charges against the officers involved in the death of 26-year-old Mario Gonzalez, according to the officers&amp;rsquo; attorney.
Highlights Mario Gonzalez, 26, stopped breathing after three officers sat on his back trying to arrest him. Alameda County District Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office determined there would be no charges against the officers involved in the death of 26-year-old Mario Gonzalez. DA O&amp;rsquo;Malley said she couldn&amp;rsquo;t prove beyond a reasonable doubt that the officers acted unlawfully.</description></item><item><title>$14M jury award for protesters could resonate around US.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624741691c879408404dc42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624741691c879408404dc42a/</guid><description>DENVER (AP) — A federal jury’s $14 million award to Denver protesters hit with pepper balls and a bag filled with lead during 2020 demonstrations over the police killing of George Floyd in Minneapolis could resonate nationwide as courts weigh more than two dozen similar lawsuits.
Highlights The jury found police used excessive force against protesters, violating their constitutional rights, and ordered the city of Denver to pay 12 who sued.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine still has 'significant majority' of its military aircraft -U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223455e5b1741458a5adda2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223455e5b1741458a5adda2/</guid><description>Ukraine still has a &amp;quot;significant majority&amp;quot; of its military aircraft available nine days after Russian forces started their invasion of the country, a U.S. defense official said on Friday.
Highlights Ukraine still has a “significant majority” of its military aircraft available nine days after Russian forces started their invasion of the country, a U.S. defense official said on Friday. The Pentagon has established a new hotline with Russia’s ministry of defense to prevent “miscalculation, military incidents and escalation” in the region.</description></item><item><title>For the first time ever, the NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia's ongoing invasion of Ukraine.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621945ea275bd3d32f600f59/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 21:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621945ea275bd3d32f600f59/</guid><description>For the first time, the NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s ongoing invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights NATO Response Force has been activated as a defensive measure in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The force consists of land, air, sea and special operations forces from the allies. It&amp;rsquo;s not clear how many troops the response force will contain. US President Joe Biden has been clear that US troops are deploying to eastern Europe to help bolster NATO countries nervous about Russia&amp;rsquo;s aggressive actions, and they will not be fighting in Ukraine, which is not a member of the NATO alliance.</description></item><item><title>White House calls Russian moves on Ukraine an invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country — a move that could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S.
Highlights Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country. The move could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S. said an invasion was already underway there. Western leaders said Tuesday that Russian troops have moved into rebel-held areas in eastern Ukraine after Putin&amp;rsquo;s recognition of their independence.</description></item><item><title>In wake of Astroworld tragedy, Houston, Harris County officials launch joint special events task force</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620903d25bc9494c44a4c415/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 13:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620903d25bc9494c44a4c415/</guid><description>Mayor Turner said the group will avoid studying what went wrong at the deadly 2021&amp;hellip;
Highlights Houston-Harris Special Events Task Force formed by Houston Mayor Sylvester Turner and Precinct 2 Commissioner Adrian Garcia. Ten concert-goers were killed and hundreds injured following a massive crowd surge at the Nov. 5 NRG Stadium concert. The city&amp;rsquo;s office of special events manages annually nearly 1,000 events attended by more than 10 million people. Turner: &amp;ldquo;The line of demarcation between the city and county properties is invisible to the public&amp;rdquo; The task force will make recommendations to improve communication, protocols and permitting requirements in Houston and Harris County &amp;ldquo;to ensure consistent operation standards for future events,&amp;rdquo; officials said.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine crisis: US rejects Russian demand to bar Ukraine from Nato</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2d1063e8c11bfc2e9fbe2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2d1063e8c11bfc2e9fbe2/</guid><description>Russia says the response does not address its concerns about Nato, but &amp;quot;gives hope&amp;quot; over other issues.
Highlights &amp;ldquo;There should be no doubt about our seriousness of purpose when it comes to diplomacy, and we&amp;rsquo;re acting with equal focus and force to bolster Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defences and prepare a swift united response to further Russian aggression,&amp;rdquo; he said. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>'Every indication' Putin plans force by mid-February: US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</guid><description>The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday.
Summary The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;I have no idea whether he&amp;rsquo;s made the ultimate decision, but we certainly see every indication that he is going to use military force sometime perhaps (between) now and the middle of February,&amp;rdquo; Deputy Secretary of State Wendy Sherman told a forum.</description></item></channel></rss>