<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>force on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/force/</link><description>Recent content in force on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/force/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine crisis: US rejects Russian demand to bar Ukraine from Nato</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2d1063e8c11bfc2e9fbe2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2d1063e8c11bfc2e9fbe2/</guid><description>Russia says the response does not address its concerns about Nato, but &amp;quot;gives hope&amp;quot; over other issues.
Highlights &amp;ldquo;There should be no doubt about our seriousness of purpose when it comes to diplomacy, and we&amp;rsquo;re acting with equal focus and force to bolster Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s defences and prepare a swift united response to further Russian aggression,&amp;rdquo; he said. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>'Every indication' Putin plans force by mid-February: US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2446ea01865fbe1db6e64/</guid><description>The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday.
Summary The United States believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin remains poised to use force against Ukraine by mid-February despite a pressure campaign to stop him, a top diplomat said Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;I have no idea whether he&amp;rsquo;s made the ultimate decision, but we certainly see every indication that he is going to use military force sometime perhaps (between) now and the middle of February,&amp;rdquo; Deputy Secretary of State Wendy Sherman told a forum.</description></item></channel></rss>