<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sunshield on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sunshield/</link><description>Recent content in sunshield on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 20:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sunshield/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>James Webb Completely and Successfully Unfolded</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9ed82c1ac588f35200db3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 20:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9ed82c1ac588f35200db3/</guid><description>Read the latest news about NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope.
Summary Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the primary mirror of James Webb Space TelescopeWebb Space Telescope final deployment underway NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope mirror deployment webcast is underway. James Webb Space Telescope launch a success NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope is successfully in space and beginning its monthlong trek to its L2 home about 1 million miles from Earth. James Webb Space Telescope on track during ascent The Ariane 5 rocket carrying NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope continues its 2nd stage burn to carry the telescope into space.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope completes tricky sunshield deployment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d533fe6c4d1903032ea0a1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d533fe6c4d1903032ea0a1/</guid><description>The James Webb Space Telescope has successfully deployed all five layers of its tennis-court-sized sunshield.
Summary The James Webb Space Telescope has successfully deployed all five layers of its tennis-court-sized sunshield, a prerequisite for the telescope&amp;rsquo;s science operations and the most nerve-wracking part of its risky deployment. &amp;ldquo;Yesterday, we did not think we were going to get through the first three layers,&amp;rdquo; Keith Parrish, the observatory manager for the James Webb Space Telescope, said in a live NASA webcast during today&amp;rsquo;s deployment.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope unfurls massive sunshield in major deployment milestone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d088aef43b8174ee0f7aa8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d088aef43b8174ee0f7aa8/</guid><description>The $10 billion James Webb Space Telescope unfolded its huge sunshield on Friday (Dec. 31), pulling the five-layer structure out by sequentially deploying two booms.
Summary The sunshield of NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope is seen here fully unfurled during prelaunch testing on Earth. One of the James Webb Space Telescope&amp;rsquo;s most nail-biting deployment steps is safely in the books. Live updates: NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope missionRelated: How the James Webb Space Telescope works in picturesShine bright like a diamond 💎With the successful deployment of our right sunshield mid-boom, or “arm,” Webb’s sunshield has now taken on its diamond shape in space.</description></item></channel></rss>