<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>videos on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/videos/</link><description>Recent content in videos on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Freedom Convoy' leader Pat King denied bail, remains in jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621977765b8589946b3687e1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621977765b8589946b3687e1/</guid><description>Leader of the so-called Freedom Convoy Pat King has been denied bail because of a &amp;quot;substantial likelihood&amp;quot; he would reoffend, according to Justice of the Peace Andrew Seymour.
Highlights Pat King has been denied bail because of a &amp;ldquo;substantial likelihood&amp;rdquo; he would reoffend, says Justice of the Peace Andrew Seymour. King, an Alberta resident who helped lead the three-week occupation in Ottawa, was arrested last Friday. He faces charges of counselling to commit mischief, counselling to disobey a court order, and counselling to obstruct police.</description></item><item><title>SF judge tosses plea deals for CA militia members linked to man who killed Oakland federal guard</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621767ccc0414357cf1f26f6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621767ccc0414357cf1f26f6/</guid><description>A San Francisco judge throws out the guilty pleas for three members of &amp;quot;Grizzly Scouts&amp;quot; who made plans to target police with Steve Carrillo.
Highlights Steven Carrillo, a Santa Cruz County Air Force sergeant, pleaded guilty Friday to fatally shooting Pat Underwood at Oakland federal building. Judge threw out guilty pleas for three members of an armed, anti-government militia who made plans to target law enforcement. The Grizzly Scouts used a Facebook account named &amp;ldquo;they say the west won&amp;rsquo;t boog&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;This is the beginning of the boog,&amp;rdquo; court records show.</description></item><item><title>Swedish King and Queen test positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d57a5e5508599f50ca391e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d57a5e5508599f50ca391e/</guid><description>STOCKHOLM — Sweden’s King Carl XVI Gustaf and Queen Silvia have tested positive for the COVID-19 virus, the palace said in a statement on Tuesday.
Summary Article contentSTOCKHOLM — Sweden’s King Carl XVI Gustaf and Queen Silvia have tested positive for the COVID-19 virus, the palace said in a statement on Tuesday. “The King and Queen, who are fully vaccinated with three injections, have mild symptoms and are feeling well, given the circumstances,” the palace said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>