<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>received on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/received/</link><description>Recent content in received on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 18:16:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/received/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Capitol rioter photographed with Pelosi's podium on Jan. 6 sentenced to prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62191cc6aab6330d753a8d20/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 18:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62191cc6aab6330d753a8d20/</guid><description>A Florida man who bragged he &amp;quot;broke the internet&amp;quot; when he was photographed carrying House Speaker Nancy Pelosi&amp;rsquo;s podium during the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was sentenced to 75 days in prison on Friday.
Highlights Adam Johnson, a stay-at-home father of five boys, traveled to D.C. in support of former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s efforts to overturn the results of the 2020 presidential election. Johnson will get credit for some time he&amp;rsquo;s already served, and will also pay a $5,000 fine.</description></item><item><title>France fines Google, Facebook for not allowing users to deny cookies as simply as accepting them.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d720514135940d89a9bd1a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d720514135940d89a9bd1a/</guid><description>The French government is fining the tech giants millions over data that tracks users' activity. They&amp;rsquo;ve given the companies three months to comply or face further fines.
Summary France&amp;rsquo;s National Commission for Information Technology and Freedom (CNIL) on Thursday hit Facebook and Google with €210 million ($237 million) in fines. Google, which also owns YouTube, was fined €150 million, breaking a record €100-million fine the company received in December 2020 over similar practices.</description></item></channel></rss>