<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>unvaccinated on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/unvaccinated/</link><description>Recent content in unvaccinated on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 14:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/unvaccinated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard tells the unvaccinated to ‘switch off your social media and switch on reality’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cc69ff22ee52e41aa5aa01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cc69ff22ee52e41aa5aa01/</guid><description>NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has begged the unvaccinated population in the state to &amp;quot;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;quot;.
Summary NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has slammed those who are still unvaccinated against COVID-19 and implored them to &amp;ldquo;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;rdquo;. NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has begged the unvaccinated population in the state to &amp;ldquo;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Tony Blair blasts unvaccinated 'idiots' as fears grow over spread of Omicron - "Frankly, if you're not vaccinated at the moment and you're eligible, and you've got no health reasons for not being unvaccinated, you're not just irresponsible. You're an idiot."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c66d2cb17fc1ddd51ae3b4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61c66d2cb17fc1ddd51ae3b4/</guid><description>The former Labour Prime Minister said those who are not vaccinated are putting strain on the NHS due to the transmissibility of the new strain.
Summary Tony Blair has slammed people who are still refusing to get the coronavirus vaccine as &amp;ldquo;idiots&amp;rdquo; with concerns growing over the spread of the Omicron variant. His comments come after First Minister Nicola Sturgeon announced new restrictions to halt the spread of Omicron which is now the dominant variant in Scotland.</description></item></channel></rss>