<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wave of suicides hits Texas National Guard’s border mission</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</guid><description>Operation Lone Star&amp;rsquo;s sudden and rapid expansion has left many Texas guardsmen struggling to balance their military and civilian lives, sometimes with tragic results.
Summary The string of suicides raises urgent questions about the mission’s conditions and purpose, as well as the way it’s organized and manned through indefinite involuntary call-ups, according to the Texas Army National Guard’s former top enlisted soldier. What’s going on out thereThe increased demand for troops on the border meant that the department had to resort to involuntarily activating entire units from the Texas National Guard and mobilizing members of the Texas State Guard.</description></item><item><title>Spain will ban smoking on all beaches and fine anyone caught lighting up £1,700</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c626f95d27db58a4624dec/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c626f95d27db58a4624dec/</guid><description>The national law, a first for Europe, will aim to combat pollution caused by cigarette butts which are a major pollutant on the country&amp;rsquo;s 3,000 miles of coastline.
Summary Spain is set to ban smoking on all of its beaches, allowing councils to fine offenders up to 2,000 euros (£1,700). Several Spanish regions, including Barcelona and the Canary islands, have already introduced similar smoking bans on beaches. Spain is set to ban smoking on all of its beaches months after a petition was signed by more than 283,000 people and delivered to the government.</description></item><item><title>Local officials call on Idaho sheriff to resign after he allegedly made disparaging comments about Native Americans</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c618d0fbec713b36154e1c/</guid><description>Members of a southeastern Idaho youth church group were being driven around by their chaperone last month,delivering Thanksgiving cards in the neighborhood to those they were thankful for when they decided last-minute to stop at the home of the county sheriff&amp;rsquo;s house, according to a probable cause affidavit later in court.
Summary What happened next outside the home of Bingham County Sheriff Craig Rowland has put the small Idaho community in the national spotlight.</description></item><item><title>Ford recalls nearly 185,000 F-150s for defect that can cause drivers to lose control of the vehicle</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c60aba88ce84939546c48c/</guid><description>A new recall affects close to 185,000 F-150 pickups from the 2021 and 2022 model years.
Summary Ford Motor Company is recalling nearly 185,000 F-150s from the 2021 and 2022 model years for a defect that can cause a fractured driveshaft. Ford reports that insulators on the underbody of the trucks can loosen and contact the aluminum driveshaft, rubbing and scoring it. Operators may observe a loose underbody insulator, or hear a rattling, clicking or clunking noise due to a loose underbody insulator contacting the driveshaft.</description></item><item><title>White House reiterates that US is ready to act if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5fcb103b540d44263e42a/</guid><description>The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine, with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;quot;ready to act if and when we need to.&amp;quot;
Summary Washington (CNN) The Biden administration on Thursday reiterated its warnings to Russia over a potential invasion of Ukraine , with one senior administration official telling reporters that the US is &amp;ldquo;ready to act if and when we need to.</description></item><item><title>Polish opposition senator hacked with spyware Pegasus by the current ruling party during the parliamentary elections</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5ee9f45555e41135a749a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5ee9f45555e41135a749a/</guid><description>WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Polish Sen. Krzysztof Brejza’s mobile phone was hacked with sophisticated spyware nearly three dozen times in 2019 when he was running the opposition&amp;rsquo;s campaign against the right-wing populist government in parliamentary elections, an internet watchdog found.
Summary (AP Photo) Polish Senator Krzysztof Brejza on the night of parliamentary elections on Oct. 13, 2019. The ruling party won a slim majority and Brejza is convinced that the hacking of his phone gave it an unfair advantage.</description></item><item><title>Supermarkets drop Brazilian beef products linked to deforestation</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5e095b621db7db8f753f8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5e095b621db7db8f753f8/</guid><description>Sainsbury’s is one of six European supermarkets to stop selling some or all beef products from South American country
Summary According to the news organisation Repórter Brasil, the company allegedly indirectly sourced cattle from illegally deforested areas. In the latest research, Repórter Brasil, working with the campaign group Mighty Earth, tracked deforestation-linked beef – including beef jerky, corned beef and fresh meat – from Brazil to European supermarket shelves. JBS claims to have checked the suppliers mentioned by Repórter Brasil and found them to be in compliance with JBS procurement policies.</description></item><item><title>Omicron could burn through the U.S. — and potentially hasten the Covid pandemic's end, says expert</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5d28689b7563d3d8f7fec/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 14:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5d28689b7563d3d8f7fec/</guid><description>Some researchers say omicron could hasten Covid&amp;rsquo;s transition from pandemic to endemic, albeit with large numbers of illnesses and potential deaths along the way. Here&amp;rsquo;s how.
Summary Now, some researchers say omicron could actually hasten the virus' transition from pandemic to endemic, albeit with large numbers of illnesses and potential deaths along the way. Omicron is highly contagious, but its influence on hospitalizations and deaths is yet unconfirmed by researchers.</description></item><item><title>Tesla, bowing to pressure, stops allowing drivers to play video games while driving</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5c477a4ecb10b90867070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 13:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5c477a4ecb10b90867070/</guid><description>The company will send out a software update that will prevent its games from being played on center consoles while the vehicle is in motion
Summary Under pressure from US auto safety regulators, Tesla has agreed to stop allowing video games to be played on center touch screens while its vehicles are moving. The move comes one day after the agency announced it would open a formal investigation into distracted driving concerns about Tesla’s video games, some of which could be played while cars are being driven.</description></item><item><title>US Marines among 12 apprehended in Okinawa for drug smuggling</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5b66c6db7c263d4a7aa08/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5b66c6db7c263d4a7aa08/</guid><description>NAHA &amp;ndash; Okinawa Prefectural Police and other authorities apprehended 12 people including three members and a civilian employee of the U.S. Marines in
Summary Okinawa Prefectural Police headquarters (Mainichi/Takayasu Endo)NAHA &amp;ndash; Okinawa Prefectural Police and other authorities apprehended 12 people including three members and a civilian employee of the U.S. Marines in Okinawa on suspicion of smuggling cannabis and cocaine into Japan from the United States through military postal services that delivered items to U.</description></item><item><title>Two Georgia poll workers sue One America News, Giuliani over debunked fraud claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5a854743f486327f4e1a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5a854743f486327f4e1a4/</guid><description>Two Georgia election workers who were the target of vote-rigging conspiracy theories have sued the far-right One America News Network, its top executives, and former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s ex-lawyer Rudy Giuliani for allegedly spreading lies about them.
Summary REUTERS/Eduardo Munoz/File PhotoDec 23 (Reuters) - Two Georgia election workers who were the target of vote-rigging conspiracy theories have sued the far-right One America News Network, its top executives, and former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s ex-lawyer Rudy Giuliani for allegedly spreading lies about them.</description></item><item><title>Japanese university finds drug effective in treating ALS</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</guid><description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University says it has found a drug effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, also known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Summary KYODO NEWS - 5 hours ago - 13:43 | All, JapanJapan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University said Friday it has found that a drug being developed for the treatment of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s is also effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, more commonly known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease. The drug has been found capable of curbing the abnormal agglomeration of protein that causes the progressive neurodegenerative disease, the state-run university in northeastern Japan said.</description></item><item><title>Teen in dressing room fatally shot by LA police firing at assault suspect, officials say</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</guid><description>A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday,
Summary LOS ANGELES — A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday, authorities said. The 14-year-old girl was found dead behind the dressing room wall, which was penetrated by gunfire, Los Angeles police officials said.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item><item><title>United Airlines preemptively cancels 112 Christmas Eve flights due to COVID-19</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5701796cb667903e95aaf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 07:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c5701796cb667903e95aaf/</guid><description>United and Delta Airlines have preemptively canceled almost 200 Christmas Eve flights, the airlines announced Thursday.
Summary United and Delta Airlines have preemptively canceled almost 200 Christmas Eve flights, the airlines announced Thursday. In a statement, United Airlines blamed the cancellations on staffing shortages due to COVID-19. Eleven of the flights were United, while no Delta flights were canceled today. One of the delayed flights is United, while no Delta flights have been delayed at this time.</description></item><item><title>The Navy Illegally Flushed Tainted Water Into Storm Drains As Red Hill Crisis Took Hold</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c56207756fc4983d3891cc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 06:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c56207756fc4983d3891cc/</guid><description>DOH says it is focusing on mitigating the crisis rather than sanctioning the Navy.
Summary “The DOH typically has the authority to take enforcement actions when there is a discharge of a pollutant to a storm drain system,” she said. Halsey Terrace resident Laura Warfold said she first saw men in uniform flushing water from fire hydrants into the grass in her backyard on Nov. 29. She noticed puddles with an oily sheen near a storm drain by her home.</description></item><item><title>US Navy seizes guns it says heading from Iran to Yemen</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c553f5da2efb5f04957dba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 05:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c553f5da2efb5f04957dba/</guid><description>The US Navy has seized 1,400 AK-47 rifles and ammunition from a fishing boat it claimed was smuggling weapons from Iran to Huthi rebels in war-torn Yemen.
Summary Yemen has been wracked by civil war since 2014, pitting Iran-backed Huthi rebels against the internationally-recognised government. &amp;ldquo;US 5th Fleet ships seized approximately 1,400 AK-47 assault rifles and 226,600 rounds of ammunition from a stateless fishing vessel,&amp;rdquo; a US navy statement Wednesday read.</description></item><item><title>US, Japan draw up joint military plan for possible Taiwan emergency: report</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c545e2cac5dd680c38bdf0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c545e2cac5dd680c38bdf0/</guid><description>The U.S.
Summary The U.S. and Japanese militaries have made a draft plan for a joint operation should an emergency with Taiwan arise, Japan&amp;rsquo;s Kyodo news agency reported Thursday. Under the draft plan, the U.S. Marine Corps would deploy troops to and set up temporary bases on the Nansei island chain, an archipelago of Japan that stretches toward Taiwan, at the first sign of a Taiwan emergency, Kyodo said. They would not speak to the specific topics planned for discussion in the 2+2 meetings with Japan.</description></item><item><title>Amazon warehouse workers on Staten Island refile union petition</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 03:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</guid><description>The group, called Amazon Labor Union, is looking to organize workers across four company warehouses on Staten Island.
Summary A labor group seeking to organize Amazon warehouse workers on New York&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island has refiled a union petition with the National Labor Relations Board, the agency confirmed Wednesday. The group, known as the Amazon Labor Union, first filed its request for a union vote in late October with signatures from more than 2,000 employees.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioters hit with severe sentences and sharp reprimands from judges</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c529bab46f6a641cfa9785/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 02:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c529bab46f6a641cfa9785/</guid><description>Some of the longest sentences have gone to rioters charged with ‘assaulting a police officer with a dangerous weapon’
Summary Since the riots, federal prosecutors have brought cases against 727 individuals over their involvement in the deadly riots. With hundreds facing criminal charges, Trump has come under growing scrutiny from the House select committee investigating the attacks. According to court documents, Devlyn Thompson helped move police shields up against a line of rioters in a tunnel, as well as hit police officers.</description></item><item><title>Russian mercenaries deploy to eastern Ukraine – sources</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c51baa07a8b73cad605b98/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c51baa07a8b73cad605b98/</guid><description>By Maria Tsvetkova and Anton Zverev MOSCOW (Reuters) - Russian mercenaries have deployed to separatist-controlled eastern Ukraine in recent weeks to b&amp;hellip;
Summary The fighter said he was planning to join up with fellow mercenaries on the Russian side of the border with the separatist-held Luhansk region in eastern Ukraine. One of the sources, a contractor who has taken part in Russian operations abroad and had already arrived in eastern Ukraine, said the deployment was for defensive purposes.</description></item><item><title>U.S. bans imports from China’s Xinjiang region, citing human rights abuses</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c50da4501fb66db7176341/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c50da4501fb66db7176341/</guid><description>Washington has previously warned businesses with supply chain and investment ties to China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang province that they could face legal consequences.
Summary WASHINGTON – President Joe Biden signed a bill Thursday that aims to crack down on human rights abuses in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang region. The legislation bans imports from Xinjiang and imposes sanctions on individuals responsible for forced labor in the region. Underscoring the broad support for addressing human rights abuses in the region, the Senate passed the bill unanimously this month following an overwhelming bipartisan vote in the House.</description></item><item><title>Kim Potter, ex-Minnesota officer, found guilty of manslaughter in death of Daunte Wright</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</guid><description>A Minneapolis jury reached an &amp;quot;outcome&amp;quot; in the trial of Kim Potter, a former police officer charged with fatally shooting Daunte Wright, a Black motorist.
Summary A Minneapolis jury on Thursday convicted former police officer Kim Potter on all charges she faced for fatally shooting Black motorist Daunte Wright — with a gun and not her Taser — earlier this year. Potter, 49, faces a maximum of 15 years in prison and is set to be sentenced Feb.</description></item><item><title>CNN Exclusive: US intel and satellite images show Saudi Arabia is now building its own ballistic missiles with help of China</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4f18423cdd004762cb169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4f18423cdd004762cb169/</guid><description>US intelligence agencies have assessed that Saudi Arabia is now actively manufacturing its own ballistic missiles with the help of China, CNN has learned, a development that could have significant ripple effects across the Middle East and complicate the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s efforts to restrain the nuclear ambitions of Iran, the Saudis' top regional rival.
Summary Iran and Saudi Arabia are bitter enemies and it is unlikely Tehran will agree to stop making ballistic missiles if Saudi Arabia has begun manufacturing its own.</description></item><item><title>New York governor signs bill criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4e36fe32d7d605f347c3f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4e36fe32d7d605f347c3f/</guid><description>New York&amp;rsquo;s governor signed legislation Wednesday criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards, according to a news release from her office.
Summary (CNN) New York&amp;rsquo;s governor signed legislation Wednesday criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards, according to a news release from her office. The law comes amid a fresh tightening of rules requiring proof of vaccination in cities across the United States &amp;ndash; including New York &amp;ndash; as the Omicron coronavirus variant spreads rapidly ahead of the Christmas holiday.</description></item><item><title>Florida pulls pro-vaccination television ads, replacing with spots that don’t mention vaccines</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4d56335023eee76ca8e6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 20:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4d56335023eee76ca8e6e/</guid><description>State sponsored commercials promoting COVID-19 vaccinations have been pulled from Florida&amp;rsquo;s airwaves.
Summary Spots are produced by the Florida Department of Health, which then disseminates them to stations around the state. Last March, the Biden administration rolled out a billion dollar ad campaign about the importance of the vaccine. AdThose videos featured pastors, local sports stars and health department veterans. These ran until early November, when the state health department made a sudden change.</description></item><item><title>Warning against unnecessary circumcision from Australian Medical Association president Mark Duncan-Smith after two-year-old dies and brother almost bleeds out in Western Australia</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4c74b8124f5fa654a52b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4c74b8124f5fa654a52b1/</guid><description>WA Australian Medical Association president Mark Duncan-Smith urged parents to only follow through with the procedure if there was a valid medical reason.
Summary And that has to be part of the evaluation of whether or not it&amp;rsquo;s appropriate for a child to have a circumcision.' His warning comes after a two-year-old boy died after suffering an allergic reaction to anaesthesia given to him during the procedure on Tuesday. The top doctor pointed out rates of circumcision had declined in Western Australia over the last few decades.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.</description></item><item><title>In an historic vote, Italy to ban fur farming and shut down all mink farms within six months</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4ab2935857033b004b419/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4ab2935857033b004b419/</guid><description>Summary ROME—The Budget Committee of the Italian Senate today voted to approve a modified version of an amendment to the budget law which will see the country’s 10 remaining mink fur farms closed within six months and a permanent ban on fur farming throughout Italy. There are very clear economic, environmental, public health and of course animal welfare reasons to close and ban fur farms. Finally, a parliamentary vote sanctions the end of unspeakable suffering inflicted on animals only in the name of profit and vanity.</description></item><item><title>Korea halts Canadian beef imports after detection of mad cow case</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c49d28e505a7cb8afb6306/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c49d28e505a7cb8afb6306/</guid><description>Korea halts Canadian beef imports after detection of mad cow case
Summary South Korea on Tuesday suspended quarantine inspections of Canadian beef following the discovery of a mad cow case in the North American country. It marks the first time in six years that a mad cow case has been confirmed in Canada. In February 2015, South Korea halted quarantine inspections of Canadian beef after the confirmation of a mad cow case in Alberta.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina police chief placed on unpaid leave for telling officers about 'clinic' to obtain Covid-19 vaccination cards without getting the shots</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c48f0e1c2c279f3766c6ad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 15:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c48f0e1c2c279f3766c6ad/</guid><description>A North Carolina police chief has been placed on unpaid leave and probation for telling officers about a &amp;quot;clinic&amp;quot; that would issue them a Covid-19 vaccination card without actually receiving the shot, local officials said.
Summary (CNN) A North Carolina police chief has been placed on unpaid leave and probation for telling officers about a &amp;ldquo;clinic&amp;rdquo; that would issue them a Covid-19 vaccination card without actually receiving the shot, local officials said.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer pill becomes 1st US-authorized home COVID treatment</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c480fac70a799e60dad67e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 14:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c480fac70a799e60dad67e/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health regulators on Wednesday authorized the first pill against COVID-19, a Pfizer drug that Americans will be able to take at home to head off the worst effects of the virus.
Summary This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)WASHINGTON (AP) — U.</description></item><item><title>Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. This increase was exacerbated during the Covid pandemic. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 13:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</guid><description>Report calls for a “modest progressive wealth tax on global multimillionaires” in order to redistribute wealth.
Summary PARIS: The share of global wealth of the world’s richest people soared at a record pace during the Covid pandemic, a report on inequality showed on Tuesday. Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires’ share of wealth on record,” the document said.</description></item><item><title>Canada should temporarily ban foreign home buyers, rezone cities - housing minister</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c464def47fd04f449d4106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c464def47fd04f449d4106/</guid><description>Municipalities should rezone broadly to allow more density and Canada should temporarily ban foreign buyers to help alleviate the housing affordability crunch faced by residents, the country&amp;rsquo;s housing minister said on Tuesday.
Summary Canada&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Housing, Diversity, and Inclusion Ahmed Hussen speaks during Question Period in the House of Commons on Parliament Hill in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada November 30, 2021. REUTERS/Blair Gable/OTTAWA, Dec 21 (Reuters) - Municipalities should rezone broadly to allow more density and Canada should temporarily ban foreign buyers to help alleviate the housing affordability crunch faced by residents, the country&amp;rsquo;s housing minister said on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Fox cancels ‘New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022’ telecast due to omicron surge</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c456c95106b7bcbd5c15e2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 11:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c456c95106b7bcbd5c15e2/</guid><description>Fox has cancelled its &amp;quot;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022&amp;quot; production in New York due to the recent surge in Covid-19 cases as the omicron variant spreads.
Summary Fox has decided against moving forward with its “New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022” production in New York due to the ongoing surge of Covid-19 and its omicron variant. “While we are confident in the health and safety protocols for ‘Fox’s New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022,’ the recent velocity of the spread of Omicron cases has made it impossible to produce a live special in Times Square that meets our standards,” Fox Entertainment said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Michigan diner owner who defied state shutdown dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c448bf11f4d88429c1eebc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c448bf11f4d88429c1eebc/</guid><description>Summary BRANCH COUNTY, MI – A diner owner who kept his restaurant open in defiance of state shutdowns has died after more than a two-month battle with COVID-19. He owned the Quincy Diner, 174 E. Chicago St. (U.S. 12) in the village of Quincy. He kept the restaurant open in December 2020, in violation of the partial shutdown ordered by the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services. Related: ‘I’d have lost the business.</description></item><item><title>Pause on student loan payments is extended through May 1</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4486cb98d38c767bbcd63/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4486cb98d38c767bbcd63/</guid><description>Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1.
Summary WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;ndash; The Biden administration is extending a student loan moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to put off debt payments during the pandemic. Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1. Interest rates will remain at 0% during that period, and debt collection efforts will be suspended.</description></item><item><title>University of Hong Kong appears to demolish Tiananmen Massacre monument in dead of night - Hong Kong Free Press HKFP</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</guid><description>Summary Workers at the University of Hong Kong (HKU) removed the Tiananmen Massacre monument late on Wednesday night, months after the university said the statue must go. Pillar of Shame. Jens Galschiøt’s Pillar of Shame monument has stood on campus for over two decades, though – in October – university authorities demanded its removal amid a crackdown on those commemorating the 1989 massacre. The University of Hong Kong ordered the removal of the Pillar of Shame, an eight-metre tall sculpture commemorating the 1989 Tiananmen Massacre, from its campus in October.</description></item><item><title>United States is world’s biggest plastic polluter, report finds</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c41e9670811afb6b1c14a8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c41e9670811afb6b1c14a8/</guid><description>None
Summary The United States is by far the biggest contributor to global plastic waste in the world, according to a new report submitted to the federal government Wednesday that called for a national strategy to tackle the growing crisis. On average, every American generates 130 kilograms (286 pounds) of plastic waste per year, with Britain next on the list at 99 kilos per person per year, followed by South Korea at 88 kilos per year.</description></item><item><title>Omicron hits all 50 states less than a month after entering U.S.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</guid><description>With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was
Summary With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was first detected in the U.S., according to an NBC News tally. A day later, multiple states and territories set records for seven-day averages, including New York, Maine, Washington, D.</description></item><item><title>Florida pulls pro-vaccination television ads, replacing with spots that don’t mention vaccines</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3f464011a29c9f16cde6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3f464011a29c9f16cde6e/</guid><description>State sponsored commercials promoting COVID-19 vaccinations have been pulled from Florida&amp;rsquo;s airwaves.
Summary Spots are produced by the Florida Department of Health, which then disseminates them to stations around the state. Last March, the Biden administration rolled out a billion dollar ad campaign about the importance of the vaccine. AdThose videos featured pastors, local sports stars and health department veterans. These ran until early November, when the state health department made a sudden change.</description></item><item><title>Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon Carjacked in South Philly</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3e65221baf63d51a3e48d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 03:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3e65221baf63d51a3e48d/</guid><description>Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon (D-5th District) was carjacked at gunpoint in South Philadelphia Wednesday afternoon, her spokesperson confirmed&amp;hellip;
Summary Pennsylvania Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon (D-5th District) was carjacked in South Philadelphia Wednesday afternoon, her spokesperson confirmed with NBC10. The spokesperson said Scanlon, 62, was carjacked at gunpoint at 2:45 p.m. at FDR Park. I&amp;rsquo;m appalled to learn of this violent crime that was perpetrated against my friend and colleague, Congresswoman Mary Gay Scanlon.</description></item><item><title>In milestone deal, Proud Boy pleads guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</guid><description>A New York man pleaded guilty Wednesday to storming the U.S. Capitol with fellow members of the far-right Proud Boys, a milestone in the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s prosecution of extremists who joined the Jan.
Summary At least four others linked to the Oath Keepers also have pleaded guilty to riot-related charges. Proud Boys members describe themselves as a politically incorrect men’s club for “Western chauvinists.” Its members frequently have engaged in street fights with antifascist activists at rallies and protests.</description></item><item><title>Michigan diner owner who defied state shutdown dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 01:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</guid><description>None
Summary BRANCH COUNTY, MI – A diner owner who kept his restaurant open in defiance of state shutdowns has died after more than a two-month battle with COVID-19. He owned the Quincy Diner, 174 E. Chicago St. (U.S. 12) in the village of Quincy. He kept the restaurant open in December 2020, in violation of the partial shutdown ordered by the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services. Related: ‘I’d have lost the business.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer pill becomes 1st US-authorized home COVID treatment</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3a002b485b06b08d59d9e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3a002b485b06b08d59d9e/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health regulators on Wednesday authorized the first pill against COVID-19, a Pfizer drug that Americans will be able to take at home to head off the worst effects of the virus.
Summary This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)WASHINGTON (AP) — U.</description></item><item><title>He wore a wire, risked his life to expose who was in the KKK</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c383d63b857dd3cfa695d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 20:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c383d63b857dd3cfa695d5/</guid><description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — For nearly 10 years, Joseph Moore lived a secret double life. At times the U.S. Army veteran donned a white robe and hood as a hit man for the Ku Klux Klan in North Florida.
Summary He wore a wire, risked his life to expose who was in the KKKJoseph Moore looks out of a window at his home in Jacksonville, Fla., on Tuesday, Dec. 7, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Pause on student loan payments is extended through May 1</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c375cb38fe6f3ff05558d5/</guid><description>Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1.
Summary WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;ndash; The Biden administration is extending a student loan moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to put off debt payments during the pandemic. Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1. Interest rates will remain at 0% during that period, and debt collection efforts will be suspended.</description></item><item><title>Cleveland-area hospitals battling latest Covid-19 surge put ad in local paper that reads: 'Help'</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 15:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c33da1441e2da677c49fa1/</guid><description>&amp;quot;Help&amp;quot; said the ad Sunday in the Cleveland Plain-Dealer, a response to the latest Covid-19 health crisis exploding in Northern Ohio, nearly two years into a pandemic that has killed more than 810,000 Americans and battered many of the nation&amp;rsquo;s hospitals.
Summary (CNN) &amp;ldquo;Help.&amp;rdquo; That word, in big black letters and surrounded by white space, called out from Ohio&amp;rsquo;s largest newspaper &amp;ndash; a desperate plea from six Cleveland-area medical systems facing a crush of Covid-19 cases.</description></item><item><title>NASA's James Webb Space Telescope launch delayed to Christmas due to bad weather</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c32f8ebb918b17a516fa61/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 14:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c32f8ebb918b17a516fa61/</guid><description>NASA&amp;rsquo;s much-awaited next-generation space telescope is finally ready to launch just as soon as the weather cooperates.
Summary The James Webb Space Telescope folded up for launch before it was encapsulated in the fairing of an Ariane 5 rocket. NASA&amp;rsquo;s much-awaited next-generation space telescope is finally ready to launch — just as soon as the weather cooperates. The James Webb Space Telescope , also known as JWST or Webb, has been in the works for decades.</description></item><item><title>Fox cancels ‘New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022’ telecast due to omicron surge</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3216fec063da1021cd228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 13:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3216fec063da1021cd228/</guid><description>Fox has cancelled its &amp;quot;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022&amp;quot; production in New York due to the recent surge in Covid-19 cases as the omicron variant spreads.
Summary Fox has decided against moving forward with its “New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022” production in New York due to the ongoing surge of Covid-19 and its omicron variant. “While we are confident in the health and safety protocols for ‘Fox’s New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022,’ the recent velocity of the spread of Omicron cases has made it impossible to produce a live special in Times Square that meets our standards,” Fox Entertainment said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Employer must face worker's lawsuit over husband's COVID death -California court</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</guid><description>Description HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CALIFORNIA-WORKERS:Employer must face worker&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit over husband&amp;rsquo;s COVID death -California court
Summary The California Court of Appeal, Second Appellate District, rejected South San Francisco-based See&amp;rsquo;s Candies' argument that the employee, Matilde Ek, must file for workers' compensation rather than seek damages in court because her husband&amp;rsquo;s death was &amp;ldquo;derivative&amp;rdquo; of her own workplace injury. Ek and her three daughters sued See&amp;rsquo;s last year, saying she contracted COVID-19 because the company failed to ensure safety in the workplace.</description></item><item><title>Iowa man arraigned on 7 charges for Jan. 6 US Capitol attack</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</guid><description>Description An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prison
Summary An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prisonDES MOINES, Iowa &amp;ndash; An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest 76-year-old man in cold case of 1978 strangling death of teen in San Francisco</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</guid><description>Description Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City
Summary Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City teen who was found dead after visiting Golden Gate Park. Mark Stanley Personette, of Conifer, Colorado, was arrested Dec.</description></item><item><title>110 Year Sentence For Truck Driver Being Reconsidered</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2e927679e9dc44622769a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 09:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2e927679e9dc44622769a/</guid><description>Description Civil rights advocates are calling for Colorado Gov. Jared Polis to intervene after a truck driver was sentenced to 110 years for a fatal crash after his brakes failed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;As Colorado law required the imposition of the sentence in this case, the law also permits the Court to reconsider its sentence in an exceptional case involving unusual and extenuating circumstances,&amp;rdquo; the motion says. According to The Associated Press, police said that after his brakes failed, Mederos drove past a truck ramp before the crash.</description></item><item><title>In an historic vote, Italy to ban fur farming and shut down all mink farms within six months - Humane Society International</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2db180927b787f25953fc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 08:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2db180927b787f25953fc/</guid><description>Description Summary ROME—The Budget Committee of the Italian Senate today voted to approve a modified version of an amendment to the budget law which will see the country’s 10 remaining mink fur farms closed within six months and a permanent ban on fur farming throughout Italy. There are very clear economic, environmental, public health and of course animal welfare reasons to close and ban fur farms. Finally, a parliamentary vote sanctions the end of unspeakable suffering inflicted on animals only in the name of profit and vanity.</description></item><item><title>Government official swims 12 hours to shore after helicopter crash off Madagascar: "My time to die hasn't come yet"</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2cd05f199143caea32f00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 07:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2cd05f199143caea32f00/</guid><description>Description The helicopter was flying Serge Gelle and others to inspect the site of a deadly shipwreck off the northeastern coast.
Summary A Madagascan minister was one of two survivors to have swum some 12 hours to shore Tuesday after their helicopter crashed off the island&amp;rsquo;s northeastern coast, authorities said. A search was still ongoing for two other passengers after the crash Monday, whose cause was not immediately clear, police and port authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Intel tells unvaccinated employees they face unpaid leave</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</guid><description>Description Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April
Summary Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in AprilPORTLAND, Ore. &amp;ndash; Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don&amp;rsquo;t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest bystander for filming traffic stop, allegedly interfering with investigation</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 05:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</guid><description>Description Killeen police arrest a man for interfering with an officer.
Summary KILLEEN, Texas (KWTX) - The Killeen Police Department arrested a man early Saturday morning for interfering with an officer conducting a traffic stop. “I have a right to be there. I have a right to record and I also have a right to free speech,” could be heard from the unnamed individual in the video. The video which is just over 130 Seconds long shows a man walking down the sidewalk when he sees police conducting a traffic stop.</description></item><item><title>Secret Service: Nearly $100B stolen in pandemic relief funds</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2a2d659180f685a50b3e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 04:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2a2d659180f685a50b3e9/</guid><description>Description The U.S. Secret Service says nearly $100 billion has been stolen from COVID-19 relief programs set up to help businesses and people who lost their jobs due to the pandemic.
Summary Nearly $100 billion at minimum has been stolen from COVID-19 relief programs set up to help businesses and people who lost their jobs due to the pandemic, the U.S. Secret Service said Tuesday. The estimate is based on Secret Service cases and data from the Labor Department and the Small Business Administration, said Roy Dotson, the agency’s national pandemic fraud recovery coordinator, in an interview.</description></item><item><title>Mum has arms ripped off, dies stopping pit bull from attacking 4-year-old son</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</guid><description>Description A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says.
Summary A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says. She said, ‘I have no arms, and I’m dying,’” Ms Pingel’s sister, Shannon Pingel, told the Wausau Daily Herald.</description></item><item><title>Missing Utah college student Madelyn Allen found alive, 'covered in coal' in suspect's basement</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 02:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</guid><description>Description Utah college student Madelyn &amp;ldquo;Maddie&amp;rdquo; Allen vanished last week and was found alive, covered in coal, in the basement of 39-year-old suspect Brent Brown.
Summary A Utah college student who vanished last week was found alive and covered in coal in the basement of a 39-year-old suspect&amp;rsquo;s home, according to authorities. The student, Madelyn Allen, 19, was reported missing after she was seen leaving her dorm at Snow College in Ephraim around 9:22 p.</description></item><item><title>Texas QAnon cult is now drinking bleach, member’s family says</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c278b0c8dd262ec076e17a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c278b0c8dd262ec076e17a/</guid><description>Description ‘She was proud to tell us that she was the one mixing it up and giving it to everybody,’ says distressed family member
Summary The family of a woman who joined a fringe QAnon cult in Texas says she’s now drinking toxic chemicals with her peers – and brags that she serves them herself. Despite two occasions when the JFKs failed to show up, Mr Protzman reportedly still has dozens of followers.</description></item><item><title>Utah billionaire leaves Mormon church, donates $600K to LGBTQ group</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</guid><description>Description Jeff Green, a billionaire from Utah, resigned from the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and donated to LGBTQ group Equality Utah.
Summary “The church leadership is not honest about its history, its finances, and its advocacy,” he wrote, according to the Tribune. “We made this investment sizable and publicly to send a message that Equality Utah isn’t going anywhere,” Green wrote, adding that he hopes the donation is the first of many.</description></item><item><title>Perfectly preserved baby dinosaur discovered curled up inside its egg</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c25c9677c8c89a4c593fe5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 23:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c25c9677c8c89a4c593fe5/</guid><description>Description An unprecedented fossil of a baby dinosaur curled up perfectly inside its egg is shedding more light on the links between dinosaurs and birds.
Summary (CNN) An unprecedented fossil of a baby dinosaur curled up perfectly inside its egg is shedding more light on the links between dinosaurs and birds. The 70-million-year-old fossil preserves the embryonic skeleton of an oviraptorid dinosaur, which has been nicknamed Baby Yingliang after the name of the Chinese museum which houses the fossil.</description></item><item><title>Chicago to Require Vaccine Proof for Indoor Spaces Like Restaurants, Bars, Gyms</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24e80f93c348e1487b143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24e80f93c348e1487b143/</guid><description>Description Chicago will soon require proof of vaccination for indoor public spaces like restaurants, bars and gyms in the new year, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor announced Tuesday,&amp;hellip;
Summary Chicago will soon require proof of vaccination for indoor public spaces like restaurants, bars and gyms in the new year, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor announced Tuesday, joining other big cities like New York and Los Angeles in adding the requirement as COVID cases surge.</description></item><item><title>Chinese companies vanish from world's top 10 by market cap</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</guid><description>Description TOKYO &amp;ndash; Tencent Holdings and Alibaba Group Holding have dropped out of the global top 10 companies in market capitalization, new data shows, leaving
Summary Alibaba Group Holding founder Jack Ma, then executive chairman, celebrates at the New York Stock Exchange on Sept. 19, 2014, the day that the company held its initial public offering and began trading there. © Getty ImagesMANAMI OGAWA, Nikkei staff writer READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Putin warns of possible military response over ‘aggressive’ Nato</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 20:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2326e6d25b985574ac25c/</guid><description>Description Russian leader’s speech to top commanders comes as tensions grow with the west over Ukraine
Summary Vladimir Putin has said he will consider a military response if Russia feels threatened by Nato, in a sign that he is not ready to de-escalate tensions over a potential invasion of Ukraine. In a combative speech on Tuesday, Putin – who has demanded “security guarantees” from Nato – told his top military commanders that the west was to blame for the rising tensions.</description></item><item><title>CDC director says initial Covid shots 'may not be enough' as omicron rapidly sweeps the nation</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c224461d573b547c66ea61/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c224461d573b547c66ea61/</guid><description>Description Dr. Rochelle Walensky said omicron has &amp;ldquo;over 50 mutations and because of those mutations, just being vaccinated with two doses may not be enough.&amp;rdquo;
Summary CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the omicron variant of the coronavirus has &amp;ldquo;over 50 mutations and because of those mutations, just being vaccinated with two doses may not be enough&amp;rdquo; ahead of the holidays. Even so, Walensky said that vaccines &amp;ldquo;may not prevent infection&amp;rdquo; according to data so far.</description></item><item><title>11-week Kellogg’s strike to end after multi-year agreement reached</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</guid><description>Description Summary The 11-week strike at Kellogg’s has come to an end after workers approved a contract with the company. Read more trending newsUnionized workers had been on strike since Oct. 5 in Michigan, Nebraska, Pennsylvania and Tennessee, The Washington Post reported.
The Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers’ International Union president Anthony Shelton said the contract makes gains for the 1,400 union workers and has no concessions.</description></item><item><title>First confirmed US death related to Omicron variant was unvaccinated and had been infected before</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</guid><description>Description A Texas man, whose death was the first confirmed Omicron-related in the US, was unvaccinated and had previously been infected with the coronavirus, according to a press release from Harris County Public Health.
Summary A large crowd of people is seen wearing face masks as a preventive measure against the spread of coronavirus as they walk through a zebra crossing in Hong Kong, China, on 12 December 2021. (Miguel Candela/SOPA Images/LightRocket/Getty Images)Hong Kong will mandate all government employees to be fully vaccinated against Covid-19, or get tested for the virus every three days, authorities announced on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>'Enormous': Sercret Service reveals scope of Covid-19 fraud</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1fa1c9cc370130354dcca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 16:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1fa1c9cc370130354dcca/</guid><description>Description CNN&amp;rsquo;s Erica Hill speaks to special agent Roy Dotson of the US Secret Service, who has been tapped to lead an investigation into the billions of dollars of Covid-19-related fraud.
Summary CNN&amp;rsquo;s Erica Hill speaks to special agent Roy Dotson of the US Secret Service, who has been tapped to lead an investigation into the billions of dollars of Covid-19-related fraud. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Authorities in Qatar, host of next year's football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children's toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours contrary to Islamic values</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1ec0c58d321ac426daacf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 15:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1ec0c58d321ac426daacf/</guid><description>Description Authorities in Qatar, host of next year&amp;rsquo;s football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children&amp;rsquo;s toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours &amp;ldquo;contrary to Islamic values&amp;rdquo;. The emirate&amp;rsquo;s commerce and industry ministry did not spell out its objection to the rainbow colours, but some of the toys bore a colour scheme very similar to the LGBTQ+ flag.
Summary Authorities in Qatar, host of next year&amp;rsquo;s football World Cup, have confiscated a line of children&amp;rsquo;s toys from stores deeming their rainbow colours &amp;ldquo;contrary to Islamic values&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Biden to announce plan for free at-home tests as he assures vaccinated Americans they don't need to cancel holiday plans</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 14:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1de0a608e8b8cb7530aff/</guid><description>Description President Joe Biden will announce Tuesday a purchase of a half-billion at-home rapid Covid-19 tests and a plan to distribute them free to Americans who request them through a website, one of a series of new steps he&amp;rsquo;ll unveil as the country faces a potentially crippling wintertime surge of infections.
Summary The 500 million new tests will be made available next month and will reach Americans through the mail, the official said.</description></item><item><title>Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</guid><description>Description A B.C. Supreme Court judge has banned Nanaimo fisherman Scott Stanley Matthew Steer from fishing for life.
Summary The sentence was delivered on Nov. 12, 2021, and it is the first lifetime ban for a Pacific region fisherman in more than a decade. Along with the lifetime ban, Steer&amp;rsquo;s sentence includes:A prohibition from being aboard a fishing vessel. Steer was caught illegally fishing for crab in the Vancouver harbour after Vancouver SeaBus officials tipped off police.</description></item><item><title>Idaho man charged with murder and cannibalism after body parts found in microwave</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</guid><description>Description Summary CLARK FORK — A northern Idaho man faces serious charges after investigators say they found a dead man’s body parts in a microwave. Russell is charged with felony first-degree murder and felony cannibalism in an amended criminal complaint filed Wednesday. Deputies went to Flaget’s truck, where they found the body naked from the waist down positioned awkwardly in the passenger seat. Some of the tissue indicated heat had been applied, possibly in the microwave for one to two minutes, according to court documents.</description></item><item><title>Petition for truck driver given 110 years in fatal crash has 4.3M signatures; truckers show support</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1b3cd60d110ff50804352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1b3cd60d110ff50804352/</guid><description>Description A change.org petition for truck driver Rogel Lazaro Aguilera-Mederos, sentenced to 110 years in a deadly Colorado pileup, has 4 million+ signatures.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos &amp;ldquo;Your honor, I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I&amp;rsquo;m alive.&amp;rdquo; The Houston truck driver spoke emotionally in court as he was sentenced for a fiery crash that killed four people. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not related to Rogel, or any of his family, I simply believe that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t deserve his sentence or these charges.</description></item><item><title>Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of US COVID-19 cases</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1a5b391caab4e2d279383/</guid><description>Description NEW YORK (AP) — Omicron has raced ahead of other variants and is now the dominant version of the coronavirus in the U.S., accounting for 73% of new infections last week, federal health officials said Monday.
Summary Omicron sweeps across nation, now 73% of new US COVID casesTravelers wait for a shuttle but to arrive at the Los Angeles International Airport in Los Angeles, Monday, Dec. 20, 2021. (AP Photo/Jae C.</description></item><item><title>Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</guid><description>Description WASHINGTON (AP) — More than 12,000 military service members refusing the COVID-19 vaccine are seeking religious exemptions, and so far they are having zero success. That total lack of approvals is creating new tensions within the military, even as the vast majority of the armed forces have gotten vaccinated.
Summary The services, urgently trying to keep the coronavirus pandemic in check by getting troops vaccinated, are now besieged with exemption requests they are unlikely to approve.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item><item><title>A professor hid a cash prize on campus. All students had to do was read the syllabus.</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 18:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61be3de570df97dee8e4a848/</guid><description>Description With every new college semester, students are faced with multiple syllabuses outlining the subjects in their classes. But do students read them thoroughly? One Tennessee professor put it to the test.
Summary But do students read them thoroughly? &amp;ldquo;It an academic trope that no one reads the syllabus,&amp;rdquo; Wilson told CNN. Wilson told CNN that his syllabus typically doesn&amp;rsquo;t change much, but with Covid protocols there was some new information this time around.</description></item></channel></rss>