<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ghislaine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ghislaine/</link><description>Recent content in ghislaine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 06:15:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ghislaine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell juror to be questioned under oath by judge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621873e47f623c24f4c5c3f8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621873e47f623c24f4c5c3f8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A Ghislaine Maxwell trial juror who said on a written questionnaire that he&amp;rsquo;d never been a sexual abuse victim will be questioned by the trial judge
Highlights A juror who said he&amp;rsquo;d never been a sexual abuse victim will be questioned by the trial judge. The juror said during jury selection for Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s criminal trial only to reveal after the trial that he was a child sex abuse victim.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell to reveal identity of ‘8 John Does’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4f80e917579524bf69b14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 05:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4f80e917579524bf69b14/</guid><description>Convicted sex-trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell will no longer fight to protect the identity of eight men who allegedly had sex with young women she and her billionaire paedophile pal Jeffrey Epstein procured for them.
Summary The British socialite and convicted sex-trafficker has ended her fight to keep the identity of eight “John Does” a secret, her lawyer said in a letter. Convicted sex-trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell will no longer fight to protect the identity of eight men who allegedly had sex with young women she and her billionaire paedophile pal Jeffrey Epstein procured for them.</description></item></channel></rss>