<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>school on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/school/</link><description>Recent content in school on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Tsunami' of woes: U.S. school shootings spike amid pandemic stress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</guid><description>Signs are emerging that the challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers studying the phenomenon worry it will only grow.
Highlights Signs are emerging that the stresses and challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers who are studying the phenomenon worry it will only get worse. Already, campuses have been the site of 141 shootings so far during the 2021-22 school year - more than at any point in the previous decade.</description></item><item><title>US conservatives linked to rich donors wage campaign to ban books from schools | US news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</guid><description>Experts warn trend is accelerating as groups push for bans of works that often address race, LGBTQ issues and marginalized people
Summary Conservative groups across the US, often linked to deep-pocketed rightwing donors, are carrying out a campaign to ban books from school libraries, often focused on works that address race, LGBTQ issues or marginalized communities. Groups purporting to be “grassroots” efforts have frequently led the charge, petitioning school boards or elected officials to remove certain books.</description></item><item><title>Video appears to confirm Lorain school worker forced student to eat from trash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</guid><description>Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can.
Summary LORAIN, Ohio (WOIO) - Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can. “The video is shocking, it’s disheartening, it’s disturbing, and it’s what this child has been saying since the beginning,” said Jared Klebanow, the attorney representing the girl’s family.</description></item><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated banned from Italian bars, restaurants, public transport - Italian prime minister Mario Draghi criticized the jab-less, who he claimed were the cause of "most of the problems"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddc5ceb9c1cb154e057483/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddc5ceb9c1cb154e057483/</guid><description>New restrictions targeting the unvaccinated came into force in Italy on Monday with a negative COVID-19 test no longer granting access to bars, restaurants and domestic public transport.
Summary New restrictions targeting the unvaccinated came into force in Italy on Monday, where a negative COVID-19 test no longer grants access to bars, restaurants, and domestic public transport. People who recently recovered COVID-19 are exempted from the new rule which will be in force until March 31.</description></item></channel></rss>