<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>school on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/school/</link><description>Recent content in school on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:15:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Racism cited as factor in police strip search of girl, 15, at London school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62336c90b37f1469895cc677/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62336c90b37f1469895cc677/</guid><description>Black child’s ordeal, which involved exposure of intimate body parts, took place without parental consent, review finds
Highlights Police strip searched 15-year-old girl in London school&amp;rsquo;s medical room. Investigation finds racism was likely to have been an ‘influencing factor’ in officers’ actions. Police apologised for what a senior officer described as the child’s “truly regrettable” treatment. Child was made to bend over, spread her legs and use her hands to spread her buttocks while coughing.</description></item><item><title>Five students charged with hate crimes in 'racially motivated' incident, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 04:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</guid><description>Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children while exclaiming “brown power!” — an incident police are calling a “racially-motivated crime.”
Highlights Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children. They allegedly yelled “It’s Opposite Day!” and “brown power!’ Police are calling the incident a racially motivated crime. In Florida, evidencing prejudice while committing a hate crime is considered a third-degree felony.</description></item><item><title>Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest "Don't say gay" bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222b39fd32798c94fe12cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 00:50:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222b39fd32798c94fe12cce/</guid><description>Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest “Don’t say gay” bill. Bill would keep schools from encouraging conversations about sexual orientation and gender identity. Measure has drawn heavy opposition from groups that have repeatedly argued it singles
Highlights Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest “Don’t say gay” bill. The bill would keep schools from encouraging conversations about sexual orientation and gender identity. The measure has drawn heavy opposition from groups that have repeatedly argued it singles out LGBTQ people.</description></item><item><title>Indoor masking no longer necessary for most of the U.S, CDC says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 16:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</guid><description>Indoor mask mandates are not necessary to be safe now across most of the United States, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Friday.
Highlights Most Americans are safe going without a mask in indoor settings, including in schools, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says. The new guidance puts more than half of the nation&amp;rsquo;s counties at low or medium risk for Covid, meaning masks are no longer necessary.</description></item><item><title>2 assistant principals in Rialto charged with failing to report multiple sexual assaults at Carter High School, authorities say.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621826b7ca20e7e1e662d59b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621826b7ca20e7e1e662d59b/</guid><description>Two assistant principals in Rialto are now facing felony charges after allegedly failing to report sexual assaults on campus to authorities.
Highlights Two assistant principals at Carter High School in Rialto are now facing felony charges after allegedly failing to report sexual assaults on campus to authorities. They were arrested at the school on Wednesday and are each being held on $150,000 bail. The district attorney&amp;rsquo;s office said the two were informed of sexual assaults that allegedly happened on campus, but didn&amp;rsquo;t alert law enforcement.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutor: Oxford school shooting suspect asked jail: 'How do I get my fan mail?'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215c21737f3b6cafcc8235e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215c21737f3b6cafcc8235e/</guid><description>Judge will decide next week whether to keep Ethan Crumbley in an adult jail, or send him to a youth facility.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley is accused of plotting to stalk, rape, torture and kill a female classmate. Prosecutor: Oxford school shooting suspect asked jail: &amp;lsquo;How do I get my fan mail?&amp;rsquo; Defense attorney says he hasn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;altered his way of thinking&amp;rdquo; since being jailed in the Nov. 30 mass shooting.</description></item><item><title>Mother of Michigan school shooting suspect pleaded to keep her job hours after the shooting, boss says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</guid><description>The text exchange was revealed in court Tuesday during a preliminary hearing for Jennifer and James Crumbley, who are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring clear warning signs that he was a threat to others.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley, 15, opened fire with a 9mm handgun at his Michigan high school, killing four students and injuring seven. His parents are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring warning signs that he was a threat to others.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles nun, 80, gets prison for $835,000 school theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</guid><description>A Los Angeles nun who stole more than $800,000 to pay for a gambling habit has been sentenced to a year in federal prison
Highlights Mary Margaret Kreuper, 80, admitted to stealing the money from 2008 to 2018 while she was principal at St. James Catholic School in the LA suburb of Torrance. She pleaded guilty last July to one count each of wire fraud and money laundering. Judge Otis D.</description></item><item><title>NJ to Lift School Masking Mandate in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</guid><description>New Jersey will lift its school mask mandate in the second week of March, Gov. Phil Murphy told the New York Times.
Highlights New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy announced Monday that the state will end its school mask mandate on March 7. Murphy said school districts can continue their own mandates if they want. Connecticut Gov. Ned Lamont announced that his state mask mandate will end on Feb. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>'Tsunami' of woes: U.S. school shootings spike amid pandemic stress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</guid><description>Signs are emerging that the challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers studying the phenomenon worry it will only grow.
Highlights Signs are emerging that the stresses and challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers who are studying the phenomenon worry it will only get worse. Already, campuses have been the site of 141 shootings so far during the 2021-22 school year - more than at any point in the previous decade.</description></item><item><title>US conservatives linked to rich donors wage campaign to ban books from schools | US news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</guid><description>Experts warn trend is accelerating as groups push for bans of works that often address race, LGBTQ issues and marginalized people
Summary Conservative groups across the US, often linked to deep-pocketed rightwing donors, are carrying out a campaign to ban books from school libraries, often focused on works that address race, LGBTQ issues or marginalized communities. Groups purporting to be “grassroots” efforts have frequently led the charge, petitioning school boards or elected officials to remove certain books.</description></item><item><title>Video appears to confirm Lorain school worker forced student to eat from trash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</guid><description>Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can.
Summary LORAIN, Ohio (WOIO) - Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can. “The video is shocking, it’s disheartening, it’s disturbing, and it’s what this child has been saying since the beginning,” said Jared Klebanow, the attorney representing the girl’s family.</description></item><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated banned from Italian bars, restaurants, public transport - Italian prime minister Mario Draghi criticized the jab-less, who he claimed were the cause of "most of the problems"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddc5ceb9c1cb154e057483/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddc5ceb9c1cb154e057483/</guid><description>New restrictions targeting the unvaccinated came into force in Italy on Monday with a negative COVID-19 test no longer granting access to bars, restaurants and domestic public transport.
Summary New restrictions targeting the unvaccinated came into force in Italy on Monday, where a negative COVID-19 test no longer grants access to bars, restaurants, and domestic public transport. People who recently recovered COVID-19 are exempted from the new rule which will be in force until March 31.</description></item></channel></rss>