<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>school on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/school/</link><description>Recent content in school on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 20:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DHS warns of domestic violent extremists who praise Uvalde shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fb0c3d2836224903a3e78/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 20:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fb0c3d2836224903a3e78/</guid><description>Domestic violent extremists praised last month&amp;rsquo;s school shooting in Uvalde, Texas, and called for at least one copycat attack, the Department of Homeland Security said.
Highlights Department of Homeland Security reissued National Terrorism Advisory System Bulletin on Tuesday. The bulletin said domestic violent extremists are propagating disinformation and inciting grievances. Homeland Security officials are also concerned about possible fallout from an expected Supreme Court decision that could overturn Roe v. Wade.</description></item><item><title>'Act like you're asleep': Wounded Uvalde teacher recounts chilling moment he 1st saw gunman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f948211c5678883f5aea1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 18:11:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f948211c5678883f5aea1/</guid><description>An elementary school teacher wounded in Uvalde described the chilling moments he first encountered a gunman who would take the lives of 19 students and two teachers.
Highlights Arnulfo Reyes was watching a movie with 11 of his students when he heard the deadly shots ringing out, he told ABC News anchor Amy Robach. The 17-year veteran teacher described multiple harrowing encounters with the gunman, offering the most vivid account yet of what transpired inside his classroom on May 24, when 18-year-old gunman Salvador Ramos attacked Robb Elementary School.</description></item><item><title>New York governor signs law raising age to own semiautomatic rifle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e7b1ced6b1d1a1926114c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e7b1ced6b1d1a1926114c/</guid><description>New Yorkers under age 21 will be prohibited from buying semiautomatic rifles under a new law signed Monday by Gov. Kathy Hochul.
Highlights New Yorkers under age 21 will be prohibited from buying semiautomatic rifles under a new law signed by Gov. Kathy Hochul. New York&amp;rsquo;s Legislature passed the bills last week, pushing the changes through after a pair of mass shootings involving 18-year-old gunmen using guns. One bill will require microstamping in new firearms, which could help law enforcement solve gun-related crimes.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde police, school district no longer cooperating with Texas probe of shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296a0263f416bb99a7370bf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296a0263f416bb99a7370bf/</guid><description>Uvalde police and school district police are no longer cooperating with the Texas Dept. of Public Safety&amp;rsquo;s probe into the Robb Elementary School shooting, sources say.
Highlights Uv.C. police say they are no longer cooperating with the state&amp;rsquo;s response to the school shooting. The decision to stop cooperating occurred soon after the attack. The school was one of the worst school shootings in U.S. history, killing two people. The attack is believed to have been the result of a school shooting in Texas that took place at a school in May 2012, killing three people, including two children and two adults.</description></item><item><title>Justin Moreira of Hyannis charged with threatening to commit school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294a5b27838abd7f0846e07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294a5b27838abd7f0846e07/</guid><description>A Cape Cod man was arrested after allegedly threatening to commit a school shooting.
Highlights Justin Moreira, 29, was arrested and charged with making terroristic threats. He is scheduled to be arraigned Tuesday in Barnstable District Court. Police received multiple reports about a Facebook post allegedly made by Moreira. Moreira was arrested at his Hyannis home and taken into custody without incident. Police searched Moreira&amp;rsquo;s home, but did not find any guns in his home.</description></item><item><title>Justice Dept. to review response to Texas school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294482e2f8a584828810c6d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294482e2f8a584828810c6d/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — The Justice Department said Sunday it will review the law enforcement response to the Texas school shooting, an unusual federal look back prompted by questions about the shifting and at times contradictory information from authorities that have enraged a community in shock and sorrow.
Highlights The Justice Department will review the law enforcement response to the Texas school shooting. The review will be conducted in a fair, impartial and independent manner and the findings will be made public.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco Giants manager: 'I don't plan on coming out for the anthem going forward until I feel better about the direction of our country'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62929d8c4f33c669c86a6cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:09:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62929d8c4f33c669c86a6cce/</guid><description>San Francisco Giants manager Gabe Kapler told reporters ahead of his team&amp;rsquo;s Friday game against the Cincinnati Reds that he intends to forgo the pregame US national anthem moving forward.
Highlights Kapler: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t plan on coming out for the anthem going forward until I feel better about the direction of our country&amp;rdquo; Kapler questioned whether the U.S. is truly &amp;ldquo;the land of the free and the home of the brave&amp;rdquo; Comments come after 19 children and two adults were killed at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, by a lone, 18-year-old gunman.</description></item><item><title>Texas school district locked down on reports of shooter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d57b739d23392644d9c5e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 22:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d57b739d23392644d9c5e/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — An 18-year-old gunman opened fire Tuesday at a Texas elementary&amp;hellip;
Highlights An 18-year-old gunman opened fire Tuesday at a Texas elementary school, killing 14 children, one teacher and injuring others. It was the deadliest shooting at a U.S. grade school since the shocking attack in Sandy Hook, Connecticut, almost a decade ago. The gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde with a handgun and possibly a rifle, Abbott says.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo suspect's posts about attack plans could be seen online 30 minutes before mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628647371fc70d8a171b0473/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628647371fc70d8a171b0473/</guid><description>Thirty minutes before an 18-year-old White man allegedly carried out a racist mass shooting Saturday at a supermarket in a mostly Black enclave of Buffalo, New York, he revealed his monthslong plot to some on social media.
Highlights NEW: New York&amp;rsquo;s attorney general launches probe into social media companies used by alleged shooter. Payton S. Gendron, 18, is accused of killing 10 people and wounding three in a racist mass shooting in Buffalo, New York.</description></item><item><title>‘Blacks only,’ ‘whites only’ signs posted on Colerain HS water fountains, parents say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285dfaa0ed5cfd71381ef10/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285dfaa0ed5cfd71381ef10/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Let’s make a change. Let’s speak on this stuff. Let’s stop hiding it.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights Signs appeared on the fountains at Colerain High School appeared to segregate the water founts along racial lines. School officials confirm the signs were posted May 5. Northwest Local School District calls the incident “unacceptable on all levels” and a deviation from the district’s “culture of inclusivity, respect, kindness and compassion for everyone” A spokesperson claims the students involved have been issued “significant” disciplinary actions.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo shooter's prior threat, hospital stay face scrutiny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628287d793848ae566447b38/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 17:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628287d793848ae566447b38/</guid><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The white gunman accused of a racist rampage at a Buffalo supermarket planned to keep killing if he had escaped the scene, the police commissioner said Monday, as authorities investigated the massacre of 10 Black people as a potential hate crime or act of domestic terrorism.
Highlights Police: Buffalo gunman aimed to keep killing if he got away. Payton Gendron, 18, had threatened to carry out a shooting at Susquehanna Valley High School in Conklin around graduation, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Birmingham teacher arrested after allegedly sexually assaulting four girls</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628100479268b0a3a61d21fd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628100479268b0a3a61d21fd/</guid><description>28-year-old man held by West Midlands police also accused of sending indecent images of himself
Highlights The 28-year-old suspect, who works at a school in Birmingham, is also accused of sending indecent images of himself. West Midlands police said the man was originally arrested on 9 May but was rearrested on Saturday morning at his home in the city. He has been suspended by the school and remains in police custody, police said.</description></item><item><title>Florida school yearbook on hold over student protest photos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627aac31f46ffe61e07f958b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 18:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627aac31f46ffe61e07f958b/</guid><description>Students at a central Florida high school were told they won’t get their yearbooks until they&amp;rsquo;re censored
Highlights Yearbooks won&amp;rsquo;t be distributed until images of students holding rainbow flags and a “love is love” sign can be covered up. District officials said they don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone thinking that the school supported the students&amp;rsquo; walkout. Florida&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rdquo; law bans classroom instruction on sexual orientation or gender identity in kindergarten through third grade.</description></item><item><title>'A tragedy': Closure of 150-year-old college underscores toll of ransomware attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a034fe95e395bb24ca612/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 06:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a034fe95e395bb24ca612/</guid><description>Lincoln College is scheduled to close its doors Friday, becoming the first U.S. institution of higher learning to shut down in part due to a ransomware attack.
Highlights Lincoln College is scheduled to close its doors Friday, becoming the first U.S. institution of higher learning to shut down in part due to a ransomware attack. The Illinois school is one of only a handful of rural American colleges that qualify as predominantly Black institutions by the Department of Education.</description></item><item><title>The Satanic Temple sues elementary school as after-school club rejected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62678e4abae8fd0668296396/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62678e4abae8fd0668296396/</guid><description>The Satanic Temple intends to prove the Pennsylvania school&amp;rsquo;s board discriminated against the organization by barring the creation of the &amp;quot;After School Satan&amp;quot; club.
Highlights The Satanic Temple has filed a lawsuit against a Pennsylvania elementary school after the school board voted to deny the establishment of the &amp;ldquo;After School Satan&amp;rdquo; club. Northern Elementary School in York, Pa., is being sued on the grounds of constitutional violation. The temple intends to prove the board discriminated against the organization by barring the creation of the club, despite other organizations being allowed to operate their own programs.</description></item><item><title>Former USC water polo coach convicted in college admissions scandal trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62529f8186ff5f2367c7d647/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 09:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62529f8186ff5f2367c7d647/</guid><description>A former University of Southern California water polo coach was convicted on Friday on charges he accepted more than $200,000 in bribes to help children get into the school as fake athletic recruits in the latest trial to result from the U.S. college admissions scandal.
Highlights Jovan Vavic, 60, guilty on all three charges he faced following an investigation into a nationwide fraud and bribery scheme. The trial was the second to result from the &amp;ldquo;Operation Varsity Blues&amp;rdquo; investigation into the scheme.</description></item><item><title>Estill County teacher resigns after writing 'You are free to be yourself' message on classroom board</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624de56eb181f5aa3dd0daf3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624de56eb181f5aa3dd0daf3/</guid><description>Tyler Clay Morgan resigned from his job as a music teacher at West Irvine Intermediate School Monday after facing controversy over a message of support.
Highlights Tyler Clay Morgan resigned from his job as a music teacher at West Irvine Intermediate School Monday. Morgan confirmed to LEX18 News that he wrote &amp;ldquo;You are free to be yourself.&amp;rdquo; on the board in his classroom along with a rainbow flag. Morgan said he is not ready to speak on camera but did post this on Facebook: &amp;ldquo;I firmly believe that students and their parents expect teachers to teach content about their assigned curriculum in a subject area&amp;rdquo; Estill County Superintendent Jeff Saylor wrote the following statement on the matter: &amp;ldquo;This matter has been addressed and closed.</description></item><item><title>Utah bans transgender athletes in girls sports despite veto</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e4c6f849e5d2b8b9ad0b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e4c6f849e5d2b8b9ad0b6/</guid><description>SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — GOP lawmakers in Utah pushed through a ban on transgender youth athletes playing on girls teams Friday, overriding a veto and joining 11 other states with similar laws amid a nationwide culture war.
Highlights Utah lawmakers override a ban on transgender youth athletes playing on girls teams Friday, overriding a veto. Lawmakers successfully flipped 10 Republicans in the House and five in the Senate who had previously voted against the proposal.</description></item><item><title>Texas attorney general says school district’s Pride week ‘breaks state law’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e2273328c947f122d03a5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e2273328c947f122d03a5/</guid><description>Ken Paxton called district’s Pride week ‘sex education’ and claimed without parental consent it is against law
Highlights Texas attorney general Ken Paxton sent a letter to the Austin school district calling Pride week ‘sex education’ and notifying the school that without parental consent, the celebration is “breaking state law” The district has held Pride week for the past eight years as a chance to celebrate LGBTQ+ students, staff and families in the district.</description></item><item><title>Florida Mandates Personal Finance Education in High Schools</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623db8bcfa014a1a30e85ae4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623db8bcfa014a1a30e85ae4/</guid><description>On Tuesday, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed bill SB 1054, which mandates personal finance education for high school graduation.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed bill SB 1054 into law on Tuesday. The legislation was unanimously passed by both the state House of Representatives and Senate in March. Florida is the latest in a growing trend of states adopting legislation that includes personal finance education for students. Currently, there are 54 bills pending in 26 states, according to Next Gen Personal Finance&amp;rsquo;s bill tracker.</description></item><item><title>Racism cited as factor in police strip search of girl, 15, at London school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62336c90b37f1469895cc677/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62336c90b37f1469895cc677/</guid><description>Black child’s ordeal, which involved exposure of intimate body parts, took place without parental consent, review finds
Highlights Police strip searched 15-year-old girl in London school&amp;rsquo;s medical room. Investigation finds racism was likely to have been an ‘influencing factor’ in officers’ actions. Police apologised for what a senior officer described as the child’s “truly regrettable” treatment. Child was made to bend over, spread her legs and use her hands to spread her buttocks while coughing.</description></item><item><title>Five students charged with hate crimes in 'racially motivated' incident, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 04:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</guid><description>Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children while exclaiming “brown power!” — an incident police are calling a “racially-motivated crime.”
Highlights Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children. They allegedly yelled “It’s Opposite Day!” and “brown power!’ Police are calling the incident a racially motivated crime. In Florida, evidencing prejudice while committing a hate crime is considered a third-degree felony.</description></item><item><title>Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest "Don't say gay" bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222b39fd32798c94fe12cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 00:50:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222b39fd32798c94fe12cce/</guid><description>Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest “Don’t say gay” bill. Bill would keep schools from encouraging conversations about sexual orientation and gender identity. Measure has drawn heavy opposition from groups that have repeatedly argued it singles
Highlights Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest “Don’t say gay” bill. The bill would keep schools from encouraging conversations about sexual orientation and gender identity. The measure has drawn heavy opposition from groups that have repeatedly argued it singles out LGBTQ people.</description></item><item><title>Indoor masking no longer necessary for most of the U.S, CDC says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 16:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a52280ecdbfad9ad39e5c/</guid><description>Indoor mask mandates are not necessary to be safe now across most of the United States, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Friday.
Highlights Most Americans are safe going without a mask in indoor settings, including in schools, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says. The new guidance puts more than half of the nation&amp;rsquo;s counties at low or medium risk for Covid, meaning masks are no longer necessary.</description></item><item><title>2 assistant principals in Rialto charged with failing to report multiple sexual assaults at Carter High School, authorities say.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621826b7ca20e7e1e662d59b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 00:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621826b7ca20e7e1e662d59b/</guid><description>Two assistant principals in Rialto are now facing felony charges after allegedly failing to report sexual assaults on campus to authorities.
Highlights Two assistant principals at Carter High School in Rialto are now facing felony charges after allegedly failing to report sexual assaults on campus to authorities. They were arrested at the school on Wednesday and are each being held on $150,000 bail. The district attorney&amp;rsquo;s office said the two were informed of sexual assaults that allegedly happened on campus, but didn&amp;rsquo;t alert law enforcement.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutor: Oxford school shooting suspect asked jail: 'How do I get my fan mail?'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215c21737f3b6cafcc8235e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215c21737f3b6cafcc8235e/</guid><description>Judge will decide next week whether to keep Ethan Crumbley in an adult jail, or send him to a youth facility.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley is accused of plotting to stalk, rape, torture and kill a female classmate. Prosecutor: Oxford school shooting suspect asked jail: &amp;lsquo;How do I get my fan mail?&amp;rsquo; Defense attorney says he hasn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;altered his way of thinking&amp;rdquo; since being jailed in the Nov. 30 mass shooting. Prosecutors say he is too dangerous to be trusted around other minors.</description></item><item><title>Mother of Michigan school shooting suspect pleaded to keep her job hours after the shooting, boss says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</guid><description>The text exchange was revealed in court Tuesday during a preliminary hearing for Jennifer and James Crumbley, who are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring clear warning signs that he was a threat to others.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley, 15, opened fire with a 9mm handgun at his Michigan high school, killing four students and injuring seven. His parents are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring warning signs that he was a threat to others.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles nun, 80, gets prison for $835,000 school theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</guid><description>A Los Angeles nun who stole more than $800,000 to pay for a gambling habit has been sentenced to a year in federal prison
Highlights Mary Margaret Kreuper, 80, admitted to stealing the money from 2008 to 2018 while she was principal at St. James Catholic School in the LA suburb of Torrance. She pleaded guilty last July to one count each of wire fraud and money laundering. Judge Otis D.</description></item><item><title>NJ to Lift School Masking Mandate in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</guid><description>New Jersey will lift its school mask mandate in the second week of March, Gov. Phil Murphy told the New York Times.
Highlights New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy announced Monday that the state will end its school mask mandate on March 7. Murphy said school districts can continue their own mandates if they want. Connecticut Gov. Ned Lamont announced that his state mask mandate will end on Feb. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>'Tsunami' of woes: U.S. school shootings spike amid pandemic stress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</guid><description>Signs are emerging that the challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers studying the phenomenon worry it will only grow.
Highlights Signs are emerging that the stresses and challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers who are studying the phenomenon worry it will only get worse. Already, campuses have been the site of 141 shootings so far during the 2021-22 school year - more than at any point in the previous decade.</description></item><item><title>US conservatives linked to rich donors wage campaign to ban books from schools | US news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</guid><description>Experts warn trend is accelerating as groups push for bans of works that often address race, LGBTQ issues and marginalized people
Summary Conservative groups across the US, often linked to deep-pocketed rightwing donors, are carrying out a campaign to ban books from school libraries, often focused on works that address race, LGBTQ issues or marginalized communities. Groups purporting to be “grassroots” efforts have frequently led the charge, petitioning school boards or elected officials to remove certain books.</description></item><item><title>Video appears to confirm Lorain school worker forced student to eat from trash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</guid><description>Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can.
Summary LORAIN, Ohio (WOIO) - Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can. “The video is shocking, it’s disheartening, it’s disturbing, and it’s what this child has been saying since the beginning,” said Jared Klebanow, the attorney representing the girl’s family.</description></item><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated banned from Italian bars, restaurants, public transport - Italian prime minister Mario Draghi criticized the jab-less, who he claimed were the cause of "most of the problems"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddc5ceb9c1cb154e057483/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddc5ceb9c1cb154e057483/</guid><description>New restrictions targeting the unvaccinated came into force in Italy on Monday with a negative COVID-19 test no longer granting access to bars, restaurants and domestic public transport.
Summary New restrictions targeting the unvaccinated came into force in Italy on Monday, where a negative COVID-19 test no longer grants access to bars, restaurants, and domestic public transport. People who recently recovered COVID-19 are exempted from the new rule which will be in force until March 31.</description></item></channel></rss>