<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>group on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/group/</link><description>Recent content in group on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gun makers lose challenge to New York law allowing lawsuits against industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293e0d4532a6e812a4117f8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293e0d4532a6e812a4117f8/</guid><description>A federal judge threw out a lawsuit by a group of gun manufacturers, distributors and retailers challenging the constitutionality of a New York law.
Highlights A federal judge threw out a lawsuit by a group of gun manufacturers, distributors and retailers challenging the constitutionality of a New York law. The law allows the state and people affected by gun violence to sue the industry. The National Shooting Sports Foundation argued the law wrongly imposes liability on companies operating anywhere in the country that make, sell or market guns or ammunition that are misused by criminals in New York.</description></item><item><title>Beat it: trucker convoy driven out after being egged by kids in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267f4e6d82d0da9443b30d6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267f4e6d82d0da9443b30d6/</guid><description>The people’s convoy had gathered outside lawmaker Buffy Wicks’s house to protest her support of an abortion rights bill
Highlights A people&amp;rsquo;s convoy gathered outside a California lawmaker&amp;rsquo;s home to protest her support of an abortion rights bill. The group was protesting legislation Wicks wrote that would end coroner investigations of stillbirths and mandate Covid vaccines for businesses. When the convoy got stuck in traffic outside an Oakland Safeway, a group of residents began throwing eggs at the stalled vehicles, shouting “get the f*** out of here” The group fled back to their base in Sacramento, complaining about their icy reception and dirty vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Trump SPAC is down 44% since Elon Musk disclosed Twitter stake</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62679bbc61b32a4d1d6322a6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 07:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62679bbc61b32a4d1d6322a6/</guid><description>Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s quest to become a social media mogul is dealing a blow to Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s social venture.
Highlights Digital World Acquisition Corporation, the controversial blank-check firm that plans to merge with Trump Media &amp;amp; Technology Group, fell 13% on Monday to close at $35.71. That&amp;rsquo;s the lowest level since the Trump deal was announced last October. The selloff comes as Musk reaches a deal to take over Twitter, one of the Big Tech companies Trump had vowed to take on.</description></item><item><title>Germany conducts nationwide raids on neo-Nazi groups</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d9fdc39551065c653ff05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 14:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d9fdc39551065c653ff05/</guid><description>Four suspected right-wing extremists have been arrested after police conducted early morning raids. Banned neo-Nazi groups were the focus of the operation.
Highlights Authorities searched the residences of 50 suspected right-wing extremists on Wednesday. Four suspects are believed to be leaders of &amp;ldquo;Atomwaffen Division&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Knockout 51&amp;rdquo; The raids began in the early morning and the neo-Nazi groups were the main focus. Authorities searched homes of 50 suspects and 11 other locations were also searched.</description></item><item><title>MacKenzie Scott donates $436 million to Habitat for Humanity</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623af2f63e64dad725cb829a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 10:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623af2f63e64dad725cb829a/</guid><description>MacKenzie Scott donated $436 million to Habitat for Humanity International and 84 of its U.S. affiliates – the largest publicly disclosed donation from the billionaire philanthropist since she pledged to give away the majority of her wealth in 2019
Highlights MacKenzie Scott donated $436 million to Habitat for Humanity International and 84 of its U.S. affiliates. The gift is the largest publicly disclosed donation from the billionaire philanthropist since she pledged to give away the majority of her wealth in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keeper pleads guilty to seditious conspiracy for Jan. 6 attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622032c56c05a31a2b20e9f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622032c56c05a31a2b20e9f1/</guid><description>Joshua James, 34, of Arab, Alabama, pleaded guilty to seditious conspiracy charges on Wednesday as part of deal with prosecutors contingent on his cooperation.
Highlights Joshua James, 34, pleads guilty to seditious conspiracy charges in exchange for reduced offense level. Plea deal is the first of its kind for a Jan. 6 defendant. James admitted he and others collected firearms at hotels on the outskirts of Washington, D.C., and were ready to use them to prevent Biden from becoming president.</description></item><item><title>Major banks pledging net zero are pouring money into the dirtiest fossil fuel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c093fdcaa3b7dcf5cbd24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c093fdcaa3b7dcf5cbd24/</guid><description>Financial institutions channeled more than $1.5 trillion into the coal industry in loans and underwriting from January 2019 to November 2021, even though many have made net-zero pledges, a report by a group of 28 non-government organizations showed.
Highlights Financial institutions channeled more than $1.5 trillion into the coal industry in loans and underwriting from January 2019 to November 2021. Reducing coal use is a key part of global efforts to slash climate-warming greenhouse gases.</description></item><item><title>US anti-vaccine mandate campaigners aim to mimic Canadian convoy tactic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd964178848bf48989161e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 21:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd964178848bf48989161e/</guid><description>American truckers attract thousands on social media for planned convoy protest to Washington DC
Highlights Facebook group called Convoy to DC 2022 quickly gained more than 100,000 members and announced a convoy next month. Facebook group was recently removed for violating QAnon policies. Organizers deny affiliation to the conspiracy movement and deny any affiliation to them. The group has moved to Telegram, where more than 28,000 have joined. In Canada trucker protests have been linked to the far right and caused days of disruption in the capital, Ottawa, as well as in a border town in Alberta.</description></item><item><title>Hactivists say they hacked Belarus rail system to stop Russian military buildup</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef75f1039fc967d4775ae1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 04:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef75f1039fc967d4775ae1/</guid><description>If confirmed, the attack would be one of the first times ransomware has been used this way.
Summary 🔺Preventing the presence of Russian troops on the territory of #Belarus. For technical reasons, reference web-resources of the Belarusian Railways and services for issuing electronic travel documents are temporarily unavailable. Belarusian Railways apologizes for the inconvenience caused. According to reports, Russia has been sending military equipment and personnel by rail into Belarus, which shares a border with Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Neo-Nazi leader sentenced to 7 years for plot to intimidate Jews, journalists</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</guid><description>A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison.
Summary A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison. The man, Kaleb Cole, 25, the former leader of the Neo-Nazi group Atomwaffen Division, was convicted in September of conspiracy, mailing threatening communications and interfering with a federally protected activity, the Justice Department said in a statement Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Utah billionaire leaves Mormon church, donates $600K to LGBTQ group</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c26aa098e5f7db1cc5de69/</guid><description>Description Jeff Green, a billionaire from Utah, resigned from the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and donated to LGBTQ group Equality Utah.
Summary “The church leadership is not honest about its history, its finances, and its advocacy,” he wrote, according to the Tribune. “We made this investment sizable and publicly to send a message that Equality Utah isn’t going anywhere,” Green wrote, adding that he hopes the donation is the first of many.</description></item></channel></rss>