<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wiped on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wiped/</link><description>Recent content in wiped on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 11:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wiped/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian state TV shows clips simulating Ireland being wiped out by nuclear weapons</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62710e81db0bd013e54c906f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 11:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62710e81db0bd013e54c906f/</guid><description>Putin associate speaks of attacks on ‘British Isles’ amid UK support for Ukraine
Highlights Putin associate speaks of attacks on ‘British Isles’ amid UK support for Ukraine. Putin associate: Attacks on &amp;lsquo;British Isles&amp;rsquo; amid UK backing for Ukraine Ukrainian support for Ukraine government and Kremlin militarising in Ukraine. Not Now I am interested: Sign up for alerts from The Irish Times not Now I&amp;rsquo;m interested in the stories you really want to know about.</description></item><item><title>Bernie Madoff’s sister and her husband found dead in apparent murder-suicide | US crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621357b98eb210085db2d598/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621357b98eb210085db2d598/</guid><description>Palm Beach county sheriff says Sondra Wiener, 87, and 90-year-old husband Marvin Wiener found dead on Thursday
Highlights Sondra Wiener, 87, and her 90-year-old husband Marvin Wiener were found unresponsive with gunshot wounds on Thursday afternoon. Palm Beach county sheriff’s office says it appears to be a murder-suicide. Madoff was known for orchestrating a massive Ponzi scheme that wiped out people&amp;rsquo;s fortunes and ruined charities. After pleading guilty in 2009 to fraud and other charges, he was sentenced to 150 years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Google plans privacy change similar to Apple's, which wiped $230 billion off Facebook's market cap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620df5447e908e3320a09c77/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 07:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620df5447e908e3320a09c77/</guid><description>Google said it will continue to support the current identifiers for the next two years.
Highlights Google said it&amp;rsquo;s developing new privacy-focused replacements for its advertising ID, a unique string of characters that identifies the user&amp;rsquo;s device. The digital IDs in smartphones often help ad-tech companies track and share information about consumers. The changes could affect big companies that have relied on tracking users across apps, like Facebook parent Meta. Apple&amp;rsquo;s adjustments hit Meta particularly hard, with the social media company&amp;rsquo;s parent company losing $232 billion from its market cap in a single day, eventually pushing the total below $600 billion.</description></item></channel></rss>