<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>calling on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/calling/</link><description>Recent content in calling on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 10:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/calling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'She created a McMess': Polk County woman arrested for calling 911 over McDonald's order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a0bf429f664b833325895/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a0bf429f664b833325895/</guid><description>The Polk County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office arrested a woman they say called 911 and assaulted restaurant workers because her McDonald&amp;rsquo;s order was wrong.
Highlights Polk County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office arrested a woman they say called 911 and assaulted restaurant workers because her McDonald&amp;rsquo;s order was wrong. Tianis Jones, 22, was arrested Friday evening. She was arrested on burglary with assault, criminal mischief, disorderly conduct and misuse of 911 charges. Surveillance video shows Jones becoming increasingly displeased with the service, despite workers offering to fix the issues as well as return her money.</description></item><item><title>Lawmakers strike the word ‘marijuana’ from all state laws, calling term racist</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626701212439d6bc37e43bec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 20:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626701212439d6bc37e43bec/</guid><description>Washington state lawmakers passed a law that changes every Revised Code of Washington with the word “marijuana” The change gets rid of the term, swapping it out for “cannabis” Supporters say the word has a
Highlights Washington state lawmakers recently passed a law that changes every Revised Code of Washington with the word “marijuana” The change gets rid of the term, swapping it out for “cannabis” Supporters say the word was used as a racist terminology to lock up Black and brown people.</description></item><item><title>26 MPs of pro-Kurdish party charged with 'offending Turkish state' after calling for Armenian Genocide recognition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cba51c565c8ac983aa5aa7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cba51c565c8ac983aa5aa7/</guid><description>During the session of the&amp;hellip;
Summary Bill Gates reveals plan to save the planetKuwait forms new cabinetAttorney: Criminal prosecution against Artur Vanetsyan terminated, there was no preparation for Armenia PM&amp;rsquo;s murderArmenia army&amp;rsquo;s General Staff chief visits air force military unitArmenia opposition MP: Constitutional Court states that government should decide who will pay for employees&amp;rsquo; PCR testsBrawl takes place in Parliament of JordanArmenia Ombudsman meets with Russia Ambassador, return of Armenian captives being held in Azerbaijan discussedArmenia launches 42 cases regarding submission of declarations by officials in 2021Armenian man who was wanted arrives in Yerevan and voluntarily shows up at police stationArmenia MOD peacekeeping brigade soldiers participate in tactical military exercisesArmenia has new Ambassador to IsraelAzerbaijani opposition journalists protesting against repressive law on mediaArmenia President and his wife pay visit to Yerablur Military PantheonArmenia Competition Protection Commission to check pricing for COVID-19 tests at Zvartnots AirportAdvocate: Criminal prosecution against Armenian detachment commander Ashot Minasyan is overNEWS.</description></item></channel></rss>