<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vaccine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vaccine/</link><description>Recent content in vaccine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 17:22:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vaccine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US supreme court rules against air force officer who refused Covid vaccine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eef9755e81ec0cd1136f1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eef9755e81ec0cd1136f1/</guid><description>Majority of court sides with Pentagon over challenge by lieutenant colonel who cited religious grounds for refusal to get vaccine
Highlights Lt Col Jonathan Dunn cited religious grounds for his refusal to get the Covid-19 vaccine. He cited a speech given by Joe Biden that led him to conclude that “the vaccine ceased to be merely a medical invention and took on a symbolic and even sacramental quality” The court ruled in March that the US navy had the authority to determine the job assignments of 35 service members who refused to get vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Pentagon approves requests for National Guard as trucker convoy eyes D.C.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621686b063bf86a7320aeb06/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621686b063bf86a7320aeb06/</guid><description>The trucker convoy is expected to arrive in the D.C. area as soon as Wednesday.
Highlights National Guard will help during truck convoy protests headed to D.C. area. Truck drivers protesting vaccine requirements are expected to arrive late Wednesday or Thursday. About 700 National Guard personnel will be deployed to help control traffic at designated traffic posts and points leading to the Capitol. Trucker convoy is expected to depart Pennsylvania on Wednesday morning and drive to the area, arriving late Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Iran returns donated vaccines because they were made in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214c5167651f89891f46238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214c5167651f89891f46238/</guid><description>TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran has returned 820,000 doses of coronavirus vaccines donated by Poland because they were manufactured in the United States, state TV reported Monday. TV quoted Mohammad Hashemi, an official in the country’s Health Ministry, as saying that Poland donated about a million doses of the British-Swedish AstraZeneca vaccine to Iran.
Highlights Iran returns donated vaccines because they were made in US. Poland donated about a million doses of the British-Swedish AstraZeneca vaccine.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer expects $54 billion in 2022 sales on Covid vaccine and treatment pill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62030e3e3d8878d511b366da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:44:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62030e3e3d8878d511b366da/</guid><description>Pfizer expects to sell $32 billion of its Covid-19 shots and $22 billion of its antiviral coronavirus treatment pill Paxlovid.
Highlights Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s fourth-quarter revenue more than doubled overall to $23.84 billion year-over-year, driven by $12.5 billion in sales of its Covid vaccine. Pfizer CEO Albert Bourla said sales of Paxlovid could be higher than the company&amp;rsquo;s guidance, but the expectations are based on deals signed or close to being signed. The company&amp;rsquo;s share was down more than 5.</description></item><item><title>Austria makes COVID-19 vaccination mandatory starting February.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5141c404a48f6bdad6630/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 07:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5141c404a48f6bdad6630/</guid><description>Austrian government presents mandatory vaccination law coming in next month
Summary “Without obligatory vaccination, we will always lag behind,” health minister Wolfgang Mueckstein said. “All experts believe that we will need high overall immunity in the population next fall as well,” Mueckstein said. If authorities judge vaccination progress still to be insufficient, they would then send reminders to people who remain unvaccinated, Nehammer said. If that still does not work, people would be sent a vaccination appointment and fined if they do not keep it.</description></item><item><title>Video shows man violently attack workers at COVID vaccine clinic in Tustin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db853837e71bddfba7f512/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db853837e71bddfba7f512/</guid><description>Video shows a man lash out and assault workers at a vaccine clinic in Tustin after he verbally attacked them and called staff &amp;quot;murderers.&amp;quot;
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos A violent attack on staff members that occurred last month at a COVID-19 vaccination clinic in Tustin resulted in a man&amp;rsquo;s arrest, police said. TUSTIN, Calif. (KABC) &amp;ndash; Staff at Families Together of Orange County said Friday they hoped the judicial system ensures employees and other health care workers are protected by the law following a violent attack at their clinic at the end of December.</description></item><item><title>Moderna donates 2.7 million vaccine doses to Mexico as COVID cases surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da96371938dd6817f5c345/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da96371938dd6817f5c345/</guid><description>Moderna donated 2.7 million COVID-19 vaccine doses to Mexico as cases surge in the country.
Summary Moderna donated 2.7 million COVID-19 vaccine doses to Mexico as cases surge in the country. The government said the doses will go to teachers as the country tries to return to fully in-person learning. The donations came after Mexico approved Cuba’s three-shot coronavirus vaccine at the end of December. Mexico has 57 percent of its population fully vaccinated and has authorized the use of 10 different vaccines.</description></item><item><title>Scientists identify antibodies that can neutralize Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd20ce5c4519e782d43bc5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 03:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd20ce5c4519e782d43bc5/</guid><description>According to a new study, a group of international researchers have found certain antibodies can target areas of the virus spike protein that don’t undergo significant changes as the virus mutates.
Summary A team of scientists have identified antibodies they say can neutralize Omicron and other COVID-19 variants. AN UNUSUAL VARIANTThe Omicron variant is considered to be “unusual” because of a large number of mutations to two key areas of the virus’ spike protein.</description></item></channel></rss>