<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vaccine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vaccine/</link><description>Recent content in vaccine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vaccine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moderna donates 2.7 million vaccine doses to Mexico as COVID cases surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da96371938dd6817f5c345/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da96371938dd6817f5c345/</guid><description>Moderna donated 2.7 million COVID-19 vaccine doses to Mexico as cases surge in the country.
Summary Moderna donated 2.7 million COVID-19 vaccine doses to Mexico as cases surge in the country. The government said the doses will go to teachers as the country tries to return to fully in-person learning. The donations came after Mexico approved Cuba’s three-shot coronavirus vaccine at the end of December. Mexico has 57 percent of its population fully vaccinated and has authorized the use of 10 different vaccines.</description></item><item><title>Scientists identify antibodies that can neutralize Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd20ce5c4519e782d43bc5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 03:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd20ce5c4519e782d43bc5/</guid><description>According to a new study, a group of international researchers have found certain antibodies can target areas of the virus spike protein that don’t undergo significant changes as the virus mutates.
Summary A team of scientists have identified antibodies they say can neutralize Omicron and other COVID-19 variants. AN UNUSUAL VARIANTThe Omicron variant is considered to be “unusual” because of a large number of mutations to two key areas of the virus’ spike protein.</description></item></channel></rss>