<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kentucky on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kentucky/</link><description>Recent content in kentucky on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 12:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kentucky/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kentucky lawmakers block abortion access with new law, effective immediately</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62581265ec7547ece70cf0aa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 12:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62581265ec7547ece70cf0aa/</guid><description>Kentucky effectively suspended legal abortion access on Wednesday as the legislature enacted a sweeping anti-abortion law that took effect right away and forces providers to stop offering abortions until they can meet certain requirements.
Highlights Kentucky legislature enacted a sweeping anti-abortion law that took effect right away. It forces providers to stop offering abortions until they can meet certain requirements. The law imposes requirements that the state&amp;rsquo;s clinics say make it too logistically difficult and expensive to operate.</description></item><item><title>Former Kentucky clerk Kim Davis violated rights of same-sex couples, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236f02da07076bc3a44fabb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236f02da07076bc3a44fabb/</guid><description>Former clerk Kim Davis refused to issue marriage licenses to two same-sex couples in 2015.
Highlights U.S. District Judge David Bunning in Ashland issued the ruling Friday in two longstanding lawsuits involving Kim Davis and two same-sex couples. With the decision, a jury trial will still need to take place to decide on damages the couples could be owed. Bunning reasoned that Davis &amp;ldquo;cannot use her own constitutional rights as a shield to violate the constitutional rights of others while performing her duties as an elected official&amp;rdquo; The case could return to the Supreme Court, which declined to take the case in October 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>