<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>angeles on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/angeles/</link><description>Recent content in angeles on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/angeles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Model and friend dumped unconscious at L.A. hospitals died of multiple drug intoxication</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b7bec70b1182b94022539/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b7bec70b1182b94022539/</guid><description>A model and her friend dropped unconscious at different Los Angeles hospitals in November, died of multiple drug intoxication, the Los Angeles coroner has ruled.
Highlights The Los Angeles County Medical Examiner-Coroner has ruled both of their deaths as homicides. Christy Giles, a 24-year-old model, and her friend Hilda Marcela Cabrales Arzola, 26, were dropped off at the hospitals on Nov. 13 by the men in a black Toyota Prius without license plates, police said at the time.</description></item><item><title>Thieves in LA are looting freight trains filled with packages from UPS, FedEx and Amazon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e29b6261b3231b8530b60a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 10:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e29b6261b3231b8530b60a/</guid><description>Photos and videos showing piles of empty boxes littered alongside rail tracks in Los Angeles County, California have gone viral as shipping companies say they&amp;rsquo;ve seen a dramatic spike in railroad theft. Some of the boxes are packages from companies like UPS, Amazon and FedEx.
Summary Washington, DC (CNN) Photos and videos showing piles of empty boxes littered alongside rail tracks in Los Angeles County, California have gone viral as shipping companies say they&amp;rsquo;ve seen a dramatic spike in railroad theft.</description></item></channel></rss>