<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>angeles on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/angeles/</link><description>Recent content in angeles on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:15:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/angeles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge: California's women on boards law is unconstitutional | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628375a70bd227cadc6b3552/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628375a70bd227cadc6b3552/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A Los Angeles judge has ruled that California’s landmark law requiring women on corporate boards is unconstitutional. Superior Court Judge Maureen Duffy-Lewis said the law that would have required boards have up to three female directors by this year violated the right to equal treatment.
Highlights Judge Maureen Duffy-Lewis issued her ruling Friday, May 13, 2022, in Los Angeles Superior Court. The conservative legal group Judicial Watch had challenged the law, claiming it was illegal to use taxpayer funds to enforce a law that violates the equal protection clause of the California Constitution by mandating a gender-based quota.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles residents advised to cut shower time by four minutes as drought worsens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c43530bd065ce6cded00d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 23:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c43530bd065ce6cded00d/</guid><description>Outdoor garden watering also reduced from three days to two from 1 June
Highlights Los Angeles residents advised to cut water usage by seven gallons a day. Residents urged to reduce their per person use by seven minutes a day, equivalent to four minutes of showering. California&amp;rsquo;s water usage jumped nearly 19 per cent in March during one of the driest months on record. California’s governor Gavin Newsom has asked residents to voluntarily help cut water use by 15 per cent.</description></item><item><title>Model and friend dumped unconscious at L.A. hospitals died of multiple drug intoxication</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b7bec70b1182b94022539/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 23:15:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b7bec70b1182b94022539/</guid><description>A model and her friend dropped unconscious at different Los Angeles hospitals in November, died of multiple drug intoxication, the Los Angeles coroner has ruled.
Highlights The Los Angeles County Medical Examiner-Coroner has ruled both of their deaths as homicides. Christy Giles, a 24-year-old model, and her friend Hilda Marcela Cabrales Arzola, 26, were dropped off at the hospitals on Nov. 13 by the men in a black Toyota Prius without license plates, police said at the time.</description></item><item><title>Thieves in LA are looting freight trains filled with packages from UPS, FedEx and Amazon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e29b6261b3231b8530b60a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 10:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e29b6261b3231b8530b60a/</guid><description>Photos and videos showing piles of empty boxes littered alongside rail tracks in Los Angeles County, California have gone viral as shipping companies say they&amp;rsquo;ve seen a dramatic spike in railroad theft. Some of the boxes are packages from companies like UPS, Amazon and FedEx.
Summary Washington, DC (CNN) Photos and videos showing piles of empty boxes littered alongside rail tracks in Los Angeles County, California have gone viral as shipping companies say they&amp;rsquo;ve seen a dramatic spike in railroad theft.</description></item></channel></rss>