<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lauderdale on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lauderdale/</link><description>Recent content in lauderdale on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 09:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lauderdale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Authorities are searching for a corrections officer and inmate who never made it to court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cfd94c4c3a3ed1951b713/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 09:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cfd94c4c3a3ed1951b713/</guid><description>Lauderdale County, Alabama, authorities are searching for a sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office employee and an inmate who went missing on their way to the courthouse on Friday at around 9:30 a.m.
Highlights Missing Assistant Director of Corrections Vicki White broke protocol when she escorted inmate Casey White from jail to the courthouse. Casey White was being held on capital murder charges and two sworn deputies should have been with him at all times, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Florida groups canvass spring breakers to warn of fentanyl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252adcaacb9302c5eec11cf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 10:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252adcaacb9302c5eec11cf/</guid><description>FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — In the days after a group of West Point cadets on spring break were sickened by fentanyl-laced cocaine at a South Florida house party, community activists sprang into action.
Highlights Community activists are warning spring breakers of a surge in recreational drugs being laced with the dangerous opioid fentanyl. Five West Point cadets on spring break were sickened by fentanyl-laced cocaine at a South Florida house party.</description></item></channel></rss>