<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>conviction on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/conviction/</link><description>Recent content in conviction on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 02:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/conviction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge sentences former reality TV star Josh Duggar to more than 12 years in prison for child pornography conviction</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628eecd0fe9d38f94600ff4a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 02:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628eecd0fe9d38f94600ff4a/</guid><description>FAYETTEVILLE, Ark. (AP) — Judge sentences former reality TV star Josh Duggar to more than 12 years in prison for child pornography conviction.
Highlights Judge sentences former reality TV star Josh Duggar to more than 12 years in prison for child pornography conviction. Duggar was convicted of child pornography in Arkansas. He was sentenced to a maximum of 12 years behind bars in Arkansas for the conviction. Josh&amp;rsquo;s wife, former wife of seven years, has been sentenced to life in prison in Arkansas, Arkansas.</description></item><item><title>Judge upholds Ghislaine Maxwell's sex trafficking conviction</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ca9c501fa98110c889f23/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ca9c501fa98110c889f23/</guid><description>A trial judge has concluded there was enough evidence to convict Ghislaine Maxwell of sex trafficking
Highlights Ghislaine Maxwell convicted of recruiting teenage girls for Jeffrey Epstein to sexually abuse from 1994 to 2004. Judge Alison J. Nathan said in written ruling that the jury’s guilty verdicts were “readily supported” by extensive witness testimony and documentary evidence. She also gave Maxwell a legal victory by concluding that three conspiracy counts charged the same crime and she can only be sentenced for one.</description></item><item><title>Derek Chauvin appeals his murder conviction in the death of George Floyd</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694f87ecd648ae1b44f5dc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694f87ecd648ae1b44f5dc/</guid><description>Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has asked the state Court of Appeals to overturn his conviction for the 2020 murder of George Floyd, according to an appeal filed Monday.
Highlights Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has asked the state Court of Appeals to overturn his conviction for the 2020 murder of George Floyd. The 82-page filing lists more than a dozen aspects of the case and trial that Chauvin&amp;rsquo;s attorney argues tainted the proceedings.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell's sex trafficking conviction upheld as US judge refuses retrial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62479e2f599992f1cc89e369/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62479e2f599992f1cc89e369/</guid><description>Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s sex trafficking conviction has been upheld, despite a juror&amp;rsquo;s acknowledgment that he had falsely stated before the trial that he had not been sexually abused.
Highlights Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s sex trafficking conviction has been upheld by a US judge. The 60-year-old Briton was convicted in December of helping Jeffrey Epstein to sexually abuse teenage girls. Maxwell requested a retrial after it emerged that one of the jurors had been sexually abused but had falsely stated before the trial that he had not been.</description></item></channel></rss>