<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>francis on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/francis/</link><description>Recent content in francis on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:07:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/francis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apparent active shooter at medical facility in Tulsa, Oklahoma.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298295f44b6a5935a8f8576/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298295f44b6a5935a8f8576/</guid><description>UPDATE: Saint Francis Health System has released the following statement concerning the shooting: Saint Francis Health System is grieving the loss of four members of our family. As a faith based organization, the only recourse we have at this moment is to pray while we navigate this tragedy. Out of respect for the families, we are not commenting on or releasing names of those lost or injured at this time.</description></item><item><title>Pope prays for end to pandemic in Christmas address</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c90239fc9612bd1a88d1e5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c90239fc9612bd1a88d1e5/</guid><description>He used his Christmas Day address to urge healthcare for all and vaccines for the poor.
Summary Pope Francis has prayed for an end to the coronavirus pandemic, using his Christmas Day address to urge healthcare for all, vaccines for the poor and for dialogue to prevail in resolving the world’s conflicts. Amid a record-setting rise in Covid-19 cases in Italy this week, only a few thousand people headed to a rain-soaked St Peter’s Square for Francis’ annual Christmas address.</description></item></channel></rss>