<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wildfire on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wildfire/</link><description>Recent content in wildfire on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wildfire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Like an inferno:' US West burning at furious pace so far</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ebc8bc73006448b9d24b0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ebc8bc73006448b9d24b0/</guid><description>LAGUNA NIGUEL, Calif. (AP) — Wildfires are on a furious pace early this year — from a California hilltop where mansions with multimillion-dollar Pacific Ocean views were torched to remote New Mexico mountains charred by a month-old monster blaze.
Highlights Wind-driven flames have torn through vegetation that is extraordinarily dry from years-long drought exacerbated by climate change. More than 2,000 square miles (5,180 square kilometers) have burned so far this year — the most at this point since 2018.</description></item><item><title>Texas governor declares state of disaster as wildfire burns over 1,000 acres</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243224cface9c8f41a7c25b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 15:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243224cface9c8f41a7c25b/</guid><description>As wildfires continue to blaze through central Texas, one particular fired named Das Goat Fire has prompted Gov. Greg Abbott to declare a state of disaster.
Highlights Das Goat Fire has burned over 1,000 acres in Medina County, Texas. Gov. Greg Abbott said the fire poses an imminent threat of severe damage. Three homes have been lost and 37 others have been threatened, according to the governor. Many areas throughout Texas will remain under a high to extreme elevated fire risk.</description></item></channel></rss>