<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suffering on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suffering/</link><description>Recent content in suffering on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suffering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Putin treated for advanced cancer and survived assassination attempt, US intelligence reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a0be5b285cfc26cd10605/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a0be5b285cfc26cd10605/</guid><description>The Russian president has received treatment for advanced cancer and was targeted in an assassination attempt, three intelligence sources have told Newsweek
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin received treatment for advanced cancer in April, three US intelligence sources have told Newsweek. The report also confirmed an assassination plot against Mr Putin in March, the organisation said. Rumours have been swirling in the past few months that Mr Putin was suffering from cancer or was in bad health as pictures of him in a debilitated state emerged.</description></item><item><title>Navy SEAL candidate dies and another hospitalized following 'Hell Week'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff4b6c1f0b1f227aa330a4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff4b6c1f0b1f227aa330a4/</guid><description>A Navy SEAL candidate died Friday and another was hospitalized in San Diego after completing a training phase known as &amp;quot;Hell Week.&amp;quot;
Highlights The cause of the SEAL candidate&amp;rsquo;s death is under investigation. The injured candidate is in stable condition at the Naval Medical Center San Diego. They began suffering symptoms &amp;ldquo;several hours&amp;rdquo; after completing a training phase known as &amp;ldquo;Hell Week&amp;rdquo; They were not &amp;ldquo;actively&amp;rdquo; training when they started to suffer symptoms, officials said.</description></item></channel></rss>