<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>used on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/used/</link><description>Recent content in used on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 17:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/used/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maker of Uvalde shooter’s rifle posted image of child with gun before massacre</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629258c016c4e415865b881e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629258c016c4e415865b881e/</guid><description>Gunmaker Daniel Defense posted online an advertising photo of a small child holding one of its AR-15-style rifles just days before one of its firearms was used in the elementary school shooting in Uvalde, Tex.
Highlights Gunmaker Daniel Defense posted the image to Twitter on May 16. The next week, a gunman used a Daniel Defense DDM4 Rifle to kill 19 children and two adults at a school in Texas. The gunmaker had planned to host an exhibitor’s booth at the upcoming National Rifle Association convention, set to begin Friday in Houston.</description></item><item><title>Jury finds alleged Nazi sympathizer guilty of 5 charges ranging from obstruction to disorderly conduct in Jan. 6 case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62922d16bf98057cb63f4582/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 14:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62922d16bf98057cb63f4582/</guid><description>Thomas Hale-Cusanelli, an alleged Nazi sympathizer and Army reservist, was charged with obstructing an official proceeding.
Highlights Thomas Hale-Cusanelli, an alleged Nazi sympathizer and Army reservist, was charged with obstructing an official proceeding. He was found guilty on five charges ranging from obstruction to disorderly conduct in the Capitol riot case. The jury was shown video, audio and social media images, as well as text messages involving his actions on and before the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Trump pays contempt fine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889eb5ac15ad9924e1b9e3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889eb5ac15ad9924e1b9e3/</guid><description>His legal team is expected to file additional documents today related to a sprawling civil financial fraud probe by New York.
Highlights Trump has paid the $110,000 fine levied after he was held in contempt by a New York judge. An attorney for Trump also filed more than a dozen affidavits due Friday in an effort to purge the contempt finding. Trump was fined $10,000 per day through May 6, the date of his most recent attempt to satisfy Judge Arthur Engoron&amp;rsquo;s demands.</description></item><item><title>Pentagon monitoring reports of possible Russian chemical weapons attack in Mariupol</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555e7974c7a3473dd87e2e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555e7974c7a3473dd87e2e/</guid><description>If Russia were to have used chemical weapons, it would signal a major escalation of its botched invasion of Ukraine, which has stalled after more than a month.
Highlights If Russia were to have used chemical weapons in Mariupol, it would represent a major escalation of the conflict. British Foreign Secretary Liz Truss also says her government is working &amp;ldquo;urgently&amp;rdquo; to verify details of alleged attack. The original report was in the form of a Telegram message posted by the Azov Regiment, an ultra-nationalist part of the Ukrainian National Guard.</description></item><item><title>LA jail guards routinely punch incarcerated people in the head, monitors find | Los Angeles sheriff’s department accused of hours-long group strip-search as court report adds to string of scandals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251249317adc028ae6f48a6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 06:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251249317adc028ae6f48a6/</guid><description>Los Angeles sheriff’s department accused of hours-long group strip-search as court report adds to string of scandals
Highlights Los Angeles sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department appears to be routinely violating use-of-force policies, court-appointed monitors say. Guards have punched incarcerated people in the head and subjected them to a “humiliating” group strip-search where they were forced to wait undressed for hours. Guards who used force in violation of policy were at times sent to “remedial training” but that “actual discipline is seldom imposed” The report raises further concerns about the department’s use of the “Wrap” device, which functions like a full-body restraining jacket and is used to ‘immobilize’ people.</description></item><item><title>Dozens killed in attack on Kharkiv, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e6fb587e2dfca36fc716b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 19:11:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e6fb587e2dfca36fc716b/</guid><description>The cities of Kharkiv and Chernihiv suffer fierce shelling despite talks between Russia and Ukraine.
Highlights Kharkiv and Chernihiv suffer fierce shelling despite talks between Russia and Ukraine. In the north-west, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second-largest city has been pounded by suspected cluster munitions. Siege tactics used to devastating effect in Syria are being unleashed around the historic city of Chernihiv. But other Ukrainian cities give a glimpse of what may lie in wait for Kyiv, the country&amp;rsquo;s second largest city, according to a report by the Russian-backed anti-government forces in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Canadian police secure downtown Ottawa as truckers’ protest ends</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621390c49fd93b849866b945/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 13:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621390c49fd93b849866b945/</guid><description>Three-week occupation over Covid precautions and Trudeau government ends with 76 vehicles towed and 191 arrests
Highlights Police secure downtown core of Ottawa with fencing after two days of tense standoffs and 191 arrests. Police used pepper spray and stun grenades on protesters, clearing most of the area in front of parliament. Prime Minister Justin Trudeau invoked emergency powers to give his government wider authority to stop the protests. Protesters initially wanted an end to cross-border Covid-19 vaccine mandates for truck drivers but the blockade turned into a demonstration against Trudeau.</description></item><item><title>Florida woman used PPP loan to hire hit man to kill young mother in front of her daughter, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e65f926b8af585e410b93/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 15:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e65f926b8af585e410b93/</guid><description>A Florida woman is accused of using some of her Covid-19 relief loan to hire a hit man to kill another woman, police said.
Highlights Le’Shonte Jones, 24, was shot multiple times on May 3 as she walked home with her 3-year-old daughter. Suspect Jasmine Martinez is accused of using some of her Covid-19 relief loan to hire a hit man to kill Jones, police say. She is alleged to have withdrawn about $10,000 from a federal Paycheck Protection Program loan she received for a single-employment beauty salon.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families settle with gun maker in historic first</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 19:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bfa85a7e72c201cfebd33/</guid><description>Nine Sandy Hook Elementary School families have announced a settlement with Remington Arms, maker of the AR-15 used in the massacre.
Highlights Remington Arms agrees to pay families $73 million in settlement. Settlement comes seven years after families sued the maker of the Bushmaster XM15-E2S semiautomatic rifle. Remington&amp;rsquo;s version of the AR-15 is substantially similar to the standard issue M16 military service rifle used by the U.S. Army and other nations’ armed forces.</description></item><item><title>Taliban announces a national suicide brigade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</guid><description>The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. These “martyrdom brigades”
Summary The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. Before sweeping into power in 2021, the Taliban used suicide bombers for 20 years to attack US, UK and Afghan troops. Japanese pilots used suicide tactics during the second world war, with the Japanese Kamikaze pilots crashing their aircraft into Allied naval vessels.</description></item></channel></rss>