<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rep on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rep/</link><description>Recent content in rep on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:17:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pennsylvania Senate candidate Fetterman suffers stroke but says he's 'well on my way to a full recovery'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281fa60e9c9afcb4158ee1c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281fa60e9c9afcb4158ee1c/</guid><description>John Fetterman, the favorite to win Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s Democratic US Senate contest, announced Sunday that he&amp;rsquo;s recovering after a stroke.
Highlights John Fetterman is at the Penn Medicine Lancaster General Hospital in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. &amp;ldquo;I had a stroke that was caused by a clot from my heart being in an A-fib rhythm for too long,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;Our campaign isn&amp;rsquo;t slowing down one bit, and we are still on track to win this primary on Tuesday,&amp;rdquo; he adds.</description></item><item><title>Rep. Jeff Fortenberry resigns from Congress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f9dff62cf537b9c986a8e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 23:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f9dff62cf537b9c986a8e/</guid><description>Rep. Jeff Fortenberry has announced he is resigning from Congress.
Highlights Rep. Jeff Fortenberry has announced he is resigning from Congress. All stories about him and any declared candidates in the Nebraska First Congressional District race have been and will be written by outside media outlets. Mike Flood is the founder and owner of Flood Communications and News Channel Nebraska. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez tests positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</guid><description>&amp;quot;She is experiencing symptoms and recovering at home,&amp;quot; her office said in a statement on Sunday.
Summary Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has tested positive for COVID-19, her office said in a statement on Sunday. The CDC recommends that Americans who test positive for COVID-19 and develop symptoms isolate for at least five full days. COVID-19 cases continue to surge across the country, with an average of nearly 700,000 new cases reported per day, according to the CDC.</description></item></channel></rss>