<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sentenced on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sentenced/</link><description>Recent content in sentenced on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 17:08:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sentenced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-Addyston police chief sentenced to 3 years probation for illegally trafficking machine guns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b917277fca9bfe4289a4d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b917277fca9bfe4289a4d/</guid><description>According to court documents, 66-year-old Dorian LaCourse played a key role in a conspiracy to traffic fully-automatic machine guns while chief of police for the Village of Addyston.
Highlights Dorian LaCourse played a key role in a conspiracy to traffic fully-automatic machine guns. As chief of police, LaCourse signed multiple &amp;ldquo;demonstration letters&amp;rdquo; falsely stating the Village of Addyston Police Department was interested in buying various types of machine guns, including military-grade weapons.</description></item><item><title>Germany: Woman sentenced after sabotaging partner's condoms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276468f7418088d7aec9e53/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 10:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276468f7418088d7aec9e53/</guid><description>In what the judge described as a &amp;quot;historic&amp;quot; case, a woman has been found guilty of sexual assault after poking holes in her partner&amp;rsquo;s condoms without his knowledge or consent.
Highlights German court found a woman guilty of sexual assault and handed her a six-month suspended sentence for purposefully damaging her partner&amp;rsquo;s condoms. The case concerned a 39-year-old woman who was in a &amp;ldquo;friends with benefits&amp;rdquo; relationship with a man, 42, who she met online.</description></item><item><title>Court Orders Jussie Smollett Release From Jail During Appeal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232ee2351e025539a7b0aac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232ee2351e025539a7b0aac/</guid><description>Jussie Smollett was ordered released from jail Wednesday by an appeals court that agreed with his lawyers that he should be released pending the appeal of his&amp;hellip;
Highlights Jussie Smollett was ordered released from jail Wednesday by an appeals court that agreed with his lawyers that he should be released pending the appeal of his conviction. The court’s decision marks the latest chapter in a strange story that began in January 2019 when Smollet, who is Black and gay, reported to Chicago police that he was the victim of a racist and homophobic attack by two men wearing ski masks.</description></item><item><title>Jussie Smollett Sentenced to Prison, Probation for Lying to Police in Staged Hate Crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622abeda999e00e3585c1740/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622abeda999e00e3585c1740/</guid><description>After an emotional day of testimony on both sides, actor Jussie Smollett has been sentenced to 150 days in jail in connection to a staged hate crime that&amp;hellip;
Highlights Jussie Smollett has been sentenced to 150 days in jail in connection to a staged hate crime. He was also ordered to pay more than $120,000 in restitution to the city of Chicago. Judge James Linn said that the incident&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;extreme premeditation&amp;rdquo; was an aggravating factor in the case.</description></item><item><title>Former Minnesota police officer Kim Potter sentenced to 2 years in prison for the killing of Daunte Wright</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62100b91e5a0954b87bec8e3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 21:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62100b91e5a0954b87bec8e3/</guid><description>Former Brooklyn Center, Minnesota, police officer Kim Potter was sentenced on Friday. Potter was convicted in December of first-degree and second-degree manslaughter for fatally shooting of 20-year-old Daunte Wright on April 11, 2021. Follow here for the latest news.
Highlights Kim Potter was convicted in December of first-degree and second-degree manslaughter for fatally shooting 20-year-old Daunte Wright. Wright&amp;rsquo;s family attorney Ben Crump said they are disappointed with the sentence. Crump compared Potter&amp;rsquo;s case to that of a Minnesota police officer Mohamed Noor, who was sentenced to four years and nine months for shooting a woman when responding to a 911 call in 2017.</description></item><item><title>Houston mother sentenced to 40 years for beating 5-year-old daughter to death with belt, DA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620efe48450d95882e0ab731/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 02:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620efe48450d95882e0ab731/</guid><description>A woman was sentenced to serve 40 years in prison after beating her 5-year-old daughter to death with a belt and lying about it, according to Harris County District Attorney Kim Ogg.
Highlights Andrea Webb, 24, was found guilty in September for first-degree felony of injury to a child. In 2019, Webb called police and told them her daughter, Samantha Bell, fell from a second-story balcony. Police found that Samantha suffered from bruises all over her body.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles nun, 80, gets prison for $835,000 school theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</guid><description>A Los Angeles nun who stole more than $800,000 to pay for a gambling habit has been sentenced to a year in federal prison
Highlights Mary Margaret Kreuper, 80, admitted to stealing the money from 2008 to 2018 while she was principal at St. James Catholic School in the LA suburb of Torrance. She pleaded guilty last July to one count each of wire fraud and money laundering. Judge Otis D.</description></item><item><title>Former Milwaukee Co. judge sentenced in child pornography case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6a56bc347458a800ce097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6a56bc347458a800ce097/</guid><description>Brett Blomme, 39, was sentenced to nine years in prison after pleading guilty to the charge on Sept. 28.
Summary MADISON, Wis. (WMTV) - A federal attorney reminded the public that “no one is above the law” Wednesday during the sentencing of a former Milwaukee County Children’s Court judge for distribution of child pornography. Brett Blomme, 39, was sentenced to nine years in prison after pleading guilty to the charge on Sept.</description></item></channel></rss>