<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hong on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hong/</link><description>Recent content in hong on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 02:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>China shuts down city of 17.5m people in bid to halt Covid outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ea45a8a6805f7263b5da3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ea45a8a6805f7263b5da3/</guid><description>Authorities adopt a zero tolerance policy in Shenzhen, imposing a lockdown and testing every resident three times
Highlights Everyone in Shenzhen, a finance and technology centre that abuts Hong Kong, will undergo three rounds of testing. The mainland government has reported 1,938 new cases, more than triple Saturday’s total. About three-quarters, or 1,412 cases, were in Jilin province in the north-east. China has reported a total of 4,636 deaths on the mainland out of 115,466 confirmed cases since the pandemic started.</description></item><item><title>Two more Tiananmen monuments removed from Hong Kong universities</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c65f2201cdcd877a651285/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c65f2201cdcd877a651285/</guid><description>Two more Hong Kong universities removed on Friday public monuments to the 1989 Tiananmen protests in Beijing, following the dismantling of a sculpture commemorating victims of the crackdown at another university this week.
Summary &amp;ldquo;I feel heartbroken and shocked,&amp;rdquo; said Felix Chow, a former Chinese University student and district councillor. When asked by Reuters whether Hong Kong or Chinese authorities had instructed all three universities to remove these Tiananmen monuments, the office of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s leader, Carrie Lam, said it had no comment.</description></item><item><title>University of Hong Kong appears to demolish Tiananmen Massacre monument in dead of night - Hong Kong Free Press HKFP</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 08:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c42d30cc946538cc5c2957/</guid><description>Summary Workers at the University of Hong Kong (HKU) removed the Tiananmen Massacre monument late on Wednesday night, months after the university said the statue must go. Pillar of Shame. Jens Galschiøt’s Pillar of Shame monument has stood on campus for over two decades, though – in October – university authorities demanded its removal amid a crackdown on those commemorating the 1989 massacre. The University of Hong Kong ordered the removal of the Pillar of Shame, an eight-metre tall sculpture commemorating the 1989 Tiananmen Massacre, from its campus in October.</description></item></channel></rss>