<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>discovered on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/discovered/</link><description>Recent content in discovered on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/discovered/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teenage girl traumatised after police strip-search, says mum</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c849dc18a28627fe2e717/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c849dc18a28627fe2e717/</guid><description>A 14-year-old girl who was strip-searched by police was traumatised by the incident, her mum says.
Highlights Olivia was strip-searched by police after an argument with two boys. She was searched by police at the scene and nothing was discovered. The 14-year-old was traumatised by the incident, her mother said. She said Olivia had been out with friends when they had an argument. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Six New Miniature Frog Species Discovered in Mexico</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278db86fa36fa201e09e385/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 09:15:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278db86fa36fa201e09e385/</guid><description>The amphibians are found under leaf litter and hatch fully grown
Highlights Scientists have discovered six new frog species in Mexico. The tiny amphibians are found under leaf litter and hatch fully-formed adults. They are known as direct-developing frogs, meaning they skip the tadpole stage and hatch as adults. The species&amp;rsquo; tiny size places them at the bottom of the food chain, serving as a delicious meal for birds, lizards, small mammals, and other frogs.</description></item><item><title>New frog species discovered in Australia – and it’s already endangered</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e4f3adb002f3d663d0dd3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e4f3adb002f3d663d0dd3/</guid><description>Mountain frog lives in Queensland’s Gondwana rainforests which were extensively burned in black summer bushfires
Highlights Australian scientists have discovered a new species of frog in south-east Queensland. The new mountain frog’s only known habitat is the world heritage-listed Gondwana rainforests which were extensively burned during the 2019-20 black summer bushfires. The frog was discovered thanks to extensive genetic testing. Scientists have been gathering and analysing the DNA of the mountain frogs in the rainforest since 2006.</description></item><item><title>Workers discover ‘unprecedented’ Phoenician necropolis in southern Spain</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d0be8d7bb1be7ad9d4308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 10:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d0be8d7bb1be7ad9d4308/</guid><description>Preliminary surveys in Osuna have turned up eight burial vaults as well as staircases
Highlights Archaeologists find Phoenician-Carthaginian cemetery in the town of Osuna, 55 miles (90km) east of Seville. Site dates back to the fourth or fifth century BC and is highly unusual as such sites are normally found in coastal areas rather than so far inland. The only similar finds have been made around the coast of Cádiz, which was founded by the Phoenicians in 1100BC and which is one of the oldest continuously inhabited cities in Europe.</description></item></channel></rss>