<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>women on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/women/</link><description>Recent content in women on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 19:08:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Candidate for San Diego County Sheriff leaves job, loses endorsement after transgender comments</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293c482f0f1b7cab3fa2e64/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 19:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293c482f0f1b7cab3fa2e64/</guid><description>During an April candidates forum, Republican John Hemmerling commented on where transgender women should use the bathroom. He says he left his job this week with the City Attorney&amp;rsquo;s Office to focus on the election, not because of backlash from his comments.
Highlights Republican John Hemmerling left his job as the chief criminal criminal prosecutor in the City Attorney’s office this week. Video surfaced showing him making comments about where transgender women should use the bathroom.</description></item><item><title>Men and boys among alleged rape victims of Russian soldiers in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272b6d28740d75f9abcb471/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 17:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272b6d28740d75f9abcb471/</guid><description>UN chief on sexual violence warns dozens of cases under investigation are ‘tip of the iceberg’
Highlights UN special representative on sexual violence in war warns dozens of cases of rape by invading forces are already under investigation. UN envoy Pramila Patten urges survivors to come forward and report rape cases. Russian forces still hold swathes of territory in the south and east of the country. Victims range from men and women of all ages, from children to elderly people, UN says.</description></item><item><title>Texas state troopers told to slim down waistline or face consequences: report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f8ee555ec26f49d60f028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 04:41:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f8ee555ec26f49d60f028/</guid><description>More than 200 Texas DPS state troopers will need to slim down by the end of the year or face disciplinary actions.
Highlights More than 200 Texas state troopers will need to slim down by the end of the year or face disciplinary actions. Officers who fail to trim down by December can be denied promotions, overtime, or even be removed from enforcement duties. Men with a waist size over 40 inches and women over 35 inches will have to track and share weight loss efforts.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis signs Florida's 15-week abortion ban into law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258c2e236048d621a24faa0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:57:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258c2e236048d621a24faa0/</guid><description>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law on Thursday a Mississippi-style anti-abortion measure that bans the procedure after 15 weeks of pregnancy without exemptions for rape, incest or human trafficking.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law on Thursday banning abortion after 15 weeks of pregnancy. The bill, which goes into effect July 1, does allow exemptions in cases where a pregnancy is &amp;ldquo;serious risk&amp;rdquo; to the mother or a fatal fetal abnormality is detected.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky governor vetoes transgender girls sports ban</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eab435db537cde8b1d520/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 09:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eab435db537cde8b1d520/</guid><description>FRANKFORT, Ky. (AP) — Kentucky&amp;rsquo;s Democratic governor on Wednesday vetoed a bill that&amp;hellip;
Highlights Gov. Andy Beshear said the Republican-backed measure “most likely” violates the U.S. Constitution&amp;rsquo;s equal protection rights. The state&amp;rsquo;s GOP-dominated legislature will have a chance to override the veto when lawmakers reconvene April 13 for the last two days of this year&amp;rsquo;s session. The bill sparked emotional debate at times but cleared both chambers with support from large majorities.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in New York City attacks on Asian women indicted on felony hate charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c083063745b28950cc1b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 09:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c083063745b28950cc1b1/</guid><description>A man arrested last month in a string of attacks on seven Asian women in New York City has been indicted on felony and misdemeanor hate crimes charges,
Highlights Steven Zajonc, 28, is charged with six felony counts of third-degree assault as a hate crime. Zajanc is accused in a three-hour string of attacks targeting Asian women on Feb. The district attorney&amp;rsquo;s office has 27 open cases related to anti-Asian hate crimes, prosecutors say.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: Squatters occupy Russian oligarch's London mansion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fa205053f8b3ad4f0e568/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 20:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fa205053f8b3ad4f0e568/</guid><description>Protesters want to give the property, believed to be owned by Oleg Deripaska, to Ukrainian refugees.
Highlights Protesters want to give the property believed to be owned by Oleg Deripaska to Ukrainian refugees. One man said: &amp;ldquo;A lot of civilians and women and children are dying every day for Putin and it&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable&amp;rdquo; Protesters want the property to be given to refugees in Ukraine. One said: &amp;lsquo;We need to protest in every way we can because this war is not right.</description></item><item><title>100 women have now graduated US Army Ranger School - Task &amp;amp; Purpose</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d99497f8054de84ffafc0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 07:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d99497f8054de84ffafc0/</guid><description>As of Friday, more than 100 women have completed the Army&amp;rsquo;s grueling Ranger School, earning the Army Ranger tab.
Highlights As of Friday, more than 100 women have completed the Army&amp;rsquo;s grueling Ranger School. The eight-week assessment and selection includes three phases that test soldiers physically and psychologically. The first women graduated Ranger School in August 2015, and since then women have continued breaking barriers. Staff Sgt. Danielle Farber, one of the first two women from the National Guard to finish Ranger School, said the school was the “hardest course I’ve done by far” The first Ranger School graduate became the first female infantry officer in the Army in August 2014, Capt.</description></item><item><title>Colombia decriminalizes abortion in historic ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62147f667f240bddea38d20a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 06:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62147f667f240bddea38d20a/</guid><description>Colombian court decriminalizes abortion for first 24 weeks of pregnancy. Restrictions will remain in place if women request an abortion after the 24th week of gestation. Women’s rights organizations had been asking to decriminalize abortion for years.
Highlights Women in Colombia are free to end pregnancies until the 24th week after insemination. Women were only allowed to abort pregnancies in cases of rape, or if the life of the mother or unborn baby was seriously compromised.</description></item></channel></rss>