<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>women on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/women/</link><description>Recent content in women on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 09:13:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suspect in New York City attacks on Asian women indicted on felony hate charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c083063745b28950cc1b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 09:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c083063745b28950cc1b1/</guid><description>A man arrested last month in a string of attacks on seven Asian women in New York City has been indicted on felony and misdemeanor hate crimes charges,
Highlights Steven Zajonc, 28, is charged with six felony counts of third-degree assault as a hate crime. Zajanc is accused in a three-hour string of attacks targeting Asian women on Feb. The district attorney&amp;rsquo;s office has 27 open cases related to anti-Asian hate crimes, prosecutors say.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: Squatters occupy Russian oligarch's London mansion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fa205053f8b3ad4f0e568/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 20:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fa205053f8b3ad4f0e568/</guid><description>Protesters want to give the property, believed to be owned by Oleg Deripaska, to Ukrainian refugees.
Highlights Protesters want to give the property believed to be owned by Oleg Deripaska to Ukrainian refugees. One man said: &amp;ldquo;A lot of civilians and women and children are dying every day for Putin and it&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable&amp;rdquo; Protesters want the property to be given to refugees in Ukraine. One said: &amp;lsquo;We need to protest in every way we can because this war is not right.</description></item><item><title>100 women have now graduated US Army Ranger School - Task &amp;amp; Purpose</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d99497f8054de84ffafc0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 07:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d99497f8054de84ffafc0/</guid><description>As of Friday, more than 100 women have completed the Army&amp;rsquo;s grueling Ranger School, earning the Army Ranger tab.
Highlights As of Friday, more than 100 women have completed the Army&amp;rsquo;s grueling Ranger School. The eight-week assessment and selection includes three phases that test soldiers physically and psychologically. The first women graduated Ranger School in August 2015, and since then women have continued breaking barriers. Staff Sgt. Danielle Farber, one of the first two women from the National Guard to finish Ranger School, said the school was the “hardest course I’ve done by far” The first Ranger School graduate became the first female infantry officer in the Army in August 2014, Capt.</description></item><item><title>Colombia decriminalizes abortion in historic ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62147f667f240bddea38d20a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 06:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62147f667f240bddea38d20a/</guid><description>Colombian court decriminalizes abortion for first 24 weeks of pregnancy. Restrictions will remain in place if women request an abortion after the 24th week of gestation. Women’s rights organizations had been asking to decriminalize abortion for years.
Highlights Women in Colombia are free to end pregnancies until the 24th week after insemination. Women were only allowed to abort pregnancies in cases of rape, or if the life of the mother or unborn baby was seriously compromised.</description></item></channel></rss>