<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>investigation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/investigation/</link><description>Recent content in investigation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 16:29:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/investigation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israel will not hold criminal inquiry into killing of journalist Shireen Abu Aqleh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628670273b78ed211ef9d111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 16:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628670273b78ed211ef9d111/</guid><description>Military police say they are satisfied with assurances of Israeli troops over death of US-Palestinian despite international demands
Highlights Israel will not launch a criminal investigation into the killing of US-Palestinian journalist Shireen Abu Aqleh, which Palestinian officials and witnesses have blamed on Israeli soldiers. The Israeli military police branch has accepted assurances of Israeli troops that they were not aware she was in a village adjacent to the Jenin refugee camp when she was killed on 11 May.</description></item><item><title>Suspect arrested in Dallas salon shooting as FBI opens hate crime investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62840f6d512ad27954770942/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 21:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62840f6d512ad27954770942/</guid><description>Dallas police arrested a suspect in connection with the May 11 shooting of three Korean women at a hair salon. The FBI opened a hate crime probe into the incident.
Highlights Dallas police arrested a suspect in connection with the May 11 shooting of three women in a hair salon in the city&amp;rsquo;s Koreatown. The incident is being investigated as a hate crime and could be linked to a series of recent shootings at Asian-run businesses.</description></item><item><title>AP News: Independent probe points to Israeli fire in journalist death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281c6e961192b99ec3c8a89/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 03:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281c6e961192b99ec3c8a89/</guid><description>JERUSALEM (AP) — As Israel and the Palestinians wrangle over the investigation into the killing of Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh, several independent groups have launched their own probes.
Highlights Shireen Abu Akleh was shot and killed while covering an Israeli raid in the occupied West Bank. She was a household name across the Arab world, known for documenting the hardship of Palestinian life under Israeli rule. Israel and Palestinians are locked in a war of narratives that already has put Israel on the defensive.</description></item><item><title>Burial sites found at 53 Native American boarding schools: Interior Dept</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c992ba64a7397161ee61f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c992ba64a7397161ee61f/</guid><description>A U.S. government investigation into the dark history of Native American boarding schools has found &amp;quot;marked or unmarked burial sites&amp;quot; at 53 of them, Interior Secretary Deb Haaland said on Wednesday.
Highlights Interior Secretary Deb Haaland announced the investigation last year into the dark history of Native American boarding schools in the United States. The schools used education to change culture so tribal land could be taken. Many children were abused at the schools, and tens of thousands were never heard from again, activists and researchers say.</description></item><item><title>Saturday night shootout at McDonald’s in Orange County after woman fires gun at deputies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fbcb55465308b3ca34e20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 11:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fbcb55465308b3ca34e20/</guid><description>Deputies responded to an armed robbery call at a McDonald’s on Saturday night. Deputies said the shooter, a woman in her 30s, fired a handgun inside and made threatening statements. All employees and customers were able to
Highlights Deputies responded to an armed robbery call at a McDonald’s on Saturday night. Deputies said the shooter, a woman in her 30s, fired a handgun inside and made threatening statements. All employees and customers were able to get out unharmed.</description></item><item><title>Judge finds Trump in contempt in legal fight with NY AG</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266f252cb0340c9aba0614b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 19:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266f252cb0340c9aba0614b/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A New York judge found former President Donald Trump in contempt of court and set in motion $10,000 daily fines Monday for failing to adequately respond to a subpoena issued by the state&amp;rsquo;s attorney general as part of a civil investigation into his business dealings.
Highlights A New York judge found former president Donald Trump in contempt of court for failing to adequately respond to a subpoena issued by the state’s attorney general as part of a civil investigation into his business dealings.</description></item><item><title>Chairman of Russian metals company calls for Bucha probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62522b1d9ecd65f4abcd34ab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62522b1d9ecd65f4abcd34ab/</guid><description>The board chairman of Russian metals company Rusal has called for an investigation into events in the Kyiv suburb of Bucha, where Ukrainian officials say Russian troops killed civilians
Highlights Board chairman of Russian metals company Rusal has called for an investigation into events in the Kyiv suburb of Bucha. Ukrainian forces and journalists discovered scores of bodies on streets and in mass graves after Russian troops withdrew. The Kremlin has said the deaths were staged by the Ukrainians to denigrate Russian forces.</description></item><item><title>Ex-prosecutor: Trump 'guilty of numerous felony violations'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623da388f676fc7e4a9394e8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 11:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623da388f676fc7e4a9394e8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A prosecutor who had been leading a criminal investigation into Donald Trump before quitting last month said in his resignation letter that he believes the former president is “guilty of numerous felony violations” and he disagreed with the Manhattan district attorney’s decision not to seek an indictment.
Highlights Mark Pomerantz told District Attorney Alvin Bragg there was “evidence sufficient to establish Mr. Trump’s guilt beyond a reasonable doubt” of allegations he falsified financial statements to secure loans and burnish his image as a wealthy businessman.</description></item><item><title>Amazon referred to DOJ for potential criminal obstruction of Congress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228eebcd2a894fbdf02fc03/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 18:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228eebcd2a894fbdf02fc03/</guid><description>The group alleges Amazon has purposely sought to mislead lawmakers as they&amp;rsquo;ve questioned the company&amp;rsquo;s private-label practices and collection of seller data.
Highlights A bipartisan group of lawmakers sent a letter to Attorney General Merrick Garland. They allege Amazon misled the House Judiciary Committee during a 16-month investigation. Lawmakers say the company made false and misleading statements about its practices. An Amazon spokesperson said there&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;no factual basis&amp;rdquo; for the allegations.</description></item><item><title>Judge says Trump and two adult children must testify in New York attorney general probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eecab10766fd4312e9a23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eecab10766fd4312e9a23/</guid><description>Lawyers for Trump, Donald Trump Jr. and Ivanka Trump attacked New York Attorney General Letitia James for political bias against Trump.
Highlights A New York judge rules that Donald Trump and two of his adult children must comply with subpoenas. The judge also ordered them to turn over evidence for a civil investigation by the state&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s Office. Attorney General Letitia James is investigating whether the Trump Organization improperly stated the valuations of various real estate assets to obtain more favorable loans, insurance rates and tax benefits.</description></item><item><title>New York attorney general asks court to enforce subpoenas of Trump children in tax fraud probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</guid><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization.
Summary New York Attorney General Letitia James has subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization, court filings made public Monday reveal. The state attorney general &amp;ldquo;is engaged in a criminal investigation that has an active grand jury.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest bystander for filming traffic stop, allegedly interfering with investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 05:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2b0ed4a2c9a56590f80e9/</guid><description>Description Killeen police arrest a man for interfering with an officer.
Summary KILLEEN, Texas (KWTX) - The Killeen Police Department arrested a man early Saturday morning for interfering with an officer conducting a traffic stop. “I have a right to be there. I have a right to record and I also have a right to free speech,” could be heard from the unnamed individual in the video. The video which is just over 130 Seconds long shows a man walking down the sidewalk when he sees police conducting a traffic stop.</description></item></channel></rss>