<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kazakhstan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kazakhstan/</link><description>Recent content in kazakhstan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kazakhstan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kazakhstan: Putin says Russia will not allow revolutions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcba91eaade13cd0479f92/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcba91eaade13cd0479f92/</guid><description>Kazakh President Kassym-Jomart Tokayev claims Islamists had sought to launch a coup under the guise of protest. The country had been targeted by &amp;quot;international terrorism,&amp;quot; according to Vladimir Putin.
Summary What Putin said on &amp;lsquo;revolution&amp;rsquo;Putin said the deployment of CSTO troops had prevented armed groups from undermining the basis of power in Kazakhstan. In pictures: Kazakhstan protests escalate Mass protests hit streets Protests were first triggered by a dramatic rise in the price of fuel.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan president authorises forces to 'fire without warning'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d88dd08ccf652a6b47a85f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 19:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d88dd08ccf652a6b47a85f/</guid><description>President Kassym-Jomart Tokayev said on Friday he had ordered security forces to open fire without warning in order to quell Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s worst unrest in decades, thanking Russia and its allies for t…
Summary A vehicle set on fire during the protests is seen on a road in Almaty, Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s largest city, on January 6, 2022. President Kassym-Jomart Tokayev said on Friday he had ordered security forces to open fire without warning in order to quell Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s worst unrest in decades, thanking Russia and its allies for their assistance in restoring order.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops arrive in Kazakhstan, as dozens of protesters killed, thousands arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</guid><description>Russia sent paratroopers to Kazakhstan to help its government end mass protests there.
Summary Small numbers of Russian paratrooper units landed at an airbase in Kazakhstan, with Russian state media showing the soldiers disembarking from transport planes and off-loading armored vehicles. The number of Russian troops was unclear, but it was estimated from several hundred to a few thousand, alongside several hundred from Belarus, Tajikistan and Armenia that were also due to arrive.</description></item><item><title>'Dozens' killed by police overnight in Kazakhstan protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d74b150f2d85ecb558b660/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d74b150f2d85ecb558b660/</guid><description>Kazakhstan: Fresh gunfire heard in Almaty as deadly unrest continues
Summary Fresh gunfire was heard in Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s economic capital Almaty on Thursday afternoon, reported AFP, as violence continues to rock the Central Asian country. Azirbek said an &amp;ldquo;anti-terrorist&amp;rdquo; operation was underway in one of the districts of Almaty where the riots were most violent. Some of the cities in Kazakhstan where protests have been taking place. Following the government&amp;rsquo;s dismissal, Deputy prime minister Alikhan Smailov is to assume the role of interim prime minister until a new cabinet is formed.</description></item></channel></rss>