<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>supreme on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/supreme/</link><description>Recent content in supreme on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/supreme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pa. Supreme Court says warrantless searches not justified by cannabis smell alone</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cfa7b627c20b2654f045ce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cfa7b627c20b2654f045ce/</guid><description>On Dec. 29, Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s highest court confirmed a decision by a trial court that said the smell of cannabis cannot be the sole basis of&amp;hellip;
Summary On Dec. 29, Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s highest court confirmed a decision by a trial court that said the smell of cannabis cannot be the sole basis of a warrantless search by police officers. Then a trooper smelled the odor of burnt marijuana through the open window of the vehicle, wrote Chief Justice Max Baer in the majority opinion .</description></item><item><title>Sarah Weddington, attorney who won Roe v Wade abortion case, dies aged 76</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</guid><description>Texan lawyer and Linda Coffee won landmark 1973 case, safeguarding right now under threat from US supreme court
Summary Sarah Weddington, an attorney who argued and won the Roe v Wade supreme court case which established the right to abortion in the US, has died. “With Linda Coffee, she filed the first case of her legal career, Roe v Wade, fresh out of law school. Sarah Weddington poses with a signed copy of the Roe v Wade decision in front of the US supreme court in 2005.</description></item></channel></rss>