<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>supreme on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supreme/</link><description>Recent content in supreme on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 21:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supreme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. abortion rights activists start 'summer of rage' with Saturday protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62801b553f6a9e6023db2c58/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 21:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62801b553f6a9e6023db2c58/</guid><description>Thousands of abortion rights supporters rallied across the United States on Saturday to express their anger over fears the Roe v. Wade case that legalized abortion nationwide will be overturned by the U.S. Supreme Court.
Highlights Protests held across the U.S. over fears the Roe v. Wade case that legalized abortion nationwide will be overturned. Large gatherings in New York, Washington, Los Angeles and Chicago with some smaller counter-protests. The court&amp;rsquo;s final ruling, which could give states the power to ban abortion, is expected in June.</description></item><item><title>Satanic Temple requests flag raising at Boston City Hall after Supreme Court rules city violated free speech rights in refusing to fly Christian flag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62729877e863103d92764d4a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 15:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62729877e863103d92764d4a/</guid><description>The Satanic Temple is hoping to raise one of its flags in front of Boston City Hall. The city refused to let Camp Constitution, a Christian organization, hoist its flag. The Supreme Court ruled that Boston violated First Amendment rights by refusing
Highlights The Satanic Temple is hoping to raise one of its flags in front of Boston City Hall. The city refused to let Camp Constitution, a New Hampshire-based Christian organization, hoist its flag at City Hall Plaza in 2017.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs Texas-style ban on most abortions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62720093b4de16de1e44862b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62720093b4de16de1e44862b/</guid><description>Oklahoma’s Republican Gov. Kevin Stitt has signed a Texas-style abortion ban that prohibits abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy
Highlights Gov. Kevin Stitt signs a Texas-style abortion ban that prohibits abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy. A similar bill approved in Texas last year led to a dramatic reduction in the number of abortions performed in that state. Stitt&amp;rsquo;s signing of the bill comes on the heels of a leaked draft opinion from the nation&amp;rsquo;s high court that it is considering weakening or overturning the landmark Roe v.</description></item><item><title>Crowds protest at Supreme Court after leak of Roe opinion draft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271b72354c6deddee3ee156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 23:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271b72354c6deddee3ee156/</guid><description>Activists expect a larger turnout Tuesday afternoon and evening, with protests planned in state capitals across the country.
Highlights More than 100 supporters of abortion rights and a smaller number of opponents continued to voice their reactions to a leaked opinion by the court signaling it was positioned to overturn Roe v. Wade. The two groups were separated by police barricades, but many of the antiabortion demonstrators present earlier Tuesday had left.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court says Boston violated First Amendment rights of group seeking to raise a Christian flag outside City Hall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270660b2af196449ec319f1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 23:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270660b2af196449ec319f1/</guid><description>The Supreme Court unanimously ruled Monday that Boston violated the First Amendment rights of a group seeking to briefly raise a Christian flag atop a city flagpole outside of City Hall as a part of a city program celebrating Boston&amp;rsquo;s greater community.
Highlights The Supreme Court ruled Monday that Boston violated the First Amendment rights of a group seeking to briefly raise a Christian flag atop a city flagpole. The case was filed in 2018 after a Boston official denied the application by the group Camp Constitution to raise a flag &amp;ndash; described as &amp;ldquo;Christian&amp;rdquo; in the application &amp;ndash; on one of the three flagpoles outside Boston&amp;rsquo;s city hall.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after setting himself on fire in front of the Supreme Court, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626479f4fadd7c8bdeffb56e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 22:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626479f4fadd7c8bdeffb56e/</guid><description>The court said there were no other injuries, and there does not appear to be a public safety concern.
Highlights Police identify the man as 50-year-old Wynn Bruce, of Boulder, Colorado. The court said there were no other injuries, and there does not appear to be a public safety concern. Police have identified a person of interest in the case, but have not named or apprehended a suspect. The incident comes amid a chaotic day in Washington D.</description></item><item><title>Brazil Supreme Court judge suspends messaging app Telegram, a key Bolsonaro platform</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236637dfab7621246b4b00d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 23:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236637dfab7621246b4b00d/</guid><description>A Supreme Court judge in Brazil ruled to block popular messaging application Telegram nationwide, barring one of far-right President Jair Bolsonaro&amp;rsquo;s favourite communication channels, in a decision p…
Highlights A Supreme Court judge in Brazil blocks Telegram, barring one of far-right President Jair Bolsonaro&amp;rsquo;s favourite communication channels. Judge cites Telegram&amp;rsquo;s failure to comply with orders from Brazilian authorities and remove messages found to contain disinformation. Decision comes as far right leader Bolsonara gears up to seek reelection in October, facing a popularity slump.</description></item><item><title>Gun-waving St. Louis couple placed on probation as lawyers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62045f4634b7b4d588f9c6e6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 00:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62045f4634b7b4d588f9c6e6/</guid><description>The Missouri Supreme Court on Tuesday placed a St. Louis couple who gained national attention for waving guns at racial injustice protesters on probation as attorneys. The court suspended Mark and Patricia McCloskeys&amp;rsquo; law licenses but delayed the suspension and put the two on probation for a year.
Highlights Mark and Patricia McCloskey, a Republican candidate for U.S. Senate in Missouri, and his wife, Patricia, received national attention for waving guns at racial injustice protesters in June 2020 encounter.</description></item><item><title>NC Supreme Court rules legislative and congressional maps as unconstitutional gerrymanders</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff1ab99970f93bf8dc47d6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 00:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff1ab99970f93bf8dc47d6/</guid><description>On Friday, Attorney General Josh Stein said that the state Supreme Court just struck down the legislative and congressional maps as an “unconstitutional partisan gerrymander.”
Highlights N.C. Supreme Court strikes down redrawn congressional and congressional maps as unconstitutional gerrymanders. Attorney General Josh Stein: The maps violate a voter’s fundamental right to vote. The unanimous decision by the three trial judges will be appealed by the advocacy groups and voters who challenged the new congressional and legislative lines.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court blocks Biden vaccine mandate for businesses, backs health-care worker rule</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0cb3b85a13bc99466417f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0cb3b85a13bc99466417f/</guid><description>The Supreme Court ruled against the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s rule for OSHA, saying it did not have the power to require vaccination for millions of Americans.
Summary The rulings came three days after the Occupational Safety and Health Administration&amp;rsquo;s emergency measure for businesses started to take effect. The Supreme Court on Thursday blocked the Biden administration from enforcing its sweeping vaccine-or-test requirements for large private companies, but allowed a vaccine mandate to stand for medical facilities that take Medicare or Medicaid payments.</description></item><item><title>Pa. Supreme Court says warrantless searches not justified by cannabis smell alone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfa7b627c20b2654f045ce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfa7b627c20b2654f045ce/</guid><description>On Dec. 29, Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s highest court confirmed a decision by a trial court that said the smell of cannabis cannot be the sole basis of&amp;hellip;
Summary On Dec. 29, Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s highest court confirmed a decision by a trial court that said the smell of cannabis cannot be the sole basis of a warrantless search by police officers. Then a trooper smelled the odor of burnt marijuana through the open window of the vehicle, wrote Chief Justice Max Baer in the majority opinion .</description></item><item><title>Sarah Weddington, attorney who won Roe v Wade abortion case, dies aged 76</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</guid><description>Texan lawyer and Linda Coffee won landmark 1973 case, safeguarding right now under threat from US supreme court
Summary Sarah Weddington, an attorney who argued and won the Roe v Wade supreme court case which established the right to abortion in the US, has died. “With Linda Coffee, she filed the first case of her legal career, Roe v Wade, fresh out of law school. Sarah Weddington poses with a signed copy of the Roe v Wade decision in front of the US supreme court in 2005.</description></item></channel></rss>