<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>push on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/push/</link><description>Recent content in push on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 01:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/push/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Utilities push back against growth of rooftop solar panels</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627867d075de3aa06c49631a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 01:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627867d075de3aa06c49631a/</guid><description>Rooftop solar is key to fighting climate change, advocates say. But utilities disagree on how much they should pay for it.
Highlights Mississippi&amp;rsquo;s Public Service Commission is considering rules that would expand subsidies for rooftop solar. Thirty-seven states reimburse at the full retail rate, but Mississippi offers significantly less. Only 586 Mississippi households have the technology to install solar panels. Advocates say the technology is crucial to weaning the energy system off fossil fuel sources that emit carbon dioxide, a major cause of global warming.</description></item><item><title>EU deal will push Google, Facebook, others to police platforms against hate speech, disinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264cf41f8f06fb43bfff2e1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264cf41f8f06fb43bfff2e1/</guid><description>European Union officials clinched the agreement in principle on the Digital Services Act after lengthy final negotiations that began Friday. The law will also force tech companies to make it easier for users to flag problems, ban online ads aimed at kids and empower regulators to punish noncompliance with billions in fines.
Highlights NEW: The Digital Services Act is one half of an overhaul for the 27-nation bloc’s digital rulebook. Big tech companies like Google and Facebook parent Meta will have to police their platforms more strictly to better protect European users from hate speech, disinformation and other harmful online content.</description></item><item><title>Soaring food prices push more Cargill family members on to world’s richest 500 list | The super-rich</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d71eb1c72ce2e5e390db9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 14:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d71eb1c72ce2e5e390db9/</guid><description>Fortunes of siblings James Cargill, Austen Cargill and Marianne Liebmann up a fifth this year
Highlights Siblings James Cargill, Austen and Marianne Liebmann join ranks of the world’s 500 richest people. They have an estimated $5.4bn (£4.1bn) fortune – up a fifth so far this year. The UN said global food prices had soared to a record high because of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The war has disrupted Black Sea exports of crucial commodities from a region that had been producing more than a quarter of world&amp;rsquo;s wheat exports.</description></item></channel></rss>