<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>person on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/person/</link><description>Recent content in person on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 23:09:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/person/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1 shot dead and multiple wounded after shooting at Graduation party in Thomaston - Fox3 Now</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ab8e160ed0e940f900ab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 23:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ab8e160ed0e940f900ab/</guid><description>ONE person is dead and two more are wounded after a gunman opened fire at a graduation party attended by 200 people in Thomaston Atlanta.
Highlights At least 200 people, mostly teens, were in the Park Lane Event Center when the shooting happened. Two people with serious injuries were taken by helicopter to a hospital in Macon, Georgia. Police have not made any arrests, but they think the suspects are not from the Thomaston area because only one of the victims lived there.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after setting himself on fire in front of the Supreme Court, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626479f4fadd7c8bdeffb56e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 22:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626479f4fadd7c8bdeffb56e/</guid><description>The court said there were no other injuries, and there does not appear to be a public safety concern.
Highlights Police identify the man as 50-year-old Wynn Bruce, of Boulder, Colorado. The court said there were no other injuries, and there does not appear to be a public safety concern. Police have identified a person of interest in the case, but have not named or apprehended a suspect. The incident comes amid a chaotic day in Washington D.</description></item><item><title>Pittsburgh Mass Shooting: 11 shot, 2 juveniles dead in Easter shooting at Airbnb in East Allegheny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c3dbfdd6f8ad9f68532c1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c3dbfdd6f8ad9f68532c1/</guid><description>Pittsburgh Police received multiple ShotSpotter alerts just after 12:30 a.m. in the 800 block of Suismon Street in the East Allegheny neighborhood of the North Side. Police say a large party was happening at the Airbnb
Highlights Pittsburgh Police received multiple ShotSpotter alerts just after 12:30 a.m. in the 800 block of Suismon Street. Police say a large party was happening at the Airbnb with as many as 200 people in attendance.</description></item><item><title>Twenty People Shot at Arkansas Car Show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623744bafa4229f7b8dac0b2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623744bafa4229f7b8dac0b2/</guid><description>A person was killed and at least 24 people were injured in a shooting at a car show in Dumas, Arkansas, on Saturday night, police said. “One suspect is in
Highlights A person was killed and at least 24 people were injured in a shooting at a car show in Dumas, Arkansas, on Saturday night. The event&amp;rsquo;s organizers, a nonprofit group called the Hoodnic Foundation, said it was “heartbroken and in shock at what took place” The conditions of the people injured and information about possible suspects was not immediately available.</description></item></channel></rss>