<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>england on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/england/</link><description>Recent content in england on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 11:12:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/england/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monkeypox case confirmed in England</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277a5705adab6185bf0bdfb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277a5705adab6185bf0bdfb/</guid><description>The patient is being treated at an infectious disease unit and the risk to the public is low, officials say.
Highlights The patient is being treated at an infectious disease unit and the risk to the public is low, officials say. UKHSA experts are working closely with NHS colleagues and will be contacting people who might have been in close contact with the patient to provide information and health advice. The health agency said: &amp;ldquo;As a precautionary measure, experts will contact people who may have been close contact to the individual to provide health advice&amp;rdquo; The risk of the public being exposed to the patient is low and low, health officials say.</description></item><item><title>Conservative MP’s Photo of ‘Empty Canadian Grocery Store’ Actually Taken in Northern England, Not Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01098a9fc418d8c678fbf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01098a9fc418d8c678fbf/</guid><description>Summary Lantsman’s tweet included a graphic featuring a photo of a perplexed woman looking at an empty grocery store shelf. “Empty Canadian grocery store shelves could become a larger problem,” the graphic states. They indicated the photo was actually taken in Northern England at the Lakes &amp;amp; Dales Co-op supermarket just outside Newcastle in the seaside town of Whitley Bay. “Our petition from Canadians demanding action in communities across the country continues to grow every hour,” Lantsman told PressProgress.</description></item></channel></rss>