<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>western on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/western/</link><description>Recent content in western on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:27:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/western/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Full lunar eclipse to bring super blood Moon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282431a6be2bf662134deff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282431a6be2bf662134deff/</guid><description>The Moon will slowly darken and turn red as it falls into Earth&amp;rsquo;s shadow.
Highlights Western parts of Europe will get a good but short view as the Moon will set during the eclipse. The Moon will slowly darken and turn red as it falls into Earth&amp;rsquo;s shadow. Look low on the horizon between 0230 and 0430 BST and you&amp;rsquo;ll see the moon falling into shadow before glowing red. It should be visible in Africa too, with the eclipse visible in western parts of the continent.</description></item><item><title>Putin may soon officially declare war on Ukraine, US and Western officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627146df96c07c69892b0674/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627146df96c07c69892b0674/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin could formally declare war on Ukraine as soon as May 9, a move that would enable the full mobilization of Russia&amp;rsquo;s reserve forces as invasion efforts continue to falter, US and Western officials believe.
Highlights Russia began evacuating its embassy in Kyiv, and Ukraine urged its citizens to leave Russia. Russian President Vladimir Putin ordered his forces not to storm the last remaining Ukrainian stronghold in the besieged city of Mariupol but to block it &amp;ldquo;so that not even a fly comes through&amp;rdquo; May 9, known as “Victory Day” inside of Russia, commemorates the country’s defeat of the Nazis in 1945.</description></item><item><title>Lavrov claims Zelensky has Jewish blood 'just like Hitler'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f93924659d0fc6cf9f535/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f93924659d0fc6cf9f535/</guid><description>The Russian Foreign Minister attacked the President of Ukraine in an interview in Italy and reiterated the claims that his country has elements of Nazism.
Highlights Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov attacked Ukraine and its president Volodymyr Zelensky in an interview in Italy. Claimed that &amp;ldquo;the fact that he is a Jew does not negate the Nazi elements in his country&amp;rdquo; Lavrov also said that the upcoming anniversary of Russia&amp;rsquo;s liberation at the end of World War II will have no bearing on Moscow&amp;rsquo;s military operations in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Mutinous Russian troops ran over their own commander, say western officials | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f81cdd6e3b5752fcfd59a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 21:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f81cdd6e3b5752fcfd59a/</guid><description>Officials describe reported incident during fighting in Ukraine as sign of ‘morale challenges’ faced by invading forces
Highlights Western officials say incident is sign of&amp;rsquo;morale challenges&amp;rsquo; faced by invading forces. Some reports said colonel of 37th separate guards motor rifle brigade was run over by tank. Western officials retracted claim in light of conflicting evidence on social media. They said key point was that he was a victim of a mutiny, not whether he had been killed or not.</description></item><item><title>Russian general Yakov Rezantsev killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f3c46d43bc77f9d9ce7a0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 16:16:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f3c46d43bc77f9d9ce7a0/</guid><description>Western officials believe low morale among Russian troops is forcing generals to the battlefield.
Highlights Western officials believe low morale among Russian troops is forcing generals to the battlefield. It is unusual for such senior Russian officers to be so close to battlefield. Western officials say they have been forced to move towards the front lines to deal with low morale of Russian troops. Russia has been hit by a growing number of problems in recent years, including the threat posed by Russia&amp;rsquo;s anti-Russian forces in Ukraine and Russia’s annexation of Crimea in 2010.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine to receive more missiles and Turkish drones, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220a2353dc68f7988b0834c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 11:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220a2353dc68f7988b0834c/</guid><description>Ukrainian Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Wednesday the country was set to receive Stinger and Javelin missiles from abroad, as well as another shipment of Turkish drones.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Wednesday the country was set to receive Stinger and Javelin missiles from abroad, as well as another shipment of Turkish drones. Western countries have pledged to supply Ukraine with weapons to fend off a Russian invasion.</description></item><item><title>White House calls Russian moves on Ukraine an invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country — a move that could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S.
Highlights Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country. The move could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S. said an invasion was already underway there. Western leaders said Tuesday that Russian troops have moved into rebel-held areas in eastern Ukraine after Putin&amp;rsquo;s recognition of their independence.</description></item><item><title>UK Says Russia Is Planning To Overthrow Ukraine’s Government - Buzzfeed News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</guid><description>“The information being released today shines a light on the extent of Russian activity designed to subvert Ukraine, and is an insight into Kremlin thinking,” Foreign Secretary Liz Truss said in a statement shared with BuzzFeed News.
Summary BAKHMUT, Ukraine — Russia has drawn up plans to install a pro-Kremlin former member of parliament to lead Ukraine as it considers a new invasion of the country and the overthrow of its central government, according to a British assessment shared with BuzzFeed News.</description></item><item><title>Satellite images show Russia still building up forces near Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</guid><description>New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.
Summary Dec 24 (Reuters) - New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.</description></item></channel></rss>