<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>western on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/western/</link><description>Recent content in western on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 11:11:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/western/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine to receive more missiles and Turkish drones, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220a2353dc68f7988b0834c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 11:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220a2353dc68f7988b0834c/</guid><description>Ukrainian Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Wednesday the country was set to receive Stinger and Javelin missiles from abroad, as well as another shipment of Turkish drones.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Wednesday the country was set to receive Stinger and Javelin missiles from abroad, as well as another shipment of Turkish drones. Western countries have pledged to supply Ukraine with weapons to fend off a Russian invasion.</description></item><item><title>White House calls Russian moves on Ukraine an invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621519d9679f0d321c8e74c4/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country — a move that could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S.
Highlights Russian lawmakers Tuesday authorized President Vladimir Putin to use military force outside the country. The move could presage a broader attack on Ukraine after the U.S. said an invasion was already underway there. Western leaders said Tuesday that Russian troops have moved into rebel-held areas in eastern Ukraine after Putin&amp;rsquo;s recognition of their independence.</description></item><item><title>UK Says Russia Is Planning To Overthrow Ukraine’s Government - Buzzfeed News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</guid><description>“The information being released today shines a light on the extent of Russian activity designed to subvert Ukraine, and is an insight into Kremlin thinking,” Foreign Secretary Liz Truss said in a statement shared with BuzzFeed News.
Summary BAKHMUT, Ukraine — Russia has drawn up plans to install a pro-Kremlin former member of parliament to lead Ukraine as it considers a new invasion of the country and the overthrow of its central government, according to a British assessment shared with BuzzFeed News.</description></item><item><title>Satellite images show Russia still building up forces near Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</guid><description>New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.
Summary Dec 24 (Reuters) - New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.</description></item></channel></rss>