<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2020 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2020/</link><description>Recent content in 2020 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:12:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guns killed more youngsters than cars for the first time in 2020</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f989bf88db1e492adf3c4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 15:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f989bf88db1e492adf3c4/</guid><description>Guns killed more in 2021, too. The increase is driven by the number of Black youths killed by firearms.
Highlights The Washington Post analysis reviewed CDC death records for people ages 1 through 19 from 2011 through October 2021. The change was caused by a 30 percent increase in gun deaths for people 19 and younger in 2020. Non-Hispanic Black youths are the only group for whom guns are deadlier than cars.</description></item><item><title>DHS watchdog says Trump's agency appears to have altered report on Russian interference in 2020 election in part because of politics</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272368ece3855a12a02b9f2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 08:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272368ece3855a12a02b9f2/</guid><description>Former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s Department of Homeland Security delayed and altered an intelligence report related to Russian interference in the 2020 election, making changes that &amp;quot;appear to be based in part on political considerations,&amp;quot; according to a newly released watchdog report.
Highlights Homeland Security delayed and altered an intelligence report related to Russian interference in the 2020 election, a watchdog report says. The report provides a damning look at the way DHS&amp;rsquo; Office of Intelligence and Analysis dealt with intelligence related to Russia&amp;rsquo;s efforts to interfere in the US.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy gets John F. Kennedy award for defending democracy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262b8047288a5f0ece06cf7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 14:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262b8047288a5f0ece06cf7/</guid><description>BOSTON (AP) — Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy is among five people named Thursday as recipients of the John F. Kennedy Profile in Courage Award for acting to protect democracy. Zelenskyy was chosen because of the way he has “marshaled the spirit, patriotism and untiring sacrifice of the Ukrainian people in a life-or-death fight for their country,” as Russia pours in troops and assaults cities and towns , the John F.</description></item><item><title>Trafficking ring moved nearly 300 guns from Georgia to Pennsylvania, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555144638320951fd70caf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555144638320951fd70caf/</guid><description>Atlanta rapper Fredrick Norman, aka “Slowkey Fred,&amp;quot; is one of 11 people facing federal charges in connection with an alleged straw-purchasing scheme, according to records and interviews.
Highlights ATF agents traced nearly 300 firearms purchased in Georgia from dozens of gun retailers to the suspects. Some were found at crime scenes and in the possession of convicted felons in Philadelphia. 11 suspects in Georgia and Pennsylvania are accused of trafficking guns from Georgia to Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>$14M jury award for protesters could resonate around US.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624741691c879408404dc42a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624741691c879408404dc42a/</guid><description>DENVER (AP) — A federal jury’s $14 million award to Denver protesters hit with pepper balls and a bag filled with lead during 2020 demonstrations over the police killing of George Floyd in Minneapolis could resonate nationwide as courts weigh more than two dozen similar lawsuits.
Highlights The jury found police used excessive force against protesters, violating their constitutional rights, and ordered the city of Denver to pay 12 who sued.</description></item><item><title>Jury awards $14 million to protesters injured by Denver police during 2020 demonstrations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ef4d7ccedc04c6b9d435a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 11:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ef4d7ccedc04c6b9d435a/</guid><description>Denver police officers violated protesters’ rights during the massive 2020 demonstrations against police brutality, a federal jury concluded Friday, awarding 12 protesters a total of $14 million in compensation following a three-week trial.
Highlights Jury awards 12 protesters a total of $14 million in compensation after a three-week trial. The jury found in favor of the 12 plaintiffs after about five hours of deliberation. The trial is believed to be the first in the U.</description></item><item><title>Deputy Virginia AG resigns after posts surface of her applauding Jan. 6 rioters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205cad80c6d2d1894afda44/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 02:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205cad80c6d2d1894afda44/</guid><description>A Republican deputy attorney general in Virginia resigned from her position Thursday after Facebook posts surfaced showing she had applauded Jan. 6 rioters and
Highlights Monique Miles resigned from her position Thursday after Facebook posts surfaced showing she had applauded Jan. 6 rioters and falsely claimed that Donald Trump won the 2020 presidential election. The Virginia attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office became aware of these posts by Miles Thursday when The Washington Post shared screenshots it obtained of her previous comments.</description></item></channel></rss>