<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>entering on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/entering/</link><description>Recent content in entering on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 08:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/entering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Coast Guard in Louisiana searching for 3 minors last seen entering Mississippi River | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626659147c37159639781d22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 08:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626659147c37159639781d22/</guid><description>The search for three children who were last seen entering the Mississippi River in New Orleans Saturday evening has been suspended, the Coast Guard said.
Highlights The search for three children who were last seen entering the Mississippi River in New Orleans has been suspended. A 15-year-old boy and two girls, ages 14 and eight, have been missing since Saturday evening. Officials didn&amp;rsquo;t say how and why the children entered the water.</description></item><item><title>Omicron hits all 50 states less than a month after entering U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4109020b5c2ac9c4e7fb7/</guid><description>With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was
Summary With holiday plans hanging in the balance for millions of people, the omicron variant has been confirmed in all 50 states roughly three weeks after it was first detected in the U.S., according to an NBC News tally. A day later, multiple states and territories set records for seven-day averages, including New York, Maine, Washington, D.</description></item></channel></rss>