<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shoot on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shoot/</link><description>Recent content in shoot on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 19:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shoot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hate crime charges announced against man accused of plotting shooting in Georgia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628695f3db7aa6f15f283355/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628695f3db7aa6f15f283355/</guid><description>Federal hate crime charges have been announced against a Georgia man after he allegedly shot into two grocery stores. He is accused of being motivated by race.
Highlights Larry Edward Foxworth allegedly fired a gun repeatedly into two convenience stores at 2:30 a.m. on July 30, 2021. The indictment alleges that Foxworth, who is white, was motivated to shoot into the stores because of the perceived race, color or national origin of the people inside the stores.</description></item><item><title>Police shoot man being held for mental health at Florida hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624232fdc14d3fc2029a2743/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 22:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624232fdc14d3fc2029a2743/</guid><description>With no space available at a mental health facility, man was shot after brandishing scissors at medical hospital
Highlights 29-year-old man was being held under the Baker Act, which allows authorities to hold someone in a mental health facility for up to 72 hours if they are a threat to themselves or others. The man was among a number of people being held in the hospital because there were no beds at the local mental health facilities.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Russian forces shoot and kill 10 people queuing for bread in Chernihiv - US embassy says | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231fe9c2437ef6503213ae2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 15:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231fe9c2437ef6503213ae2/</guid><description>The US embassy in Kyiv says it is &amp;quot;considering all available options to ensure accountability for any atrocity crimes in Ukraine&amp;quot;.
Highlights 10 people shot and killed in Chernihiv, northern Ukraine, US embassy in Kyiv says. US embassy: &amp;ldquo;Such horrific attacks must stop. We are considering all available options to ensure accountability for atrocity crimes&amp;rdquo; UK Ministry of Defence says Ukraine exploiting Russia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;lack of manoeuvre&amp;rdquo; and inflicting heavy losses. Russian troops are continuing to fire missiles at Ukrainian targets, and rockets are hitting civilian buildings and infrastructure, an adviser says.</description></item></channel></rss>