<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>strips on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/strips/</link><description>Recent content in strips on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 17:16:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/strips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>States look for solutions as US fentanyl deaths keep rising.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249d5c98d9086439c691610/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 17:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249d5c98d9086439c691610/</guid><description>As the addiction and overdose crisis that has gripped the U.S. for two decades turns even deadlier, state governments are scrambling for ways to stem the destruction wrought by fentanyl and other synthetic opioids.
Highlights As the number of U.S. overdose deaths continues to soar, states are trying to take steps to combat a flood of the drug that has proved the most lethal &amp;ndash; illicitly produced fentanyl. The urgency is heightened because of the deepening impact of the drugs.</description></item><item><title>Veterans ask Queen to strip Prince Andrew of honorary military titles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</guid><description>Duke will no longer use HRH title in any official capacity, and will fight US sexual assault lawsuit as private citizen
Summary In a devastating blow to Prince Andrew, who was born His Royal Highness, Buckingham Palace also said he would no longer use the HRH royal style in any official capacity. Buckingham Palace said in a statement on Thursday: “With the Queen’s approval and agreement, the Duke of York’s military affiliations and royal patronages have been returned to the Queen.</description></item></channel></rss>