<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>powell on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/powell/</link><description>Recent content in powell on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/powell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Water is so low in the Colorado River, feds are holding some back so one dam can keep generating power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728a1923276fefa5f6eab5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728a1923276fefa5f6eab5/</guid><description>The decision will keep more water in Lake Powell, the reservoir located at the Glen Canyon Dam in northern Arizona.
Highlights The decision will keep more water in Lake Powell, the reservoir located at the Glen Canyon Dam in northern Arizona. Officials said the actions will help save water, protect the dam&amp;rsquo;s ability to produce hydropower and provide officials with more time to figure out how to operate the dam at lower water levels.</description></item><item><title>Fed to fight inflation with fastest rate hikes in decades</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270491beb3c8e9ef6477017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270491beb3c8e9ef6477017/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve is poised this week to accelerate its most drastic steps in three decades to attack inflation by making it costlier to borrow — for a car, a home, a business deal, a credit card purchase — all of which will compound Americans&amp;rsquo; financial strains and likely weaken the economy.
Highlights The Federal Reserve is poised this week to begin unleashing its most drastic steps in three decades to attack inflation by making it costlier to borrow.</description></item></channel></rss>