<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>finlands on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/finlands/</link><description>Recent content in finlands on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/finlands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finland's parliament votes yes to NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283f315e7677f707da6610e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 19:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283f315e7677f707da6610e/</guid><description>Finland&amp;rsquo;s parliament on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a proposal to apply for membership of the NATO military alliance in a historic policy shift prompted by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Finland&amp;rsquo;s parliament on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a proposal to apply for membership of the NATO military alliance in a historic policy shift prompted by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Of 200 lawmakers, 188 voted in favour and eight against the application, Speaker Matti Vanhanen said.</description></item><item><title>Finland's Parliament approves Nato application | News | Yle Uutiset</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283ae30a12a2b223feafe78/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:21:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283ae30a12a2b223feafe78/</guid><description>Following a 14-hour debate, the motion was passed by 188 votes to 8.
Highlights Finland will seek to join the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation (Nato) President Sauli Niinistö and Prime Minister Sanna Marin (SDP) announced the move on Sunday. Following a 14-hour debate, the motion was passed by 188 votes to 8. A total of 212 speeches were made to Parliament during the debate that preceded the vote. The president and government are now able to put the official application process into motion, possibly as soon as later on Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Finland starts much-delayed nuclear plant, brings respite to power market</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e50429e80fd8f661a7422/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 20:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e50429e80fd8f661a7422/</guid><description>Finland&amp;rsquo;s much-delayed Olkiluoto 3 nuclear reactor started test production on Saturday, operator TVO said, delivering power to the national grid which over time is expected to reduce the need for electricity imports and lead to lower prices.
Highlights Finland&amp;rsquo;s much-delayed Olkiluoto 3 nuclear reactor started test production on Saturday. The 1.6 gigawatt reactor had originally been due to open in 2009. It is Finland&amp;rsquo;s first new nuclear plant in over four decades and Europe&amp;rsquo;s first in almost 15 years.</description></item></channel></rss>