<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ship on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ship/</link><description>Recent content in ship on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Court in Fiji approves U.S. warrant to seize Russian-owned mega-yacht</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273e9a3de069e6f5988e8b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273e9a3de069e6f5988e8b1/</guid><description>American and Fijian officials claim the $325 million Amadea is owned by sanctioned billionaire Suleiman Kerimov.
Highlights American and Fijian officials claim the $325 million Amadea is the property of Suleiman Kerimov, an oligarch who built his fortune on gold mining. Kerimov was sanctioned in March by the United States, United Kingdom and European Union in response to the Russian invasion of Ukraine. The Cayman Islands-flagged yacht berthed in Fiji on April 13, according to local reports and maritime analytics website Marine Traffic.</description></item><item><title>Sinking of Russian warship raises tense questions about fate of crew</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eba43e21003ce0d15c886/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 13:34:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eba43e21003ce0d15c886/</guid><description>A state television anchor also demands answers about how the debacle happened.
Highlights The Russian warship Moskva sank last week after being hit by two Ukrainian missiles. The Russian Defense Ministry said all crew members had been evacuated. But several families are contradicting this claim in Russian media reports and on social media. Social media groups uniting mothers of Russian soldiers deployed in Ukraine are filling up with photos and pleas from parents looking for their missing sons.</description></item><item><title>Woman, 58, falls to death from mast of historic ship in Galveston, Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62025f5ddb358fc7e201c6df/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62025f5ddb358fc7e201c6df/</guid><description>A woman fell to her death from a mast on a historic ship that’s featured at a Texas museum after her safety harness somehow came unclipped, police said.
Highlights 58-year-old woman died Saturday after falling from a mast on the tall ship Elissa. The Elissa is berthed at Galveston’s seaport museum. Training classes are held each year on the Elissa and they include lessons in sail rigging. Ship was built in 1877, from a scrapyard in Greece in 1978, according to the historical foundation.</description></item></channel></rss>