<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crisis on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crisis/</link><description>Recent content in crisis on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crisis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US tells Putin to choose confrontation or dialogue over Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</guid><description>Secretary of state Antony Blinken says week of talks is moment of truth for Vladimir Putin
Summary Formal talks are under way between US and Russian officials in Geneva over the fate of Ukraine, amid low expectations and high tensions driven by fears that the Kremlin will order an invasion. The other path is confrontation and massive consequences for Russia if it renews its aggression on Ukraine. “We’re about to test the proposition of which path President Putin wants to take this week,” Blinken, told the ABC News programme This Week.</description></item><item><title>Crocodiles turn on humans amid Iran water crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc4de1358c9c16e1e8e1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 12:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc4de1358c9c16e1e8e1ca/</guid><description>The creatures are attacking as their habitats shrink, a grim side-effect of Iran&amp;rsquo;s water shortages.
Summary Lying on the floor of his modest home, Siahouk was in excruciating pain from the injury to his right hand, the result of a nightmarish encounter. Just two days earlier, on a scorchingly hot August afternoon, the frail 70-year-old shepherd had gone to fetch water from a pond when he was pounced on by a gando, the local name for a mugger crocodile in Iran&amp;rsquo;s Baluchistan region.</description></item></channel></rss>