<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crisis on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crisis/</link><description>Recent content in crisis on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:37:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crisis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘We are going to die’: Food shortages worsen Sri Lanka crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628834386b628c0d59f1c9bc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628834386b628c0d59f1c9bc/</guid><description>Prime minister warns of a food crisis after chemical fertilisers ban by previous government drastically cut crop yields.
Highlights Prime Minister warns of a food crisis after ban on chemical fertilisers by the previous government drastically cut crop yields. Government promises to buy enough fertiliser for the next planting season to boost harvests. President Rajapaksa appointed nine new members to the cabinet on Friday, including to the critical health, trade and trade and ministries.</description></item><item><title>J&amp;amp;J, distributors finalize $26B landmark opioid settlement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621938516df82d6dfbff4e0f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 20:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621938516df82d6dfbff4e0f/</guid><description>CAMDEN, N.J. (AP) — Drugmaker Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and three major distributors finalized nationwide settlements over their role in the opioid addiction crisis Friday, an announcement that clears the way for $26 billion to flow to nearly every state and local government in the U.S.
Highlights Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, AmerisourceBergen, Cardinal Health and McKesson announced the settlement plan last year. The deal was contingent on getting participation from a critical mass of state and local governments.</description></item><item><title>‘Freedom Convoy’ protesters shut down third border crossing as Ottawa police warn of arrests ‘without a warrant’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620653efcdee5ffe18c39374/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 12:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620653efcdee5ffe18c39374/</guid><description>Raucous protests against vaccine mandates and coronavirus restrictions blocked a third border crossing with the United States.
Highlights The mayor of Windsor, Ontario, says the city and auto groups are seeking an injunction to end a blockade by protesters. The self-styled “Freedom Convoy,” now heading into its third weekend, has paralyzed the Canadian capital. The White House says it is “monitoring” the situation at the border “very closely” and that Cabinet officials are “engaged around the clock’ to bring this to a swift end” The protests started in opposition to U.</description></item><item><title>US tells Putin to choose confrontation or dialogue over Ukraine | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc6630b8d620f47e97082d/</guid><description>Secretary of state Antony Blinken says week of talks is moment of truth for Vladimir Putin
Summary Formal talks are under way between US and Russian officials in Geneva over the fate of Ukraine, amid low expectations and high tensions driven by fears that the Kremlin will order an invasion. The other path is confrontation and massive consequences for Russia if it renews its aggression on Ukraine. “We’re about to test the proposition of which path President Putin wants to take this week,” Blinken, told the ABC News programme This Week.</description></item><item><title>Crocodiles turn on humans amid Iran water crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc4de1358c9c16e1e8e1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 12:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc4de1358c9c16e1e8e1ca/</guid><description>The creatures are attacking as their habitats shrink, a grim side-effect of Iran&amp;rsquo;s water shortages.
Summary Lying on the floor of his modest home, Siahouk was in excruciating pain from the injury to his right hand, the result of a nightmarish encounter. Just two days earlier, on a scorchingly hot August afternoon, the frail 70-year-old shepherd had gone to fetch water from a pond when he was pounced on by a gando, the local name for a mugger crocodile in Iran&amp;rsquo;s Baluchistan region.</description></item></channel></rss>