<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>navy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/navy/</link><description>Recent content in navy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 05:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/navy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flotilla Of Russian Landing Ships Has Entered The English Channel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea3df018a6d262efb9a633/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 05:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea3df018a6d262efb9a633/</guid><description>Evidence mounts that the six landing ships are ultimately headed toward the Black Sea and possible action against Ukraine.
Summary A group of Russian amphibious warfare vessels — three of which left the Baltic Sea region yesterday, preceded by another three the day before — have started to enter the English Channel. Multiple reports confirm that all six of the Russian Navy warships have begun their passage through the English Channel, after which they will enter the Atlantic Ocean.</description></item><item><title>$4 million worth of heroin seized by U.S. Navy in Arabian Sea</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cef0e0f536cbfc298016a0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cef0e0f536cbfc298016a0/</guid><description>United States navy vessels seized 849 pounds of heroin in the Arabian Sea worth some $4 million, in a major bust by the international maritime operation in the
Summary United States navy vessels seized 849 pounds of heroin in the Arabian Sea worth some $4 million, in a major bust by the international maritime operation in the region, officials said Thursday. The USS Tempest and USS Typhoon seized the drugs hidden aboard a stateless fishing vessel plying Mideast waters, the international task force said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>