<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>footage on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/footage/</link><description>Recent content in footage on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/footage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Family wants world to see footage of Grand Rapids fatal police shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253d721dbaa5507da6d5a5a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253d721dbaa5507da6d5a5a/</guid><description>A Grand Rapids police officer shot and killed Patrick Lyoya, 26, during a traffic stop earlier this week. Hundreds of people joined the Lyoya family urging police to release bodycam and dashcam footage of the shooting. The officer,
Highlights Hundreds of people join the Lyoya family urging police to release bodycam and dashcam footage. Patrick Lyoya, 26, was shot and killed by a Grand Rapids police officer during a traffic stop earlier this week.</description></item><item><title>A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop for speeding and asked to see the officer's supervisor, video footage shows.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</guid><description>Video footage shows a Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who began recording his traffic stop, saying he was feeling unsafe
Highlights A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop, video footage shows. Delane Gordon began recording when the March 10 stop started to make him feel unsafe, attorney says. The man wound up facing additional charges of resisting arrest and obstruction of justice.</description></item><item><title>Video shows Florida police sergeant grabbing fellow officer by her throat</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e246f87c716e8014992abf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e246f87c716e8014992abf/</guid><description>A Florida police sergeant has been relieved of his supervisory responsibilities and is under investigation after he was filmed grabbing an officer by her throat, according to officials.
Summary A Florida police sergeant has been relieved of his supervisory responsibilities and is under investigation after he was filmed grabbing an officer by her throat, according to officials. Sunrise police shared body camera video of the Nov. 19 incident with NBC News, but the footage was muted with faces blurred, except for the sergeant&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item></channel></rss>