<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weapon on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weapon/</link><description>Recent content in weapon on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 06:21:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weapon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Naomi Judd died of self-inflicted firearm wound, Ashley Judd reveals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627df8ba4a924e532e109005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 06:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627df8ba4a924e532e109005/</guid><description>Ashley Judd and her family wanted the world to hear from them how Naomi Judd died.
Highlights Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh was shot and killed in the West Bank Wednesday. Casey White is being held on capital murder charges in Lauderdale County, Florida. Ashley Judd and her family wanted the world to hear from them how Naomi Judd died. The younger Judd appeared in an interview with Diane Sawyer, which aired on “Good Morning America” She and her sister Wynonna Judd announced on April 30 that they had lost their mother “to the disease of mental illness” They said they wanted to shed light on mental illness, explaining that it is “important to make the distinction between the loved one and the disease” READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Rep. Madison Cawthorn caught bringing loaded gun through airport security</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626852ae85a87c0c9952ec2f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 20:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626852ae85a87c0c9952ec2f/</guid><description>Madison Cawthorn, a Republican congressman from North Carolina, was caught trying to go through security with a loaded gun at Charlotte Douglas International Airport.
Highlights Madison Cawthorn, a Republican congressman from North Carolina, was caught trying to go through security with a loaded gun at Charlotte Douglas International Airport Tuesday morning. He was issued a citation for possession of a dangerous weapon on city property by Charlotte Mecklenburg police. This was the second time the congressman has been stopped trying to bring a weapon through airport security.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: Police Officer Kills Dog in Miami-Dade After Barking Complaint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</guid><description>A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing him while responding to&amp;hellip;
Summary A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing the 8-month-old. The incident happened in unincorporated Miami-Dade near Miami Gardens on Wednesday, January 12 around 7 p.m. as a police officer was responding to a call regarding dogs barking.</description></item></channel></rss>