<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>state on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/state/</link><description>Recent content in state on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 04:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/state/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida pulls pro-vaccination television ads, replacing with spots that don’t mention vaccines</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3f464011a29c9f16cde6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3f464011a29c9f16cde6e/</guid><description>State sponsored commercials promoting COVID-19 vaccinations have been pulled from Florida&amp;rsquo;s airwaves.
Summary Spots are produced by the Florida Department of Health, which then disseminates them to stations around the state. Last March, the Biden administration rolled out a billion dollar ad campaign about the importance of the vaccine. AdThose videos featured pastors, local sports stars and health department veterans. These ran until early November, when the state health department made a sudden change.</description></item><item><title>Michigan diner owner who defied state shutdown dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 01:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</guid><description>None
Summary BRANCH COUNTY, MI – A diner owner who kept his restaurant open in defiance of state shutdowns has died after more than a two-month battle with COVID-19. He owned the Quincy Diner, 174 E. Chicago St. (U.S. 12) in the village of Quincy. He kept the restaurant open in December 2020, in violation of the partial shutdown ordered by the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services. Related: ‘I’d have lost the business.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item></channel></rss>