<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>state on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/state/</link><description>Recent content in state on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/state/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US: Turkey's NATO issues with Sweden, Finland will be fixed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629272f6d7aabfc0ae2ece69/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:08:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629272f6d7aabfc0ae2ece69/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said Friday he’s confident Turkey’s objections to Finland and Sweden joining NATO can be overcome swiftly, possibly in time for a summit of alliance leaders at the end of next month.
Highlights U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken says Turkey’s objections to Finland and Sweden joining NATO can be overcome swiftly. Turkey has cited alleged support for Kurdish militants whom Turkey considers terrorists and restrictions on weapons sales to Turkey.</description></item><item><title>Michigan election bureau says 2 leading Republican candidates for governor filed fraudulent signatures, disqualifying them</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f6f4a0cd3622516b50630/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 12:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f6f4a0cd3622516b50630/</guid><description>Michigan&amp;rsquo;s elections bureau says five Republican candidates for governor, including two leading contenders, failed to file enough valid nominating signatures and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t qualify for the August primary.
Highlights Michigan&amp;rsquo;s elections bureau says five Republican candidates for governor failed to file enough valid nominating signatures and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t qualify for the August primary. The stunning recommendations immediately transformed the race in the battleground state. Democrats had challenged their petitions, alleging mass forgery and other issues.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court makes it more difficult for prisoners to argue they had ineffective counsel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bf7dbb07cfbfad9b5be73/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 21:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bf7dbb07cfbfad9b5be73/</guid><description>The Supreme Court said Monday that state prisoners may not present new evidence in federal court in support of a claim that their post-conviction counsel in state court was ineffective in violation of the Constitution.
Highlights The 6-3 opinion was penned by Justice Clarence Thomas. In dissent, Justice Sonia Sotomayor called the decision &amp;ldquo;perverse&amp;rdquo; and said the court had gutted precedent. The ruling is a major defeat for two inmates on death row who said they had compelling claims that their lawyers failed to pursue.</description></item><item><title>Female student killed by mob at Nigeria school over blasphemy claims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f814f04c7cfd962d4ee98/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 10:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f814f04c7cfd962d4ee98/</guid><description>A female student in northern Nigeria was killed by a mob who stoned, beat and set fire to her for allegedly posting a blasphemous statement against the Prophet Mohammed, according to police.
Highlights Deborah Yakubu was surrounded by fellow students and attacked on Thursday, police say. The incident happened at the Shehu Shagari school in Sokoto, northern Nigeria. Two people have been arrested and &amp;ldquo;the suspects in the viral video on Twitter were spotted and will be nailed soon,&amp;rdquo; police spokesperson Sanusi Abubakar said.</description></item><item><title>California Gov. Newsom unveils historic $97.5 billion budget surplus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f297c513f4dfb338b9c3a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f297c513f4dfb338b9c3a/</guid><description>California is entering the next budget year with a record-smashing surplus of nearly $100 billion, Gov. Gavin Newsom said Friday.
Highlights Gov. Gavin Newsom unveils revised budget plan of just over $300 billion for next fiscal year. State has collected $55 billion more in taxes than officials expected in January. Newsom has tens of billions of dollars more to spend on new and existing initiatives as he seeks re-election in the fall.</description></item><item><title>South Carolina marks Confederate Memorial Day on Tuesday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627af1cc8c00f14515b30757/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 23:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627af1cc8c00f14515b30757/</guid><description>South Carolina will close state offices on Tuesday to mark Confederate Memorial Day.
Highlights The observation of the holiday is every year on May 10. South Carolina is among a handful of states in the South with such an official holiday. State offices in Alabama and Mississippi closed down for Confederate Memorial Days last month. A bill that would allow state employees to take the Juneteenth holiday or any other day instead of Confederate Memorial Day unanimously passed the South Carolina Senate in March but is stuck in a House committee and will likely die when the session ends Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Lithuania recognises war in Ukraine as genocide, Russia as terrorist state</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a5a32344d628e8556570e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 12:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a5a32344d628e8556570e/</guid><description>On Tuesday, the Lithuanian parliament voted unanimously to recognise Russia’s war against Ukraine as genocide.
Highlights Lithuanian parliament voted unanimously to recognise Russia’s war against Ukraine as genocide. The resolution passed with 128 votes in favour, none against and no abstentions. It states that Russia&amp;rsquo;s armed forces and mercenaries have committed mass war crimes on Ukrainian territory. The intent is to wholly or partially destroy the Ukrainian nation and break its spirit by killing entire families, including children, abducting and raping people, and mocking them and the bodies of the murdered, the document states.</description></item><item><title>California Targets Loud Exhaust With Sound Activated Camera Enforcement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627898015275b456ec920daf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 04:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627898015275b456ec920daf/</guid><description>Six California cities may take part in the automated enforcement pilot program aimed at curbing noise pollution.
Highlights California is set to implement camera-automated exhaust noise enforcement. The pilot program will span from January 2023 to December 2027 and will be tested in six different cities across the state. Camera-enforced fines will be issued only after subsequent violations of the 95- and 80-decibel ceiling for cars and motorcycles, respectively. It is not immediately clear how these cameras will pinpoint vehicles in traffic, or how they will differentiate between cars and bikes.</description></item><item><title>Levi Strauss to reimburse abortion travel for employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272dec9a5f9b96fe31e7d26/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272dec9a5f9b96fe31e7d26/</guid><description>Levi Strauss &amp;amp; Co said on Wednesday it will reimburse travel expenses for its full- and part-time employees who need to travel to another state for health care services, including abortions.
Highlights Levi Strauss &amp;amp; Co. will reimburse travel expenses for its full- and part-time employees who need to travel to another state for health care services, including abortions. The apparel company best known for its jeans is the latest U.</description></item><item><title>Lawmakers in 19 states want legal refuge for trans youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62721aadfb6ffda3e903ce6b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 06:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62721aadfb6ffda3e903ce6b/</guid><description>CONCORD, N.H. (AP) — Democratic lawmakers in more than a dozen states are following California’s lead in seeking to offer legal refuge to displaced transgender youth and their families. The coordinated effort being announced Tuesday by the LGBTQ Victory Institute and other advocates comes in response to recent actions taken in conservative states.
Highlights Democratic lawmakers in more than a dozen states are following California’s lead in seeking to offer legal refuge to displaced transgender youth and their families.</description></item><item><title>Police found 150 skulls at a "crime scene" in Mexico. It turns out the victims, mostly women, were ritually decapitated over 1,000 years ago.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e333b7dc0ba0bb398a666/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 07:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e333b7dc0ba0bb398a666/</guid><description>Experts say the victims in the cave had probably been ritually decapitated and the skulls put on display on a kind of trophy rack.
Highlights Police found about 150 skulls in a cave near the Guatemalan border in 2012. It took a decade of tests and analysis to determine the skulls were from sacrificial victims killed between A.D. 900 and 1200. Pre-Hispanic skull piles in Mexico usually show a hole bashed through each side of every skull, and were usually found in ceremonial plazas, not caves.</description></item><item><title>Millions must cut water use in drought-stricken California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694624aeedfccb4efc7c16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694624aeedfccb4efc7c16/</guid><description>Southern California&amp;rsquo;s water supplier requires 6 million people to cut their outdoor watering to one day a week as drought continues to plague the state. The board of the Metropolitan Water District of Southern California declared a water shortage emergency and required the cutback
Highlights Southern California&amp;rsquo;s largest water supplier requires 6 million people to cut outdoor watering to one day a week as drought continues to plague the state. The board of the Metropolitan Water District of Southern California declared a water shortage emergency and required the cities and water agencies it supplies to implement the cutback on June 1 and enforce it or face hefty fines.</description></item><item><title>Beat it: trucker convoy driven out after being egged by kids in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267f4e6d82d0da9443b30d6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 13:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267f4e6d82d0da9443b30d6/</guid><description>The people’s convoy had gathered outside lawmaker Buffy Wicks’s house to protest her support of an abortion rights bill
Highlights A people&amp;rsquo;s convoy gathered outside a California lawmaker&amp;rsquo;s home to protest her support of an abortion rights bill. The group was protesting legislation Wicks wrote that would end coroner investigations of stillbirths and mandate Covid vaccines for businesses. When the convoy got stuck in traffic outside an Oakland Safeway, a group of residents began throwing eggs at the stalled vehicles, shouting “get the f*** out of here” The group fled back to their base in Sacramento, complaining about their icy reception and dirty vehicles.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis signs Florida's 15-week abortion ban into law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258c2e236048d621a24faa0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:57:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258c2e236048d621a24faa0/</guid><description>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law on Thursday a Mississippi-style anti-abortion measure that bans the procedure after 15 weeks of pregnancy without exemptions for rape, incest or human trafficking.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law on Thursday banning abortion after 15 weeks of pregnancy. The bill, which goes into effect July 1, does allow exemptions in cases where a pregnancy is &amp;ldquo;serious risk&amp;rdquo; to the mother or a fatal fetal abnormality is detected.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky governor vetoes proposed 15-week abortion ban</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62525a18678a9e98f303498f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 04:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62525a18678a9e98f303498f/</guid><description>Gov. Andy Beshear issued the veto Friday. He raised doubts about the bill&amp;rsquo;s constitutionality. And he criticized it for not including exceptions for pregnancies caused by rape or incest.
Highlights Democratic Gov. Andy Beshear vetoes bill that would ban abortions in Kentucky after 15 weeks of pregnancy. State lawmakers will have a chance to override the veto when they reconvene next week for the final two days of this year’s 60-day legislative session.</description></item><item><title>Germany conducts nationwide raids on neo-Nazi groups</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d9fdc39551065c653ff05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 14:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d9fdc39551065c653ff05/</guid><description>Four suspected right-wing extremists have been arrested after police conducted early morning raids. Banned neo-Nazi groups were the focus of the operation.
Highlights Authorities searched the residences of 50 suspected right-wing extremists on Wednesday. Four suspects are believed to be leaders of &amp;ldquo;Atomwaffen Division&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Knockout 51&amp;rdquo; The raids began in the early morning and the neo-Nazi groups were the main focus. Authorities searched homes of 50 suspects and 11 other locations were also searched.</description></item><item><title>U.S. seeks new lithium sources as demand for clean energy grows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62436874c68b093770803a5d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62436874c68b093770803a5d/</guid><description>The element is critical to the development of lithium-ion batteries, which are rechargeable batteries seen as critical to reducing the carbon emissions created by cars and other forms of transportation.
Highlights The U.S. will need far more lithium to achieve its clean energy goals. The element is critical to development of rechargeable lithium-ion batteries that are seen as key to reducing climate-changing carbon emissions created by cars and other forms of transportation.</description></item><item><title>Madeleine Albright, first female US secretary of state, dies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bf0b21a2561a567ca0a40/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bf0b21a2561a567ca0a40/</guid><description>Madeleine Albright, the first female US secretary of state and who helped steer Western foreign policy in the aftermath of the Cold War, has died. She was 84 years old.
Highlights Madeleine Albright was 84 years old. The cause of her death was cancer, her family says. She was a central figure in President Bill Clinton&amp;rsquo;s administration. She championed the expansion of NATO and championed human rights and democracy across the globe.</description></item><item><title>Firing-squad executions get the greenlight in South Carolina</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62356611622f555e6036ad94/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 05:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62356611622f555e6036ad94/</guid><description>South Carolina has given the greenlight to firing-squad executions
Highlights South Carolina has given the greenlight to firing-squad executions, a method codified into state law last year. The state Corrections Department said Friday that renovations have been completed on the death chamber in Columbia. The three shooters, all volunteers, will have rifles loaded with live ammunition, with their weapons trained on the inmate&amp;rsquo;s heart. South Carolina is one of eight states to still use the electric chair and one of four to allow a firing squad.</description></item><item><title>Russia's state TV hit by stream of resignations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62321b032a9e50869ab44014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 17:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62321b032a9e50869ab44014/</guid><description>Marina Ovsyannikova&amp;rsquo;s protest highlighted a growing number of journalists leaving their jobs at Kremlin-run TV channels.
Highlights EU bans RT&amp;rsquo;s various outlets as well as those of fellow Kremlin outlet Sputnik. Russia&amp;rsquo;s German-based state news agency Ruptly has also endured a spate of resignations. Marina Ovsyannikova&amp;rsquo;s protest highlighted a growing number of journalists leaving their jobs at Kremlin-run TV channels. Days later, the EU said it was banning all of RT&amp;rsquo;s outlets for their &amp;ldquo;campaign of disinformation, information manipulation and distortion of facts&amp;rdquo; The EU has also banned all of the outlets for &amp;ldquo;disinformation, misinformation and distortion of facts&amp;rdquo; Russia&amp;rsquo;s state-run television news agency also has a number of resigning journalists from their jobs.</description></item><item><title>Texas Gov. orders state agencies to investigate gender-affirming care for trans kids as child abuse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621777f16bb4431580594e4c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 12:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621777f16bb4431580594e4c/</guid><description>Abbott wrote that doctors, nurses, teachers and anyone who comes into contact with a child has a requirement to report parents.
Highlights Texas Gov. Greg Abbott ordered state agencies to investigate gender-affirming care for transgender kids as child abuse. The order&amp;rsquo;s immediate impacts on transgender children&amp;rsquo;s access to treatments remain unclear. Experts and doctors fear an increase in mental health crises among transgender kids due to anti-trans bills introduced in state legislatures.</description></item><item><title>Group of protesting truckers begin trip to DC area this week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621454d17ce5f7bf69e6e87a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621454d17ce5f7bf69e6e87a/</guid><description>Inspired by the trucker convoy in Canada, a group from California says they will now head to Washington D.C. to protest COVID-19 restrictions.
Highlights Inspired by the trucker convoy in Canada, a group from California says they will now head to Washington D.C. to protest COVID-19 restrictions. Convoy will start Wednesday at Adelanto Stadium in Southern California. Convoys will make about 10 stops on the way to the Beltway area, including in Arizona, Ohio and Hagerstown, Maryland.</description></item><item><title>Florida appeals court overturns conviction of Miami police officer who shot autistic man's caretaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</guid><description>A South Florida appeals court Wednesday overturned the conviction of a former North Miami Police Department officer who was found guilty of negligence for shooting an autistic man&amp;rsquo;s caretaker in 2016, court documents show.
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal overturned a &amp;ldquo;conviction for misdemeanor culpable negligence&amp;rdquo; for Jonathan Aledda. Florida State Attorney Katherine Fernandez Rundle said the decision is &amp;ldquo;disappointing to all who believed that this shooting incident was unnecessary and incorrect&amp;rdquo; In July 2016, officers encountered Arnaldo Rios-Soto, a man with severe developmental disabilities, and his caretaker Charles Kinsey in the middle of an intersection, court documents show.</description></item><item><title>Walmart drops mask mandate for vaccinated employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209825c9a722b4ddafe6871/</guid><description>Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. State-mandated masks will no longer be required unless required by state or local government. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in pharmacies will be required to
Highlights Walmart drops mask and Covid-19 sick leave policy for US associates. Unvaccinated employees and those who work in clinical care settings will be required to keep wearing masks. Several states, from New York to California, have issued their own plans to lift indoor mask mandates.</description></item><item><title>Judge restores protections for gray wolves across much of US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207b24a2c31ece6ab67e917/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207b24a2c31ece6ab67e917/</guid><description>A judge has restored federal protections for gray wolves across much of the U.S. after they were removed in the waning days of the Trump administration
Highlights A judge has restored federal protections for gray wolves across much of the U.S. after they were removed in the waning days of the Trump administration. The ruling does not directly impact wolves in the northern Rocky Mountains of Idaho, Montana and Wyoming and portions of several adjacent states.</description></item><item><title>Minnesota authorities can't arrest or threaten journalists after judge approves settlement arising from George Floyd protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62042df6656512be663614e2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62042df6656512be663614e2/</guid><description>A federal judge has approved a settlement prohibiting Minnesota authorities from arresting, threatening to arrest, or using force against journalists.
Highlights A federal judge approves a settlement barring Minnesota authorities from arresting, threatening to arrest, or using force against journalists. The settlement stemmed from police tactics used against journalists during protests over the deaths of George Floyd and Daunte Wright. The American Civil Liberties Union called the action groundbreaking and said it requires state law enforcement to be held accountable to the First Amendment.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma National Guard members can’t sue anonymously over COVID-19 vaccine mandate, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff74d04b7a6aefc2747021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 07:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff74d04b7a6aefc2747021/</guid><description>The state of Oklahoma argued that naming the Guard members challenging the federal COVID vaccine mandate could expose them to a range of harms.
Highlights Oklahoma National Guard members can&amp;rsquo;t sue anonymously over COVID-19 vaccine mandate, judge rules. Governor, attorney general and 16 unnamed Guard members filed a lawsuit in December seeking to block the mandate. Judge rules that the public interest overrides concerns about privacy or personal safety. Guard members say they are willing to make their names known to the court and to the U.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi becomes 37th U.S. state to legalize medical marijuana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc28b32058cec7c9c20fb8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 19:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc28b32058cec7c9c20fb8/</guid><description>Mississippi joined 36 other U.S. states in legalizing marijuana for medical use on Wednesday, as the governor signed legislation permitting cannabis for treatment of severe, debilitating health conditions such as cancer, AIDS and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Highlights Mississippi joins 36 other U.S. states in legalizing marijuana for medical use on Wednesday. The governor signed legislation permitting cannabis for treatment of severe, debilitating health conditions such as cancer, AIDS and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease. Governor Tate Reeves said the final version passed last week by the Republican-controlled legislature was designed to curb recreational marijuana use.</description></item><item><title>Federal Judges order Alabama to redraw Congressional map</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efbc3414f11a3484311746/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efbc3414f11a3484311746/</guid><description>A 3-judge federal panel is rejecting Alabama’s newly-drawn Congressional district map and sending it back to the legislature.
Summary BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (WBRC) - A 3-judge federal panel is rejecting Alabama’s newly-drawn Congressional district map and sending it back to the legislature saying it likely violates Section 2 of the Voting Rights Act. The judges say plaintiffs are likely to prove “Black voters have less opportunity than other Alabamians to elect candidates of their choice to Congress.</description></item><item><title>Florida school district cancels professor’s civil rights lecture over critical race theory concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef67cd9bfe62d379f3076a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef67cd9bfe62d379f3076a/</guid><description>Critical race theory concerns played a role in a Florida school district cancelling a civil rights lecture.
Summary MIAMI — A Florida school district canceled a professor’s civil rights history seminar for teachers, citing in part concerns over “critical race theory” — even though his lecture had nothing to do with the topic. DeSantis also wants to empower parents to sue schools that teach critical race theory. “Critical Race Theory and factual history are two different things.</description></item><item><title>Qatar in talks with the US on supplying Europe with gas as Russia, Ukraine tensions mount</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee246320aee75c50cff906/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 04:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee246320aee75c50cff906/</guid><description>Summary More than 40% of Europe’s liquified natural gas (LNG) supply comes from Russia, and almost a third of the latter’s gas passes through Ukraine. Concerns over an invasion increased late last year as Russia was seen dispatching its troops on its border with Ukraine. Europe receives more than 40% of its gas supply from Russia whilst almost a third of its shipments pass through Ukraine. On 14 January, Reuters reported that the US State Department was in talks with energy companies to shift around gas supplies to Europe.</description></item><item><title>New York and other north-eastern US states see a rapid fall in Covid cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e770befc473a38d50de86e/</guid><description>Despite decreasing positivity rates, hospitals continue to struggle amid a surging patient load and staff shortages
Summary New York City and some north-eastern US states appear to be seeing rapid decreases in their numbers of Covid-19 cases in recent days, raising the possibility that the Omicron wave has now already peaked in some parts of America. “Overall, the prognosis, the forecast, for Covid is much brighter than it had been before.</description></item><item><title>Alabama woman who joined Islamic State stuck in refugee camp</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0147423285a11aff0d008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 12:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0147423285a11aff0d008/</guid><description>BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (AP) — Attorneys for a woman who left her Alabama home to join the Islamic State terror group plan to continue fighting for her and her young son even though the Supreme Court declined to consider her lawsuit seeking to re-enter the United States, one of the lawyers said Wednesday.
Summary FILE - This undated photo provided by attorney Hassan Shibly shows Hoda Muthana, who was born in New Jersey in 1994 and grew up in Alabama.</description></item><item><title>West Virginia governor feels 'extremely unwell' after testing positive for Covid-19 and cancels state legislature address</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df09430c04fe59d06c7f00/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df09430c04fe59d06c7f00/</guid><description>West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice tested positive Tuesday for Covid-19 and described feeling &amp;quot;extremely unwell&amp;quot; as he isolates at home, according to a statement.
Summary (CNN) West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice tested positive Tuesday for Covid-19 and described feeling &amp;ldquo;extremely unwell&amp;rdquo; as he isolates at home, according to a statement. Justice, 70, awoke Tuesday morning with congestion and a cough, eventually developing a headache and fever, he said in the statement.</description></item><item><title>Florida governor calls on feds for more COVID antibody doses</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d46f24cc876a1c26fe9c0e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d46f24cc876a1c26fe9c0e/</guid><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis called on the federal government Monday to allow states to directly purchase monoclonal antibody treatments from companies, saying the state is ready to open new monoclonal antibody treatment sites but is waiting on treatments.
Summary The governor said during a news conference that additional sites would open in South and Central Florida when the state receives more treatments, which he said could be between 30,000-40,000 additional doses. [TRENDING: Cooler weather comes to Central Florida | WATCH: Snow falls in Florida.</description></item><item><title>Virginia AG sues town where police threatened Black Army lieutenant during stop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</guid><description>Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.
Summary Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging Thursday that the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.</description></item><item><title>Harry Reid, former Senate majority leader and Democratic kingmaker, dies at 82 - The Nevada Independent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc3fcdd3f6bd95dc0e2050/</guid><description>Over more than three decades of service in Congress, Reid earned a reputation for fighting relentlessly to protect his home state and everyday Americans. As Senate Democratic leader for a dozen years, he played an instrumental role in passing the Affordable Care Act and shepherding through Congress pivotal economic recovery legislation in the wake of the Great Recession.
Summary He also turned the Nevada State Democratic Party into a well-oiled political operation — nicknamed the Reid Machine — responsible for securing numerous Democratic victories in close races over the last decade.</description></item><item><title>Wave of suicides hits Texas National Guard’s border mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</guid><description>Operation Lone Star&amp;rsquo;s sudden and rapid expansion has left many Texas guardsmen struggling to balance their military and civilian lives, sometimes with tragic results.
Summary The string of suicides raises urgent questions about the mission’s conditions and purpose, as well as the way it’s organized and manned through indefinite involuntary call-ups, according to the Texas Army National Guard’s former top enlisted soldier. What’s going on out thereThe increased demand for troops on the border meant that the department had to resort to involuntarily activating entire units from the Texas National Guard and mobilizing members of the Texas State Guard.</description></item><item><title>Florida pulls pro-vaccination television ads, replacing with spots that don’t mention vaccines</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3f464011a29c9f16cde6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 04:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3f464011a29c9f16cde6e/</guid><description>State sponsored commercials promoting COVID-19 vaccinations have been pulled from Florida&amp;rsquo;s airwaves.
Summary Spots are produced by the Florida Department of Health, which then disseminates them to stations around the state. Last March, the Biden administration rolled out a billion dollar ad campaign about the importance of the vaccine. AdThose videos featured pastors, local sports stars and health department veterans. These ran until early November, when the state health department made a sudden change.</description></item><item><title>Michigan diner owner who defied state shutdown dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 01:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3ca2dc487adcf40b3b090/</guid><description>None
Summary BRANCH COUNTY, MI – A diner owner who kept his restaurant open in defiance of state shutdowns has died after more than a two-month battle with COVID-19. He owned the Quincy Diner, 174 E. Chicago St. (U.S. 12) in the village of Quincy. He kept the restaurant open in December 2020, in violation of the partial shutdown ordered by the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services. Related: ‘I’d have lost the business.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item></channel></rss>