<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>times on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/times/</link><description>Recent content in times on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 05:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/times/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Please send the police now': Uvalde student called 911 multiple times during shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291aeaa021c7a51c7009ce4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 05:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291aeaa021c7a51c7009ce4/</guid><description>At least two children called 911, one of whom begged for help, during Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s mass shooting at a Uvalde, Texas, elementary school.
Highlights One girl called 911 more than five times, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Steven C. McCraw said. He did not name the children but said both of them survived the attack at Robb Elementary School. 19 students and two teachers were killed in the shooting at a Uvalde, Texas, elementary school.</description></item><item><title>Air Force crew disciplined for landing on Martha's Vineyard to pick up vintage BMW motorcycle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ec9d222ed85291d965504/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 21:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ec9d222ed85291d965504/</guid><description>An Air Force crew has been disciplined for making an unplanned stop on Martha&amp;rsquo;s Vineyard so a crew member could pick up a vintage motorcycle.
Highlights The crew was with the U.S. Air Force Reserve’s 53rd Weather Reconnaissance Squadron, 403rd Wing. The stop was made so that a crew member could pick up a vintage motorcycle. Air Force leadership was reportedly unaware of the detour during a training mission in March.</description></item><item><title>A man was fatally stabbed at the Dave &amp;amp; Busters in Times Square</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f84a1f74fd90f7ca4533b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 07:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f84a1f74fd90f7ca4533b/</guid><description>A man died after being stabbed in the chest on Saturday following a dispute at the Dave &amp;amp; Busters in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Times Square.
Highlights Allen Stanford, 39, of Harlem, was identified by the New York City Police Department as the victim. Jesse Armstrong, 41, was arrested and charged with murder Sunday. Police officers responded to a &amp;ldquo;call of an assault in progress&amp;rdquo; inside 234 West 42 Street, where the Dave &amp;amp; Busters is located.</description></item><item><title>Asian woman punched 125 times in New York attack; suspect charged with attempted murder as hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623013532bd52389fdf73657/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 04:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623013532bd52389fdf73657/</guid><description>A man was charged with attempted murder in what police have described as a &amp;quot;brutal hate crime&amp;quot; against an Asian woman in New York state last week, with video
Highlights Tammel Esco, 42, was arrested and accused of calling a 67-year-old woman an &amp;ldquo;Asian b&amp;mdash;-,&amp;rdquo; following her into a building and severely beating her Friday in Yonkers, New York state. The woman, who was not publicly identified, is stable and recovering in a hospital, police said.</description></item><item><title>US, Allies rush tons of weapons and ammunition to Ukraine as Russian troops close on Kyiv, New York Times reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223ee84c9ad9f98fde02d1c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 23:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223ee84c9ad9f98fde02d1c/</guid><description>About 14 wide-bodied transport planes flew tons of ammunition and weapons to include Javelin antitank missiles, rocket launchers, and guns to an airfield near the Ukraine border Friday as Western nations rushed to bolster the Ukrainian army as Russian troops close in on the capital of Kyiv, The New York Times reported.
Highlights About 14 wide-bodied transport planes flew tons of ammunition and weapons to an airfield near the Ukraine border Friday as Western nations rushed to bolster the Ukrainian army as Russian troops close in on the capital of Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Florida woman charged with murder after allegedly stabbing husband 140 times</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62133b70e8991d2bc69fd4ea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 07:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62133b70e8991d2bc69fd4ea/</guid><description>A Florida woman has been charged with first-degree murder after police say she allegedly stabbed her husband more than 140 times.
Highlights Joan Burke, 61, who is being held without bond, appeared before a Palm Beach County judge on Sunday via video conference. Police say they responded to Burke&amp;rsquo;s home on the evening of February 11 after receiving a call from a man who identified himself as the son of the suspect.</description></item><item><title>Ottawa: police use pepper spray and stun grenades to clear trucker protest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211795717f05bdace1ac286/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 23:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211795717f05bdace1ac286/</guid><description>‘We told you to leave,’ police say on Twitter, before confronting protesters against Covid mandates and Trudeau government
Highlights Police used pepper spray and stun grenades to break up the blockade of trucks and demonstrators in downtown Ottawa. Truckers have been protesting against Covid-19 vaccine requirements for truck drivers in Canada for more than three weeks. Police, who were accused of using heavy-handed tactics, deployed Mounties on horseback, claimed there were no serious injuries.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Palin loses defamation case against New York Times</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ad3933e58e89ba58acef7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 22:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ad3933e58e89ba58acef7/</guid><description>A U.S. judge on Monday said he will throw out Sarah Palin&amp;rsquo;s defamation lawsuit against the New York Times after concluding that the newspaper did not in an editorial maliciously link the former Alaska governor and 2008 Republican U.S. vice presidential candidate to a mass murder.
Highlights Sarah Palin&amp;rsquo;s defamation lawsuit against the New York Times will be thrown out, U.S. District Judge Jed Rakoff says. The judge says Palin failed to show the Times acted with &amp;ldquo;actual malice&amp;rdquo; in a June 2017 editorial.</description></item><item><title>Area more than six times the size of Manhattan destroyed in Brazilian Amazon in January</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc8bfe277d2eb22f97d9e4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 02:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc8bfe277d2eb22f97d9e4/</guid><description>Deforestation levels in the Brazilian Amazon hit a new record for January.
Highlights Deforestation levels in the Brazilian Amazon hit a new record for January just three weeks into the year. Nearly 360 square kilometres of forest cover – an area more than six times the size of Manhattan – were destroyed in the Amazon from 1 January to 21 January. Deforestation has surged since far-right President Jair Bolsonaro took office in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Japan Is Working on a COVID-19 Vaccine That Offers Lifelong Immunity</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</guid><description>While pharma companies focus on developing variant-specific boosters, Japan is working on a vaccine that could offer lifelong immunity.
Summary Researchers at the Tokyo Metropolitan Institute of Medical Science are working on a COVID-19 vaccine that not only delivers lifelong immunity against the SARS-CoV-2 virus but could also be transported at room temperature to far-off corners of the world, The Japan Times reported. The vaccine that is being developed by Michinori Kohara and his team of researchers employs the most successful vaccine used in history, one against smallpox.</description></item><item><title>Fox cancels ‘New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022’ telecast due to omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3216fec063da1021cd228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 13:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3216fec063da1021cd228/</guid><description>Fox has cancelled its &amp;quot;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022&amp;quot; production in New York due to the recent surge in Covid-19 cases as the omicron variant spreads.
Summary Fox has decided against moving forward with its “New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022” production in New York due to the ongoing surge of Covid-19 and its omicron variant. “While we are confident in the health and safety protocols for ‘Fox’s New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022,’ the recent velocity of the spread of Omicron cases has made it impossible to produce a live special in Times Square that meets our standards,” Fox Entertainment said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>