<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mps on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mps/</link><description>Recent content in mps on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conservative MP’s Photo of ‘Empty Canadian Grocery Store’ Actually Taken in Northern England, Not Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01098a9fc418d8c678fbf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 15:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01098a9fc418d8c678fbf/</guid><description>Summary Lantsman’s tweet included a graphic featuring a photo of a perplexed woman looking at an empty grocery store shelf. “Empty Canadian grocery store shelves could become a larger problem,” the graphic states. They indicated the photo was actually taken in Northern England at the Lakes &amp;amp; Dales Co-op supermarket just outside Newcastle in the seaside town of Whitley Bay. “Our petition from Canadians demanding action in communities across the country continues to grow every hour,” Lantsman told PressProgress.</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson has been accused of targeting the BBC in a desperate attempt to save his own premiership</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e53e4c6dd01c7123db8cae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 10:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e53e4c6dd01c7123db8cae/</guid><description>Government insider says announcement about abolishing licence fee was not expected this weekend
Summary Boris Johnson has been accused of targeting the BBC in a desperate attempt to save his own premiership, as the Labour leader insisted he had broken the law by attending lockdown parties and then lying about it. A number of Tory MPs are said to be poised to demand Johnson’s resignation amid anger from constituents over allegations of a party culture in Westminster while coronavirus restrictions were in place.</description></item></channel></rss>