<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mean on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mean/</link><description>Recent content in mean on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 09:15:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RCMP officers privately warned their loved ones that a killer was on the loose, but didn’t warn the broader public</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2175aec34835f5cde04e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2175aec34835f5cde04e/</guid><description>Sandra McCulloch, a lawyer representing many of the murder victims&amp;rsquo; families, spoke to the Mass Casualty Commission yesterday. She was speaking to the failure of the RCMP to issue an emergency alert to warn the public during the murder spree.
Highlights Sandra McCulloch was playing with her two pre-schoolers when she learned of the April 19, 2020, mass murder spree. McCulloch said she was lucky to have a friend who had a member of the RCMP as a family member, who was alerting their loved ones.</description></item><item><title>Russia accuses Ukraine of attacking oil depot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249652957e00ef849a7f057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 09:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249652957e00ef849a7f057/</guid><description>Russia claims a Ukrainian helicopter raid set fuel tanks ablaze in Belgorod, a Russian city.
Highlights Russia claims a Ukrainian helicopter raid set fuel tanks ablaze in Belgorod, a Russian city. &amp;ldquo;I will neither confirm nor deny this information,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;It does not mean that Ukraine has to bear responsibility for all those catastrophes and all those events that happen on the territory of the Russian Federation. This is not the first time we have seen such accusations,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description></item></channel></rss>