<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>release on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/release/</link><description>Recent content in release on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 13:42:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yellowstone visitor dies after bison gores her, tosses her 10 feet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62976c95e0cecba2d87dedb2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 13:42:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62976c95e0cecba2d87dedb2/</guid><description>A woman visiting Yellowstone National Park died after a bison gored her and tossed her into the air, park officials said Tuesday.
Highlights The 25-year-old woman was visiting from Ohio. The woman approached the female bison Monday morning after it came close to a boardwalk at Black Sand Basin, near Old Faithful geyser. An estimated 2,300 to 5,500 bison live at the park, and they have injured more people than any other animal.</description></item><item><title>Worker lost arm from injury at U.S. mail facility in North Carolina, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623092ac3e2f303de2035120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 13:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623092ac3e2f303de2035120/</guid><description>The arm of a mechanic working at a U.S. mail facility in North Carolina was amputated last year after coming into contact with a machine that had a safety guard removed, the U.S. Labor Department has found.
Highlights Inspection identified ‘repeat and serious safety violations’ at facility in Greensboro, North Carolina. Facility failed to train staff on working near conveyors or proper methods for safely operating equipment, agency says. Facility allowed workers without adequate training and protective equipment to perform tests on live electrical equipment.</description></item><item><title>Man used COVID loan to buy Pokémon card, sentenced to prison.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622739c4be3299fe68de2766/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 11:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622739c4be3299fe68de2766/</guid><description>A Georgia man has been sentenced to three years in prison after he used a COVID-19 relief loan to buy a rare Pokémon card, according to the Department of Justice.
Highlights Vinath Oudomsine, 31, was awarded an Economic Injury Disaster Loan (EIDL) for $85,000 after claiming to own a small business that supported 10 employees. He used $57,789 of the loan to buy a first-edition, shadowless and holographic Charizard card with a 9.</description></item><item><title>Biden orders release of Trump White House logs to Congress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d5a95e486b50bd850c2ff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 20:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d5a95e486b50bd850c2ff/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is ordering the release of Trump White House visitor logs to the House committee investigating the riot of Jan. 6, 2021, once more rejecting former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s claims of executive privilege.
Highlights President Joe Biden is ordering the release of Trump White House visitor logs to the House committee investigating the riot of Jan. 6, 2021. The committee has sought a trove of data from the National Archives, including presidential records that Trump had fought to keep private.</description></item><item><title>New York governor signs bill criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4e36fe32d7d605f347c3f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4e36fe32d7d605f347c3f/</guid><description>New York&amp;rsquo;s governor signed legislation Wednesday criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards, according to a news release from her office.
Summary (CNN) New York&amp;rsquo;s governor signed legislation Wednesday criminalizing fake Covid-19 vaccination cards, according to a news release from her office. The law comes amid a fresh tightening of rules requiring proof of vaccination in cities across the United States &amp;ndash; including New York &amp;ndash; as the Omicron coronavirus variant spreads rapidly ahead of the Christmas holiday.</description></item></channel></rss>