<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>workers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/workers/</link><description>Recent content in workers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 02:53:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/workers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla loses bid to move sexual harassment lawsuit to arbitration</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d9a212adcb1c231e1cc7e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 02:53:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d9a212adcb1c231e1cc7e/</guid><description>A California state judge has rejected Tesla Inc&amp;rsquo;s bid to send a lawsuit alleging widespread sexual harassment at the company&amp;rsquo;s flagship assembly plant to private arbitration, allowing it to move forward in court.
Highlights California state judge rejects Tesla Inc&amp;rsquo;s bid to send a lawsuit alleging widespread sexual harassment to private arbitration. California Superior Court Judge Stephen Kaus in Oakland denied Tesla&amp;rsquo;s motion to compel arbitration in a brief order on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus committee: Meat companies lied about impending shortage and put workers at risk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62800d99efaaee5ea978e3d4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 20:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62800d99efaaee5ea978e3d4/</guid><description>At the height of the pandemic, as the coronavirus infected tens of thousands of meat industry workers and caused hundreds to die, executives at the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest meat producers were aware of the transmission risk in their plants and successfully lobbied the Trump White House and the USDA to circumvent coronavirus prevention measures and regulations, according to the latest findings of a congressional investigation.
Highlights Committee finds meatpackers lobbied the White House and the USDA to circumvent prevention measures and regulations.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717187170404dccf614c0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 18:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717187170404dccf614c0d/</guid><description>The US labor market remained on fire in March with a record 4.5 million workers quitting their jobs, new data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed Tuesday.
Highlights The number of quits increased most significantly in the professional and business services sector, as well as construction. The overall quits rate moved up to 3%, a level not seen since December 2021. The job openings rate inched back up to 7.</description></item><item><title>Most U.S. workers took an inflation pay cut in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62272c503972e986984c59dd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 10:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62272c503972e986984c59dd/</guid><description>Most American workers have taken a pay cut in the past two years - even if they didn’t know it.
Highlights Most American workers have taken a pay cut in the past two years - even if they didn&amp;rsquo;t know it. Rainfall near a half an inch expected in Brevard, North Carolina. Rain in the forecast is expected to fall 90% this week, and rain could fall as high as 90% in the coming days.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court blocks Biden vaccine mandate for businesses, backs health-care worker rule</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0cb3b85a13bc99466417f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0cb3b85a13bc99466417f/</guid><description>The Supreme Court ruled against the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s rule for OSHA, saying it did not have the power to require vaccination for millions of Americans.
Summary The rulings came three days after the Occupational Safety and Health Administration&amp;rsquo;s emergency measure for businesses started to take effect. The Supreme Court on Thursday blocked the Biden administration from enforcing its sweeping vaccine-or-test requirements for large private companies, but allowed a vaccine mandate to stand for medical facilities that take Medicare or Medicaid payments.</description></item><item><title>Workers at nearly 80 Kroger's King Soopers go on strike as talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03e92708b1033bb719187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03e92708b1033bb719187/</guid><description>More than 8,000 workers at nearly 80 King Soopers stores went on strike for better wages on Wednesday as negotiations stalled, but the stores stayed open as the Kroger Co-owned Colorado chain hired temporary staff and promoted online ordering.
Summary A union member raises a sign outside a Kroger&amp;rsquo;s King Soopers store during a protest as workers go on strike in Denver, Colorado, U.S., January 12, 2022. The striking workers are employed at King Soopers stores in the Denver metropolitan area, Boulder, Parker and Broomfield cities of Colorado, among others.</description></item><item><title>United CEO says vaccine mandate appears to have ended weekly deaths of employees from Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</guid><description>A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday.
Summary A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday. &amp;ldquo;Prior to our vaccine requirement, tragically, more than one United employee on average per week was dying from COVID,&amp;rdquo; Kirby wrote.</description></item><item><title>US farms made $200million via human smuggling and labor trafficking operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7e8df00c61d353cf0b258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7e8df00c61d353cf0b258/</guid><description>Two dozen conspirators forced workers to pay fees for travel and housing while forcing them to work for little to no pay
Summary Initially, the worker was told they would be working on a blueberry farm, but was sent to a corn-farming operation instead. “There was a lot of abuse for little pay,” the worker added. They were excluded from the National Labor Relations Act passed in 1935, and the Fair Labor Standards Act of 1938.</description></item><item><title>Locked-out New Zealanders outraged as visa scheme for rich foreigners resumes. Critics say the wealthy will be able to buy their way in while citizens lose out on quarantine spots.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6b3794cfd4927f11a1805/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6b3794cfd4927f11a1805/</guid><description>Critics say the wealthy will be able to buy their way in while citizens lose out on quarantine spots
Summary With their visas in hand, investors may apply to compete for spots in New Zealand’s congested MIQ system. According to information released under the Official Information Act, New Zealand’s policy of granting visas to wealthy investors reached its height in 2016-2017 when 446 wealthy investors were granted visas. Due to the emergence of Covid-19 and the closing of New Zealand’s borders, just 51 investor visas were granted in 2020-2021.</description></item><item><title>Employer must face worker's lawsuit over husband's COVID death -California court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</guid><description>Description HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CALIFORNIA-WORKERS:Employer must face worker&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit over husband&amp;rsquo;s COVID death -California court
Summary The California Court of Appeal, Second Appellate District, rejected South San Francisco-based See&amp;rsquo;s Candies&amp;rsquo; argument that the employee, Matilde Ek, must file for workers&amp;rsquo; compensation rather than seek damages in court because her husband&amp;rsquo;s death was &amp;ldquo;derivative&amp;rdquo; of her own workplace injury. Ek and her three daughters sued See&amp;rsquo;s last year, saying she contracted COVID-19 because the company failed to ensure safety in the workplace.</description></item></channel></rss>