<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukrainian on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukrainian/</link><description>Recent content in ukrainian on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:13:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukrainian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia claims mass civilian graves found in Donbas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d84ee1d83feb21c70940e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d84ee1d83feb21c70940e/</guid><description>Moscow accuses Ukraine of genocide against Russian-speakers. *West has raised fears of a &amp;quot;false flag&amp;quot; operation.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s Investigative Committee claimed mass graves of hundreds of Russian-speaking civilians had been found in the Donbas region. The committee claimed that the civilians were killed by Ukrainian shelling. The announcement comes a day after Russian President Vladimir Putin stated that &amp;ldquo;in our view what is now happening in Donbas is genocide&amp;rdquo; and claimed that there were &amp;ldquo;mass violations of human rights in Ukraine&amp;rdquo; Despite claims by Russia that it has been withdrawing troops, NATO and Western officials have stated that troops continue to arrive at the border.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: NATO prepares for possible Russian invasion as diplomats fear talks will fail | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</guid><description>There are fears Vladimir Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war - with a Ukrainian source saying they expect any Russian attack would be intense but limited.
Summary That was the warning from Jens Stoltenberg, the head of the NATO alliance, which is braced for the possibility of a further Russian invasion of the vast eastern European state. A fear among western diplomats is that President Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war, eight years on from his annexation of Crimea and the backing of an insurgency in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item></channel></rss>