<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukrainian on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukrainian/</link><description>Recent content in ukrainian on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:10:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukrainian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian soldier pleads guilty at Ukraine war crimes trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62860965105208870f83676f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62860965105208870f83676f/</guid><description>A 21-year-old Russian soldier facing the first war crimes trial since Moscow invaded Ukraine has pleaded guilty to killing an unarmed civilian
Highlights Sgt. Vadim Shishimarin could get life in prison for allegedly shooting a 62-year-old Ukrainian man in the head. Shishhimarin was a captured member of a Russian tank unit. He was prosecuted under a section of the Ukrainian criminal code that addresses the laws and customs of war. Investigators are investigating allegations that Russian troops violated Ukrainian and international law by killing, torturing and abusing possibly thousands of Ukrainian civilians.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian speaks out after Russian troops buried him alive - CNN Video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283948721539f5897e649ba/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283948721539f5897e649ba/</guid><description>CNN&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Bell speaks with a Ukrainian who, along with his brothers, was beaten, shot and buried by Russian soldiers.
Highlights CNN&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Bell speaks with a Ukrainian who, along with his brothers, was beaten, shot and buried by Russian soldiers. He tells how he was beaten and killed by Russian forces in Ukraine. His brothers were beaten and shot by Russian troops, and his brothers were killed and buried. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bell talks with the Ukrainian who was killed by the Russians at the hands of the Russian army in Ukraine in 2010.</description></item><item><title>Putin tries to justify Ukraine invasion; Russian forces continue to storm Mariupol steel plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1095e7461c917c05b323/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1095e7461c917c05b323/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Putin has attempted to justify his unprecedented invasion of Ukraine on &amp;quot;Victory Day&amp;quot; — a key event on the country&amp;rsquo;s calendar.
Highlights Putin said the West was &amp;ldquo;preparing for the invasion of our land, including Crimea,&amp;rdquo; Putin said. He added that NATO was creating threats at Russia&amp;rsquo;s borders. Russia had amassed some 190,000 troops on its borders with Ukraine in the weeks before its invasion. There was little evidence of military aggression from Ukraine toward Russia, and Moscow&amp;rsquo;s claims to the contrary were seen by many as a pretext for justifying the invasion.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Russia accused of targeting hospitals in 'terror bombing' campaign</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278a41d9aa33a0d7af7a690/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 05:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278a41d9aa33a0d7af7a690/</guid><description>Russia has been accused of waging psychological warfare against the Ukrainian people by targeting hospitals, as Sky News analysis shows that almost 60% of attacks on healthcare facilities worldwide this year have been carried out by Russian forces.
Highlights World Health Organisation has recorded 186 of these attacks since the invasion began. They have killed at least 73 healthcare workers and patients in Ukraine. Tell-tale signs suggest the bombings are consistent with a deliberate Russian tactic.</description></item><item><title>Russia attempts to trade civilians for military prisoners - Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d380bddfb5478d9520097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 13:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d380bddfb5478d9520097/</guid><description>Inconsistent air support has left Russia facing considerable challenges, the UK&amp;rsquo;s ministry of defence says.
Highlights Ukrainian soldiers are under siege on the territory of the Azovstal steel plant. The number of people holed up in Mariupol is unclear but it’s thought to be hundreds, including some children. The fighters’ relatives say the men are exhausted, dirty and hungry with food and water supplies running out. They say they’re even ready to act as a human shield if that helps evacuate the men to safety.</description></item><item><title>US Secretary of State Antony Blinken will visit Kyiv on Sunday - Zelensky</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626540912723ebe1cce58c71/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 12:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626540912723ebe1cce58c71/</guid><description>The US secretary of state, and the defence secretary, are expected in Ukraine later, President Zelensky says.
Highlights Two residential blocks were hit, killing at least eight people, including a three-month-old, her mother and grandmother. The Ukrainian government has said the killing of baby Kira and the seven other victims is an act of terror, designed to break people’s will to fight. The Russians claim they hit legitimate military facilities. But, there could be another rationale for the strikes, one that is as effective as it is cynical.</description></item><item><title>Germany will provide training and maintenance to Ukrainian military, foreign minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260771f926d2271050d0132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 21:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260771f926d2271050d0132/</guid><description>Germany will provide training and maintenance to the Ukrainian military, German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock said in Latvia Wednesday.
Highlights Germany will provide training and maintenance to the Ukrainian military, German foreign minister says. Annalena Baerbock said that Germany could not provide further weaponry as the country had no weapons it could “deliver quickly and without delay right now. Germany has chosen not to make public all the weapons it has previously sent to Ukraine, she said.</description></item><item><title>Russia threatens to up Kyiv strikes over cross-border attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62598bb5f9eb9a2104bd511b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62598bb5f9eb9a2104bd511b/</guid><description>Moscow says it hit a ‘military’ factory outside of Ukraine’s capital in response to ‘sabotage’ in Russia.
Highlights Moscow says it hit a ‘military’ factory outside of Ukraine’s capital in response to ‘sabotage’ in Russia. It says it will increase the “number and scale of missile strikes” against targets in the city. The threat came after Moscow accused Ukrainian troops of launching assaults in Russian border areas on Thursday – a charge Ukraine denies.</description></item><item><title>Russia denies Moskva has sunk after apparent Ukrainian missile strike | Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258ee966e6ecd4e5e80e47b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 04:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258ee966e6ecd4e5e80e47b/</guid><description>US defence officials say it is unclear what caused blast which Ukraine claims to be result of missile strikes
Highlights Russia’s flagship cruiser Moskva is on fire but still afloat and moving across the Black Sea, the Pentagon confirms. The Ukrainian southern military command claims to have struck the cruiser with Neptune anti-ship missiles, causing it to start sinking and forcing the crew to abandon ship. Russia&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry said it was investigating what had happened, but denied reports that it had sunk and claimed the fires had been extinguished.</description></item><item><title>Mariupol mayor says siege has killed more than 10K civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625499e1fcb75036ac08b36e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 21:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625499e1fcb75036ac08b36e/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The mayor of the Ukrainian port city of Mariupol said Monday that more than 10,000 civilians have died in the Russian siege of his city, and that the death toll could surpass 20,000, with corpses that were “carpeted through the streets.”
Highlights Mariupol Mayor Vadym Boychenko says more than 10,000 civilians have died in the Russian siege of his city. He says corpses have been “carpeted through the streets” and the death toll could surpass 20,000.</description></item><item><title>German intelligence reportedly intercepted Russian radio calls discussing the murder of civilians in Bucha - According to "Der Spiegel"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ee61261805c05e9cc3b5e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 13:25:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ee61261805c05e9cc3b5e/</guid><description>The German government has indications that Russia was involved in the killing of civilians in the Ukrainian town of Bucha based on satellite images, a security source said on Thursday.
Highlights Der Spiegel: German intelligence agency intercepted radio messages from Russian military sources discussing killing of civilians in Bucha. BND foreign intelligence office declined to comment on the matter. Local officials say more than 300 people were killed by Russian forces in the Ukrainian town of Bucha alone, and around 50 of them were executed.</description></item><item><title>'We're not finding soldiers, just innocent people': The horror of Russian occupation revealed in Borodianka</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d300e5c25d567ed6164bc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 06:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d300e5c25d567ed6164bc/</guid><description>Oksana Kostychenko walks down a narrow pathway, leading to her back garden in Borodianka. The flower beds on one side are surprisingly well arranged, contrasting with the wanton destruction all around.
Highlights Body of a man found face-down with a bag over his head and hands tied behind his back. Authorities on site say all indications show he was another civilian casualty of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s war. Russian forces occupied Borodianka, Kyiv, for more than a month, razed to ground by long-range attacks.</description></item><item><title>Rape as a weapon: huge scale of sexual violence endured in Ukraine emerges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ad28f66dc62d0bcef8b27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 11:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ad28f66dc62d0bcef8b27/</guid><description>Women and girls have recounted the abuse they have suffered at the hands of Russian soldiers
Highlights Women and girls across Ukraine are grappling with the threat of rape as a weapon of war. Evidence of sexual violence has emerged from areas under Russian control. Gang-rapes, assaults taking place at gunpoint, and rapes committed in front of children are among the grim reports. Women fear it will lead to deep suffering for years to come as Russia withdraws from the country.</description></item><item><title>‘They said they’d mutilate and kill me,’ says kidnapped Ukrainian journalist</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249c85083fa7b3c1d6b867f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 16:16:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249c85083fa7b3c1d6b867f/</guid><description>Russian soldiers tortured Oleh Baturin and threatened to harm his family. Now released, he talks about his terrifying eight-day ordeal
Highlights Ukrainian journalist Oleh Baturin, 43, was held captive for eight days in Kherson. He was interrogated, tortured, threatened with mutilation and death, he said. Sunday will mark two weeks since his release. He has always had a reputation as an uncompromising, courageous fighter against injustice, corruption and the violation of human rights.</description></item><item><title>Slovakia Expels 35 Russian Diplomats</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245d42d421e08168bc52b2d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245d42d421e08168bc52b2d/</guid><description>Change in rules set to take effect from Friday, but Kremlin decree indicates workaround for foreign currency purchases.
Highlights Most Russian troops stationed at Ukraine’s defunct Chernobyl nuclear power plant have left the site, according to state nuclear operator Energoatom. President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s decree indicates a workaround for foreign currency purchases. Foreign buyers of Russian gas will have to use special accounts at Gazprombank to pay for the import of the energy source.</description></item><item><title>Russian Media: "Vladimir Putin has assumed a historic responsibility for the final solution of the Ukrainian question"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623760a5871577f2f340a45a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 17:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623760a5871577f2f340a45a/</guid><description>A quickly deleted article referred to the independence of Belarus and Ukraine as a &amp;quot;terrible catastrophe.&amp;quot;
Highlights Opinion piece seemingly published by Russian news agency RIA Novosti before being quickly taken down. Petr Akopov wrote that Russia is &amp;ldquo;restoring its unity&amp;rdquo; and providing a &amp;ldquo;solution to the Ukrainian question&amp;rdquo; in its invasion of Ukraine. The article was recorded by the Internet Archive&amp;rsquo;s Wayback Machine before it was taken offline. It referred to the 1991 declarations of independence by Belarus and Ukraine as a &amp;ldquo;terrible catastrophe&amp;rdquo; and an &amp;ldquo;unnatural dislocation&amp;rdquo; Author theorized that Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s statehood would not be liquidated if Russia succeeds in its goals, but would instead be &amp;ldquo;reorganized, re-established and returned to its natural state&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Zelenskiy calls for peace talks with Moscow, urges Swiss to target oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62371bb76b9730d766122619/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 12:19:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62371bb76b9730d766122619/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy called on Saturday for comprehensive peace talks with Moscow and also urged Switzerland to do more to crack down on Russian oligarchs who he said were helping wage war on his country with their money.
Highlights Britain says Russia now pursuing strategy of attrition that could exacerbate humanitarian crisis. Russia says its hypersonic missiles have destroyed a large underground depot for missiles and aircraft ammunition in the western Ivano-Frankivsk region.</description></item><item><title>Russia says it used hypersonic missiles in Ukraine for first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236fe2f5d0597f9286eeef5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 10:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236fe2f5d0597f9286eeef5/</guid><description>Aeroballistic missiles destroyed a large underground warehouse containing missiles and aviation ammunition, Moscow says.
Highlights Russia says it used its newest Kinzhal hypersonic missiles for the first time in Ukraine to destroy a weapons storage site in the country’s west. The aeroballistic missiles destroyed a large underground warehouse containing missiles and aviation ammunition, Moscow says. The region of Ivano-Frankivsk shares a 50km (30 miles) long border with NATO member Romania. President Vladimir Putin announced an array of new weapons in 2018 in one of his most bellicose speeches in years, saying they could hit almost any point in the world and evade a United States-built missile shield.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds of bulletproof vests donated for Ukraine stolen in Manhattan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233c0607b84b6a173eaecb8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 23:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233c0607b84b6a173eaecb8/</guid><description>They were swiped from the Ukrainian Congress Committee of America building. Police are seeking the culprits.
Highlights About 400 bulletproof vests stolen from Ukrainian Congress Committee of America building. The vests were donated to be sent to Ukraine to help in its war against Russia. The NYPD is seeking those responsible for the theft of the vests. Police are seeking the culprits and are searching for those responsible. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Siege of Mariupol: Fresh Russian attacks throw evacuation into chaos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62246d6a16ff34d663ffe6a8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 08:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62246d6a16ff34d663ffe6a8/</guid><description>Mass evacuation postponed because of continued Russian shelling.
Highlights Red Cross calls scenes in Mariupol and other Ukrainian cities &amp;ldquo;heartbreaking&amp;rdquo; The International Community of the Red Cross says it is in dialogue with the parties about the safe passage of civilians from different cities affected by the conflict. Mass evacuation postponed because of continued Russian shelling. Red Cross: It is &amp;ldquo;in dialogue&amp;rdquo; with parties to allow safe passage to civilians from other cities affected in conflict.</description></item><item><title>US, Allies rush tons of weapons and ammunition to Ukraine as Russian troops close on Kyiv, New York Times reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223ee84c9ad9f98fde02d1c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 23:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223ee84c9ad9f98fde02d1c/</guid><description>About 14 wide-bodied transport planes flew tons of ammunition and weapons to include Javelin antitank missiles, rocket launchers, and guns to an airfield near the Ukraine border Friday as Western nations rushed to bolster the Ukrainian army as Russian troops close in on the capital of Kyiv, The New York Times reported.
Highlights About 14 wide-bodied transport planes flew tons of ammunition and weapons to an airfield near the Ukraine border Friday as Western nations rushed to bolster the Ukrainian army as Russian troops close in on the capital of Kyiv.</description></item><item><title>Blake Lively and Ryan Reynolds pledge to match donations for Ukrainian refugees up to $1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c4c81396f00d56b306798/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 04:16:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c4c81396f00d56b306798/</guid><description>Actors Blake Lively and Ryan Reynolds are promising to match every donation up to $1 million for refugees fleeing war in Ukraine, the couple said on social media.
Highlights Actors Blake Lively and Ryan Reynolds promise to match every donation up to $1 million for refugees fleeing war in Ukraine. About 368,000 refugees have managed to leave, the U.N. refugee agency reports. EU Commissioner for Home Affairs Ylva Johansson says EU needs to prepare for millions of refugees to arrive.</description></item><item><title>Russia claims mass civilian graves found in Donbas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d84ee1d83feb21c70940e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d84ee1d83feb21c70940e/</guid><description>Moscow accuses Ukraine of genocide against Russian-speakers. *West has raised fears of a &amp;quot;false flag&amp;quot; operation.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s Investigative Committee claimed mass graves of hundreds of Russian-speaking civilians had been found in the Donbas region. The committee claimed that the civilians were killed by Ukrainian shelling. The announcement comes a day after Russian President Vladimir Putin stated that &amp;ldquo;in our view what is now happening in Donbas is genocide&amp;rdquo; and claimed that there were &amp;ldquo;mass violations of human rights in Ukraine&amp;rdquo; Despite claims by Russia that it has been withdrawing troops, NATO and Western officials have stated that troops continue to arrive at the border.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: NATO prepares for possible Russian invasion as diplomats fear talks will fail | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</guid><description>There are fears Vladimir Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war - with a Ukrainian source saying they expect any Russian attack would be intense but limited.
Summary That was the warning from Jens Stoltenberg, the head of the NATO alliance, which is braced for the possibility of a further Russian invasion of the vast eastern European state. A fear among western diplomats is that President Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war, eight years on from his annexation of Crimea and the backing of an insurgency in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Considers Warning Ukraine of a Russian Invasion in Real-Time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c57e2c882d1b7d2c63bf03/</guid><description>U.S. officials say intelligence sharing is essential to the Ukrainian government’s survival, even as they try to avoid escalating the situation.
Summary “The number one thing we can do is real time actionable intelligence that says, ‘The Russians are coming over the berm,’” said Evelyn Farkas, who served as deputy assistant secretary of defense for Russia, Ukraine and Eurasia in the Obama administration. But if Russian tanks are moving over the border, and Ukraine targets them, it will be hard for Mr.</description></item></channel></rss>