<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tv on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tv/</link><description>Recent content in tv on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 18:10:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Todd and Julie Chrisley, stars of TV show 'Chrisley Knows Best,' found guilty on federal charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0e5faba2cc4ab65c5d016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 18:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0e5faba2cc4ab65c5d016/</guid><description>Todd and Julie Chrisley, reality television stars from &amp;quot;Chrisley Knows Best,&amp;quot; found guilty on federal charges including bank fraud and tax evasion.
Highlights Todd and Julie Chrisley are found guilty of conspiring to defraud community banks out of more than $30 million in fraudulent loans. They were also convicted of tax evasion, wire fraud and obstruction of justice. A judge places the Chrisleys on location monitoring and home detention. They must alert probation officers to any spending over $1,000, the judge says.</description></item><item><title>A viewer called to criticize a TV anchor in Missouri over being 'very Asian'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5c0e15220d37632ccb954/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5c0e15220d37632ccb954/</guid><description>A news anchor in Missouri was deeply hurt when a viewer criticized her for being &amp;quot;very Asian&amp;quot; but within hours, Asian Americans across the country stood up for her.
Summary (CNN) A news anchor in Missouri was deeply hurt when a viewer criticized her for being &amp;ldquo;very Asian&amp;rdquo; but within hours, Asian Americans across the country stood up for her. Last week, an unidentified woman called CNN affiliate KSDK in St.</description></item></channel></rss>