<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>funeral on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/funeral/</link><description>Recent content in funeral on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 16:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/funeral/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anonymous donor pays all funeral expenses for Uvalde shooting victims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62939b025f9797e23073b791/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62939b025f9797e23073b791/</guid><description>Anonymous donor pays all funeral expenses for Uvalde shooting victims. Cost of all of the funeral expenses totaled about $175,000. Texas Gov. Greg Abbott briefed the public on the mental health services that will be available to those affected
Highlights Anonymous donor pays all funeral expenses for Uvalde shooting victims. Cost of all of the funeral expenses totaled about $175,000. Texas Gov. Greg Abbott briefed the public on the mental health services that will be available to those affected by the murders.</description></item><item><title>Catholic and Jewish leaders condemn fascist display at Rome funeral</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dedf00b504810042dab413/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dedf00b504810042dab413/</guid><description>Outrage in Italy after mourners give fascist salute outside church and coffin is draped in Nazi flag
Summary Catholic and Jewish leaders in Rome have condemned an “offensive and unacceptable” funeral procession in which the coffin was draped in a Nazi flag and mourners gave the fascist salute outside a church. Photos and video of of the Monday funeral service published online showed about two dozen people gathered outside the church as the swastika-draped coffin emerged, shouting “presente!</description></item></channel></rss>