<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>medical on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/medical/</link><description>Recent content in medical on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:07:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/medical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apparent active shooter at medical facility in Tulsa, Oklahoma.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298295f44b6a5935a8f8576/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298295f44b6a5935a8f8576/</guid><description>UPDATE: Saint Francis Health System has released the following statement concerning the shooting: Saint Francis Health System is grieving the loss of four members of our family. As a faith based organization, the only recourse we have at this moment is to pray while we navigate this tragedy. Out of respect for the families, we are not commenting on or releasing names of those lost or injured at this time.</description></item><item><title>A doctor claimed he had a ‘miracle cure’ for covid. He’s going to prison.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296840cdc710408731507bd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 21:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296840cdc710408731507bd/</guid><description>San Diego doctor Jennings Staley pleaded guilty to attempting to smuggle in a barrel of hydroxychloroquine powder with the help of a Chinese supplier.
Highlights Jennings Ryan Staley was sentenced last week to 30 days in prison and a year of home confinement for the scheme. He pleaded guilty last year to trafficking in hydroxychloroquine, a drug used to treat the coronavirus. The drug was touted by President Donald Trump, starting in the early days of the pandemic, as a “game changer’s game changer.</description></item><item><title>Alabama passes bill making some transgender healthcare a felony</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62505146df7ff676b6db2ea8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62505146df7ff676b6db2ea8/</guid><description>Alabama lawmakers passed a bill on Thursday that would criminalize gender-affirming healthcare for transgender youth, with a threat of 10 years in prison for medical providers.
Highlights The bill would make it a felony punishable with up to 10 years in prison to provide medical care to minors. The bill is the latest in a flurry of measures in Republican-led states dealing with transgender youth. The American Civil Liberties Union called it the first bill of its kind to make healthcare for transgender youth a felony.</description></item><item><title>Rare Minnesota Zoo Tiger named "Putin" dies during medical procedure.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d6b7a3f7639566a245755/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 07:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d6b7a3f7639566a245755/</guid><description>Putin was considered “one of the most genetically valuable Amur tigers” in a North American breeding program.
Highlights The 12-year-old male Amur tiger experienced cardiac failure, Minnesota Zoo says. He was born in the Czech Republic in 2009, where he was given the name “Putin” He was brought to the Minnesota Zoo as a recommendation of the Amur Tiger Global Species Management Plan. Putin was considered “one of the most genetically valuable Amur tigers” in a North American breeding program, the zoo says.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones skips deposition in Sandy Hook settlement, defying court order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b8ccbb12553c31f040b2b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 21:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b8ccbb12553c31f040b2b/</guid><description>Alex Jones had been ordered to appear before the court on Wednesday after a judge denied&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones failed to show up for a deposition scheduled Wednesday morning in Texas. The far-right-wing radio host is being sued by the families of children killed in the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting. The deposition is now scheduled for Thursday morning. A judge ruled Tuesday that a physician&amp;rsquo;s note submitted only for the judge’s viewing did not provide enough evidence on its claim that Jones was “confined to his home” as a result of “medical conditions” making it impossible for him to sit for the scheduled, in-person deposition.</description></item><item><title>Texas court halts child abuse investigations into parents of trans kids</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ae48e11821b66a2b5cfb1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 09:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ae48e11821b66a2b5cfb1/</guid><description>A Texas appeals court has once again halted child abuse investigations into parents of trans children who provide gender-affirming care.
Highlights An appeals court has again blocked the state from investigating gender-affirming care for trans children as child abuse. In February, Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton published an opinion saying such procedures are &amp;ldquo;abuse&amp;rdquo; Texas Gov. Greg Abbott ordered the Department of Family and Protective Services to investigate gender affirmation procedures.</description></item><item><title>Equifax, Experian and TransUnion to wipe out most medical debt on credit report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62381838b50b3bc13f861a15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 06:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62381838b50b3bc13f861a15/</guid><description>Equifax, Experian and TransUnion will eliminate debt from the accounts of consumers who faced unexpected medical bills they were unable to pay.
Highlights Equifax, Experian and TransUnion are removing nearly 70% of medical debt from credit reports. Americans racked up $88 billion in medical debt on consumer credit records as of June 2021, CFPB says. Black, Hispanic, young and low-income consumers are most likely to be impacted by medical debt, bureau says.</description></item><item><title>3 officers found guilty on federal charges in George Floyd’s killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218393e9285cd3dae3fde40/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218393e9285cd3dae3fde40/</guid><description>A federal jury has reached a verdict in the trial of three former Minneapolis police officers charged with violating the civil rights of George Floyd.
Highlights Three Minneapolis police officers convicted of violating civil rights of George Floyd. Floyd&amp;rsquo;s brother: &amp;ldquo;It can never be justice because I can never get George back&amp;rdquo; Former officers J. Alexander Kueng, Thomas Lane and Tou Thao found guilty of depriving Floyd of his civil rights.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi ambulance providers fear a system collapse is near</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdf96f46869d129e1a70bc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 04:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdf96f46869d129e1a70bc/</guid><description>Mississippi’s ambulance system is falling apart, pushing more and more workers from a job that was a hard sell even before the pandemic.
Highlights Mississippi&amp;rsquo;s ambulance system is falling apart, pushing more and more workers from a job that was a hard sell even before the pandemic. Ambulance companies say they have given up on job postings because no one is applying, making it harder to quantify how large the holes are statewide.</description></item><item><title>Arkansas jail sued over ivermectin treatments has alleged history of leaving ailing inmates "harmed and worse off"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb8ecbb70d6ed393be6bc5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 08:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb8ecbb70d6ed393be6bc5/</guid><description>At least 37 federal lawsuits have been filed against the jail and/or its doctor since his contract began in 2016.
Highlights Walt Kelly was taken to Washington County Detention Center in Arkansas in November 2017 for two counts of delivering an ounce of marijuana. Kelly, 49, was undergoing treatment for bipolar disorder. Kelly said he was left &amp;ldquo;left to die in my own misery, in my mental health nightmare&amp;rdquo; last year.</description></item><item><title>Legislator dies using medical suicide law he helped pass</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 21:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</guid><description>A former Vermont legislator and House majority leader has died with the help of a law he himself helped pass that allows the terminally ill to end their own lives, his wife said. Willem Jewett died Jan.
Summary The former Vermont lawmaker and House majority leader died on Wednesday, Jan. 12, 2022. Jewett, who had cancer, helped pass a Vermont&amp;rsquo;s aid-in-dying law that allows terminally ill patients to ask their doctors for a lethal dose of medication.</description></item><item><title>Quebec says it will tax those who remain unvaccinated against COVID-19 without a medical reason</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfc012615c48af4a17a4b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfc012615c48af4a17a4b1/</guid><description>Quebec Premier François Legault said it was a measure for &amp;quot;fairness&amp;quot; for the 90% of residents who are vaccinated.
Summary The Premier of Quebec François Legault at a press conference on November 18, 2021 in Montreal, Canada. Minas Panagiotakis/Getty Images10% of Quebec&amp;rsquo;s adult population is unvaccinated for COVID-19, Premier François Legault said. The unvaccinated, however, make up half of all ICU beds in the province, Legault said. Quebec&amp;rsquo;s Premier François Legault announced on Tuesday that the province plans to tax people who are unvaccinated against COVID-19 for non-medical reasons.</description></item><item><title>Seattle Kraken fan called a hero after noticing Canucks staffer's cancerous mole during game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d169ba61c6e97258bcc758/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 09:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d169ba61c6e97258bcc758/</guid><description>A Seattle Kraken fan is being praised as a hero after helping the assistant equipment manager of the Vancouver Canucks identify a cancerous mole on his neck in the middle of a game.
Summary A Seattle Kraken fan is being praised as a hero — and awarded $10,000 — after helping the assistant equipment manager of the Vancouver Canucks identify a cancerous mole on his neck in the middle of a game.</description></item><item><title>Warning against unnecessary circumcision from Australian Medical Association president Mark Duncan-Smith after two-year-old dies and brother almost bleeds out in Western Australia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4c74b8124f5fa654a52b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4c74b8124f5fa654a52b1/</guid><description>WA Australian Medical Association president Mark Duncan-Smith urged parents to only follow through with the procedure if there was a valid medical reason.
Summary And that has to be part of the evaluation of whether or not it&amp;rsquo;s appropriate for a child to have a circumcision.' His warning comes after a two-year-old boy died after suffering an allergic reaction to anaesthesia given to him during the procedure on Tuesday. The top doctor pointed out rates of circumcision had declined in Western Australia over the last few decades.</description></item></channel></rss>