<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>possible on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/possible/</link><description>Recent content in possible on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 01:04:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/possible/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 dead, 3 hurt in shooting at Houston flea market</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281a2f766463cc0f00016d8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 01:04:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281a2f766463cc0f00016d8/</guid><description>Two people are dead and three others are hurt in a shooting at a Houston flea market on Sunday, the Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said.
Highlights Thousands of people were at the busy flea market in Houston, Texas. Two people died on scene and three men were hospitalized in critical condition, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said. The shooting appeared to stem from an altercation between five men, the Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said.</description></item><item><title>Pentagon monitoring reports of possible Russian chemical weapons attack in Mariupol</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555e7974c7a3473dd87e2e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555e7974c7a3473dd87e2e/</guid><description>If Russia were to have used chemical weapons, it would signal a major escalation of its botched invasion of Ukraine, which has stalled after more than a month.
Highlights If Russia were to have used chemical weapons in Mariupol, it would represent a major escalation of the conflict. British Foreign Secretary Liz Truss also says her government is working &amp;ldquo;urgently&amp;rdquo; to verify details of alleged attack. The original report was in the form of a Telegram message posted by the Azov Regiment, an ultra-nationalist part of the Ukrainian National Guard.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: NATO prepares for possible Russian invasion as diplomats fear talks will fail | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</guid><description>There are fears Vladimir Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war - with a Ukrainian source saying they expect any Russian attack would be intense but limited.
Summary That was the warning from Jens Stoltenberg, the head of the NATO alliance, which is braced for the possibility of a further Russian invasion of the vast eastern European state. A fear among western diplomats is that President Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war, eight years on from his annexation of Crimea and the backing of an insurgency in eastern Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>