<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>children on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/children/</link><description>Recent content in children on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 09:12:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas judge blocks investigations into parents of trans children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c63f24578b3189de8a9c7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 09:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c63f24578b3189de8a9c7/</guid><description>A Texas judge on Friday blocked the state from investigating as child abuse gender-confirming care for transgender youth.
Highlights District Judge Amy Clark Meachum issued a temporary injunction preventing the state from enforcing Republican Gov. Greg Abbott’s directive to compel the Department of Family and Protective Services to investigate gender-confirming care for transgender youth. The ACLU and Lambda Legal sued on behalf of the parents of a family with a trans child.</description></item><item><title>Moscow police detain children for laying flowers at Ukrainian embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 13:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</guid><description>Children aged seven to 11 with peace signs detained for hours while two women face trial on unspecified charges
Highlights Children aged seven to 11 were held with their mothers in a police van before being taken to a police station. They were released hours later and face trial and a fine on unspecified charges. Ukrainian foreign minister, Dmytro Kuleba, said it was another sign of the toll Putin’s war against Ukraine is taking on children.</description></item><item><title>Sacramento church shooting leaves 5 dead, including 3 children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</guid><description>Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office confirmed.
Highlights Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento. The victims included three girls ages 9, 10 and 13, officials said. The shooter, who is unidentified, had a restraining order against him, an official said.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item></channel></rss>