<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>children on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/children/</link><description>Recent content in children on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 02:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Illinois found to be routinely housing wards of the state in Chicago’s jail for kids</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a00f5d77bcd758689a5a8c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 02:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a00f5d77bcd758689a5a8c/</guid><description>The state’s child welfare agency says it has nowhere else to put the children. Opponents call it cruel, and a civil rights violation.
Highlights WBEZ first reported on the crisis in 2015. 84 children in the care of the Illinois Department of Children and Family Services were left in the juvenile detention center after a judge ordered their release. One boy, originally detained on a robbery case, is still being held more than eight months after he was released.</description></item><item><title>‘I hope I hit one of them kids’: Woman fires shots into home with children inside, records show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629c23a5b582322eba73eb13/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629c23a5b582322eba73eb13/</guid><description>Johari Jenkins is charged with multiple counts of criminal attempt first-degree murder, aggravated assault and more. A witness said she heard Jenkins state, “I might as well get another one today by killing you and your kids b****
Highlights Johari Jenkins is charged with multiple counts of criminal attempt first-degree murder, aggravated assault and more after an incident on May 2. Jenkins allegedly fired four to five times into the living room window of a Memphis home.</description></item><item><title>Shooter warning signs get lost in sea of social media posts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930139bbd2a49a95d81d25/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 05:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930139bbd2a49a95d81d25/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The warning signs were there for anyone to stumble upon, days before the 18-year-old gunman entered a Texas elementary school and slaughtered 19 children and two teachers .
Highlights Gunman who killed 19 children and two teachers in Texas left a digital trail that hinted at what was to come. The warning signs were there for anyone to stumble upon, days before the massacre. Instagram photo of a hand holding a gun magazine, a TikTok profile that warned, “Kids be scared,” and the image of two AR-style semi-automatic rifles displayed on a rug, pinned to the top of the killer’s Instagram profile.</description></item><item><title>FDA authorizes Pfizer Covid booster dose for kids ages 5 to 11 years old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284ab81bdb402c784425edc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284ab81bdb402c784425edc/</guid><description>The FDA determined that a third shot can help boost protection for children in this age group and the benefits outweigh the risks.
Highlights Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s Covid vaccine for children ages 5 to 11 at least five months after their two-dose primary series. CDC has final say on whether health-care providers should start administering the boosters. The FDA determined that a third shot can help boost protection for children in this age group and the benefits outweigh the risks, the FDA says.</description></item><item><title>Mother arrested after 3 children found dead inside Southern California home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a814d84cdf4fe815eb109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a814d84cdf4fe815eb109/</guid><description>A Southern California mother and a juvenile believed to be her 16-year-old son have been arrested after three children were found dead inside a San Fernando Valley home Sunday, according to the Los Angeles Police Department.
Highlights Police say they responded to the home in the 22000 block of Victory Boulevard in the West Hills neighborhood around 7:40 a.m. Sunday to calls for an assault with deadly weapon. When the Los Angeles Fire Department arrived at the scene, they pronounced all three children dead.</description></item><item><title>CDC investigating 109 cases of severe hepatitis in kids across two dozen states, including 5 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627664556300ace33b5a0929/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 12:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627664556300ace33b5a0929/</guid><description>The cases of severe hepatitis have been found across 25 states and territories.
Highlights The CDC is investigating 109 cases of severe hepatitis in children, including five deaths. More than 90% of the kids were hospitalized and 14% required liver transplants. The cases occurred over the past seven months across 25 states and territories. Hepatitis is an inflammation of the liver that is often caused by viral infections, but environmental factors can also play a role.</description></item><item><title>Disney to help employees, their children obtain 'gender-affirming' procedures, per report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625212e372c06826bac574c6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625212e372c06826bac574c6/</guid><description>A Disney official said during a virtual conference on the company’s “Reimagine Tomorrow” initiative that they will be working with their benefits team to assist employees and their children with obtaining “gender-affirmation procedures. ” Such procedures typically include puberty blockers, breast removal, and genital reassignment surgery, according to Manhattan Institute senior fellow and a contributing editor at City Journal Christopher Rufo, who reported on the comments Thursday.
Highlights Disney to help employees and their children obtain &amp;lsquo;gender-affirming&amp;rsquo; procedures, per report.</description></item><item><title>Toddler fatally shoots 4-year-old sister at Pennsylvania gas station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d2158c7b19c4060101caa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 05:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d2158c7b19c4060101caa/</guid><description>A 2-year-old boy fatally shot his 4-year-old sister at a Pennsylvania gas station Tuesday, authorities said.
Highlights The children were in a car parked at a gas pump in Chester, south of Philadelphia. It wasn’t immediately clear what kind of gun it was or how he got it. The girl was immediately taken to a local hospital, where she was pronounced dead. 258 children 11 and younger have been killed or injured by gunfire this year, according to the Gun Violence Archive, a nonprofit website that tracks shootings in the U.</description></item><item><title>Cadbury faces fresh accusations of child labour on cocoa farms in Ghana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249f13e2e230952f74004c9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249f13e2e230952f74004c9/</guid><description>A new TV documentary alleges that children as young as 10 are using machetes to harvest pods
Highlights Children as young as 10 are allegedly being forced to work long hours on cocoa farms in Ghana. Children were also filmed using sharp knives to open cocoa pods and swinging long sticks with blades tied to them to harvest the pods from the cocoa trees. Mondelēz International owns Cadbury, which made global profits last year of more than £3.</description></item><item><title>Security Guard At Columbus Jewish School Arrested After Threatening To 'Shoot Parents Picking Up Children'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249e4090bccf2a4d90f720a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 18:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249e4090bccf2a4d90f720a/</guid><description>Thomas Develin, 24, of the Northwest Side, was arrested Wednesday. He posted a photo of himself on social media site Discord holding a gun with the message “I’m at a Jewish school and about to make
Highlights Thomas Develin, 24, of the Northwest Side, was arrested Wednesday. He posted a photo of himself on social media site Discord holding a gun with the message “I’m at a Jewish school and about to make it everyone’s problem” He also posted about wanting to shoot the parents picking up their children from school.</description></item><item><title>Estelle Harris Dies: ‘Seinfeld’s Estelle Costanza, ‘Toy Story’ Franchise’s Mrs. Potato Head Was 93</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249811538ec16488999c4b9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249811538ec16488999c4b9/</guid><description>Estelle Harris, who played George Costanza&amp;rsquo;s mother Estelle on &amp;lsquo;Seinfeld,&amp;rsquo; died today, aged 93.
Highlights Estelle Harris, who played George Costanza&amp;rsquo;s mother Estelle on the iconic NBC sitcom Seinfeld, died Saturday evening of natural causes in Palm Desert, California. Born Estelle Nussbaum in New York City on April 22, 1928, Harris appeared on 27 episodes of Seinfeld between 1992 and 1998. Harris is also known for voicing Mrs. Potato Head in three installments of Pixar’s Toy Story franchise (2, 3 and 4) Other film credits include Promoted, CBGB, Playing Mona Lisa, Dancing in September, What&amp;rsquo;s Cooking?</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian kids with cancer evacuated from Poland to St. Jude Children's Hospital - CBS News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ba973f2e3fc6e9b2ad5c5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ba973f2e3fc6e9b2ad5c5/</guid><description>Four children with cancer — just 9 months to 9 years old— have been evacuated from Ukraine to St Jude Children&amp;rsquo;s Research Hospital in Memphis, the U.S. State Department said.
Highlights Four Ukrainian children, ages 9 months to 9 years, have been airlifted from Poland to Memphis. St. Jude is the first hospital in the U.S. to receive Ukrainian patients, the hospital said in a press release. The hospital said it will provide the children with cancer care and &amp;ldquo;trauma-informed psychosocial therapy&amp;rdquo; The State Department said it &amp;ldquo;supported airlift of these pediatric oncology patients and some of their immediate family members from Poland&amp;rdquo; to Memphis International Airport, but did not offer more details about the role it played.</description></item><item><title>Texas judge blocks investigations into parents of trans children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c63f24578b3189de8a9c7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 09:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c63f24578b3189de8a9c7/</guid><description>A Texas judge on Friday blocked the state from investigating as child abuse gender-confirming care for transgender youth.
Highlights District Judge Amy Clark Meachum issued a temporary injunction preventing the state from enforcing Republican Gov. Greg Abbott’s directive to compel the Department of Family and Protective Services to investigate gender-confirming care for transgender youth. The ACLU and Lambda Legal sued on behalf of the parents of a family with a trans child.</description></item><item><title>Moscow police detain children for laying flowers at Ukrainian embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 13:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220c0032b336a8417dcd804/</guid><description>Children aged seven to 11 with peace signs detained for hours while two women face trial on unspecified charges
Highlights Children aged seven to 11 were held with their mothers in a police van before being taken to a police station. They were released hours later and face trial and a fine on unspecified charges. Ukrainian foreign minister, Dmytro Kuleba, said it was another sign of the toll Putin’s war against Ukraine is taking on children.</description></item><item><title>Sacramento church shooting leaves 5 dead, including 3 children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</guid><description>Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office confirmed.
Highlights Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento. The victims included three girls ages 9, 10 and 13, officials said. The shooter, who is unidentified, had a restraining order against him, an official said.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item></channel></rss>