<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>children on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/children/</link><description>Recent content in children on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:14:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sacramento church shooting leaves 5 dead, including 3 children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</guid><description>Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office confirmed.
Highlights Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento. The victims included three girls ages 9, 10 and 13, officials said. The shooter, who is unidentified, had a restraining order against him, an official said.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item></channel></rss>