<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blm on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/blm/</link><description>Recent content in blm on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:15:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/blm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BLM co-founder admits she held parties at mansion bought with donor funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bd2eef1dbe204e3793f09/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bd2eef1dbe204e3793f09/</guid><description>Black Lives Matter Co-Founder Patrisse Cullors admitted in an Associated Press interview she spent overnights and hosted multiple personal events at the group’s controversial Malibu mansion. Cullors’sstatements come after she claimed to have “never misappropriated funds” related to the Black Lives Matter Global Network Foundation’s (BLMGNF) purchase of a $6 million Malibu home with donor funds.
Highlights Patrisse Cullors admitted in an Associated Press interview she spent overnights and hosted multiple personal events at the group&amp;rsquo;s controversial Malibu mansion.</description></item><item><title>Equine virus identified in deaths of wild captive horses in Colorado</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f62792a8eb5fe62c6ec66/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f62792a8eb5fe62c6ec66/</guid><description>Laboratory tests have pinpointed the equine virus suspected of triggering an outbreak of a respiratory illness that has killed at least 95 captive wild horses in less than a week at a federal corral in Colorado, U.S. government officials said on Thursday.
Highlights Outbreak emerged April 23 at the BLM&amp;rsquo;s Wild Horse and Burro Corrals in Canon City, Colorado. Virus strain, an equine influenza designated &amp;ldquo;subtype H3N8,&amp;rdquo; is not uncommon in both wild and domestic horses.</description></item><item><title>Local BLM chapter posts bail for man charged with attempted murder of mayoral candidate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f398145d88ce574f204e9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f398145d88ce574f204e9/</guid><description>LOUISVILLE, Ky. (TND) — A man who is charged with the attempted murder of a mayoral candidate in Louisville is no longer in jail after a local Black Lives Matter chapter teamed up with a community bail fund to post his bail. Quintez Brown, 21, who is said to be a &amp;quot;social justice activist&amp;quot; running as a candidate for Louisville&amp;rsquo;s metro council, allegedly tried to assassinate Democrat mayoral candidateCraig Greenberg.</description></item></channel></rss>