<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>station on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/station/</link><description>Recent content in station on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 17:16:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/station/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>After Russian forces pull back, a shattered town breathes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62433ebf6e2fa075ed2ab079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 17:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62433ebf6e2fa075ed2ab079/</guid><description>TROSTYANETS, Ukraine (AP) — The bodies of two Russian soldiers lie abandoned in the woods.
Highlights Trostyanets, 400km (250 miles) east of capital Kyiv, Ukraine, has seized back control from Russian forces. The more than month-old war has killed thousands and driven more than 10 million Ukrainians from their homes including almost 4 million from their country. It is not clear where the Russian forces went, under what circumstances they fled or whether the town will remain free of them in the days ahead.</description></item><item><title>Gas station drops prices to $2.25 a gallon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e19061f2ca9d826b46728/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 16:17:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e19061f2ca9d826b46728/</guid><description>BURNSVILLE, N. C. (WLOS/WKRC) — Amid an international surge in the cost of fuel, a North Carolina gas station surprised drivers Thursday by dropping prices. Regular gas was selling for $2. 25 a gallon at the Burnsville Citgo at the corner of U. S. 19 East and Depot Street. The station&amp;rsquo;s owners said they just wanted to help people, even though they took a loss by cutting prices. And customers who spoke to News 13 say they appreciate it.</description></item><item><title>Woman attacked with hammer in New York subway station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</guid><description>A 57-year-old woman was hit in the head with a hammer several times and robbed in one of the latest violent crimes in a New York subway station, police said.
Highlights The woman&amp;rsquo;s family identified her as Nina Rothschild, a scientist for the New York City Department of Health. She was attacked about 11 p.m. Thursday by a 6-foot tall male wearing a dark jacket, bluejeans and holding a cane, police say.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19: Antarctica research station battling coronavirus outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61daa43b6dbf231ea0f69f65/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61daa43b6dbf231ea0f69f65/</guid><description>Princess Elisabeth Polar Station implemented strict rules to avoid infections, but at least 16 of its 25 workers have tested positive for COVID, according to a report.
Summary COVID-19: Antarctica research station battling coronavirus outbreak Princess Elisabeth Polar Station implemented strict rules to avoid infections, but at least 16 of its 25 workers have tested positive for COVID, according to a report. Image: Princess Elisabeth is the world&amp;rsquo;s first zero emission polar research station.</description></item></channel></rss>