<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>station on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/station/</link><description>Recent content in station on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:10:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/station/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Woman attacked with hammer in New York subway station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</guid><description>A 57-year-old woman was hit in the head with a hammer several times and robbed in one of the latest violent crimes in a New York subway station, police said.
Highlights The woman&amp;rsquo;s family identified her as Nina Rothschild, a scientist for the New York City Department of Health. She was attacked about 11 p.m. Thursday by a 6-foot tall male wearing a dark jacket, bluejeans and holding a cane, police say.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19: Antarctica research station battling coronavirus outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61daa43b6dbf231ea0f69f65/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 09:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61daa43b6dbf231ea0f69f65/</guid><description>Princess Elisabeth Polar Station implemented strict rules to avoid infections, but at least 16 of its 25 workers have tested positive for COVID, according to a report.
Summary COVID-19: Antarctica research station battling coronavirus outbreak Princess Elisabeth Polar Station implemented strict rules to avoid infections, but at least 16 of its 25 workers have tested positive for COVID, according to a report. Image: Princess Elisabeth is the world&amp;rsquo;s first zero emission polar research station.</description></item></channel></rss>