<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deployment on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deployment/</link><description>Recent content in deployment on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 22:15:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deployment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia warns of nuclear deployment if Sweden and Finland join NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62589cdc4cd9b642eb502347/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 22:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62589cdc4cd9b642eb502347/</guid><description>One of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s closest allies warned NATO on Thursday that if Sweden and Finland joined the U.S.-led military alliance then Russia would deploy nuclear weapons and hypersonic missiles in a European exclave.
Highlights Finland and Sweden are considering joining the NATO alliance. If Sweden and Finland join the U.S.-led military alliance then Russia would deploy nuclear weapons and hypersonic missiles in a European exclave. Russia has the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest arsenal of nuclear warheads and along with China and the United States is one of the global leaders in hypersonics missile technology.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope completes tricky sunshield deployment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d533fe6c4d1903032ea0a1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d533fe6c4d1903032ea0a1/</guid><description>The James Webb Space Telescope has successfully deployed all five layers of its tennis-court-sized sunshield.
Summary The James Webb Space Telescope has successfully deployed all five layers of its tennis-court-sized sunshield, a prerequisite for the telescope&amp;rsquo;s science operations and the most nerve-wracking part of its risky deployment. &amp;ldquo;Yesterday, we did not think we were going to get through the first three layers,&amp;rdquo; Keith Parrish, the observatory manager for the James Webb Space Telescope, said in a live NASA webcast during today&amp;rsquo;s deployment.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Space Telescope begins unfolding delicate, massive sunshield</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc078de752c07dd01092ce/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc078de752c07dd01092ce/</guid><description>NASA&amp;rsquo;s massive new space observatory has entered its most perilous phase yet as it begins the careful process of unfurling its delicate sunshield.
Summary NASA&amp;rsquo;s massive new space observatory has entered its most perilous phase yet as it begins the careful process of unfurling its delicate sunshield. The James Webb Space Telescope launched on Sunday (Dec. 25) and will be a revolutionary new observatory focused on studying the universe in infrared light.</description></item></channel></rss>