<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mastercard on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mastercard/</link><description>Recent content in mastercard on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 05:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mastercard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visa, Mastercard suspend operations in Russia over Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224428465f666ec98c78328/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 05:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224428465f666ec98c78328/</guid><description>U.S. payments firms Visa Inc and Mastercard Inc on Saturday said they were suspending operations in Russia over the invasion of Ukraine, and that they would work with clients and partners to cease all transactions there.
Highlights U.S. payments firms Visa Inc (V.N) and Mastercard Inc on Saturday said they were suspending operations in Russia over the invasion of Ukraine, and that they would work with clients and partners to cease all transactions there.</description></item><item><title>Visa, Mastercard block Russian banks from network</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e7e61917dc355ca3fa331/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e7e61917dc355ca3fa331/</guid><description>Payments News
Highlights Visa and Mastercard have cut Russian financial institutions off from their payments networks. The move was sought by Ukraine National Bank Governor Kyrylo Shevchenko to increase pressure on Vladimir Putin and his regime. The card giants each pledged to donate $2 million for humanitarian assistance to help Ukrainians displaced by the war. The U.N. expects to swell to as many as 5 million people displaced by war, the UN expects to reach 5 million by the end of the year, according to the U.</description></item></channel></rss>