<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>surgery on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/surgery/</link><description>Recent content in surgery on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:43:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/surgery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colorado Supreme Court rules in favor of woman who expected to pay $1,337 for surgery but was charged $303,709</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285929f6952b13c044ee069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285929f6952b13c044ee069/</guid><description>A woman who expected to pay $1,337 for surgery at a Westminster hospital but was billed $303,709 may be off the hook for the massive bill after the Colorado Supreme Court ruled in her favor Monday.
Highlights Lisa French was billed $303,709 for a pair of back surgeries in 2014 at St. Anthony North Health Campus. The Colorado Supreme Court ruled Monday that the contracts she signed with the hospital do not obligate her to pay the hospital’s secretive “chargemaster” price rates.</description></item><item><title>Alabama passes bill making some transgender healthcare a felony</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62505146df7ff676b6db2ea8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62505146df7ff676b6db2ea8/</guid><description>Alabama lawmakers passed a bill on Thursday that would criminalize gender-affirming healthcare for transgender youth, with a threat of 10 years in prison for medical providers.
Highlights The bill would make it a felony punishable with up to 10 years in prison to provide medical care to minors. The bill is the latest in a flurry of measures in Republican-led states dealing with transgender youth. The American Civil Liberties Union called it the first bill of its kind to make healthcare for transgender youth a felony.</description></item><item><title>Wrestling Legend Scott Hal (Razor Ramon) To Be Taken Off Life Support After Suffering Multiple Heart Attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f4d7d6adfb5c6f82aeb79/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f4d7d6adfb5c6f82aeb79/</guid><description>Kevin Nash revealed Sunday night that his long-time partner and best friend, Scott Hall, is being taken off life support.
Highlights Kevin Nash informed Sunday night that his long-time tag partner and best friend, Scott Hall, is being taken off life support. Hall was placed on life support Saturday after enduring three heart attacks. Hall underwent hip surgery last week, but reportedly suffered a setback when a blood clot got loose.</description></item></channel></rss>