<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gay on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gay/</link><description>Recent content in gay on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 19:13:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida students win yearbook flap over "Don't Say Gay" bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c0aad3e9eff1fa90caf41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 19:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c0aad3e9eff1fa90caf41/</guid><description>Students at a central Florida high school are declaring victory after taking their protest to their school board over plans to censor a yearbook page showing a student walkout against the state&amp;rsquo;s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law
Highlights Florida school board overruled superintendent&amp;rsquo;s plan to cover up a yearbook page showing a student walkout. Page showed students waving rainbow flags and a “love is love” sign during a walkout against the state&amp;rsquo;s so-called “Don’t Say Gay” law.</description></item><item><title>Gay parents called 'rapists' and 'pedophiles' in Amtrak incident</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625af97eef317c75de59bb88/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625af97eef317c75de59bb88/</guid><description>Gay parents were called &amp;quot;pedophiles&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;rapists&amp;quot; while riding an Amtrak train on Tuesday, amid a recent uptick in charged rhetoric about LGBTQ issues.
Highlights Robbie Pierce, his husband and their two young children were enjoying a scenic train ride on the Pacific coast. The couple said a man sitting across the aisle turned their family vacation into a nightmare. The man continued to shout at the family of four, yelling, “That’s not a family!</description></item><item><title>Alabama legislature passes 'Don't Say Gay,' trans care and bathroom ban bills</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625060280f64251b5da48776/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625060280f64251b5da48776/</guid><description>Two bills targeting the LGBTQ community passed on Thursday.
Highlights Two bills targeting the LGBTQ community passed on Thursday. SB 184, the Vulnerable Child Protection Act, would ban gender-affirming care to minors under 18. HB 322 would ban trans students from using bathrooms and locker rooms that align with their gender identity. The Trevor Project has condemned the passage of such bills as an attack on bodily autonomy for trans youth and their families.</description></item><item><title>Gay men still face hurdles to donate blood amid national shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0e753f686cffe716fcdac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0e753f686cffe716fcdac/</guid><description>Gay and bisexual men are still restricted from giving blood, in a move that LGBTQ activists call discriminatory.
Summary The U.S. is facing a national blood crisis, the &amp;ldquo;worst blood shortage in over a decade,&amp;rdquo; the American Red Cross warns. Despite this urgent need for donations, people who have sex with gay or bisexual men are still facing restrictions on their ability to give blood. The agency changed the deferral period from 12 months to three months in November 2020 as blood donations fell and hospitals faced critical shortages during the first year of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>