<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cnn on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cnn/</link><description>Recent content in cnn on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:13:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cnn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida appeals court overturns conviction of Miami police officer who shot autistic man's caretaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</guid><description>A South Florida appeals court Wednesday overturned the conviction of a former North Miami Police Department officer who was found guilty of negligence for shooting an autistic man&amp;rsquo;s caretaker in 2016, court documents show.
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal overturned a &amp;ldquo;conviction for misdemeanor culpable negligence&amp;rdquo; for Jonathan Aledda. Florida State Attorney Katherine Fernandez Rundle said the decision is &amp;ldquo;disappointing to all who believed that this shooting incident was unnecessary and incorrect&amp;rdquo; In July 2016, officers encountered Arnaldo Rios-Soto, a man with severe developmental disabilities, and his caretaker Charles Kinsey in the middle of an intersection, court documents show.</description></item><item><title>White father and son charged for chasing and shooting at Black FedEx driver</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 07:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</guid><description>Two White men are facing criminal charges after a Black FedEx Express driver alleged that he was chased and shot at while delivering packages in Brookhaven, Mississippi.
Highlights D&amp;rsquo;Monterrio Gibson, 24, says he was delivering packages to a home when he was shot at. He says he heard &amp;ldquo;at least five shots and heard the bullets hitting the van,&amp;rdquo; police report says. Two men have been charged with conspiracy and shooting into a vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Virginia family gets keys to Habitat for Humanity's first 3D-printed home in the US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca4594ec17f800508a266c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca4594ec17f800508a266c/</guid><description>Christmas came early for one Virginia family that just received the keys to their new 3D-printed home.
Summary (CNN) One Virginia family received the keys to their new 3D-printed home in time for Christmas. The home is Habitat for Humanity&amp;rsquo;s first 3D-printed home in the nation, according to a Habitat news release. Janet V. Green, CEO of Habitat for Humanity Peninsula and Greater Williamsburg, told CNN it partnered with Alquist , a 3D printing company, earlier this year to begin the process.</description></item></channel></rss>