<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cnn on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cnn/</link><description>Recent content in cnn on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 23:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cnn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CNN reporter threatened with trespassing after grilling Uvalde police chief over his actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629943361042e4a25eada900/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629943361042e4a25eada900/</guid><description>Shimon Prokupecz had earlier been grilling police chief Pedro Arredondo about his actions during the Uvalde shooting
Highlights CNN reporter was threatened with charges of trespassing if he and his crew didn’t leave the school district’s offices. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Simon Prokupecz shared a video of a confrontation with Uvalde Police Chief Pedro “Pete” Arredondo outside the school building where he had retreated behind earlier. The Texas Department of Public Safety maintains that the chief of the school police chief is not cooperating with investigators.</description></item><item><title>Israeli police beat mourners with batons at funeral procession for veteran journalist</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e85116c341496d719ec59/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e85116c341496d719ec59/</guid><description>Mourners flocked to Jerusalem&amp;rsquo;s streets on Friday to attend the burial of veteran Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh, who was shot dead on Wednesday while reporting on a military raid in the West Bank city of Jenin, and were met with violence by Israeli police as they tried to carry the coffin on foot. The funeral was taking place a day after a memorial procession that brought thousands to the West Bank city of Ramallah.</description></item><item><title>Mexican truck drivers block major US-Mexico point of entry in protest of Texas border inspections</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625542b6d80e5885a05d543f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 09:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625542b6d80e5885a05d543f/</guid><description>Commercial traffic at Pharr-Reynosa International Bridge &amp;ndash; a major port of entry for the US-Mexico border that handles both commercial and passenger vehicles &amp;ndash; is &amp;quot;halted temporarily&amp;quot; due to an ongoing protest on the Mexican side of the border and there are &amp;quot;no southbound movements by US carriers,&amp;quot; a US Customs and Border Protection official confirmed to CNN Monday.
Highlights Commercial traffic at a major port of entry for the US-Mexico border is &amp;ldquo;halted temporarily&amp;rdquo; There are &amp;ldquo;no southbound movements by US carriers,&amp;rdquo; a US Customs and Border Protection official said.</description></item><item><title>Denmark opens its arms to Ukrainians, while trying to send Syrian refugees home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a9d339dbd4509149ed748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:52:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a9d339dbd4509149ed748/</guid><description>When Denmark became the first liberal democracy to tell Syrian refugees to return to their war-torn home in 2019, Russian jets were still dropping missiles in Syria, in an effort to help President Bashar al-Assad&amp;rsquo;s regime regain control of the country.
Highlights Denmark is drafting legislation that will suspend asylum rules for Ukrainians. The move would allow Ukrainians to enter the EU without a visa and to choose which country to go to.</description></item><item><title>Florida appeals court overturns conviction of Miami police officer who shot autistic man's caretaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</guid><description>A South Florida appeals court Wednesday overturned the conviction of a former North Miami Police Department officer who was found guilty of negligence for shooting an autistic man&amp;rsquo;s caretaker in 2016, court documents show.
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal overturned a &amp;ldquo;conviction for misdemeanor culpable negligence&amp;rdquo; for Jonathan Aledda. Florida State Attorney Katherine Fernandez Rundle said the decision is &amp;ldquo;disappointing to all who believed that this shooting incident was unnecessary and incorrect&amp;rdquo; In July 2016, officers encountered Arnaldo Rios-Soto, a man with severe developmental disabilities, and his caretaker Charles Kinsey in the middle of an intersection, court documents show.</description></item><item><title>White father and son charged for chasing and shooting at Black FedEx driver</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 07:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62075d7d8553334cccdefaab/</guid><description>Two White men are facing criminal charges after a Black FedEx Express driver alleged that he was chased and shot at while delivering packages in Brookhaven, Mississippi.
Highlights D&amp;rsquo;Monterrio Gibson, 24, says he was delivering packages to a home when he was shot at. He says he heard &amp;ldquo;at least five shots and heard the bullets hitting the van,&amp;rdquo; police report says. Two men have been charged with conspiracy and shooting into a vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Virginia family gets keys to Habitat for Humanity's first 3D-printed home in the US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca4594ec17f800508a266c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca4594ec17f800508a266c/</guid><description>Christmas came early for one Virginia family that just received the keys to their new 3D-printed home.
Summary (CNN) One Virginia family received the keys to their new 3D-printed home in time for Christmas. The home is Habitat for Humanity&amp;rsquo;s first 3D-printed home in the nation, according to a Habitat news release. Janet V. Green, CEO of Habitat for Humanity Peninsula and Greater Williamsburg, told CNN it partnered with Alquist , a 3D printing company, earlier this year to begin the process.</description></item></channel></rss>