<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sullivan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sullivan/</link><description>Recent content in sullivan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 09:14:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sullivan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet troll faces trial after Capitol riot plea fizzles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628215e80b4a877dec42b83c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628215e80b4a877dec42b83c/</guid><description>A federal judge scheduled a trial next year for a far-right internet troll after the man, known to his social media followers as “Baked Alaska,” balked at pleading guilty on Wednesday to a criminal charge stemming from the U.S.
Highlights U.S. District Judge Emmet Sullivan refused to accept a guilty plea by Anthime Gionet after he professed his innocence at the start of what was scheduled to be a plea agreement hearing.</description></item><item><title>US intelligence indicates Russia preparing operation to justify invasion of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1ba4a8dd513471b08f5be/</guid><description>The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.
Summary Washington (CNN) The US has information that indicates Russia has prepositioned a group of operatives to conduct a false-flag operation in eastern Ukraine, a US official told CNN on Friday, in an attempt to create a pretext for an invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>