<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>offers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/offers/</link><description>Recent content in offers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 18:18:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/offers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia offers ceasefire for civilians to leave Azovstal plant in Mariupol, says defense ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266e5e84fc5fab4d47612b1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 18:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266e5e84fc5fab4d47612b1/</guid><description>Russia’s Ministry of Defense has offered to cease all hostilities around the Azovstal steel plant in besieged Mariupol to allow civilians to leave “in any direction they choose.”
Highlights Russian government says it will allow civilians to leave in any direction they choose. Government says it has set up a round-the-clock humanitarian corridor for civilians. U.S. officials have said Russia has repeatedly broken its pledge to allow civilian access to the Azovstal factory in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk offers to buy Twitter for $54.20 a share, saying it needs to be 'transformed as private company'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258495c129f5f7553cb4782/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 16:19:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258495c129f5f7553cb4782/</guid><description>Elon Musk offered to buy Twitter for $54.20 a share, saying the social media company needs to be transformed privately.
Highlights Elon Musk offers to buy Twitter for $54.20 a share in a filing published Thursday. Musk&amp;rsquo;s offer values Twitter at about $43 billion. Twitter shares were up about 4% Thursday morning after closing at $45.85 a share on Wednesday. Musk first disclosed his 9.2% stake in Twitter on April 4.</description></item></channel></rss>