<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2021 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2021/</link><description>Recent content in 2021 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Proud Boys leader Tarrio loses latest bid for release from jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62923b3af82ddfc2a1be7cef/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62923b3af82ddfc2a1be7cef/</guid><description>A judge has denied the latest request by Enrique Tarrio, the former top leader of the right-wing group the Proud Boys, for release from jail while he awaits trial on criminal charges relating to last year&amp;rsquo;s attack on the U.S. Capitol.
Highlights Enrique Tarrio, the former top leader of the right-wing group the Proud Boys, has been held in jail since September 2021. He is among the most high-profile of more than 775 people criminally charged for their roles in the assault on the Capitol by supporters of then-President Donald Trump in an effort to keep Congress from certifying Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s election victory.</description></item><item><title>Amazon stock plunges as company reports nearly $4B loss</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c7155b26c0c1c39632df9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 23:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c7155b26c0c1c39632df9/</guid><description>Amazon&amp;rsquo;s stock plummeted after the company reported on Thursday slowing growth and higher costs in its latest quarter and offered a disappointing revenue outlook.
Highlights Amazon reported a net loss of $3.8 billion for the quarter ended March 31, a sharp drop from the same period last year. It was also a big miss from the $4.4 billion profit that analysts surveyed by Refinitiv had forecast. The tech giant attributed the loss largely to a $7.</description></item><item><title>U.S. FAA to make zero tolerance unruly passenger policy permanent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626069ddb3d32695c645e680/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 20:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626069ddb3d32695c645e680/</guid><description>The Federal Aviation Administration&amp;rsquo;s (FAA) &amp;quot;zero-tolerance policy&amp;quot; for addressing unruly passengers will become permanent even after a court ended transportation mask requirements, the agency said on Wednesday.
Highlights Federal Aviation Administration&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;zero-tolerance policy&amp;rdquo; for addressing unruly passengers will become permanent even after a court ended transportation mask requirements. A federal judge on Monday struck the down the 14-month-old transportation mask policy. Under the policy, the FAA issues fines to passengers for unruly behavior instead of warning letters or counseling.</description></item><item><title>Report: Conspiracy theorists fuel bump in extremist killings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c5b98a8f37f34ce6be996/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 02:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c5b98a8f37f34ce6be996/</guid><description>Newer strains of far-right movements fueled by conspiracy theories, misogyny and anti-vaccine proponents contributed to a modest rise in killings by domestic extremists in the United States last year, according to a report released Tuesday by a Jewish civil rights group.
Highlights Killings by domestic extremists increased from 23 in 2020 to at least 29 last year, with right-wing extremists killing 26 of those people in 2021, the Anti-Defamation League said in a report first provided to The Associated Press.</description></item><item><title>Wholesale prices jumped 9.7% , setting record for 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e13bc6a4746d73025930f5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e13bc6a4746d73025930f5/</guid><description>Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.7% for all of 2021, setting an annual record and providing further evidence that inflation is still present at all levels of the U.S. economy
Summary Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.7% for all of 2021, setting an annual record and providing further evidence that inflation is still present at all levels of the U.S. economyWASHINGTON &amp;ndash; Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.</description></item><item><title>Tim Cook earned over 1,400 times the average Apple worker in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d960bd299b7b512d0f9cfe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d960bd299b7b512d0f9cfe/</guid><description>Apple Inc boss Tim Cook&amp;rsquo;s pay in 2021 was 1,447 times that of the average employee at the tech giant, a filing on Thursday showed, fueled by stock awards that helped him earn a total of nearly $100 million.
Summary Apple CEO Tim Cook attends the premiere for season two of the television series &amp;ldquo;Ted Lasso&amp;rdquo; at Pacific Design Center in West Hollywood, California, U.S. July 15, 2021. In 2021, the median pay for employees was $68,254, Apple said, adding it had selected a new median employee for comparison due to changes in hiring and compensation.</description></item></channel></rss>