<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hospital on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hospital/</link><description>Recent content in hospital on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hospital/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pregnant woman, baby die after Russia bombed maternity ward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</guid><description>MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned. Images of the woman being rushed to an ambulance on a stretcher had circled the world, epitomizing the horror of an attack on humanity’s most innocent.
Highlights A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned.</description></item><item><title>US man who got 1st pig heart transplant dies after 2 months</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228e086c5d6a1a2c0f17cd9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228e086c5d6a1a2c0f17cd9/</guid><description>The first person to receive a heart transplant from a pig has died, two months after the groundbreaking experiment, the Maryland hospital that performed the surgery announced Wednesday. David Bennett, 57, died Tuesday at the University of Maryland Medical Center.
Highlights David Bennett, 57, died Tuesday at the University of Maryland Medical Center. Doctors didn’t give an exact cause of death, saying only that his condition had begun deteriorating several days earlier.</description></item><item><title>Suicide bombing at Pakistan mosque kills at least 56, injures nearly 200</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62229cf23a51adcc5be8e478/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 23:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62229cf23a51adcc5be8e478/</guid><description>A suicide bomber struck inside a Shia Muslim mosque in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s northwestern city of Peshawar during Friday prayers, killing at least 56 worshippers and wounding 194 people, hospital officials said.
Highlights A suicide bomber strikes inside a Shia Muslim mosque in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s northwestern city of Peshawar during Friday prayers, killing at least 56 worshippers and wounding 194 people. No militant group immediately claimed responsibility for the attack. Both the Islamic State group and the Pakistani Taliban — a militant group separate from the Taliban in Afghanistan — have carried out similar attacks in the past in the area.</description></item><item><title>Polish state has ‘blood on its hands’ after death of woman refused an abortion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</guid><description>Family says young mother’s health deteriorated rapidly after the twins she was carrying died a week apart in the womb
Summary The family of a Polish woman who died on Tuesday after doctors refused to perform an abortion when the foetus’s heart stopped beating have accused the government of having “blood on their hands”. Her death comes a year after Poland introduced one of the most restrictive abortion laws in Europe.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 patient whose family sued to keep him on ventilator dies after transfer from Mercy Hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 07:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</guid><description>Scott Quiner, a COVID-19 patient from Buffalo, Minnesota, whose wife sued Mercy Hospital in Coon Rapids to keep him on a ventilator, died Saturday morning at a Texas hospital, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney confirmed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;On behalf of the family of Scott Quiner, I would like to thank the public for the outpouring of love and support during this difficult time,&amp;rdquo; Holsten said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;The family now requests privacy while they grieve the loss of their beloved husband and father.</description></item></channel></rss>