<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hospital on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hospital/</link><description>Recent content in hospital on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 11:10:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hospital/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hinckley, who shot Reagan in 1981, granted full freedom</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62989a5e0d1e3dc84e8f576b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 11:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62989a5e0d1e3dc84e8f576b/</guid><description>A federal judge on Wednesday granted John Hinckley, the man who shot and wounded President Ronald Reagan and three others in a 1981 assassination attempt, unconditional release from the remaining restrictions he faced, U.S. media reported.
Highlights John Hinckley Jr. shot and wounded President Ronald Reagan and three others in 1981 assassination attempt. Judge lifts travel and internet usage restrictions against Hinckleys, who has been living on his own in Virginia.</description></item><item><title>Wray: FBI blocked planned cyberattack on children's hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62987e5a543e99ca166906d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62987e5a543e99ca166906d3/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The FBI thwarted a planned cyberattack on a children&amp;rsquo;s hospital in Boston that was to have been carried out by hackers sponsored by the Iranian government, FBI Director Christopher Wray said Wednesday.
Highlights FBI Director Christopher Wray says his agents thwarted a planned cyberattack on a Boston children&amp;rsquo;s hospital that was to have been carried out by hackers sponsored by the Iranian government. Wray told a Boston College cybersecurity conference that his agents learned of the planned digital attack from an unspecified intelligence partner and got Boston Children’s Hospital the information it needed last summer to block what would have been “one of the most despicable cyberattacks I’ve seen” The speech took place as the FBI continues to combat ransomware attacks from criminal gangs, a continuing concern for U.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Supreme Court rules in favor of woman who expected to pay $1,337 for surgery but was charged $303,709</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285929f6952b13c044ee069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285929f6952b13c044ee069/</guid><description>A woman who expected to pay $1,337 for surgery at a Westminster hospital but was billed $303,709 may be off the hook for the massive bill after the Colorado Supreme Court ruled in her favor Monday.
Highlights Lisa French was billed $303,709 for a pair of back surgeries in 2014 at St. Anthony North Health Campus. The Colorado Supreme Court ruled Monday that the contracts she signed with the hospital do not obligate her to pay the hospital’s secretive “chargemaster” price rates.</description></item><item><title>DA moves to dismiss a murder charge against a Texas woman accused of a self-induced abortion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625348226b2f2c5c1dfc592f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 21:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625348226b2f2c5c1dfc592f/</guid><description>Lizelle Herrera, 26, was released from custody Saturday night on $500,000 bond. Then, on Sunday, the DA said the Starr County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Department &amp;quot;did their duty in investigating the incident brought to their attention by the reporting hospital.&amp;quot; However, he said that this is not a criminal matter under Texas law.
Highlights Lizelle Herrera, 26, was arrested Thursday and held on $500,000 bond. She was released from custody Saturday night after an abortion rights advocacy fund posted bail on her behalf.</description></item><item><title>Four people are dead after a driver crashed a vehicle into Salem, Oregon, encampment of unhoused people</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62409b5406eaa744d5558b60/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 17:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62409b5406eaa744d5558b60/</guid><description>Four people died early Sunday morning after a motorist crashed a vehicle into an encampment of unhoused people in Salem, Oregon, according to a news release from the Salem Police Department.
Highlights Two people died at the scene of the crash, while two others died after being taken to a hospital, police say. The driver of the vehicle was also taken by ambulance to hospital. Road closures will remain in effect Sunday morning while the incident is investigated, police said.</description></item><item><title>Pregnant woman, baby die after Russia bombed maternity ward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</guid><description>MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned. Images of the woman being rushed to an ambulance on a stretcher had circled the world, epitomizing the horror of an attack on humanity’s most innocent.
Highlights A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned.</description></item><item><title>US man who got 1st pig heart transplant dies after 2 months</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228e086c5d6a1a2c0f17cd9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228e086c5d6a1a2c0f17cd9/</guid><description>The first person to receive a heart transplant from a pig has died, two months after the groundbreaking experiment, the Maryland hospital that performed the surgery announced Wednesday. David Bennett, 57, died Tuesday at the University of Maryland Medical Center.
Highlights David Bennett, 57, died Tuesday at the University of Maryland Medical Center. Doctors didn’t give an exact cause of death, saying only that his condition had begun deteriorating several days earlier.</description></item><item><title>Suicide bombing at Pakistan mosque kills at least 56, injures nearly 200</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62229cf23a51adcc5be8e478/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 23:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62229cf23a51adcc5be8e478/</guid><description>A suicide bomber struck inside a Shia Muslim mosque in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s northwestern city of Peshawar during Friday prayers, killing at least 56 worshippers and wounding 194 people, hospital officials said.
Highlights A suicide bomber strikes inside a Shia Muslim mosque in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s northwestern city of Peshawar during Friday prayers, killing at least 56 worshippers and wounding 194 people. No militant group immediately claimed responsibility for the attack. Both the Islamic State group and the Pakistani Taliban — a militant group separate from the Taliban in Afghanistan — have carried out similar attacks in the past in the area.</description></item><item><title>Polish state has ‘blood on its hands’ after death of woman refused an abortion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</guid><description>Family says young mother’s health deteriorated rapidly after the twins she was carrying died a week apart in the womb
Summary The family of a Polish woman who died on Tuesday after doctors refused to perform an abortion when the foetus’s heart stopped beating have accused the government of having “blood on their hands”. Her death comes a year after Poland introduced one of the most restrictive abortion laws in Europe.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 patient whose family sued to keep him on ventilator dies after transfer from Mercy Hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 07:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</guid><description>Scott Quiner, a COVID-19 patient from Buffalo, Minnesota, whose wife sued Mercy Hospital in Coon Rapids to keep him on a ventilator, died Saturday morning at a Texas hospital, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney confirmed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;On behalf of the family of Scott Quiner, I would like to thank the public for the outpouring of love and support during this difficult time,&amp;rdquo; Holsten said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;The family now requests privacy while they grieve the loss of their beloved husband and father.</description></item></channel></rss>