<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>axios on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/axios/</link><description>Recent content in axios on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/axios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EA Sports to remove Russian teams from FIFA, NHL video games</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ff9edef7727f2e5a706f7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ff9edef7727f2e5a706f7/</guid><description>EA sports wrote the move is &amp;quot;in line with our partners at FIFA and UEFA[.]&amp;quot;
Highlights Russian and Belarusian hockey teams have been removed from all international competitions. The International Ice Hockey Federation has also banned Russia and Belarus from international games. EA Sports said the move is &amp;ldquo;in line with the decision to remove the Russian national team from the latest FIFA video game franchise. The decision was made by the International Hockey Federation, the European Union and the Russian Federation of Hockey Hockey Federation.</description></item><item><title>Crypto exchanges resist call to block Russian users</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ea87bda4813d65713911d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 23:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ea87bda4813d65713911d/</guid><description>Some large exchanges have said blanket bans on Russia-based addresses would unfairly hurt innocent Russians.
Highlights Binance, Kraken and Kraken have said they will comply with U.S. sanctions. Some exchanges say blanket bans on Russia-based addresses would unfairly hurt innocent Russians. Some experts say the focus on crypto as a platform for sanctions evasion is misguided. Still, the markets are not big enough to absorb sanctions-abating levels of currency, says Chainalysis&amp;rsquo; co-head of public policy at Chainalysis.</description></item></channel></rss>