<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>record on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/record/</link><description>Recent content in record on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 09:14:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/record/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meet the 100-year-old man who's worked at the same company for 84 years - CNN Video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280c46bb9b8d88818db4bc7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 09:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280c46bb9b8d88818db4bc7/</guid><description>Walter Orthmann holds the Guinness World Record for longest time spent at a single company. Just how long? 84 years. The 100-year-old Brazilian shares his advice for making your career a lifelong pursuit of happiness.
Highlights Walter Orthmann holds the Guinness World Record for longest time spent at a single company. The 100-year-old Brazilian shares his advice for making your career a lifelong pursuit of happiness. The World Record holder holds the world record for most time spent working at one company in 84 years.</description></item><item><title>Sherpa woman (Lakpa Sherpa) climbs Everest for 10th time, breaks own record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627db06c126e70f21580aac6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 01:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627db06c126e70f21580aac6/</guid><description>A Nepali Sherpa broke her own record as the most successful female climber of Mount Everest by reaching the summit of the world’s highest peak Thursday
Highlights A Nepali Sherpa broke her own record as the most successful female climber of Mount Everest. Lakpa Sherpa and several other climbers took advantage of favorable weather to reach the 8,849-meter (29,032-foot) summit. The 48-year-old Sherpa, 48, never got a chance to get a formal education because she had to start earning a living by carrying climbing gear and supplies for trekkers.</description></item><item><title>Erriyon Knighton, teen who broke Usain Bolt junior records, shatters another</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626eb2caa93a3e4dde8643fb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626eb2caa93a3e4dde8643fb/</guid><description>Erriyon Knighton, who last year at age 17 broke Usain Bolt junior sprint records, shattered his own U20 record in the 200m.
Highlights Erriyon Knighton broke Usain Bolt junior sprint records last year at age 17. Knighton clocked 19.49 seconds in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, the world’s fastest time since the 2012 Olympics. His time is the second-fastest 200m ever recorded by an American after Michael Johnson&amp;rsquo;s then-world record 19.32 at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana girl, 4, dies after grandmother allegedly forced her to drink bottle of whiskey</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62640952c85330f1c8831916/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62640952c85330f1c8831916/</guid><description>A Louisiana child died after the girl’s grandmother forced her to drink a bottle of whiskey while her mother watched, authorities said Friday.
Highlights China Record, 4, was found with a blood alcohol level of.68 after officers were dispatched to a home east of Baton Rouge on Thursday morning. She was forced to drink half a bottle of whiskey while her mother watched, police said. Her cause of death was acute alcohol poisoning, the East Baton Rouge Coroner’s Office said.</description></item><item><title>Americans suffer deadly fentanyl overdoses in record numbers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fcec34e067375c511eb55/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 09:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fcec34e067375c511eb55/</guid><description>Families in Nashville learn the deadly reality of fentanyl after child suffers fatal overdose.
Highlights In the first 18 months of the COVID-19 pandemic, a record number of Americans died from drug overdoses. Most of the deaths involve the potent drug fentanyl, which is 50 to 100 times more potent than morphine. Fentanyl-related fatalities began to skyrocket nationwide after drug dealers and cartels began to lace the chemical into drugs that they were already selling, often targeting addicted users looking for a more powerful high.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war pushes world food prices to record high</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252923055fd8134934d1105/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252923055fd8134934d1105/</guid><description>Ukraine war pushes world food prices to record high
Highlights Food and Agriculture Organization says world food prices hit an all-time high in March following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The disruption in export flows resulting from the Feb, 24 invasion and international sanctions against Russia has spurred fears of a global hunger crisis. Russia and Ukraine account for a huge share of the globe&amp;rsquo;s exports in several major commodities, including wheat, vegetable oil and corn.</description></item><item><title>Shanghai Disney closes as city sees record surge in Covid cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238a77af0e46b8b5fcb6be2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 16:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238a77af0e46b8b5fcb6be2/</guid><description>China&amp;rsquo;s financial hub of Shanghai reported on Monday a record daily surge in local Covid-19 infections as authorities scrambled to test residents and rein in the Omicron variant, while closing its Disney resort until further notice.
Highlights Shanghai reported 24 new domestically transmitted Covid cases with confirmed symptoms for Sunday. It is the fourth consecutive day that Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s local asymptomatic infections have increased. Authorities scrambled to test residents and rein in the Omicron variant, while closing its Disney resort until further notice.</description></item><item><title>Two lawmakers want Hertz, Avis to answer questions on rising U.S. rental prices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235ca668898d3c1600dbc13/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 12:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235ca668898d3c1600dbc13/</guid><description>Two U.S. House Democratic lawmakers on Friday asked Hertz Global Holdings, and Avis Budget Group to answer questions about rising rental car prices and higher industry profits.
Highlights Two U.S. House Democratic lawmakers on Friday asked Hertz Global Holdings, (HTZ.O) and Avis Budget Group to answer questions about rising rental car prices and higher industry profits. The lawmakers want documents and information by April 1. Hertz posted a record adjusted profit in the fourth quarter as demand for rental cars remained strong, but post-bankruptcy restructuring costs yielded a large net loss.</description></item><item><title>Food prices jump 24.1% yr/yr to hit record high in Feb, U.N. agency says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622329518e54682d0b087443/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 09:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622329518e54682d0b087443/</guid><description>World food prices hit a record high in February, led by a surge in vegetable oils and dairy products, to post a 24.1% increase year-on-year, the U.N. food agency said on Friday.
Highlights Food and Agriculture Organization&amp;rsquo;s food price index, which tracks most globally traded food commodities, averaged 140.7 points last month. Food prices have contributed to a broader surge in inflation as economies recover from coronavirus crisis. FAO economist Upali Galketi Aratchilage said concerns over crop conditions and export availabilities provided only a partial explanation to the increase in global food prices.</description></item><item><title>The number of U.S. cities with an average home price of $1 million tripled last year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62173e7300a4427f77836404/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62173e7300a4427f77836404/</guid><description>With the average price of a home up 19.6% last year, 146 new &amp;quot;million-dollar cities&amp;quot; were added in 2021 — the most ever in one year.
Highlights 146 new million-dollar cities were added in 2021, bringing the total number to a new record of 481. California, Massachusetts and New York added the most new cities with average home values above $1 million. The median price of a home in the U.</description></item><item><title>Record 88% of Japanese 'feel friendly' toward U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef83f6a756a360bf0e8e5d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 05:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef83f6a756a360bf0e8e5d/</guid><description>The percentage of Japanese who &amp;quot;feel friendly&amp;quot; toward the United States increased to an all-time high of 88.5 percent, a Japanese government poll showed Friday, reflecting strengthened ties between the allies in such areas as security and the economy. The figure is up 4.5 percentage points from the previous survey…
Summary The percentage of Japanese who &amp;ldquo;feel friendly&amp;rdquo; toward the United States increased to an all-time high of 88.5 percent, a Japanese government poll showed Friday, reflecting strengthened ties between the allies in such areas as security and the economy.</description></item><item><title>U.S. reports at least 1.1 million COVID cases in a day, shattering global record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd8d8991e65330abc578a1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd8d8991e65330abc578a1/</guid><description>The United States reported 1.35 million new coronavirus infections on Monday, according to a Reuters tally, the highest daily total for any country in the world as the spread of the highly contagious Omicron variant showed no signs of slowing.
Summary The previous record was 1.03 million cases on Jan. 3. A large number of cases are reported each Monday due to many states not reporting over the weekend. The seven-day average for new cases has tripled in two weeks to over 700,000 new infections a day.</description></item><item><title>Astronomers spot dying star just before it explodes and record supernova | Science &amp;amp; Tech News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d89bec6d2f6425886fb36c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d89bec6d2f6425886fb36c/</guid><description>The discovery reveals new details about how red supergiants evolve just before going supernova, potentially allowing astronomers to detect them in the future.
Summary Astronomers have for the first time imaged the last moments in the life of a red supergiant star. &amp;ldquo;This is a breakthrough in our understanding of what massive stars do moments before they die,&amp;rdquo; said Dr Wynn Jacobson-Galán, lead author of the study. &amp;ldquo;Direct detection of pre-supernova activity in a red supergiant star has never been observed before in an ordinary Type II supernova.</description></item><item><title>A record 4.5 million Americans quit their jobs in November</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4c3878b869f089772879c/</guid><description>A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.
Summary New York (CNN Business) A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics. This pushed the quits rate to 3%, matching the high from September. Workers were most likely to quit their jobs in the hospitality industry, which had by far the highest quits rate at 6.</description></item><item><title>Wearing masks outdoors mandatory in Paris starting Friday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8066c775ab3f79990e35/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8066c775ab3f79990e35/</guid><description>Wearing masks even outdoors will be mandatory in Paris starting on Friday, French authorities have announced, as the country struggles to come to grips with an Omicron surge. France is leading Europe…
Summary People wearing face masks walk on the Palais Royal grounds in Paris on January 16, 2021Wearing masks even outdoors will be mandatory in Paris starting on Friday, French authorities have announced, as the country struggles to come to grips with an Omicron surge.</description></item><item><title>Florida reports 46,923 new coronavirus cases, shattering state daily record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd6722f3238650c09f2f4f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd6722f3238650c09f2f4f/</guid><description>Florida&amp;rsquo;s 46,923 new daily coronavirus cases shattered the state record for residents and became the third state in the nation to pass 4 million infections, according to data submitted to the Centers for Disease Control. Also, hospitalizations have risen to 3,836, the highest in 2 1/2 months.
Summary The first cases were reported in Florida on March 1, 2020. Twice week a CDC revises new daily cases in data provided by the state.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong police seize record 1.2 tonnes of ketamine worth HK $ 840 million in biggest single bust , 4 arrested in raid on pier</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8757dd8712ba5f5cc65b2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8757dd8712ba5f5cc65b2/</guid><description>Four suspects, aged 32 to 47, detained at Sam Ka Tsuen Ferry Pier in Yau Tong on Thursday morning.
Summary Police seized more than a tonne of ketamine in a single operation. Photo: Xiaomei Chen READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>