<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lawyers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawyers/</link><description>Recent content in lawyers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:14:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawyers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cardi B wins order forcing YouTuber to remove defamatory videos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ccd42136da741d067a3eb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ccd42136da741d067a3eb/</guid><description>A judge has ordered Latasha Kebe, known as Tasha K, to to delete and never repost defamatory videos.
Highlights Latasha Kebe, known as Tasha K, has been ordered to delete and never repost defamatory videos. Lawyers for the singer said Kebe had waged &amp;ldquo;a campaign to damage and destroy [Cardi B&amp;rsquo;s] reputation among her fans and the consuming public&amp;rdquo; The judge has ordered Kebe to delete the videos and never re-post them again.</description></item><item><title>Judge says Prince Andrew cannot block lawsuit from accuser Virginia Giuffre on grounds she no longer lives in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1f65925409083e7270f82/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1f65925409083e7270f82/</guid><description>The written order comes three days before the release of details of a 2009 settlement agreement between Jeffrey Epstein and Virginia Giuffre - an agreement lawyers for the Duke of York say protects him from claims such as those brought by Ms Giuffre.
Summary Ms Giuffre alleges she was abused by the prince multiple times in 2001, while she was being sexually assaulted by financier Jeffrey Epstein. The written order was filed three days before the release of details of a 2009 settlement agreement between Epstein and Ms Giuffre.</description></item><item><title>Judge slaps down attempt to halt Prince Andrew's sexual assault case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0f92f04a163ebd72ac347/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0f92f04a163ebd72ac347/</guid><description>A JUDGE in the US has denied a motion from lawyers for the Duke of York to halt proceedings in a civil lawsuit against Prince Andrew while an issue…
Summary A JUDGE in the US has denied a motion from lawyers for the Duke of York to halt proceedings in a civil lawsuit against Prince Andrew while an issue of where his accuser lives is dealt with. Earlier this week Andrew’s lawyers had called for the case against the royal in the US to be stopped because Virginia Giuffre is “actually domiciled in Australia”.</description></item></channel></rss>