<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arm on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arm/</link><description>Recent content in arm on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 21:14:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4 teens accused of dragging woman to death plead not guilty - ABC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62743e000aad08cf5899be0a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 21:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62743e000aad08cf5899be0a/</guid><description>Four teens accused in the dragging death of an elderly New Orleans woman whose arm was severed during a carjacking have pleaded not guilty
Highlights Four teens charged with murder in the dragging death of an elderly New Orleans woman whose arm was severed during a carjacking have pleaded not guilty. Linda Frickey, 73, died after she became entangled in a seatbelt as carjackers sped away with her vehicle that day.</description></item><item><title>Worker lost arm from injury at U.S. mail facility in North Carolina, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623092ac3e2f303de2035120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 13:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623092ac3e2f303de2035120/</guid><description>The arm of a mechanic working at a U.S. mail facility in North Carolina was amputated last year after coming into contact with a machine that had a safety guard removed, the U.S. Labor Department has found.
Highlights Inspection identified ‘repeat and serious safety violations’ at facility in Greensboro, North Carolina. Facility failed to train staff on working near conveyors or proper methods for safely operating equipment, agency says. Facility allowed workers without adequate training and protective equipment to perform tests on live electrical equipment.</description></item></channel></rss>