<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>president on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/president/</link><description>Recent content in president on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 10:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/president/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge dismisses Trump federal lawsuit against New York Attorney General Letitia James over her probe of business</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291f4fcc416c3706ecde433/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291f4fcc416c3706ecde433/</guid><description>Ex-President Donald Trump and his company are being investigated by New York Attorney General Letitia James over valuations of real estate assets.
Highlights A federal judge dismissed a federal lawsuit by former President Donald Trump that sought to bar a civil investigation of his business by New York Attorney General Letitia James. The ruling by U.S. District Judge Brenda Sannes came a day after a state appeals court in New York upheld subpoenas issued by James compelling Trump and two of his adult children to appear for questioning under oath as part of her probe.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan to hold constitutional referendum that strips Nazarbayev's immunity and restricts power of president in the government</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ce73282833d835f2a2e57/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 14:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ce73282833d835f2a2e57/</guid><description>On June 5, Kazakhs will vote on a package of reforms intended to transform the country from a super-presidential system to a “presidential system with a strong parliament.”
Highlights Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s president Kassym-Jomart Tokayev called protesters terrorists and requested support from the Russian-backed Collective Security Treaty Organization to quell mass unrest. The vote will take place on June 5, just one month after the proposed reforms were released. The reform package addresses 33 separate articles – about one third of the total constitutional articles – and was developed by a working group.</description></item><item><title>School assignment shows Obama next to primates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889026cb459cedada18ccd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 07:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889026cb459cedada18ccd/</guid><description>The Oakland County, Michigan, school&amp;rsquo;s director of diversity described her reaction and response to the assignment that included the former president&amp;rsquo;s photo.
Highlights The Roeper School in Michigan is on leave after the assignment included the former president&amp;rsquo;s photo. The assignment asked, “Which of the following are primates?” Many parents and students were offended by the assignment. The school did not hold classes Thursday; police were stationed outside due to threats made online.</description></item><item><title>Judge finds Trump in contempt in legal fight with NY AG</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266f252cb0340c9aba0614b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 19:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266f252cb0340c9aba0614b/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A New York judge found former President Donald Trump in contempt of court and set in motion $10,000 daily fines Monday for failing to adequately respond to a subpoena issued by the state&amp;rsquo;s attorney general as part of a civil investigation into his business dealings.
Highlights A New York judge found former president Donald Trump in contempt of court for failing to adequately respond to a subpoena issued by the state’s attorney general as part of a civil investigation into his business dealings.</description></item><item><title>Jan. 6 rioter who said he wanted Trump's 'approval' found guilty by jury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</guid><description>A Donald Trump supporter who told jurors that he was &amp;quot;following presidential orders&amp;quot; when he stormed the Capitol was found guilty.
Highlights Dustin Thompson, 38, of Ohio, admitted he stole a coat rack and a bottle of liquor from the Capitol. He testified that he was seeking former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s “respect’ and “approval” on Jan. 6, 2021. Thompson&amp;rsquo;s attorney argued that “Donald Trump encouraged people like Dustin Thompson to storm the Capitol’s Capitol&amp;quot; District Judge Reggie Walton ordered Thompson detained until his sentencing, even though the government didn’t ask him to.</description></item><item><title>Jackson confirmed as first Black female high court justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f46293f1eb44866a7eef0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 20:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f46293f1eb44866a7eef0/</guid><description>The Senate confirmed Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Thursday, shattering a historic barrier by securing her place as the first Black female justice.
Highlights The Senate confirmed Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court on Thursday. She will take her seat when Justice Stephen Breyer retires this summer, solidifying the liberal wing of the 6-3 conservative-dominated court. Jackson will be just the third Black justice, after Thurgood Marshall and Clarence Thomas.</description></item><item><title>Postal workers hope new law will 'stop the bleeding' at U.S. Postal Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eb95f2dc254370c322023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 10:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eb95f2dc254370c322023/</guid><description>Postal workers in Wisconsin are optimistic that a new law overhauling the U.S. Postal Service and injecting more than $100 billion into the service will help put an end to years of instability in the service.
Highlights Postal Service Reform Act will save money by reducing USPS’s health care costs and eliminating a burdensome federal requirement that the service pre-fund retirees&amp;rsquo; expenses. The bill also makes six-day delivery a matter of law, after some cost-cutting plans could have ended Saturday service.</description></item><item><title>Brazil's Bolsonaro in hospital after feeling discomfort</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242ed3058ac854da04be3f1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 11:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242ed3058ac854da04be3f1/</guid><description>A high Brazilian officials says President Jair Bolsonaro is being examined at an army hospital in the capital due to a possible intestinal obstruction
Highlights President Jair Bolsonaro is being examined at an army hospital in the capital due to a possible intestinal obstruction, a key minister says. Brazil&amp;rsquo;s president has been in and out of hospitals since he was stabbed in his abdomen at a campaign event before the 2018 elections.</description></item><item><title>Judge: 'More likely than not' that Trump 'corruptly attempted' to block Congress from counting votes on January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624224b07d71fc0d9e494070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 21:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624224b07d71fc0d9e494070/</guid><description>A federal judge said Monday that former President Donald Trump and right-wing attorney John Eastman may have been planning a crime as they sought to disrupt the January 6 congressional certification of the presidential election.
Highlights Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson, President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s pick to replace retiring Justice Stephen Breyer on the U.S. Supreme Court, would become the first Black woman to serve on the Supreme Court if confirmed. Former President Donald Trump and right-wing attorney John Eastman may have been planning a crime as they sought to disrupt the January 6 congressional certification of the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Russian PM: Ukraine invasion 'beginning of the end' for Putin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f653710da133b99840b98/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 19:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f653710da133b99840b98/</guid><description>The first Russian Prime Minister under President Putin tells LBC he has at most two years left at the helm before he is ousted.
Highlights Ex-Russian PM: Ukraine invasion &amp;lsquo;beginning of the end&amp;rsquo; for Putin&amp;rsquo;s reign as Prime Minister. First Russian Prime Minister under President Putin tells LBC he has at most two years left at the helm before he is ousted. Putin has already been knocked for six by the West&amp;rsquo;s response to the Ukraine war thus far, says ex-PM.</description></item><item><title>Trump aide Manafort removed from plane for revoked passport</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b55876002ef165478a08f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 17:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b55876002ef165478a08f/</guid><description>MIAMI (AP) — Former Trump adviser Paul Manafort was removed from a plane at Miami International Airport before it took off for Dubai because he carried a revoked passport, officials said Wednesday.
Highlights Paul Paul Paul was removed from a plane at Miami International Airport before it took off for Dubai because he carried a revoked passport, officials said Wednesday. Miami-Dade police confirmed Wednesday, March 23, 2022, that he was removed.</description></item><item><title>Russian foreign minister praises Fox News coverage of war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623527b9f4ca64ee362fcd4d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623527b9f4ca64ee362fcd4d/</guid><description>Sergei Lavrov says only Fox is presenting an ‘alternative point of view’ rather than ‘information terrorism’
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister praises Fox News for its coverage of Ukraine. Sergei Lavrov says only Fox is presenting an ‘alternative point of view’ rather than ‘information terrorism’ in the US. Comments came as six western nations accused Moscow of using UN security council to launder disinformation and spread propaganda. Russian diplomats again raised allegations that the US was involved in biological weapons, which have been repeatedly denied by both Washington and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Arnold Schwarzenegger speaks to Russians in emotional plea against war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623414f1e147874adf6bc92c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 05:13:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623414f1e147874adf6bc92c/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I&amp;rsquo;m speaking to you today because there are things that are being kept from you,&amp;quot; he said. &amp;quot;Terrible things that you should know about.&amp;quot;
Highlights Arnold Schwarzenegger posted a heartfelt nine-minute video message on Twitter. He spoke of his admiration for the Russian people and his father&amp;rsquo;s experience in World War II. Schwarzenegger: &amp;ldquo;To President Putin, I say: You started this war. You are leading this war&amp;rdquo; He said the Russian government&amp;rsquo;s claim that it&amp;rsquo;s attempting to &amp;ldquo;de-Nazify&amp;rdquo; Ukraine was completely untrue, pointing out that Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president, Volodymir Zelenskyy, is Jewish and lost relatives in the Holocaust.</description></item><item><title>Sharpsville man convicted of Capitol riot involvement dead at age 37</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9056cbf4ff5c76a4acb0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9056cbf4ff5c76a4acb0/</guid><description>An obituary posted on the Flynn Funeral Home website says that Matthew Perna of Sharpsville died on Friday “of a broken heart”.
Highlights Matthew Perna and Stephen Ayres of Champion, Ohio were each indicted on the same charges. Investigators say the two attempted to obstruct members of congress as they were certifying President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s election and destroyed federal property in the process. An obituary posted on the Flynn Funeral Home website says that Matthew Perna of Sharpsville, Ohio died on Friday “of a broken heart” The two men were each charged with obstructing congressmen and destroying federal property.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Trump's bid to shield January 6 records, bringing end to legal battle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62152846663c5b6e90e95e31/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62152846663c5b6e90e95e31/</guid><description>The Supreme Court already rejected Trump&amp;rsquo;s emergency request to block the release of his records to the January 6 select committee.
Highlights The Supreme Court turned away the former president&amp;rsquo;s legal fight with the House select committee investigating the January 6 assault on the U.S. Capitol. The panel received more than 700 pages of records sought by the panel earlier this month. Trump asserted executive privilege over more than 750 pages of documents related to the events of January 6, including presidential diaries, visitor logs, handwritten notes from then-White House chief of staff Mark Meadows, binders from then White House press secretary Kayleigh McEnany, and a draft executive order on election integrity.</description></item><item><title>Putin orders Russian peacekeepers to eastern Ukraine's two breakaway regions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621463535c241dc1b0bf42c0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621463535c241dc1b0bf42c0/</guid><description>President Vladimir Putin ordered his defence ministry to despatch Russian peacekeepers to eastern Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s two breakaway regions, according to a decree published early on Tuesday after he said Moscow would recognise their independence.
Highlights Putin orders Russian defence ministry to despatch Russian peacekeepers to eastern Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s breakaway regions. Putin earlier signed decrees to recognise the two breakaway areas as independent statelets defying Western warnings that such a step would be illegal and kill off long-running peace talks.</description></item><item><title>Turkmenistan’s despot finds a worthy successor: his son - "A horse-obsessed personality cult becomes a dynasty"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62120608cc39a745a2c049ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62120608cc39a745a2c049ee/</guid><description>A horse-obsessed personality cult becomes a dynasty | Asia
Highlights Gurbanguly Berdymukhamedov, Turkmenistan’s president, is still a spring chicken by the standards of his contemporaries. Islam Karimov ruled Uzbekistan until his death at 78 in 2016. Nursultan Nazarbayev, the former president of Kazakhstan, was the same age before he made way, in 2019, for a younger leader. A snap election will be held on March 12th. The stage has been set for Central Asia&amp;rsquo;s first hereditary succession since the era of the Khans.</description></item><item><title>Biden orders release of Trump White House logs to Congress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d5a95e486b50bd850c2ff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 20:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d5a95e486b50bd850c2ff/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is ordering the release of Trump White House visitor logs to the House committee investigating the riot of Jan. 6, 2021, once more rejecting former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s claims of executive privilege.
Highlights President Joe Biden is ordering the release of Trump White House visitor logs to the House committee investigating the riot of Jan. 6, 2021. The committee has sought a trove of data from the National Archives, including presidential records that Trump had fought to keep private.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian President pushes back on Biden: 'There are no minor incursions'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea05be5207a8818afc9f3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 01:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea05be5207a8818afc9f3d/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky publicly pushed back Thursday on US President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments that a &amp;quot;minor incursion&amp;quot; by Russia into Ukraine would prompt a lesser response than a full-scale invasion, in an implicit rebuke of Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments.
Summary (CNN) Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky publicly pushed back Thursday on US President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments that a &amp;ldquo;minor incursion&amp;rdquo; by Russia into Ukraine would prompt a lesser response than a full-scale invasion, in an implicit rebuke of Biden&amp;rsquo;s comments.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Trump's request to block release of White House records from January 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8de5b0d7f72459feb655f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8de5b0d7f72459feb655f/</guid><description>President Joe Biden had refused to invoke executive privilege, as Donald Trump wanted to prevent White House records from going to the January 6 riot panel.
Summary The Supreme Court on Wednesday rejected a request by former President Donald Trump to block White House records from being sent to a House select committee investigating the January 6 Capitol riot. The ruling, which Trump cannot appeal, sets the stage for more than 700 pages of Trump White House records to soon be sent by the National Archives to the committee, which had issued a subpoena for them.</description></item><item><title>Erdogan Warns Russia Against Invading Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d75fa8853e1d19c44438/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s supply of combat drones to Ukraine has drawn the wrath of Russia.
Summary Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Tuesday warned Russia against invading Ukraine, calling the former Soviet republic a &amp;ldquo;powerful&amp;rdquo; country with international friends. Speaking to Turkish reporters in Albania, Erdogan said he intended to discuss the rising tensions with Russian President Vladimir Putin. &amp;ldquo;You cannot handle these things by saying &amp;lsquo;I will invade something, I will take it&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rdquo; Turkish media quoted Erdogan as saying.</description></item><item><title>French President Emmanuel Macron said he “really wants to piss off” the unvaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d517e13adecc797b78cc9c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d517e13adecc797b78cc9c/</guid><description>French President Emmanuel Macron raised eyebrows and provoked a fair amount of shock on Tuesday when he warned people in France not yet vaccinated against Covid-19 that he would annoy them by limiting access to key aspects of life in the country.
Summary “I don’t want to piss the French people off… But as for the non-vaccinated, I really want to piss them off (emmerder). You will no longer be able to go for a coffee, you will no longer be able to go to the theatre.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman wants Turkey's President to stop bringing up the brutal killing of journalist Jamal Khashoggi</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d41ac129bfb18fac385dd2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d41ac129bfb18fac385dd2/</guid><description>Khashoggi was killed in a Saudi consulate in Istanbul in October 2018. Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan will meet with MBS next month.
Summary A composite image of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi and Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman. Journalist Jamal Khashoggi was murdered in a Saudi consulate in Istanbul in 2018. Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman wants Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan to promise that he won&amp;rsquo;t mention journalist Jamal Khashoggi&amp;rsquo;s murder again, The Wall Street Journal reported.</description></item></channel></rss>