<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rising on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rising/</link><description>Recent content in rising on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 06:13:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dr. Scott Gottlieb says rising monkeypox cases suggest it's spread 'pretty wide'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628882dbd1ab10fd8904e3fc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 06:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628882dbd1ab10fd8904e3fc/</guid><description>Gottlieb’s remarks come two days after U.S. health officials confirmed a case of the virus in a man from Massachusetts who recently traveled to Canada.
Highlights Dr. Scott Gottlieb said the virus won&amp;rsquo;t cause a major epidemic like Covid. He said many people may be incubating the virus, which has a long incubation period of 21 days or more. The New York City Department of Health said Thursday it&amp;rsquo;s investigating a possible case in a man who&amp;rsquo;s being treated at NYC Health + Hospitals/Bellevue.</description></item><item><title>Stranded dog saved from rising tide after rescuers attach sausage to drone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea13b660290325961df1f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea13b660290325961df1f7/</guid><description>Team in Hampshire ties sausage to drone as ‘last resort’ to rescue Millie the jack russell from mudflats
Summary It worked gloriously and Millie has been reunited with her grateful owner after following the dangling sausage to higher, safer ground. But they pressed ahead and after checking Civil Aviation Authority regulations, and the MTOW [maximum takeoff weight] of their machines, the rescuers calculated they could attach a single sausage to a drone.</description></item><item><title>Amid rising prices, American families fall deeper in debt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ded0fa26a34e54c497f052/</guid><description>Between inflation and ongoing supply chain issues, prices are rising and it&amp;rsquo;s eating away at the average family budget.
Summary Higher prices are already taking a toll. As consumers pay more for everything from groceries to gasoline, household income is failing to keep pace with a higher overall cost of living, according to recent reports. Over the past two years, median income fell 3% while the cost of living rose nearly 7%, due, in part, to rising housing and medical costs.</description></item><item><title>Covid hospitalizations are rising across the country, even in high-vaccination states</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6dda91fbcf1a9d358adf4/</guid><description>Hospitalization rates have increased in 29 states and territories since Nov. 1, according to an NBC News analysis of data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary The latest surge that is driving up the number of Covid cases across the country is also putting more people in hospitals, even in highly vaccinated states. Hospitalizations around the nation have risen 39 percent from Nov.</description></item></channel></rss>