<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>boris on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/boris/</link><description>Recent content in boris on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/boris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prime Minister Boris Johnson admits he attended No.10 'BYOB' garden party during the height of the first lockdown, as Labour Leader Keir Starmer demands his resignation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df6ba987f7f85ca08ef90a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df6ba987f7f85ca08ef90a/</guid><description>Prime minister apologises and accepts the public feel &amp;quot;rage&amp;quot; at his actions, as Keir Starmer demands his resignation.
Summary House of Commons via PA Wire/PA ImagesBoris Johnson has admitted he attended the No.10 “bring your own booze” party during the height of the first lockdown. Speaking at the start of PMQs on Wednesday, the prime minister apologised for the gathering on May 20, 2020. AdvertisementBut defending his actions, Johnson said he believed at the time it was a “work event” permitted “technically”under the rules when he “went into that garden”.</description></item><item><title>COVID: Boris Johnson accused of hosting another party during lockdown</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de364f09d2bfecc84304f5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de364f09d2bfecc84304f5/</guid><description>According to a leaked email, more than 40 people attended a Downing Street garden party amid the UK&amp;rsquo;s restrictions on gatherings. Johnson is already under pressure for a number of other events held amid lockdowns.
Summary British Prime Minister Boris Johnson face renewed criticism on Tuesday of his government&amp;rsquo;s conduct during the first nationwide coronavirus lockdown in 2020. Johnson dodged questions from lawmakers in Parliament on Tuesday, sending a junior minister to face MPs in his stead.</description></item></channel></rss>