<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>documents on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/documents/</link><description>Recent content in documents on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 19:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/documents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>No documents in Prince Andrew's possession to prove inability to sweat claim</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0a4cec0f091a4ed19ac47/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0a4cec0f091a4ed19ac47/</guid><description>The Duke of York has revealed there are no witnesses or documents to support his claim.
Summary He also said he had no documents in his possession regarding the &amp;ldquo;peculiar medical condition&amp;rdquo; he said prevented him from sweating. The claims were made in court documents filed on Thursday night in response to discovery requests made by his alleged victim, Virginia Roberts Giuffre. Ms Giuffre has lodged a civil claim for unspecified damages, alleging that the Duke assaulted or raped her on three separate occasions in 2001 when she was 17.</description></item><item><title>Virginia Giuffre's lawyers demand proof that Prince Andrew can't sweat</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d018364c587f23c6ad050e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d018364c587f23c6ad050e/</guid><description>Prince Andrew has been asked to provide documents proving his &amp;quot;alleged medical inability to sweat&amp;quot; in a court filing by attorneys for Virginia Roberts Giuffre, who has accused the royal of sexual assault in a US civil lawsuit.
Summary (CNN) Prince Andrew has been asked to provide documents proving his &amp;ldquo;alleged medical inability to sweat&amp;rdquo; in a court filing by attorneys for Virginia Roberts Giuffre, who has accused the royal of sexual assault in a US civil lawsuit.</description></item></channel></rss>