<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lawmakers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawmakers/</link><description>Recent content in lawmakers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:13:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawmakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida lawmakers approve bill to restrict rooftop solar incentives</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62290a60047c33a7f9ded5b3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62290a60047c33a7f9ded5b3/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. &amp;ndash; Major changes could be coming to rooftop solar energy in the state of Florida. House Bill 741 was passed by both the Florida House and Senate this past week, and will now be sent to Governor DeSantis to sign. Caption: WEAR. The legislation would effect a process called net metering. Net metering is the process in which additional energy goes into what is called a grid and homeowners are then given dollar for dollar credit by power companies, such as Florida Power &amp;amp; Light.</description></item><item><title>Lawmakers asking for a federal investigation into travel nurse salaries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62036942cae09c5eb4c35920/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62036942cae09c5eb4c35920/</guid><description>A bipartisan letter signed by lawmakers across the nation has asked the COVID-19 response team to investigate potential price gouging by some nursing staff agencies. Some local healthcare workers say this growing scrutiny could lead to state-level restrictions. “It wasn&amp;rsquo;t even COVID that was rough, it was more of a staffing issue, and not being treated how I felt like I deserve to be treated as a nurse, and not getting breaks, not even urinating in a 12 hour shift.</description></item></channel></rss>