<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>connecticut on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/connecticut/</link><description>Recent content in connecticut on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 02:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/connecticut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Feds: National Guard members on state duty can join unions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870142d921a0dada4896c9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870142d921a0dada4896c9/</guid><description>HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — The Department of Justice has given the green light to National&amp;hellip;
Highlights A 1978 federal law makes it a criminal felony for members of the armed forces, including the National Guard, to join or attempt to form a labor organization. The department on Tuesday settled a federal lawsuit filed in Connecticut by labor unions. Some Texas National Guard members already have moved ahead with their plans, joining the Texas State Employees Union starting in February.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones after CT deposition in Sandy Hook defamation case: ‘I could have done a better job’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f622a41d64e74d5897f29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 22:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f622a41d64e74d5897f29/</guid><description>Alex Jones sat for depositions on Tuesday and Wednesday in the Sandy Hook case, ending&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones sat for a second day of questioning under oath in the Sandy Hook defamation case on Wednesday. Jones said in a video that he was being demonized for falsely reporting that the worst crime in modern Connecticut history never happened. Jones flew to Connecticut this week from the Texas headquarters of his “Infowars” internet program.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones’ escalating $25K fine starts Friday; judge denies motion to lift sanction while he appeals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624778ee18cd63398b2ad11e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 22:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624778ee18cd63398b2ad11e/</guid><description>An escalating $25,000 daily fine began on Friday for Alex Jones as part of the defamation&amp;hellip;
Highlights Infowars host Alex Jones faces three jury trials to determine damages in defamation case he lost to Sandy Hook families. Judge Barbara Bellis says Jones defying her orders to answer questions under oath last week. Jones says he will sit for two days of depositions starting April 11. Bellis: If Jones does travel to Connecticut to answer pretrial questions, he can apply to the court for a refund.</description></item></channel></rss>