<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>server on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/server/</link><description>Recent content in server on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Just before Buffalo shooting, 15 users signed into suspect’s chatroom, says person familiar with review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62874d7bbc147e10b44fabc8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62874d7bbc147e10b44fabc8/</guid><description>The users were able to scroll through months of voluminous writings and racist screeds.
Highlights Alleged gunman Payton Gendron&amp;rsquo;s online chatroom invitation was accepted by 15 users, according to a person with knowledge of the messaging platform Discord’s investigation into the matter. When the 15 accepted the invite to that server, they were able to scroll back through months of his voluminous writings and racist screeds. The invitation, headed “Happening: This is not a drill,” also included a separate link to an account on the video streaming service Twitch, where he allegedly broadcast video of his attack from a camera mounted on his military-style helmet.</description></item><item><title>Amazon’s Twitch, Discord, 4chan face New York AG probe after Buffalo shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285ed4fa471f2a8fba31693/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285ed4fa471f2a8fba31693/</guid><description>Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Twitch, Discord, 4chan and 8chan will be among the platforms her office will probe.
Highlights New York&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General Letitia James will investigate social media companies in connection to the shooting. The shooter initially livestreamed his actions to Twitch during the massacre at Tops grocery store on Saturday. James&amp;rsquo; office will also focus on 4chan, 8chan and Discord, but is not limited to those platforms. Investigators will look at online resources the gunman &amp;ldquo;used to discuss and amplify his intentions and acts to carry out this attack,&amp;rdquo; the AG said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>