<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>island on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/island/</link><description>Recent content in island on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 22:14:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/island/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine Welcomes Home Soldier Who Told "Go F*** Yourself" To Russians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243848a9884d4361e564f43/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 22:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243848a9884d4361e564f43/</guid><description>A Ukrainian soldier who told a Russian warship to &amp;quot;go f*** yourself&amp;quot; before he was captured by the invading force has returned home, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Ministry tweeted.
Highlights Ukrainian soldier Roman Hrybov has returned home from Russian captivity, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Ministry tweeted. The soldier and his small squad had been defending a small island called Snake Island in the Black Sea during the early days of the Russian invasion in late February.</description></item><item><title>"Mega" iceberg releases 152 billion tons of fresh water into ocean</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef2f93dffb0db4d8023292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef2f93dffb0db4d8023292/</guid><description>The iceberg was once one of the largest on record. Now it&amp;rsquo;s melting, and scientists are waiting to see how it&amp;rsquo;s going to impact South Georgia&amp;rsquo;s marine life.
Summary When the massive A68A iceberg snapped off its ice shelf in July 2017, it was the sixth-largest iceberg on record. The iceberg once measured roughly 5,719 square kilometers — nearly half the size of Connecticut — but it started to disintegrate once it arrived to the South Georgia island in the Atlantic Ocean.</description></item><item><title>A Small British Island Is Looking for Someone to Run Its Pub – and Serve as 'King'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4fbce52ddfc5bd29fa794/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4fbce52ddfc5bd29fa794/</guid><description>Piel Island has crowned the pub landlord as king of the island for at least 200 years, and they&amp;rsquo;re looking for someone new to take over the job.
Summary Or maybe you have bigger dreams: An island all to your own or being crowned a king (or queen)? A small British island is currently on the lookout for all three – though the gig may be harder work than it sounds.</description></item><item><title>Amazon warehouse workers on Staten Island refile union petition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 03:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c537cc3f9f9011273e4748/</guid><description>The group, called Amazon Labor Union, is looking to organize workers across four company warehouses on Staten Island.
Summary A labor group seeking to organize Amazon warehouse workers on New York&amp;rsquo;s Staten Island has refiled a union petition with the National Labor Relations Board, the agency confirmed Wednesday. The group, known as the Amazon Labor Union, first filed its request for a union vote in late October with signatures from more than 2,000 employees.</description></item></channel></rss>