<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mandate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mandate/</link><description>Recent content in mandate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:50:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mandate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Carhartt CEO says he's still mandating staff vaccinations. Now he's facing a boycott.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed84da689a7785f0c4199d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed84da689a7785f0c4199d/</guid><description>CEO Mark Valade said an unvaccinated workforce is a &amp;quot;business risk that our company is unwilling to take.&amp;quot;
Summary Some customers are vowing to boycott Carhartt products after a January 14 internal memo from CEO Mark Valade surfaced on social media. Despite the ruling, Valade wrote, Carhartt would maintain its corporate policy of requiring its 5,500 workers to be vaccinated. Even so, some conservatives were having none of it: &amp;ldquo;Went from &amp;ldquo;Buy Carhartt&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Bye Carhartt&amp;rdquo; real quick!</description></item><item><title>United CEO says vaccine mandate appears to have ended weekly deaths of employees from Covid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 01:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de283a2e85fa8f60359870/</guid><description>A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday.
Summary A companywide vaccine mandate appears to have ended a grim weekly event at United Airlines — the death of an employee from Covid-19, the carrier’s top executive said Tuesday. &amp;ldquo;Prior to our vaccine requirement, tragically, more than one United employee on average per week was dying from COVID,&amp;rdquo; Kirby wrote.</description></item><item><title>Federal vaccine mandate for employers with 100 or more staff now in effect</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd474638760bd14c6b703a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd474638760bd14c6b703a/</guid><description>Should the employee choose to not get the shot, they must undergo weekly testing and wear a mask at the place of employment.
Summary The Biden Administrations new federal vaccine mandate for employers will 100 or more employees goes into effect on Monday. The 100 or more employee tally is for each entire company, no matter how many employees are at individual worksites. Fully remote workers and staff members who work outside exclusively should be included in the 100 or more employee tally, however, they are not subject to the federal vaccine mandate requirements.</description></item><item><title>Massachusetts state trooper fired over Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID vaccine mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 09:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</guid><description>Summary A Massachusetts state trooper was fired this week for not complying with Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate, which required more than 40,000 Executive Department employees to be fully immunized by mid-October. The development comes a week after MassLive reported the state had fired at least 60 Department of Correction workers for noncompliance. A volunteer at the Edith Nourse Rogers Memorial Veterans Hospital and the Special Olympics, the fired trooper “was never disciplined in any way shape or form” by the Massachusetts State Police prior to Baker’s vaccine mandate, SPAM said.</description></item></channel></rss>