<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>land on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/land/</link><description>Recent content in land on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:22:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/land/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Work begins to turn 99,000 hectares in England into ‘nature recovery’ projects | Conservation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62937378a79cb528aa2c223a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62937378a79cb528aa2c223a/</guid><description>Five projects to receive funding from Defra and Natural England to tackle wildlife loss and improve access to nature
Highlights Five landscape-scale projects in the West Midlands, Cambridgeshire, the Peak District, Norfolk and Somerset. Aim to help tackle wildlife loss and the climate crisis, and improve public access to nature. Will share an initial £2.4m pot from the Department for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs and Natural England. Work in the projects will range from converting farmland into chalk grassland to restoring ‘dewponds’ and managing wetlands sustainably.</description></item><item><title>Biden administration announces it will resume onshore oil and gas lease sales with higher royalty rate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b235f006fb22d490d16df/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 20:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b235f006fb22d490d16df/</guid><description>The Department of Interior announced Friday it planned to resume onshore oil and gas lease sales on federal land.
Highlights The new royalty rate is 18.75% instead of 12.5%. It&amp;rsquo;s the first time the rate has been increased. The increase comes after a plan to increase the rate was put on hold last year. The rate is higher than the previous rate that was used to calculate the amount of oil and gas per capita consumption in the U.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine minister says the Ukrainian Military has regained control of ‘whole Kyiv region’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62492ca59ce80d90a36246ec/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62492ca59ce80d90a36246ec/</guid><description>Russia-Ukraine news from April 2: Ukraine’s president says retreating Russian forces creating ‘catastrophic’ situation.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s top negotiator in peace talks with Russia says Moscow&amp;rsquo;verbally&amp;rsquo; agreed to key Ukrainian proposals. Red Cross to make new attempt to evacuate civilians from besieged city of Mariupol. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president says retreating Russian troops are leaving behind land mines creating a “catastrophic” situation. Ukraine has regained control of ‘whole Kyiv region’ after invading Russian forces retreated from some key towns near the Ukrainian capital, deputy defence minister Ganna Maliar has said.</description></item></channel></rss>