<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>map on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/map/</link><description>Recent content in map on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 01:20:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/map/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York's highest court blocks Democratic-drawn congressional map over gerrymandering</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269ebca6f22525d8ffd34af/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 01:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269ebca6f22525d8ffd34af/</guid><description>New York&amp;rsquo;s highest court blocked the state&amp;rsquo;s Democratic-drawn congressional map Wednesday, concluding that the new boundaries represented a partisan gerrymander that violates the state constitution.
Highlights The court ruled that a new map must be created for the 2022 election. The map would have given Democrats an advantage in 22 of the state&amp;rsquo;s 26 congressional districts. The ruling is a blow to Democrats, as they had viewed redistricting in New York as one of their best chances to shape district lines in their favor.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court allows Alabama voting maps that advocates say disenfranchise Black voters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201d57f5f1510f93945c860/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201d57f5f1510f93945c860/</guid><description>In a 5-4 vote, the Supreme Court cleared the way Monday for Alabama to use its new congressional district map even though a lower court said it violated the Vot
Highlights The court granted a request from Alabama Republicans to put a hold on the lower court ruling. The case is the first to reach the Supreme Court involving the redrawing of political boundaries with 2020 census results. Blacks account for just over a quarter of the state’s total population but have a voting majority in only one of its seven congressional districts.</description></item></channel></rss>