<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officers/</link><description>Recent content in officers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 17:16:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde massacre coverage: Media hassled by out-of-town police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f87d83957ea09f7e6df57/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 17:16:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f87d83957ea09f7e6df57/</guid><description>Law enforcement has intimidated, harassed and impeded journalists covering the aftermath of the Robb Elementary School shooting.
Highlights Police from across Texas converge on Uvalde to assist with traffic control, dispatching and other responsibilities. Some officers have ordered reporters off public sidewalks and used public safety vehicles to block journalists from taking photos of funerals and burials. Out-of-town officers are under the command of Dilley Police Chief Homer Delgado, the top law enforcement official in a small town about 60 miles southeast of Uvald.</description></item><item><title>EXPLAINER: Hundreds charged with crimes in Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f415f0320a96268ad331a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 12:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f415f0320a96268ad331a/</guid><description>More than 800 people across the U.S. have been charged in the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol, which left officers bloodied and sent lawmakers into hiding, and federal authorities continue to make new arrests practically every week.
Highlights More than 800 people across the U.S. have been charged in the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol that left officers bloodied and sent lawmakers running in fear, and federal authorities continue to make new arrests practically every week.</description></item><item><title>CNN reporter threatened with trespassing after grilling Uvalde police chief over his actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629943361042e4a25eada900/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629943361042e4a25eada900/</guid><description>Shimon Prokupecz had earlier been grilling police chief Pedro Arredondo about his actions during the Uvalde shooting
Highlights CNN reporter was threatened with charges of trespassing if he and his crew didn’t leave the school district’s offices. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Simon Prokupecz shared a video of a confrontation with Uvalde Police Chief Pedro “Pete” Arredondo outside the school building where he had retreated behind earlier. The Texas Department of Public Safety maintains that the chief of the school police chief is not cooperating with investigators.</description></item><item><title>Police Release Photo After Witnesses Claimed ‘Unarmed’ Pregnant Women Was Shot 5 Times During Arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629934d10ec5aadb0d86095e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 22:08:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629934d10ec5aadb0d86095e/</guid><description>In Kansas City, Missouri, Police Were Responding To A Carjacking Report When 26-year-old Leonna Hale Attempted To Cooperate With Officers Before Being Shot Five Times And Handcuffed On The Ground.
Highlights Leonna Hale, 26, was shot 5 times in Kansas City, Missouri, on Friday. Police were responding to reports of a carjacking when they encountered a pregnant woman and her boyfriend at a Family Dollar. Police report states that officers determined that Hale was armed.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde police chief who delayed officer response to shooting to join City Council</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291d9810cc9a70796c069ee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291d9810cc9a70796c069ee/</guid><description>The police chief who reportedly made the call not to immediately send officers into Robb Elementary School to confront a gunman was elected to Uvalde&amp;rsquo;s City Cou
Highlights Peter Arredondo, the chief of police for the Uvalde Consolidated Independent School District, stopped at least 19 officers from breaking into the school as the gunman opened fire for at least an hour. He believed that the shooter had barricaded himself and that the children were not under an active threat, Texas Department of Public Safety director Steven McCraw said Friday.</description></item><item><title>Unarmed 13-Year-Old Shot By Chicago Cops During Foot Chase On West Side</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287169ca3c0248048a92ede/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 04:19:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287169ca3c0248048a92ede/</guid><description>West Siders questioned why the officer shot the boy instead of using nonlethal force. “You can’t take back a bullet. At the end of the day, we’re dealing with human life,” a local business owner said.
Highlights A 13-year-old boy is hospitalized in serious condition, a Civilian Office of Police Accountability spokesperson says. The shooting was captured on multiple cameras and now under investigation, officials say. The boy, who had been in the car, got out and ran away as officers walked up to it, police say.</description></item><item><title>Post-Floyd probe finds discrimination by Minneapolis police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a31eb977fe2b8190c7b9e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a31eb977fe2b8190c7b9e/</guid><description>ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — The Minneapolis Police Department has engaged in a pattern of race discrimination for at least a decade, including stopping and arresting Black people at a higher rate than white people, using force more often on people of color and maintaining a culture where racist language is tolerated, a state investigation launched after George Floyd’s killing found.
Highlights Minnesota Department of Human Rights released report Wednesday. Report: Minneapolis Police Department engaged in a pattern of race discrimination for at least a decade.</description></item><item><title>Proud Boys member pleads guilty for role in US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a1301f8848a840c5851bd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a1301f8848a840c5851bd/</guid><description>Plea agreement filed in federal court calls for Louis Enrique Colon to admit to a single felony charge and cooperate with prosecutors
Highlights Louis Enrique Colon pleads guilty to obstructing police officers in Washington, DC. Plea agreement calls for Colon to admit to a single felony charge and cooperate with prosecutors. Colon faces up to five years in prison and a fine of up to $250,000. One of the dozens of police officers injured during the insurrection testified on Wednesday that he didn’t punch or pick a fight with a retired New York police officer charged with attacking the officer.</description></item><item><title>No charges for cop who fatally shot Amir Locke</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e8f139662a51d696712b6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 07:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e8f139662a51d696712b6/</guid><description>No criminal charges will be filed in the fatal police shooting of Amir Locke.
Highlights Amir Locke, a legal gun owner, was fatally shot by Minneapolis police officers in February. Locke was not a suspect in the crime for which the warrant was issued and was not named in the document. Locke&amp;rsquo;s mother: &amp;ldquo;Can you imagine knowing that you&amp;rsquo;ll never get to see your 22-year-old baby ever again?&amp;rdquo; Locke&amp;rsquo;s legal team says it is &amp;ldquo;deeply disappointed&amp;rdquo; by the decision.</description></item><item><title>Video contrasts police depiction of stun gun on Black man.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624990f66b065c5cad7d6f66/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 12:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624990f66b065c5cad7d6f66/</guid><description>NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee police officer who used his stun gun on a DoorDash driver wrote an arrest report saying the man had become argumentative while denying he was speeding, refused to hand over identifying information, demanded to see a supervisor and stayed in his car when ordered to get out.
Highlights Driver, Delane Gordon, a food delivery driver, began recording his traffic stop for speeding and asked to see the officer&amp;rsquo;s supervisor.</description></item><item><title>Trial Starts In Lawsuit Over Denver Cops Use Of Force In George Floyd Protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62276456b92a59b6a712d207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62276456b92a59b6a712d207/</guid><description>Trial for a lawsuit accusing Denver police of using indiscriminate force two years ago against people protesting the killing of George Floyd was set to start Monday in federal court. About a dozen lawsuits have been filed on behalf of over 60 people injured or
Highlights Trial for a lawsuit accusing Denver police of using indiscriminate force two years ago against people protesting the killing of George Floyd was set to start Monday in federal court.</description></item><item><title>Minneapolis officers ignored training, lacked 'decency' in Floyd arrest, jury hears</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215fa5cc1c319fb0c64e112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 09:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215fa5cc1c319fb0c64e112/</guid><description>A federal prosecutor told a jury in closing arguments on Tuesday that three former Minneapolis police officers ignored their training and basic human decency by failing to intervene when their colleague knelt on George Floyd&amp;rsquo;s neck during a deadly arrest.
Highlights Prosecutors say three Minneapolis officers ignored training and basic human decency by failing to intervene when colleague knelt on George Floyd&amp;rsquo;s neck during a deadly arrest. Defense attorneys say prosecutors failed to prove the three men acted with deliberate indifference.</description></item><item><title>Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying 'sovereign stuff is not valid'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</guid><description>Detroit police break up peaceful and permitted Native sugarbush ceremony in River Rouge Park
Highlights Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying&amp;rsquo;sovereign stuff is not valid&amp;rsquo; Police officers shut down Indigenous sugarbush festival in River Rouge Park. Ceremony was held to kick off the third annual tapping season as part of the Detroit Sugarbush Project. Organizers say they had valid fire permits and approval from the city of Detroit. A video posted to Instagram shows officers standing side-by-side along the edge of the clearing as smoke from the recently extinguished fire billowed between them and attendees and attendees.</description></item><item><title>Florida appeals court overturns conviction of Miami police officer who shot autistic man's caretaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</guid><description>A South Florida appeals court Wednesday overturned the conviction of a former North Miami Police Department officer who was found guilty of negligence for shooting an autistic man&amp;rsquo;s caretaker in 2016, court documents show.
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal overturned a &amp;ldquo;conviction for misdemeanor culpable negligence&amp;rdquo; for Jonathan Aledda. Florida State Attorney Katherine Fernandez Rundle said the decision is &amp;ldquo;disappointing to all who believed that this shooting incident was unnecessary and incorrect&amp;rdquo; In July 2016, officers encountered Arnaldo Rios-Soto, a man with severe developmental disabilities, and his caretaker Charles Kinsey in the middle of an intersection, court documents show.</description></item><item><title>Meijer theft suspect was a white man in his 30s. Police detained 60-year-old Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</guid><description>The incident is yet another example, a lawsuit says, of a Black person being confronted by law enforcement merely for going about his daily life.
Highlights Police were looking for a shoplifter in a West Chester Meijer in 2021. Police detained a 60-year-old Black man, Eric Lindsay, who was wearing an orange down coat and a brown-and-tan scarf. Lindsay, a business professional, was questioned for several minutes in an aisle as other shoppers looked on.</description></item><item><title>Two Denver police officers suspended for excessive force for using pepper spray, baton on peaceful protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 12:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</guid><description>Two Denver police officers will serve unpaid suspensions for using excessive force on demonstrators during two separate protests in 2020.
Highlights Officer Jesse Trudel twice used pepper spray on people peacefully protesting the murder of George Floyd. Body camera video shows the people he targeted were not posing any threat, police disciplinary letter says. Another officer, Daniel Veith, will serve a five-day unpaid suspension for using his baton to hit a person who was protesting the forced removal of an encampment of people experiencing homelessness on Aug.</description></item><item><title>More police officers sue Trump over January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</guid><description>Police officers are suing the former president for alleged wrongful conduct and inciting a riot.
Summary Three more law enforcement officers are suing former President Trump in two separate lawsuits over his words and actions leading up to the January 6, 2021, assault on the Capitol. &amp;ldquo;When Officer Tabron finally did get home around midnight, he removed his chemical-soaked clothes, showered, and tried to sleep. &amp;ldquo;The weight on Officer Moore has been heavy and inescapable.</description></item><item><title>NYC police officer shot while resting in car between shifts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 06:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</guid><description>Authorities say a New York City police officer&amp;rsquo;s skull was broken when he was shot New Year&amp;rsquo;s morning while sleeping in his personal vehicle between shifts but he is expected to fully recover
Summary The officer left the vehicle and was aided by a sergeant who saw blood coming from his head before an ambulance took him to the hospital, Sewell said. She said it was unknown whether the seven-year member of the force was targeted, but the round was apparently fired from “a significant distance away” and other officers sleeping in their vehicles nearby did not hear gunfire.</description></item></channel></rss>