<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officers/</link><description>Recent content in officers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 12:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two Denver police officers suspended for excessive force for using pepper spray, baton on peaceful protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 12:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</guid><description>Two Denver police officers will serve unpaid suspensions for using excessive force on demonstrators during two separate protests in 2020.
Highlights Officer Jesse Trudel twice used pepper spray on people peacefully protesting the murder of George Floyd. Body camera video shows the people he targeted were not posing any threat, police disciplinary letter says. Another officer, Daniel Veith, will serve a five-day unpaid suspension for using his baton to hit a person who was protesting the forced removal of an encampment of people experiencing homelessness on Aug.</description></item><item><title>More police officers sue Trump over January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</guid><description>Police officers are suing the former president for alleged wrongful conduct and inciting a riot.
Summary Three more law enforcement officers are suing former President Trump in two separate lawsuits over his words and actions leading up to the January 6, 2021, assault on the Capitol. &amp;ldquo;When Officer Tabron finally did get home around midnight, he removed his chemical-soaked clothes, showered, and tried to sleep. &amp;ldquo;The weight on Officer Moore has been heavy and inescapable.</description></item><item><title>NYC police officer shot while resting in car between shifts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 06:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</guid><description>Authorities say a New York City police officer&amp;rsquo;s skull was broken when he was shot New Year&amp;rsquo;s morning while sleeping in his personal vehicle between shifts but he is expected to fully recover
Summary The officer left the vehicle and was aided by a sergeant who saw blood coming from his head before an ambulance took him to the hospital, Sewell said. She said it was unknown whether the seven-year member of the force was targeted, but the round was apparently fired from “a significant distance away” and other officers sleeping in their vehicles nearby did not hear gunfire.</description></item></channel></rss>