<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officers/</link><description>Recent content in officers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 14:13:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trial Starts In Lawsuit Over Denver Cops Use Of Force In George Floyd Protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62276456b92a59b6a712d207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62276456b92a59b6a712d207/</guid><description>Trial for a lawsuit accusing Denver police of using indiscriminate force two years ago against people protesting the killing of George Floyd was set to start Monday in federal court. About a dozen lawsuits have been filed on behalf of over 60 people injured or
Highlights Trial for a lawsuit accusing Denver police of using indiscriminate force two years ago against people protesting the killing of George Floyd was set to start Monday in federal court.</description></item><item><title>Minneapolis officers ignored training, lacked 'decency' in Floyd arrest, jury hears</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215fa5cc1c319fb0c64e112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 09:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215fa5cc1c319fb0c64e112/</guid><description>A federal prosecutor told a jury in closing arguments on Tuesday that three former Minneapolis police officers ignored their training and basic human decency by failing to intervene when their colleague knelt on George Floyd&amp;rsquo;s neck during a deadly arrest.
Highlights Prosecutors say three Minneapolis officers ignored training and basic human decency by failing to intervene when colleague knelt on George Floyd&amp;rsquo;s neck during a deadly arrest. Defense attorneys say prosecutors failed to prove the three men acted with deliberate indifference.</description></item><item><title>Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying 'sovereign stuff is not valid'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</guid><description>Detroit police break up peaceful and permitted Native sugarbush ceremony in River Rouge Park
Highlights Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying&amp;rsquo;sovereign stuff is not valid&amp;rsquo; Police officers shut down Indigenous sugarbush festival in River Rouge Park. Ceremony was held to kick off the third annual tapping season as part of the Detroit Sugarbush Project. Organizers say they had valid fire permits and approval from the city of Detroit.</description></item><item><title>Florida appeals court overturns conviction of Miami police officer who shot autistic man's caretaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f0eb9b7c7f8dde71d3be2/</guid><description>A South Florida appeals court Wednesday overturned the conviction of a former North Miami Police Department officer who was found guilty of negligence for shooting an autistic man&amp;rsquo;s caretaker in 2016, court documents show.
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal overturned a &amp;ldquo;conviction for misdemeanor culpable negligence&amp;rdquo; for Jonathan Aledda. Florida State Attorney Katherine Fernandez Rundle said the decision is &amp;ldquo;disappointing to all who believed that this shooting incident was unnecessary and incorrect&amp;rdquo; In July 2016, officers encountered Arnaldo Rios-Soto, a man with severe developmental disabilities, and his caretaker Charles Kinsey in the middle of an intersection, court documents show.</description></item><item><title>Meijer theft suspect was a white man in his 30s. Police detained 60-year-old Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</guid><description>The incident is yet another example, a lawsuit says, of a Black person being confronted by law enforcement merely for going about his daily life.
Highlights Police were looking for a shoplifter in a West Chester Meijer in 2021. Police detained a 60-year-old Black man, Eric Lindsay, who was wearing an orange down coat and a brown-and-tan scarf. Lindsay, a business professional, was questioned for several minutes in an aisle as other shoppers looked on.</description></item><item><title>Two Denver police officers suspended for excessive force for using pepper spray, baton on peaceful protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 12:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbc7e74bb0b3bcb6f5a22d/</guid><description>Two Denver police officers will serve unpaid suspensions for using excessive force on demonstrators during two separate protests in 2020.
Highlights Officer Jesse Trudel twice used pepper spray on people peacefully protesting the murder of George Floyd. Body camera video shows the people he targeted were not posing any threat, police disciplinary letter says. Another officer, Daniel Veith, will serve a five-day unpaid suspension for using his baton to hit a person who was protesting the forced removal of an encampment of people experiencing homelessness on Aug.</description></item><item><title>More police officers sue Trump over January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</guid><description>Police officers are suing the former president for alleged wrongful conduct and inciting a riot.
Summary Three more law enforcement officers are suing former President Trump in two separate lawsuits over his words and actions leading up to the January 6, 2021, assault on the Capitol. &amp;ldquo;When Officer Tabron finally did get home around midnight, he removed his chemical-soaked clothes, showered, and tried to sleep. &amp;ldquo;The weight on Officer Moore has been heavy and inescapable.</description></item><item><title>NYC police officer shot while resting in car between shifts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 06:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d13f87dcb7a95876f5f185/</guid><description>Authorities say a New York City police officer&amp;rsquo;s skull was broken when he was shot New Year&amp;rsquo;s morning while sleeping in his personal vehicle between shifts but he is expected to fully recover
Summary The officer left the vehicle and was aided by a sergeant who saw blood coming from his head before an ambulance took him to the hospital, Sewell said. She said it was unknown whether the seven-year member of the force was targeted, but the round was apparently fired from “a significant distance away” and other officers sleeping in their vehicles nearby did not hear gunfire.</description></item></channel></rss>