<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>working on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/working/</link><description>Recent content in working on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 11:12:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/working/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monkeypox case confirmed in England</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277a5705adab6185bf0bdfb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277a5705adab6185bf0bdfb/</guid><description>The patient is being treated at an infectious disease unit and the risk to the public is low, officials say.
Highlights The patient is being treated at an infectious disease unit and the risk to the public is low, officials say. UKHSA experts are working closely with NHS colleagues and will be contacting people who might have been in close contact with the patient to provide information and health advice. The health agency said: &amp;ldquo;As a precautionary measure, experts will contact people who may have been close contact to the individual to provide health advice&amp;rdquo; The risk of the public being exposed to the patient is low and low, health officials say.</description></item><item><title>Spotify and Discord down for thousands of users</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228c401912dbf49753bbf6a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 15:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228c401912dbf49753bbf6a/</guid><description>Spotify and messaging platform Discord were down for thousands of users on Tuesday. More than 138,000 users had reported issues with Spotify, while over 65,000 said there were problems with Discord.
Highlights Spotify and messaging platform Discord were down for thousands of users on Tuesday. Outages may be affecting a larger number of users, according to outage tracking website Downdetector.com. Spotify did not immediately respond to a request for comment. Discord said it was aware of an issue causing message failures and is working on a fix.</description></item><item><title>‘Right to disconnect’: boss may no longer call employees after hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5420dad7affa4707dccb7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5420dad7affa4707dccb7/</guid><description>From next month, federal civil servants no longer have to be reachable after normal working hours, as they will be given the &amp;quot;right to disconnect.&amp;quot;
Summary Photo by Ron Lach from PexelsFrom 1 February, federal civil servants will no longer have to answer phone calls from their boss after normal working hours, a circular from Minister of Civil Service Petra De Sutter states. De Sutter emphasised the so-called “right to disconnect” – the right to be unreachable – of federal civil servants in her circular, according to reports in De Morgen, which saw the letter.</description></item></channel></rss>