<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>think on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/think/</link><description>Recent content in think on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 06:17:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/think/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canadian sniper ‘Wali’ alive in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623abb694403b29c031ad60d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 06:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623abb694403b29c031ad60d/</guid><description>Russian reports had said former Canadian soldier had been quickly killed in fighting
Highlights Reports of a famed Canadian sniper’s demise at the hand of Russian forces in Ukraine have proved premature. The man known as “Wali” spoke with the Star in a video interview Tuesday in which he said he had been “the last to learn” of his own death. The 40-year-old Quebec soldier, who asked that his real name not be used, left in early March to join Ukrainian forces on the front lines.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau promises to support Ukraine as Canadian warship departs for Black Sea</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e995286dc41a7a20015e9b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e995286dc41a7a20015e9b/</guid><description>A Canadian warship departed for Europe and the Black Sea near Russia on Wednesday, as Prime Minister Justin Trudeau admitted to fears of a Russian invasion in Ukraine.
Summary HALIFAX - A Canadian warship departed for Europe and the Black Sea near Russia on Wednesday, as Prime Minister Justin Trudeau admitted to fears of a Russian invasion in Ukraine. “We&amp;rsquo;re looking at many different factors when we make decisions on how to best support the people of Ukraine,” he said.</description></item><item><title>Quebec says it will tax those who remain unvaccinated against COVID-19 without a medical reason</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfc012615c48af4a17a4b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 06:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfc012615c48af4a17a4b1/</guid><description>Quebec Premier François Legault said it was a measure for &amp;quot;fairness&amp;quot; for the 90% of residents who are vaccinated.
Summary The Premier of Quebec François Legault at a press conference on November 18, 2021 in Montreal, Canada. Minas Panagiotakis/Getty Images10% of Quebec&amp;rsquo;s adult population is unvaccinated for COVID-19, Premier François Legault said. The unvaccinated, however, make up half of all ICU beds in the province, Legault said. Quebec&amp;rsquo;s Premier François Legault announced on Tuesday that the province plans to tax people who are unvaccinated against COVID-19 for non-medical reasons.</description></item></channel></rss>