<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ransomware on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ransomware/</link><description>Recent content in ransomware on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 09:10:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ransomware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wray: FBI blocked planned cyberattack on children's hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62987e5a543e99ca166906d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62987e5a543e99ca166906d3/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The FBI thwarted a planned cyberattack on a children&amp;rsquo;s hospital in Boston that was to have been carried out by hackers sponsored by the Iranian government, FBI Director Christopher Wray said Wednesday.
Highlights FBI Director Christopher Wray says his agents thwarted a planned cyberattack on a Boston children&amp;rsquo;s hospital that was to have been carried out by hackers sponsored by the Iranian government. Wray told a Boston College cybersecurity conference that his agents learned of the planned digital attack from an unspecified intelligence partner and got Boston Children’s Hospital the information it needed last summer to block what would have been “one of the most despicable cyberattacks I’ve seen” The speech took place as the FBI continues to combat ransomware attacks from criminal gangs, a continuing concern for U.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer asks employees who were overpaid as result of a ransomware attack to pay company back</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246c2338cb53e12bebfad19/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 09:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246c2338cb53e12bebfad19/</guid><description>Ransomware attack on Kronos resulted in Pfizer employees being over-compensated company-wide. Pfizer asked employees to pay back the company, and some underpaid.
Highlights Ransomware attack on Kronos resulted in Pfizer employees being over-compensated company-wide. Pfizer asked employees to pay back the company after the attack. Some employees were underpaid, some overpaid, Pfizer says. The company has not responded to requests for more information from the company to respond to the attack, which occurred in early December.</description></item></channel></rss>