<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>spain on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spain/</link><description>Recent content in spain on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 23:14:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spain and Mexico speed up their bilateral relations by signing political, feminist and scientific and cultural cooperation agreements. They agree on mutually-beneficial effects of investments in both countries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e7ad2a247d3cf780874d5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 23:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e7ad2a247d3cf780874d5/</guid><description>Minister for Foreign Affairs, European Union and Cooperation, José Manuel Albares, signed a total of four agreements with his Mexican counterpart, Marcelo Ebrard. The two countries reaffirm the value they assign to their relationship of fraternity.
Highlights Spanish and Mexican ministers sign four agreements to step up close relations between the two countries. The two countries reaffirm the value they assign to their relationship of fraternity. The Spanish language also played a privileged role in their talks, regarding which they underlined the value of their shared language.</description></item><item><title>Pets' welfare will be considered in divorce battles in Spain</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7bb8ca5f5c8438a4c2f25/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7bb8ca5f5c8438a4c2f25/</guid><description>Spain will consider a pet&amp;rsquo;s welfare when couples divorce or break-up from Wednesday in a legal shift that strengthens the case for couples obtaining shared custody of their animals.
Summary Madrid, Spain Spain will consider a pet&amp;rsquo;s welfare when couples divorce or break-up from Wednesday in a legal shift that strengthens the case for couples obtaining shared custody of their animals. The decision follows similar moves in France and Portugal and obliges judges to consider pets as sentient beings rather than objects owned by one or the other partner, a trend that was already underway before the law was passed.</description></item><item><title>Spain’s leftist cabinet approves landmark labour law reform which aims to reduce the use of temporary contracts and boost job security.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd833b98a1415b195d51e4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd833b98a1415b195d51e4/</guid><description>Spain&amp;rsquo;s leftist cabinet approved Tuesday (28 December) a landmark labour law reform which aims to reduce the use of temporary contracts and boost job security.
Summary Spain’s leftist cabinet approved Tuesday (28 December) a landmark labour law reform which aims to reduce the use of temporary contracts and boost job security. Spain is currently the European Union nation where the use of temporary contracts is highest, but the reform tightens conditions for their use in the eurozone’s fourth-largest economy.</description></item></channel></rss>