<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>area on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/area/</link><description>Recent content in area on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 03:47:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/area/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wichita police investigate deadly shooting as possible hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62958fcb518a20e444c717c6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 03:47:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62958fcb518a20e444c717c6/</guid><description>The Wichita Police Department has arrested 27-year-old Roger R. Gale on charges of first-degree murder and aggravated assault stemming from the investigation into the fatal shooting of 30-year-old Emm
Highlights Roger Gale, 27, has been arrested on charges of first-degree murder and aggravated assault. Police say they are still looking for suspects in the shooting death of Emm Emm, 30. “We&amp;rsquo;re still checking cameras in the area, local businesses and talking with witnesses,” said Chief Fort Fort.</description></item><item><title>Soldier dies after being attacked by bear on base in Alaska</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bfd95c55693f79bea8ecf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 18:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bfd95c55693f79bea8ecf/</guid><description>Officials say it happened during a training exercise. They&amp;rsquo;re still looking for the bear.
Highlights The soldier was part of a small group in a training area west of the Anchorage Regional Landfill when the bear attacked. The name of the soldier was being withheld pending next-of-kin notification. Alaska Wildlife Troopers were searching for the bear in the area, which is closed to the public for all recreational activity. Officials say the incident happened during a training exercise at Joint Base Elmendorf-Richardson in Alaska.</description></item><item><title>Trucks, RVs and cars flock to Washington area to protest COVID restrictions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622435515177d2208d04539b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 04:15:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622435515177d2208d04539b/</guid><description>More than a thousand large trucks, recreational vehicles and cars are gathering on the outskirts of Washington as part of a protest against COVID-19 restrictions that threatens to roll on the U.S. capital in the coming days.
Highlights More than a thousand large trucks, recreational vehicles and cars are gathering on the outskirts of Washington. The so-called &amp;ldquo;People&amp;rsquo;s Convoy&amp;rdquo; is calling for an end to all pandemic-related restrictions. It was inspired by demonstrations last month that paralyzed Ottawa, Canada&amp;rsquo;s capital city.</description></item></channel></rss>