<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ukraines on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraines/</link><description>Recent content in ukraines on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 09:09:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ukraines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine pleads for weapons as Russian onslaught threatens to turn the tide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293382d8d3ce6188618bced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 09:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293382d8d3ce6188618bced/</guid><description>As support among some European allies appears to waver, Kyiv calls for advanced rocket systems to hit Russia’s supply lines
Highlights US has agreed to provide more military weapons to Ukraine this week. Russia has threatened to use its own military equipment against rebels in Ukraine. But Britain and other European countries are yet to agree on a plan to provide weapons to Russia. Russian President Vladimir Putin is expected to meet with US President George W Bush on the sidelines of the war.</description></item><item><title>Russia Is Leaking Data Like a Sieve</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e0b139ee1592822d733bb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 01:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e0b139ee1592822d733bb/</guid><description>Ukraine claims to have doxed Russian troops and spies, while hacktivists are regularly leaking private information from Russian organizations.
Highlights Ukraine claims to have doxed 1,600 Russian troops in one fell swoop. Another data set allegedly contains details of 620 Russian spies registered to work at the Moscow office of the FSB. The data offers unparalleled glimpses into closed-off private institutions and may be a gold mine for investigators. Both sides in this conflict are very good at information operations, says Philip Ingram, a former colonel in British military intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy says Ukraine captured pro-Putin politician Viktor Medvedchuk who escaped house arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62565bffb59d3b5f0770f639/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 05:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62565bffb59d3b5f0770f639/</guid><description>Zelenskyy posted a photo on social media showing a disheveled Medvedchuk seated by a radiator clasped in handcuffs.
Highlights Viktor Medvedchuk had been under house arrest on treason charges since last year. He allegedly escaped shortly after Russia launched its invasion in late February. His lawyers have denied wrongdoing. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Security Service posted a mugshot of him on its official Twitter account, along with a cavalier warning for other Russia-allied Ukrainians.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s Foreign Affairs Minister: Russian troops will launch missiles on Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62223b774fe8e8b6d8a1da28/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62223b774fe8e8b6d8a1da28/</guid><description>Ukrainian Minister of Foreign Affairs Dmytro Kuleba stated that in order to execute its information attack on Ukraine, Russia intends to strike its own territory.
Highlights Minister of Foreign Affairs Dmytro Kuleba said Russia will lose the information war with Ukraine. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s tactic has been to &amp;ldquo;uncover these provocations before they are committed,&amp;rdquo; he said. Russia is preparing provocations to improve its position in the information field, he said. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defence publishes this information to block misinformation along the lines of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s attack on Russian territory, he added.</description></item><item><title>Spain dispatches warship to the Black Sea to boost Ukraine’s defences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9db750b7fa8a5cd2e4868/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9db750b7fa8a5cd2e4868/</guid><description>TVP World/Telewizja Polska S. A.
Summary Amidst growing tension and Russia’s ever-more realistic ambitions to invade Ukraine, Spain has sent off its warship to the Black Sea and said that it would dispatch even more to reinforce other EU states’ units, should the NATO-Russia talks turn out a fiasco and Russian aggression a reality. The centre-left cabinet of Spanish PM Pedro Sanchez confirmed that the warship had been sent off. According to “El Mundo” daily, Mr Albares was asked if Spain would send its troops to Ukraine in the event of Russia’s invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>