<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>removed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/removed/</link><description>Recent content in removed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 09:13:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/removed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JetBlue pilot pulled off plane after failing breathalyzer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622086a21f781d9d618d2e9e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 09:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622086a21f781d9d618d2e9e/</guid><description>A 52-year-old JetBlue pilot was pulled off a plane in Buffalo after blowing a blood alcohol content that was four times the legal limit for pilots.
Highlights The 52-year-old pilot blew a 0.17 on a breathalyzer test, police said. He was released to JetBlue security and may face federal charges, official says. The flight to Ft. Lauderdale was delayed for over four hours. The pilot denied drinking the morning of the flight, according to the police report, but claimed he drank 7-8 beverages the night before.</description></item><item><title>Detroit Police commissioner removed from towing committee after downplaying bribery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c75c3c77346718417030b3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c75c3c77346718417030b3/</guid><description>Detroit police commissioner has been unappointed from a committee overseeing the towing industry after controversial comments during a 7 Action News interview where she downplayed the gravity of bribery.
Summary DETROIT (WXYZ) — A Detroit police commissioner has been unappointed from a committee overseeing the towing industry after making controversial comments where she downplayed the seriousness of bribery. Jim Holley—the chair of the Board of Police Commissioners—removed Bernard from the board’s towing committee.</description></item></channel></rss>