<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>soldiers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soldiers/</link><description>Recent content in soldiers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 02:12:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soldiers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine’s not-so-secret weapon against Russia: an army of volunteers supplying the front - National</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62368d718daaf266c4f4e0a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 02:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62368d718daaf266c4f4e0a9/</guid><description>While NATO countries ship weapons to Ukraine, a far more expansive effort within the country runs supplies to soldiers and civilians on the front lines.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s attempt to seize its western neighbour has triggered Europe’s worst refugee crisis since the Second World War. NATO countries have been shipping anti-tank weapons and air defence systems to Ukraine. But it has also led to a mass mobilization of citizens unseen since then.</description></item><item><title>U.S. soldiers alive, despite Russia 'fake news' report, U.S. military says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 10:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</guid><description>Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well, the Tennessee National Guard said on Thursday.
Highlights Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well. President Joe Biden ordered the withdrawal of U.</description></item><item><title>Wave of suicides hits Texas National Guard’s border mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</guid><description>Operation Lone Star&amp;rsquo;s sudden and rapid expansion has left many Texas guardsmen struggling to balance their military and civilian lives, sometimes with tragic results.
Summary The string of suicides raises urgent questions about the mission’s conditions and purpose, as well as the way it’s organized and manned through indefinite involuntary call-ups, according to the Texas Army National Guard’s former top enlisted soldier. What’s going on out thereThe increased demand for troops on the border meant that the department had to resort to involuntarily activating entire units from the Texas National Guard and mobilizing members of the Texas State Guard.</description></item></channel></rss>