<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>soldiers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soldiers/</link><description>Recent content in soldiers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:16:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soldiers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian mercenaries and Mali army accused of killing 300 civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d4c3a8940161e34f54ad7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d4c3a8940161e34f54ad7/</guid><description>Human Rights Watch says deaths during anti-jihadist operation in Moura ‘the worst atrocity in Mali in a decade’
Highlights Human Rights Watch says 300 civilian men were allegedly executed over five days in March. HRW says it is the worst single atrocity reported in Mali’s decade-long armed conflict. Mali&amp;rsquo;s army has long been accused of rights abuses during counter-insurgency operations. It has forged closer links with Russia after its relations soured with the west – its former ally France – which has committed to scaling down its forces in the Sahel region.</description></item><item><title>80 Ukrainian soldiers believed dead after Russian missile strikes hit barracks as they slept</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236aa7fd7c8d7d117b5c2bf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 04:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236aa7fd7c8d7d117b5c2bf/</guid><description>Up to 200 people are thought to have been inside the barracks in Mykolaiv when they were attacked.
Highlights Up to 200 troops were thought to have been inside the barracks in Mykolaiv when they were targeted. At least 50 bodies have been recovered, a Ukrainian serviceman said. The death toll has not been confirmed by Ukrainian authorities because the attack involved a military site, according to reports. A soldier who survived the attack said he was woken by the sound of explosions at 6am.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s not-so-secret weapon against Russia: an army of volunteers supplying the front - National</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62368d718daaf266c4f4e0a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 02:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62368d718daaf266c4f4e0a9/</guid><description>While NATO countries ship weapons to Ukraine, a far more expansive effort within the country runs supplies to soldiers and civilians on the front lines.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s attempt to seize its western neighbour has triggered Europe’s worst refugee crisis since the Second World War. NATO countries have been shipping anti-tank weapons and air defence systems to Ukraine. But it has also led to a mass mobilization of citizens unseen since then.</description></item><item><title>U.S. soldiers alive, despite Russia 'fake news' report, U.S. military says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 10:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62345b8ba4b7f5189ffa3e76/</guid><description>Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well, the Tennessee National Guard said on Thursday.
Highlights Three current and former members of the Tennessee National Guard falsely identified in a Russian media report as mercenaries who were killed in Ukraine are in fact alive and well. President Joe Biden ordered the withdrawal of U.</description></item><item><title>Wave of suicides hits Texas National Guard’s border mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c634ea74116955ce2e40e5/</guid><description>Operation Lone Star&amp;rsquo;s sudden and rapid expansion has left many Texas guardsmen struggling to balance their military and civilian lives, sometimes with tragic results.
Summary The string of suicides raises urgent questions about the mission’s conditions and purpose, as well as the way it’s organized and manned through indefinite involuntary call-ups, according to the Texas Army National Guard’s former top enlisted soldier. What’s going on out thereThe increased demand for troops on the border meant that the department had to resort to involuntarily activating entire units from the Texas National Guard and mobilizing members of the Texas State Guard.</description></item></channel></rss>