<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>asian on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/asian/</link><description>Recent content in asian on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 17:15:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/asian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man wanted in seven separate attacks against Asian women in one day, NYPD says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220f798ddc05b934c3116d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 17:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220f798ddc05b934c3116d3/</guid><description>The suspect who allegedly attacked seven Asian women over a two-hour period Sunday in Manhattan has been arrested and charged with hate crimes, police announced.
Highlights Steven Zajonc, 28, was arrested Wednesday, charged with seven counts each of assault as a hate crime, aggravated harassment and harassment. He was taken into custody after barricading himself in the New York Public Library. He allegedly punched or hurt seven Asian women over a two-hour period on Sunday in Manhattan.</description></item><item><title>A viewer called to criticize a TV anchor in Missouri over being 'very Asian'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5c0e15220d37632ccb954/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5c0e15220d37632ccb954/</guid><description>A news anchor in Missouri was deeply hurt when a viewer criticized her for being &amp;quot;very Asian&amp;quot; but within hours, Asian Americans across the country stood up for her.
Summary (CNN) A news anchor in Missouri was deeply hurt when a viewer criticized her for being &amp;ldquo;very Asian&amp;rdquo; but within hours, Asian Americans across the country stood up for her. Last week, an unidentified woman called CNN affiliate KSDK in St.</description></item></channel></rss>