<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>inflation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inflation/</link><description>Recent content in inflation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 21:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/inflation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Powell says 'inflation is much too high' and the Fed will take 'necessary steps' to address</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238e9c7f6ed779fe160c797/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 21:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238e9c7f6ed779fe160c797/</guid><description>Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell vowed tough action on inflation, which he said jeopardizes an otherwise strong recovery.
Highlights Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell vowed tough action on inflation, which he said jeopardizes an otherwise strong economic recovery. Powell said interest rate hikes would continue until inflation is under control. The Fed raised interest rates for the first time in more than three years in an attempt to battle inflation that is running at its highest level in 40 years.</description></item><item><title>Doritos bags will now have 5 fewer chips thanks to inflation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232b63ad99ccdb365c3584f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 04:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232b63ad99ccdb365c3584f/</guid><description>The snack&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Frito-Lay, confirmed this week how the snack’s parent company is cutting down on the number of chips in each bag. As a result of inflation, bags of Doritos will now
Highlights Doritos is just the latest snack that has fallen victim to “shrinkflation,” an ever-pervasive phenomenon in which beloved foodstuffs are getting cut down to size due to inflation. Other brands such as Charmin, Bounty, Gatorade, and Crest have also shrunk down their product sizes in order to keep costs tame for consumers.</description></item><item><title>As inflation heats up, 64% of Americans are now living paycheck to paycheck</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</guid><description>The number of Americans living paycheck to paycheck is climbing, despite rising wages.
Highlights The cost of living is growing at the fastest annual pace in about four decades. At the start of 2022, 64% of the U.S. population was living paycheck to paycheck, up from 61% in December. Even among those earning six figures, 48% said they are now living paycheck-to-paycheck. When wages rise at a slower pace than inflation, those paychecks won&amp;rsquo;t go as far at the grocery store and at the gas pump.</description></item><item><title>Most U.S. workers took an inflation pay cut in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62272c503972e986984c59dd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 10:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62272c503972e986984c59dd/</guid><description>Most American workers have taken a pay cut in the past two years - even if they didn’t know it.
Highlights Most American workers have taken a pay cut in the past two years - even if they didn&amp;rsquo;t know it. Rainfall near a half an inch expected in Brevard, North Carolina. Rain in the forecast is expected to fall 90% this week, and rain could fall as high as 90% in the coming days.</description></item></channel></rss>