<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>students on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/students/</link><description>Recent content in students on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:53:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/students/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A mother says her son was sold in a mock slave auction. School district votes unanimously on action plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</guid><description>A North Carolina school board voted unanimously Monday to approve an action plan after reported racial bullying in the district, including a student-organized mock auction of Black students.
Highlights A group of parents and community members had called on the Chatham County School District to make changes after several reported racial bullying instances at schools in the district. Ashley Palmer said her Black son told her that some of his classmates were sold in a mock slave auction at J.</description></item><item><title>Five students charged with hate crimes in 'racially motivated' incident, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 04:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</guid><description>Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children while exclaiming “brown power!” — an incident police are calling a “racially-motivated crime.”
Highlights Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children. They allegedly yelled “It’s Opposite Day!” and “brown power!’ Police are calling the incident a racially motivated crime. In Florida, evidencing prejudice while committing a hate crime is considered a third-degree felony.</description></item><item><title>In Minneapolis strike, teachers say kids aren't all right</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cfed7d659ffb5875f00e7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cfed7d659ffb5875f00e7/</guid><description>Teachers in Minneapolis say they’ve noticed more kids with anxiety and depression
Highlights Teachers in Minneapolis say they’ve noticed more kids with anxiety and depression. One school counselor says she’s seen more fights and drug use. The district is seeking reduced caseloads for special education teachers, school psychologists, social workers and counselors. It&amp;rsquo;s also seeking increased reserves of special education aides and others to help teachers. At least 2,000 Minneapolis teachers, staffers and supporters bundled up for a rally outside the state Capitol on Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>6 West Point cadets overdose on fentanyl during spring break, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cd4746dfe881370939d71/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cd4746dfe881370939d71/</guid><description>Six West Point cadets on spring break in Fort Lauderdale were hospitalized after overdosing on a powder substance laced with the drug fentanyl, police said Friday.
Highlights Six West Point cadets on spring break in Fort Lauderdale were hospitalized after overdosing on a powder substance laced with the drug fentanyl. Authorities in Broward County, Florida, have made an arrest in connection to the overdoses. The names of the students have not been released, though police said the college students are from New York.</description></item><item><title>Two students and ACLU sue Missouri school district over removing 8 books from libraries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210ed2b43aeb25326800481/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210ed2b43aeb25326800481/</guid><description>Two students have sued a Missouri school district over its decision to remove eight books from school libraries, arguing the novels were banned because they discuss issues surrounding race, gender and sexual identity.
Highlights Two students have sued a Missouri school district over its decision to remove eight books from school libraries. The ACLU argues the novels were banned because they discuss issues surrounding race, gender and sexual identity. The lawsuit was filed Tuesday by the American Civil Liberties Union of Missouri (ACLU) against the Wentzville School District on behalf of the students who are minors and not named in the complaint.</description></item><item><title>Anti-mandate protest outside B.C. high school leads to confrontation, protester hurling insults at student</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dda8bcdaa3cb85878f8c5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 05:18:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dda8bcdaa3cb85878f8c5/</guid><description>An anti-mandate protest outside a South Okanagan high school resulted in a verbal confrontation between adults and students and, in one case, a protester yelling a racially charged insult and profanity at a student.
Highlights Incident occurred at Southern Okanagan Secondary School in Oliver, B.C., on Friday, Feb. Students say an anti-mandate protest outside a school resulted in a verbal confrontation between adults and students. In one case, a protester yelled a racially charged insult and profanity at a student.</description></item><item><title>LA schools to require students to wear non-cloth face masks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread. Starting Monday, students must wear “well-fitted, non-cloth masks with a nose wire” at all times, including outdoors, the district announced.
Summary LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread.</description></item><item><title>62,000 Los Angeles students and staff test positive for Covid ahead of return to school Tuesday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</guid><description>As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show.
Summary (CNN) As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show. The Los Angeles Unified School District (LAUSD) is requiring all students and employees to show a negative test result before returning. It is the nation&amp;rsquo;s second largest district, with more than 640,000 students in grades K-12.</description></item><item><title>Taking a step back: US colleges returning to online classes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</guid><description>With COVID-19 cases surging just as students are about to return from winter break, dozens of U.S. colleges are moving classes online again for at least the first week or so of the semester — and some warn it could stretch longer if the wave of infection doesn’t subside soon.
Summary The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online. The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online.</description></item></channel></rss>