<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>students on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/students/</link><description>Recent content in students on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/students/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LA schools to require students to wear non-cloth face masks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread. Starting Monday, students must wear “well-fitted, non-cloth masks with a nose wire” at all times, including outdoors, the district announced.
Summary LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread.</description></item><item><title>62,000 Los Angeles students and staff test positive for Covid ahead of return to school Tuesday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</guid><description>As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show.
Summary (CNN) As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show. The Los Angeles Unified School District (LAUSD) is requiring all students and employees to show a negative test result before returning. It is the nation&amp;rsquo;s second largest district, with more than 640,000 students in grades K-12.</description></item><item><title>Taking a step back: US colleges returning to online classes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</guid><description>With COVID-19 cases surging just as students are about to return from winter break, dozens of U.S. colleges are moving classes online again for at least the first week or so of the semester — and some warn it could stretch longer if the wave of infection doesn’t subside soon.
Summary The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online. The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online.</description></item></channel></rss>