<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>students on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/students/</link><description>Recent content in students on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/students/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rosaries, bouquets and tiny caskets: Uvalde begins to bury its dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295f7758062616263523ef6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295f7758062616263523ef6/</guid><description>In a Texas town scarred by gun massacre, anger and grief gives way to a relentless cycle of mourning as two weeks of funerals begin.
Highlights Funeral home in U.S. reopens for mourners for victims of U.N. school shooting. “There’s going to be a lot of tears and sadness, but as we continue to celebrate their lives, they will turn into tears of joy,” priest says. Funeral director: “It&amp;rsquo;s okay to be angry.</description></item><item><title>‘Blacks only,’ ‘whites only’ signs posted on Colerain HS water fountains, parents say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285dfaa0ed5cfd71381ef10/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 06:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285dfaa0ed5cfd71381ef10/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Let’s make a change. Let’s speak on this stuff. Let’s stop hiding it.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights Signs appeared on the fountains at Colerain High School appeared to segregate the water founts along racial lines. School officials confirm the signs were posted May 5. Northwest Local School District calls the incident “unacceptable on all levels” and a deviation from the district’s “culture of inclusivity, respect, kindness and compassion for everyone” A spokesperson claims the students involved have been issued “significant” disciplinary actions.</description></item><item><title>Anonymous donor clears student debt of Wiley College graduates in Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e3d30916c1a696774ada9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 11:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e3d30916c1a696774ada9/</guid><description>Students graduating from a historically Black college in East Texas were told at their commencement ceremony that an anonymous donor had paid their balances.
Highlights Anonymous donor pays student balances owed to Wiley College in East Texas. The estimated total for the balances owed by the graduating class of 2022 was about $300,000. The 2007 movie “The Great Debaters” starring Denzel Washington was inspired by the 1935 debate in which Wiley prevailed over the University of Southern California’s nationally-known, powerhouse team at a time when the nation was heavily segregated.</description></item><item><title>Gay high schooler says he's 'being silenced' by Florida's LGBTQ law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d5bd804233099d9be3d63/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 19:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d5bd804233099d9be3d63/</guid><description>Florida high school senior Zander Moricz was called into his principal’s office last week.
Highlights Florida high school senior Zander Moricz was called into his principal&amp;rsquo;s office last week. Moricz, 18, was the first openly LGBTQ student to hold the title at Pine View High School in Osprey, Florida. He said he was told if his graduation speech referenced his activism, officials would cut off his microphone and halt the ceremony.</description></item><item><title>Local students hold own Diversity Day after it is cancelled by school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c7ae6a6f30a65d3e634f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 03:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c7ae6a6f30a65d3e634f1/</guid><description>ANDERSON TOWNSHIP, Ohio (WKRC) - Students in the Forest Hills District have been fighting to keep Diversity Day on the calendar. The school board took issue with the tradition of talking about cultural and racial differences. Caption: Local students hold own Diversity Day after it is cancelled by school (WKRC) Diversity Day is officially cancelled for 2022 and will not take place at Turpin High School, but students refuse to accept the board’s decision and will hold Diversity Day off campus.</description></item><item><title>Florida school yearbook on hold over student protest photos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627aac31f46ffe61e07f958b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 18:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627aac31f46ffe61e07f958b/</guid><description>Students at a central Florida high school were told they won’t get their yearbooks until they&amp;rsquo;re censored
Highlights Yearbooks won&amp;rsquo;t be distributed until images of students holding rainbow flags and a “love is love” sign can be covered up. District officials said they don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone thinking that the school supported the students&amp;rsquo; walkout. Florida&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rdquo; law bans classroom instruction on sexual orientation or gender identity in kindergarten through third grade.</description></item><item><title>Georgia high school athletic group bans transgender athletes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273541b1729976094dafbf0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273541b1729976094dafbf0/</guid><description>Amplifying Atlanta
Highlights Georgia High School Association’s executive committee voted unanimously for the change. It will take effect for the next school year. Proponents say transgender girls have an unfair advantage because they were born as stronger males. At least 12 Republican-led states have passed laws banning transgender women or girls in sports. Other GOP states are considering similar bans in other GOP-led sports. Critics say excluding transgender children would send a harmful message to a group that&amp;rsquo;s already vulnerable to suicide or harming themselves.</description></item><item><title>Bogus test taker to be sentenced in college admissions scam</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625169d4cf46c084cb94cc43/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 11:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625169d4cf46c084cb94cc43/</guid><description>A former Florida prep school administrator has been sentenced to prison and a University of Southern California water polo coach has been convicted in the long running college admissions bribery scandal
Highlights A former Florida prep school administrator has been sentenced to prison and a University of Southern California water polo coach has been convicted in the long running college admissions bribery scandal. Mark Riddell, who was paid handsomely to take college entrance exams for wealthy students, was handed a four-month prison sentence, ordered to serve two years of supervised release and forfeit nearly $240,000.</description></item><item><title>First federal lawsuit filed against Florida's "Don't Say Gay" law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624716dc86f17a330bcad78e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 15:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624716dc86f17a330bcad78e/</guid><description>The law &amp;quot;is an unlawful attempt to stigmatize, silence, and erase LGBTQ people in Florida’s public schools.&amp;quot;
Highlights The law bans classroom instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity from kindergarten through 3rd grade. It is the first federal challenge to the law. The law &amp;ldquo;is an unlawful attempt to stigmatize, silence, and erase LGBTQ people in Florida&amp;rsquo;s schools,&amp;rdquo; the group says. The bill was signed by Florida lawmakers on Monday, and is set to be debated by the U.</description></item><item><title>NTSB: Child was driving truck that struck van killing 9</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62342381cf840d6c98840160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 06:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62342381cf840d6c98840160/</guid><description>HOBBS, N.M. (AP) — A 13-year-old was driving the pickup truck that struck a van in West Texas in a fiery collision that killed nine people, including six members of a college golf team and their coach, a National Transportation Safety Board official said Thursday.
Highlights University of the Southwest men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s golf teams were involved in a fatal car crash half a mile north of State Highway 115 on Farm-to-Market Road 1788 in Andrews County.</description></item><item><title>A mother says her son was sold in a mock slave auction. School district votes unanimously on action plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623134d262e3e804e8b9740e/</guid><description>A North Carolina school board voted unanimously Monday to approve an action plan after reported racial bullying in the district, including a student-organized mock auction of Black students.
Highlights A group of parents and community members had called on the Chatham County School District to make changes after several reported racial bullying instances at schools in the district. Ashley Palmer said her Black son told her that some of his classmates were sold in a mock slave auction at J.</description></item><item><title>Five students charged with hate crimes in 'racially motivated' incident, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 04:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</guid><description>Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children while exclaiming “brown power!” — an incident police are calling a “racially-motivated crime.”
Highlights Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children. They allegedly yelled “It’s Opposite Day!” and “brown power!’ Police are calling the incident a racially motivated crime. In Florida, evidencing prejudice while committing a hate crime is considered a third-degree felony.</description></item><item><title>In Minneapolis strike, teachers say kids aren't all right</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cfed7d659ffb5875f00e7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cfed7d659ffb5875f00e7/</guid><description>Teachers in Minneapolis say they’ve noticed more kids with anxiety and depression
Highlights Teachers in Minneapolis say they’ve noticed more kids with anxiety and depression. One school counselor says she’s seen more fights and drug use. The district is seeking reduced caseloads for special education teachers, school psychologists, social workers and counselors. It&amp;rsquo;s also seeking increased reserves of special education aides and others to help teachers. At least 2,000 Minneapolis teachers, staffers and supporters bundled up for a rally outside the state Capitol on Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>6 West Point cadets overdose on fentanyl during spring break, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cd4746dfe881370939d71/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cd4746dfe881370939d71/</guid><description>Six West Point cadets on spring break in Fort Lauderdale were hospitalized after overdosing on a powder substance laced with the drug fentanyl, police said Friday.
Highlights Six West Point cadets on spring break in Fort Lauderdale were hospitalized after overdosing on a powder substance laced with the drug fentanyl. Authorities in Broward County, Florida, have made an arrest in connection to the overdoses. The names of the students have not been released, though police said the college students are from New York.</description></item><item><title>Two students and ACLU sue Missouri school district over removing 8 books from libraries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210ed2b43aeb25326800481/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210ed2b43aeb25326800481/</guid><description>Two students have sued a Missouri school district over its decision to remove eight books from school libraries, arguing the novels were banned because they discuss issues surrounding race, gender and sexual identity.
Highlights Two students have sued a Missouri school district over its decision to remove eight books from school libraries. The ACLU argues the novels were banned because they discuss issues surrounding race, gender and sexual identity. The lawsuit was filed Tuesday by the American Civil Liberties Union of Missouri (ACLU) against the Wentzville School District on behalf of the students who are minors and not named in the complaint.</description></item><item><title>Anti-mandate protest outside B.C. high school leads to confrontation, protester hurling insults at student</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dda8bcdaa3cb85878f8c5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 05:18:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dda8bcdaa3cb85878f8c5/</guid><description>An anti-mandate protest outside a South Okanagan high school resulted in a verbal confrontation between adults and students and, in one case, a protester yelling a racially charged insult and profanity at a student.
Highlights Incident occurred at Southern Okanagan Secondary School in Oliver, B.C., on Friday, Feb. Students say an anti-mandate protest outside a school resulted in a verbal confrontation between adults and students. In one case, a protester yelled a racially charged insult and profanity at a student.</description></item><item><title>LA schools to require students to wear non-cloth face masks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eee93bf13ca2e4ed3a69c8/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread. Starting Monday, students must wear “well-fitted, non-cloth masks with a nose wire” at all times, including outdoors, the district announced.
Summary LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Los Angeles Unified School District said it will prohibit students from wearing cloth masks as the highly transmissible omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread.</description></item><item><title>62,000 Los Angeles students and staff test positive for Covid ahead of return to school Tuesday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</guid><description>As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show.
Summary (CNN) As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show. The Los Angeles Unified School District (LAUSD) is requiring all students and employees to show a negative test result before returning. It is the nation&amp;rsquo;s second largest district, with more than 640,000 students in grades K-12.</description></item><item><title>Taking a step back: US colleges returning to online classes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</guid><description>With COVID-19 cases surging just as students are about to return from winter break, dozens of U.S. colleges are moving classes online again for at least the first week or so of the semester — and some warn it could stretch longer if the wave of infection doesn’t subside soon.
Summary The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online. The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online.</description></item></channel></rss>