<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>desantis on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/desantis/</link><description>Recent content in desantis on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:55:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/desantis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ron DeSantis' press secretary registers as foreign agent after getting dinged by Department of Justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a160e68a90b6ad6e0a441d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a160e68a90b6ad6e0a441d/</guid><description>Georgia on her mind
Highlights Christina Pushaw worked for Georgia&amp;rsquo;s Mikheil Saakashvili between 2018 and 2020. The Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis&amp;rsquo; press secretary registered as a foreign agent this week. Pushaw responded to the report by retweeting conservative supporters and accusing liberals of hypocrisy in their rush to call out her undeclared work. She was also defended by Gov. De Santis during a press conference, calling the story a &amp;ldquo;smear piece&amp;rdquo; Pushaw was the Florida governor&amp;rsquo;s press secretary and spokesperson for the Florida Republican Party, who is a frequent subject of the pages of the Florida Open Source blog, the Palm Beach Post.</description></item><item><title>Florida judge says DeSantis' redistricting map is unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c26c2b704900ae51c2319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 21:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c26c2b704900ae51c2319/</guid><description>The circuit judge is expected to issue a formal order on Thursday or Friday.
Highlights A Florida judge struck down a portion of a redistricting map drawn by Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis&amp;rsquo; and his staff. The new maps make it harder for North Florida voters to elect a Black member of Congress in the 5th congressional district, where nearly half its residents are Black. The judge is expected to issue a formal order on Thursday or Friday to ensure that the maps are not in effect during November&amp;rsquo;s election.</description></item><item><title>Florida Gov. DeSantis signs bill revoking Disney's special district status</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62634efcec7856751f735831/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:58:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62634efcec7856751f735831/</guid><description>Sunsetting the Reedy Creek Improvement District means that local counties will likely be left to foot the bill for potholes and emergency services at Disney World.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law a bill revoking the Walt Disney Company&amp;rsquo;s special district status in the state, just days after the legislation was first introduced. The bill, which would see the Reedy Creek Improvement District dissolved, passed the state Senate on Wednesday and the state&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives on Thursday by a vote of 70-38.</description></item><item><title>‘The governor is an enemy of the people,’ well-known activist says as he’s handcuffed ahead of DeSantis news conference</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4dfa5dd187fb13ff9f722/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4dfa5dd187fb13ff9f722/</guid><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis had a scheduled COVID-19 news conference Tuesday morning at the Florida Department of Health – Duval County in Jacksonville, but it was a well-known activist who showed up at the news conference ahead of the governor who stole the show.
Summary A well-known activist was placed into handcuffs Tuesday after he refused to leave the Department of Health building in Jacksonville ahead of Gov. Ron DeSantis’ scheduled press conference.</description></item></channel></rss>