<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>practices on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/practices/</link><description>Recent content in practices on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 20:14:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California once prohibited Native American fire practices. Now, it's asking tribes to use them to help prevent wildfires.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b519b650c8789a7f70b38/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 20:14:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b519b650c8789a7f70b38/</guid><description>California is calling upon Native American tribes to bring back the once-prohibited practice of lighting controlled burns to help prevent devastating wildfires that have wreaked havoc on the state.
Highlights Gov. Gavin Newsom’s Wildfire and Forest Resilience Task Force has launched a new plan – “Strategic Plan for Expanding the Use of Beneficial Fire” Native American tradition of prescribed, cultural burns will be revived, Newsom says. These burns are purposefully set, low-intensity fires to rid the land of wildfire fuel like debris, scrub, undergrowth and certain grasses.</description></item><item><title>Fort Lauderdale police chief fired over minority-first practices in hiring and promotions, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62247ad9d8c03a5aff85ba95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 09:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62247ad9d8c03a5aff85ba95/</guid><description>The city of Fort Lauderdale has fired its police chief Larry Scirotto, who has been in office for less than a year, following allegations of discriminatory practices for promotions.
Highlights Larry Scirotto was sworn-in as police chief in mid-August. The city of Fort Lauderdale had hired a law firm by November to investigate complaints of discrimination. The law firm&amp;rsquo;s report says he implemented an approach to hiring and promotion that was unfairly focused on minority candidates.</description></item></channel></rss>