<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>delayed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/delayed/</link><description>Recent content in delayed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 18:16:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/delayed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DeSantis staff delayed release of Gaetz associate Halsey Beshears’ spending records</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c8766ef25cabba021e200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c8766ef25cabba021e200/</guid><description>In a move criticized by advocates of Florida’s open government laws, Gov. Ron DeSantis’ staff intervened in a public records request related to a former appointee who is reportedly connected to a federal sex trafficking investigation, documents obtained by News 6 show.
Highlights Gov. Ron DeSantis intervened in a public records request, documents obtained by News 6 show. The governor&amp;rsquo;s staff delayed the release of Halsey Beshears&amp;rsquo; financial records for more than two months.</description></item><item><title>Palestinian baby dies after treatment delayed by Israeli blockade of Gaza</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62480629b2eefebe79cfac36/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62480629b2eefebe79cfac36/</guid><description>Fatima al-Masri, a 19-month-old with a hole in her heart, waited five months for Israel to issue a permit to allow her to travel to Jerusalem for treatment
Highlights Fatima al-Masri, 19 months, died in Gaza after waiting for five months for a permit to leave the blockaded enclave for treatment. She was diagnosed last year with a hole in the heart and died on Friday. Human rights groups say Israel’s blockade of Gaza was responsible for her death.</description></item><item><title>United Airlines preemptively cancels 112 Christmas Eve flights due to COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5701796cb667903e95aaf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 07:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5701796cb667903e95aaf/</guid><description>United and Delta Airlines have preemptively canceled almost 200 Christmas Eve flights, the airlines announced Thursday.
Summary United and Delta Airlines have preemptively canceled almost 200 Christmas Eve flights, the airlines announced Thursday. In a statement, United Airlines blamed the cancellations on staffing shortages due to COVID-19. Eleven of the flights were United, while no Delta flights were canceled today. One of the delayed flights is United, while no Delta flights have been delayed at this time.</description></item></channel></rss>