<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mother on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mother/</link><description>Recent content in mother on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mother/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mother arrested after 3 children found dead inside Southern California home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a814d84cdf4fe815eb109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a814d84cdf4fe815eb109/</guid><description>A Southern California mother and a juvenile believed to be her 16-year-old son have been arrested after three children were found dead inside a San Fernando Valley home Sunday, according to the Los Angeles Police Department.
Highlights Police say they responded to the home in the 22000 block of Victory Boulevard in the West Hills neighborhood around 7:40 a.m. Sunday to calls for an assault with deadly weapon. When the Los Angeles Fire Department arrived at the scene, they pronounced all three children dead.</description></item><item><title>San Jose Kidnapping: 3-Month-Old Baby Found, Suspects in Custody</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626909a0a183b6dd22a3843a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 09:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626909a0a183b6dd22a3843a/</guid><description>A 3-month-old baby who was taken from a San Jose home has been found safe.
Highlights 3-month-old Brandon Cuellar was taken to a hospital as a precaution. The baby was taken for a checkup before being reunited with his mother, sources tell NBC Bay Area. Police said a suspect entered an apartment in the 1000 block of Elm Street on Monday afternoon and took the baby as the child&amp;rsquo;s grandmother was unloading groceries.</description></item><item><title>Teen suspect accused of shooting 16-year-old 22 times free on bond, court records say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</guid><description>The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records.
Summary HOUSTON – The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records. Frank Deleon Jr., 17, was taken into custody Monday and charged with murder for the Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>