<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>probe on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/probe/</link><description>Recent content in probe on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 21:11:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/probe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hate crime probe sought in Mississippi attempted shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620973ec350b2ff4079d19f9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 21:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620973ec350b2ff4079d19f9/</guid><description>Attorneys for a Black delivery driver are calling for a federal hate crimes investigation into the attempted shooting of the driver in Mississippi
Highlights FedEx driver D’Monterrio Gibson, 24, dropped off a package at a house in south Mississippi. He says he noticed a white pickup truck pulling away from another house on the same lot. He said the pickup driver tried to cut him off as he left the driveway.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Pope Benedict XVI admits false statement during abuse probe testimony - Pope Emeritus Benedict XVI has admitted providing false testimony during an investigation into sexual abuse in Germany's Catholic Church.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef2178478ee139df443606/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ef2178478ee139df443606/</guid><description>Pope Emeritus Benedict XVI has admitted to providing false testimony during an investigation into sexual abuse in Germany&amp;rsquo;s Catholic Church.
Summary The life of German Pope Benedict XVI &amp;lsquo;We are pope&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;We are pope&amp;rdquo; reads the headline of Germany&amp;rsquo;s leading tabloid, &amp;ldquo;Bild.&amp;rdquo; The life of German Pope Benedict XVI &amp;lsquo;Scourge&amp;rsquo; of sexual violence Pope Benedict did try to address the issue of sexual abuse, including reaching out to victims. The life of German Pope Benedict XVI Criticism from Germany On his third visit to Germany, Benedict XVI was received by adoring crowds, such as here in Erfurt.</description></item></channel></rss>