<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wanted on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wanted/</link><description>Recent content in wanted on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 06:21:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wanted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Naomi Judd died of self-inflicted firearm wound, Ashley Judd reveals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627df8ba4a924e532e109005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 06:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627df8ba4a924e532e109005/</guid><description>Ashley Judd and her family wanted the world to hear from them how Naomi Judd died.
Highlights Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh was shot and killed in the West Bank Wednesday. Casey White is being held on capital murder charges in Lauderdale County, Florida. Ashley Judd and her family wanted the world to hear from them how Naomi Judd died. The younger Judd appeared in an interview with Diane Sawyer, which aired on “Good Morning America” She and her sister Wynonna Judd announced on April 30 that they had lost their mother “to the disease of mental illness” They said they wanted to shed light on mental illness, explaining that it is “important to make the distinction between the loved one and the disease” READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>I'm shocked by my church leaders in Moscow' - priest in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c74e28e467345088be36d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c74e28e467345088be36d/</guid><description>The Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s war stance has prompted some Ukrainian priests and parishioners to cut ties.
Highlights Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s war stance has prompted some Ukrainian priests and parishioners to cut ties. &amp;ldquo;We were living peacefully until they came. But far from protecting us they bombed and tortured and killed. Now that has changed,&amp;rdquo; says one priest. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>France moves to ban incest for the first time since 1791</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df95ed78cc50f5be42b606/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 03:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df95ed78cc50f5be42b606/</guid><description>In France, incest is legal unless children are involved, but Adrien Taquet, the secretary of state for children, said the government wanted to criminalise incestuous relationships.
Summary The French government is planning to ban incest for the first time since 1791. In an interview with AFP, Mr Taquet said: &amp;lsquo;Whatever the age, you don’t have sexual relations with your father, your son or your daughter. He said he wanted the 18-year threshold for incest to be reviewed, saying he was in favour of a &amp;lsquo;clear ban&amp;rsquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>