<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trafficking on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trafficking/</link><description>Recent content in trafficking on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 03:41:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trafficking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Marshals' operation recovers 16 missing children and uncovers allegations of sex trafficking, agency says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253a333584e9b74ee851209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 03:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253a333584e9b74ee851209/</guid><description>A three-month operation by the US Marshals Service in Louisiana led to the recovery of 16 missing children, the arrest of five individuals and uncovered allegations of sex trafficking in several of the cases, according to the agency.
Highlights The operation, dubbed &amp;ldquo;Fresh Start,&amp;rdquo; took place in the New Orleans area from January 1 of this year until March 31. It was led by the Missing Child Unit of the US Marshals Service Eastern District of Louisiana New Orleans Task Force.</description></item><item><title>US arrests yakuza leader over alleged drugs for missiles deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625088e289e9fc6c6d73c6b5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625088e289e9fc6c6d73c6b5/</guid><description>Japanese organised crime boss and three Thais accused of trying to secure US-made weapons for Myanmar rebels, LTTE.
Highlights Prosecutors say Japanese organised crime boss and three Thais aimed to secure US-made weapons for Myanmar armed groups and Tamil Tigers. Takeshi Ebisawa, Sompak Rukrasaranee, Somphob Singhasiri and Suksan Jullanan were arrested in New York on Monday and Tuesday on drug and arms trafficking and money laundering charges. The four men had been under investigation by US Drug Enforcement Administration agents in Thailand since at least 2019.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell's sex trafficking conviction upheld as US judge refuses retrial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62479e2f599992f1cc89e369/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62479e2f599992f1cc89e369/</guid><description>Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s sex trafficking conviction has been upheld, despite a juror&amp;rsquo;s acknowledgment that he had falsely stated before the trial that he had not been sexually abused.
Highlights Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s sex trafficking conviction has been upheld by a US judge. The 60-year-old Briton was convicted in December of helping Jeffrey Epstein to sexually abuse teenage girls. Maxwell requested a retrial after it emerged that one of the jurors had been sexually abused but had falsely stated before the trial that he had not been.</description></item><item><title>Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 22:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</guid><description>The 44-year-old woman who was filmed in a TikTok video, had been sold at least three times, Chinese officials said.
Highlights Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say. Chinese authorities say she had been sold at least three times, first when she was 20 years old. She was discovered after being filmed in a TikTok video. A man claiming to be her husband said she was mentally ill.</description></item><item><title>Lawsuit accuses Cincinnati health staffing company of labor trafficking</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e11463a5faaf5bd96139b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 09:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e11463a5faaf5bd96139b/</guid><description>A health care staffing company based in Cincinnati is being sued by workers it recruited from the Philippines, who are accusing the company of violating federal and state human trafficking laws.
Highlights Fast-growing Health Carousel is headquartered in Cincinnati, has an Austin Landing office, and in recent years has acquired other Dayton-area staffing firms. The lawsuit was first filed in March 2020 and is seeking class action status. The plaintiffs are still working on getting certification for their proposed class action lawsuit.</description></item></channel></rss>