<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>armor on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/armor/</link><description>Recent content in armor on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 15:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/armor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Red Dawn’ hits Ukraine after destroyed Russian armor gets tagged with ‘Wolverines’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251a3d1b9537cb907086159/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 15:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251a3d1b9537cb907086159/</guid><description>A recent photo from Ukraine shows an abandoned Russian BMP-2 graffitied with &amp;quot;Wolverines&amp;quot; in an apparent reference to the movie &amp;quot;Red Dawn.&amp;quot;
Highlights A photo shows an abandoned Russian BMP-2 with the word “Wolverines” scrawled on the side in white spray paint in an apparent homage to the 1984 Cold War-era action flick “Red Dawn’s” A Ukrainian oil and gas company head snapped a photo of the vehicle. The photo was shared to Twitter on Thursday in response to a tweet by NPR&amp;rsquo;s White House correspondent, Scott Detrow, who wrote that “We were driving too fast to get a clear picture – but we just drove past a destroyed Russian tank with WOLVERINES spraypainted across it.</description></item><item><title>16-year-old killed when teens wearing body armor take turns shooting at each other in Florida, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250978f6d6c0ae440f105bb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 20:14:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250978f6d6c0ae440f105bb/</guid><description>A 16-year-old boy was killed when he and another teen took turns shooting at each other while wearing a form of body armor, according to police.
Highlights Joshua Vining and Colton Whitler, both 17, were arrested Thursday in connection with the fatal shooting of Christopher Leroy Broad Jr. Police said Vining fatally shot Broad as the two were taking turns shooting at each other while wearing a vest containing “a form of body armor” An 18-year-old who was with the group — identified as Evan Vowell — recorded the shooting on his cell phone and turned over the footage to be used as evidence.</description></item></channel></rss>