<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>district on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/district/</link><description>Recent content in district on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/district/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Texas school district asks parents to become substitute teachers amid COVID surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</guid><description>According to Hays CISD, parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation to become substitute teachers.
Summary The Hays Consolidated Independent School District (Hays CISD) in Kyle is asking parents to consider applying to become a substitute teacher as coronavirus continues to surge across Texas. According to Hays CISD, the parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation.</description></item></channel></rss>