<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>district on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/district/</link><description>Recent content in district on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 06:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/district/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>16-year-old arrested; planned shooting with explosives at Berkeley High, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629854a55d246e7940b39938/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 06:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629854a55d246e7940b39938/</guid><description>A 16-year-old boy was arrested after recruiting others to participate in a mass school shooting that could have included a bombing at Berkeley High School, police say.
Highlights Berkeley, California, police say they received a tip on Saturday that the boy was recruiting others in plans of a shooting that included explosives. Police say they discovered parts to explosives and assault rifles, several knives, and electronic items that could be used to create additional weapons.</description></item><item><title>Ban on protests in front of homes signed by Gov. DeSantis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282f3f312e8507aa5dab823/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 01:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282f3f312e8507aa5dab823/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Anyone who protests in front of a private residence in Florida can face jail time and fines under a bill Republican Gov. Ron DeSantis signed Monday. The legislation makes it a second-degree misdemeanor to protest in a manner that is aimed at intentionally harassing or disturbing someone in their home.
Highlights Ban on protests in front of homes signed by Gov. DeSantis. Florida governor said the new law will prevent protests in Florida like those waged by abortion rights protesters.</description></item><item><title>21 people were injured in shootings in downtown Milwaukee; Mayor Johnson imposes curfew Saturday night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628127e5baac9bf6b4717134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628127e5baac9bf6b4717134/</guid><description>Eleven people are in custody, 10 guns were recovered and all the victims are expected to survive after three shootings near the Deer District and Water Street in Milwaukee following the Bucks Game 6 playoff game.
Highlights Milwaukee Mayor Cavalier Johnson imposes curfew Saturday night for under-21s. Mayor: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re going to do something about what happened here in this neighborhood last night&amp;rdquo; 11 people, ranging in age from 19 to 30, were arrested and 10 guns were recovered.</description></item><item><title>17 people shot on N. Water St. Friday night, Milwaukee police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628053c6389460d8cae0b735/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628053c6389460d8cae0b735/</guid><description>17 people were shot on Water St. in downtown Milwaukee Friday night, according to Milwaukee Police.
Highlights 17 people were shot on Water St. in downtown Milwaukee Friday night. Police say it happened just after 11:00 p.m. Friday in the 1100 block of N. Water St., near E. Highland Ave. The victims range from 15 to 47 years of age, police say. Police and Mayor Cavalier Johnson held a press conference Saturday afternoon to address Friday&amp;rsquo;s violence.</description></item><item><title>One of Ahmaud Arbery's killers had 16 phone calls with DA before arrest, court filings say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275da44488a5a806f788401/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275da44488a5a806f788401/</guid><description>In the weeks following the fatal shooting of Ahmaud Arbery, Greg McMichael, one of the men later convicted in Arbery&amp;rsquo;s death, participated in 16 phone calls with the former Brunswick Judicial Circuit District Attorney Jackie Johnson, according to court documents filed in the Superior Court of Glynn County on Wednesday.
Highlights The three men were found guilty in February of trying to run away from each other. The three were sentenced to life in prison.</description></item><item><title>Millions must cut water use in drought-stricken California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694624aeedfccb4efc7c16/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 13:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694624aeedfccb4efc7c16/</guid><description>Southern California&amp;rsquo;s water supplier requires 6 million people to cut their outdoor watering to one day a week as drought continues to plague the state. The board of the Metropolitan Water District of Southern California declared a water shortage emergency and required the cutback
Highlights Southern California&amp;rsquo;s largest water supplier requires 6 million people to cut outdoor watering to one day a week as drought continues to plague the state. The board of the Metropolitan Water District of Southern California declared a water shortage emergency and required the cities and water agencies it supplies to implement the cutback on June 1 and enforce it or face hefty fines.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court declines to block elite high school’s new admissions policy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269250de27efce9be21a1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269250de27efce9be21a1ca/</guid><description>The Supreme Court declined to block a top-rated high school from using an admissions plan that a community group says discriminates against Asian Americans.
Highlights Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology changed its admission system two years ago. The school did away with a requirement to take three standardized tests, submit an essay and get teacher recommendations. The new system requires applicants to have taken a rigorous load of middle school courses with a high grade-point average.</description></item><item><title>Beijing races to contain 'urgent and grim' Covid outbreak as Shanghai lockdown continues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62660ce5ce46c457e8275cd1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 02:53:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62660ce5ce46c457e8275cd1/</guid><description>Beijing is racing to track a Covid-19 outbreak that may have been spreading in the capital for a week, city authorities said over the weekend, raising the prospect more stringent restrictions could soon be implemented in line with other Chinese cities.
Highlights Beijing is racing to track a Covid-19 outbreak that may have been spreading in the capital for a week. The capital recorded 19 new local cases on Sunday, bringing the total in the city since April 22 to 60.</description></item><item><title>Philadelphia toddler dies after being shot at drugs deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626585a0ae6503a079253902/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626585a0ae6503a079253902/</guid><description>The district attorney said there is reason to believe the cause of death was due to the original injuries from the shooting in 2019.
Highlights Yaseem Jenkins, who was just 11 months at the time of the shooting, died on Tuesday, according to a statement by his family. The district attorney said they are awaiting an inquest report to establish the cause of death, but said they have reason to believe the three-year-old died due to his original injuries from the incident three years ago.</description></item><item><title>Gravity Payments CEO Dan Price charged with sexual assault amid ongoing felony rape investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62630ca7995bccd28c2b8bc3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 20:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62630ca7995bccd28c2b8bc3/</guid><description>Gravity Payments CEO Dan Price has been charged with two counts of fourth-degree assault and one count of reckless driving. The charges stem from an alleged assault with sexual motivation. Price is also being investigated for “felony rape of
Highlights Dan Price has been charged with two counts of fourth-degree assault and one count of reckless driving in Seattle Municipal Court. The charges stem from an alleged assault with sexual motivation.</description></item><item><title>Plan to search school lunches, limit snacks sparks backlash in Pennsylvania district</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e109db9a60ce902354f2b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 22:14:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e109db9a60ce902354f2b/</guid><description>A Pennsylvania school on Monday started limiting the amount of snacks students can bring to school, sparking outrage from some parents.
Highlights Facebook post from Aliquippa School District in Pennsylvania said students had started bringing &amp;ldquo;excessive amounts of outside snacks,&amp;rdquo; like shopping bags full of chips and canned drinks. Anything more than one 4-ounce bag of chips, one beverage up to 20 ounces will be thrown out by security. District superintendent said decision to limit snacks was made because students were selling and trading food, causing distractions.</description></item><item><title>Pennsylvania high school on lockdown after shooting, district says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c945614e63c644e1d6e44/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 19:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c945614e63c644e1d6e44/</guid><description>A student at Erie High School in Pennsylvania was injured during a shooting Monday morning, and a person of interest fled, according to officials.
Highlights Multiple shots were fired at Erie High School shortly after 9:20 a.m., Erie’s Public Schools said in a statement. One student was injured but stable, the district said in the afternoon. Police are searching for a person of interest who fled the campus. The school will be closed leading up to spring break, which begins next week, according to district.</description></item><item><title>In Minneapolis strike, teachers say kids aren't all right</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cfed7d659ffb5875f00e7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cfed7d659ffb5875f00e7/</guid><description>Teachers in Minneapolis say they’ve noticed more kids with anxiety and depression
Highlights Teachers in Minneapolis say they’ve noticed more kids with anxiety and depression. One school counselor says she’s seen more fights and drug use. The district is seeking reduced caseloads for special education teachers, school psychologists, social workers and counselors. It&amp;rsquo;s also seeking increased reserves of special education aides and others to help teachers. At least 2,000 Minneapolis teachers, staffers and supporters bundled up for a rally outside the state Capitol on Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Minneapolis school teachers call a strike; classes canceled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62287dcd67fc0059580cec29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62287dcd67fc0059580cec29/</guid><description>Minneapolis public school teachers called a strike on Monday, their first for more than 50 years, leading the school district to cancel classes for 30,000 students beginning Tuesday until the work stoppage is resolved.
Highlights Some 4,500 teachers and support staff plan to form picket lines at school buildings on Tuesday morning and hold a rally and march in the afternoon. Teachers are demanding better wages, mental health support and limits on class sizes.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee woman accused of trading items for sexual encounters with 9 high school students</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215de457eb39a996791f944/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 07:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215de457eb39a996791f944/</guid><description>Melissa A. Blair, of Englewood, Tennessee, is accused of having sexual encounters with nine high school boys for more than a year, authorities say.
Highlights Melissa A. Blair, 38, of Englewood, Tennessee, is accused of exchanging items for sexual encounters with nine high school boys she spoke with on social media. She was indicted on Feb. 15 on 23 charges, including 18 counts of aggravated statutory rape, four counts of human trafficking by patronizing prostitution and one count of solicitation of a minor.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco Police reportedly link woman to crime using DNA taken from her rape kit San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 15:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</guid><description>San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out
Highlights San Francisco police used DNA collected from rape exam to link a woman to a crime, district attorney says. District attorney Chesa Boudin says use of victims’ DNA could violate the state&amp;rsquo;s Victims’ Bill of Rights as well as constitutional laws related to unreasonable searches and seizures. State senator Scott Wiener, who represents the city, says lawmakers are seeking to determine whether a change in state law was needed to prevent the practice.</description></item><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Texas school district asks parents to become substitute teachers amid COVID surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</guid><description>According to Hays CISD, parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation to become substitute teachers.
Summary The Hays Consolidated Independent School District (Hays CISD) in Kyle is asking parents to consider applying to become a substitute teacher as coronavirus continues to surge across Texas. According to Hays CISD, the parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation.</description></item></channel></rss>