<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>district on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/district/</link><description>Recent content in district on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 07:12:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/district/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tennessee woman accused of trading items for sexual encounters with 9 high school students</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215de457eb39a996791f944/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 07:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215de457eb39a996791f944/</guid><description>Melissa A. Blair, of Englewood, Tennessee, is accused of having sexual encounters with nine high school boys for more than a year, authorities say.
Highlights Melissa A. Blair, 38, of Englewood, Tennessee, is accused of exchanging items for sexual encounters with nine high school boys she spoke with on social media. She was indicted on Feb. 15 on 23 charges, including 18 counts of aggravated statutory rape, four counts of human trafficking by patronizing prostitution and one count of solicitation of a minor.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco Police reportedly link woman to crime using DNA taken from her rape kit San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 15:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</guid><description>San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out
Highlights San Francisco police used DNA collected from rape exam to link a woman to a crime, district attorney says. District attorney Chesa Boudin says use of victims’ DNA could violate the state&amp;rsquo;s Victims’ Bill of Rights as well as constitutional laws related to unreasonable searches and seizures. State senator Scott Wiener, who represents the city, says lawmakers are seeking to determine whether a change in state law was needed to prevent the practice.</description></item><item><title>3 Pennsylvania officers charged in shooting death of 8-year-old girl at high school football game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 03:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e77ed18c32e7000a405e34/</guid><description>Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl at a high school football game.
Summary Criminal charges have been filed against three Pennsylvania police officers in connection with the shooting death of an 8-year-old girl and the wounding of three others at a high school football game last year. The girl, Fanta Bility, was killed on Aug. 27 when gunfire broke out shortly after the conclusion of a game at Academy Park High School in Sharon Hill, a community of about 5,700 residents near the Philadelphia International Airport.</description></item><item><title>Texas school district asks parents to become substitute teachers amid COVID surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</guid><description>According to Hays CISD, parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation to become substitute teachers.
Summary The Hays Consolidated Independent School District (Hays CISD) in Kyle is asking parents to consider applying to become a substitute teacher as coronavirus continues to surge across Texas. According to Hays CISD, the parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation.</description></item></channel></rss>