<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>donald on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/donald/</link><description>Recent content in donald on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 03:36:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/donald/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Utah hunting guide faces felony charge for Donald Trump Jr.’s big-game hunt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289af7a326f453252954bcc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 03:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289af7a326f453252954bcc/</guid><description>Prosecutors have indicated there was no evidence showing Trump Jr. would have known about alleged baiting that went on during the hunt.
Highlights Utah hunting guide Wade Lemon faces five years in state prison for the death of a bear killed during a guided hunt on May 18, 2018. Donald Trump Jr. was in Utah to help launch Hunter Nation, a hunting advocacy group. The group would later launch its own super PAC, Hunter Nation Action, which spent $96,997 in ads against Democrats in the 2020 election.</description></item><item><title>New York Attorney General asks judge to hold Donald Trump in contempt for refusing to turn over documents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f53b199f7ef8e298cdcea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 21:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f53b199f7ef8e298cdcea/</guid><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James also asked the judge to fine Trump $10,000 per day for refusing to comply with an order to turn over documents.
Highlights New York Attorney General Letitia James wants to hold former President Donald Trump in contempt of court for refusing to comply with a judge&amp;rsquo;s order to turn over documents. James is investigating allegations that the Trump Organization manipulated the stated values of various real estate assets to get better financial terms when applying for loans and insurance, and for tax purposes.</description></item><item><title>January 6 Committee issues subpoena for Kimberly Guilfoyle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622192654cb35a99cdb818a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 04:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622192654cb35a99cdb818a1/</guid><description>The House select committee investigating the January 6 Capitol Hill riot has issued a subpoena for Kimberly Guilfoyle, a former Donald Trump campaign aide and the fiancée of Donald Trump Jr., the son of the former President.
Highlights Kimberly Guilfoyle’s subpoena comes after an ill-fated attempt by the committee to get her to cooperate voluntarily. She abruptly ended the proceedings because she was unhappy that members of the committee were participating in the deposition.</description></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani, three other Trump allies subpoenaed in January 6 riot probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</guid><description>Former New York mayor Rudy Giuliani Giuliani led efforts for Trump after the 2020 election to challenge results that showed President Joe Biden had won.
Summary Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, personal attorney to U.S. President Donald Trump, speaks in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 7, 2020. Eduardo Munoz | ReutersThe select House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot on Tuesday issued subpoenas to Rudy Giuliani, another former lawyer for ex-President Donald Trump, and two other allies.</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump golf resorts claimed at least £3.3m in UK furlough support: Former US president’s two Scottish resorts claimed emergency support during Covid pandemic.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cafc7a09274a986eb67dee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 12:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cafc7a09274a986eb67dee/</guid><description>Former US president’s two Scottish resorts claimed emergency support during Covid pandemic
Summary Donald Trump’s loss-making Scottish golf resorts claimed in excess of £3.3m in emergency support from the UK government, to help furlough staff during the Covid pandemic. Other government data shows Trump Turnberry and Trump International Scotland in Aberdeenshire then made further claims this year while the UK government’s job retention scheme was still in force. Global controls on air travel, particularly from the US golfing visitors; the impacts on staffing, supply chains and costs from Brexit; and general inflation, had all hit the Trump businesses, he added.</description></item></channel></rss>