<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wife on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wife/</link><description>Recent content in wife on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:17:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wife/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Estranged husband shot wife, 4-year-old daughter, mother-in-law before killing himself, sheriff says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287cd0be0040f439efdbe12/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287cd0be0040f439efdbe12/</guid><description>The Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office is investigating a shooting with at least four people dead. Murder-suicide may be involved.
Highlights NEW: Harris County Sheriff Ed Gonzalez says the man appeared to have shot his wife and his mother-in-law before turning the gun on himself. NEW: The husband and wife were going through a divorce in recent months, and there were reports of the man being abusive to his 4-year-old daughter, the sheriff says.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelensky Says Russian Troops Came Close To Capturing Him And His Family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c0fedd00fe590fad89470/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 16:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c0fedd00fe590fad89470/</guid><description>The Ukrainian leader is praised globally for his courage amid the Russian attack. Zelensky refused US offer to leave the country.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said in a recent interview that Russian troops came very close to capturing him and his family. He made the revelation while speaking to Time magazine, while recalling the intense early days of the Ukraine war. Russian President Vladimir Putin announced the invasion on February 24, and Zelenski recalled from the memories that exist “in a fragmented way” The President said he was informed that a Russian strike teams had parachuted into Kyiv to kill or capture him and.</description></item><item><title>Man who spent 19 years in a coma before regaining awareness dies at 57</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a67340a9fe525ee99286d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 03:34:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a67340a9fe525ee99286d/</guid><description>Terry Wayne Wallis, the man who spent 19 years in a coma before he regained awareness in 2003, has died, according to an obituary. He was 57.
Highlights Terry Wayne Wallis, of Big Flat, Arkansas, was in a car accident in 1984. He was minimally conscious, but doctors believed he would remain forever in a coma. Instead, he started talking in 2003, believing no time had passed. Wallis became known as “The Man Who Slept for 19 Years,&amp;quot; inspiring headlines like “Miracle in Arkansas&amp;quot; He first recognized his mother and asked for milk and Pepsi, according to the BBC in July 2003.</description></item><item><title>Curtis Reeves, retired police captain who fatally shot man in movie theater, acquitted</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a35418f0f606d551f953d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 14:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a35418f0f606d551f953d/</guid><description>A Florida jury acquitted retired Florida police captain Curtis Reeves in the shooting death of a man in a movie theater eight years ago.
Highlights Curtis Reeves was accused of second-degree murder and aggravated battery in the 2014 killing of Chad Oulson. Reeves pleaded not guilty and claimed self-defense, saying he feared he would be attacked. The case garnered widespread attention at the time of the killing, partly because of Reeves&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;stand your ground&amp;rdquo; claim.</description></item><item><title>After 8 years, a retired Florida police captain will stand trial for killing a man in an argument about texting in a movie theater</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8038a60eb127de16e169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8038a60eb127de16e169/</guid><description>A 79-year-old man is finally expected to stand trial this week, eight years after he fatally shot a man who was texting in a Florida movie theater.
Highlights Curtis Reeves, 79, fatally shot Chad Oulson in January 2014, eight years after he got into an argument over texting. The case garnered widespread attention in part due to the defendants&amp;rsquo; self defense claim under Florida&amp;rsquo;s controversial &amp;ldquo;stand your ground&amp;rdquo; law. A judge denied that the law did not apply in this case, forcing it to trial.</description></item><item><title>New Details Reportedly Emerge Alleging Alex Jones' Wife Struck Him Over 20 Times, Left Right-Wing Radio Host In "Fear For His Life" During Christmas Eve Domestic Assault</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cab6254e35b94c2809f2ea/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cab6254e35b94c2809f2ea/</guid><description>Summary And apparently, it was so bad that it left the Right-wing radio lost in “fear for his life,” according to police documents obtained and reviewed by the publication. Wulff Jones was ultimately arrested on Christmas Eve night following the domestic assault, outside the couple’s Austin, Texas, home. Alex was quick with a statement in response to the reports, telling the Associated Press, “It’s a private family matter that happened on Christmas Eve.</description></item></channel></rss>