<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>double on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/double/</link><description>Recent content in double on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 19:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/double/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pfizer accused of pandemic profiteering as profits double</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620411a27dc2ee05167d53a8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 19:11:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620411a27dc2ee05167d53a8/</guid><description>Drugmaker makes $37bn in vaccine sales and predicts bumper year ahead from Covid jabs and pill
Highlights Pfizer forecast another bumper year in 2022, with a big boost coming from its Covid-19 pill Paxlovid. The US drugmaker&amp;rsquo;s overall revenues in 2021 doubled to $81.3bn. The bumper sales prompted accusations from campaigners of ‘pandemic profiteering’ The group Global Justice Now said the annual revenue of $81bn was more than the GDP of most countries.</description></item><item><title>Israeli PM announces plan to double the amount of settlers living in Golan Heights — a multimillion dollar project meant to further consolidate Israel's hold on the territory it captured from Syria more than five decades ago</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8d7eff9cd1fcdb7a049f2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8d7eff9cd1fcdb7a049f2/</guid><description>Israel says it plans to double the amount of settlers living in the Golan Heights and invest hundreds of millions of dollars developing the area
Summary Israel says it plans to double the amount of settlers living in the Golan Heights and invest hundreds of millions of dollars developing the areaMEVO HAMA, Golan Heights &amp;ndash; Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett said Sunday the country intends to double the amount of settlers living in the Israeli-controlled Golan Heights with a multimillion-dollar plan meant to further consolidate Israel’s hold on the territory it captured from Syria more than five decades ago.</description></item></channel></rss>