<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>report on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/report/</link><description>Recent content in report on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Capitol Police intelligence official says she sounded alarm about potential violence days before January 6 riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</guid><description>&amp;quot;We knew there were going to be thousands of protesters. And we knew there were gonna be extremists there,&amp;quot; the official said.
Summary Three days before the January 6 riot, a top Capitol Police intelligence official sounded the alarm about potential violence at the U.S. Capitol. Julie Farnam, now the acting director of intelligence for the Capitol Police, had been with the department for 72 days when violent protestors attacked the Capitol on January 6th.</description></item><item><title>Police: 2nd person arrested after child says she was locked in closet for 25 days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7beade982a21ad8b2876e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 01:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7beade982a21ad8b2876e/</guid><description>Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant.
Summary Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant. JACKSONVILLE, Fla. – Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant.</description></item><item><title>Uber driver charged with raping passenger during Vegas ride</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c715e9017344910229fb6a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 13:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c715e9017344910229fb6a/</guid><description>An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police say fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las Vegas
Summary An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police say fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las VegasLAS VEGAS &amp;ndash; An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police said fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las Vegas.</description></item><item><title>Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. This increase was exacerbated during the Covid pandemic. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 13:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</guid><description>Report calls for a “modest progressive wealth tax on global multimillionaires” in order to redistribute wealth.
Summary PARIS: The share of global wealth of the world’s richest people soared at a record pace during the Covid pandemic, a report on inequality showed on Tuesday. Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires’ share of wealth on record,” the document said.</description></item></channel></rss>