<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>report on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/report/</link><description>Recent content in report on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pelosi's husband arrested for DUI</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293fd2b637fd27ae83c57ca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293fd2b637fd27ae83c57ca/</guid><description>House Speaker Nancy Pelosi&amp;rsquo;s husband was arrested for driving under the influence, according to the Napa County Criminal Justice Network&amp;rsquo;s public booking report.
Highlights Paul Pelosi, 82, was arrested at 11:44 p.m. PT Saturday and charged with driving under the influence and driving with a blood alcohol content of 0.08% or higher. Both charges are misdemeanors. The speaker was in Rhode Island on Sunday to speak at Brown University’s commencement ceremony.</description></item><item><title>Rents in the US just hit another record high</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62875aeead586c408d73c731/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 09:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62875aeead586c408d73c731/</guid><description>Rents in the US climbed to a new record high again in April, and they are expected to keep rising.
Highlights The national median rent was $1,827 a month in April, up 16.7% from a year ago. If recent trends continue, the typical rent could be more than $2,000 a month by August. The continued surge in rental prices is driven by a mismatch between rental supply and rising demand, says Realtor.</description></item><item><title>Army officer who reported Trump probably faced retaliation, inquiry finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286b217023b102e0a6eaae8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 21:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286b217023b102e0a6eaae8/</guid><description>Yevgeny Vindman, a former White House adviser, &amp;quot;was the subject of unfavorable personnel actions&amp;quot; after raising alarm about President Donald Trump’s actions toward Ukraine, the Defense Department&amp;rsquo;s inspector general determined.
Highlights Yevgeny Vindman and his twin brother raised alarm about President Trump’s actions toward Ukraine. The report says it is “more likely than not’t” that the Army officer was the subject of ‘unfair personnel actions’ that were in reprisal for his communications with superiors.</description></item><item><title>Post-Floyd probe finds discrimination by Minneapolis police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a31eb977fe2b8190c7b9e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a31eb977fe2b8190c7b9e/</guid><description>ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — The Minneapolis Police Department has engaged in a pattern of race discrimination for at least a decade, including stopping and arresting Black people at a higher rate than white people, using force more often on people of color and maintaining a culture where racist language is tolerated, a state investigation launched after George Floyd’s killing found.
Highlights Minnesota Department of Human Rights released report Wednesday. Report: Minneapolis Police Department engaged in a pattern of race discrimination for at least a decade.</description></item><item><title>US home prices are rising so fast, property taxes can't keep up</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fb293edb62d9e3ee27dfe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 07:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fb293edb62d9e3ee27dfe/</guid><description>Home prices skyrocketed last year and, as expected, property taxes have followed.
Highlights The average property tax on a single-family home rose by 1.8% last year to $3,785. That has resulted in an effective tax rate of 0.9%, down from 1.1% in 2020. But this small silver lining in the housing market may not last long, a real estate data company says. &amp;ldquo;Tax assessments are lagging behind rising property values, and will likely continue to go up in 2022,&amp;rdquo; a market intelligence expert says.</description></item><item><title>Army report finds horses that carry the coffins of America's heroes live in 'unsatisfactory' conditions, after 2 die</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625042c77211b14eee386296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 14:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625042c77211b14eee386296/</guid><description>The military horses that carry America&amp;rsquo;s heroes to their final resting place in Arlington National Cemetery are living in unsanitary and potentially life-threatening conditions, according to a US Army report reviewed exclusively by CNN, consuming poor-quality feed, suffering from parasites and standing in their own excrement in tiny mud lots scattered with gravel and construction waste.
Highlights A US Army report reviewed exclusively by CNN found a host of systemic problems with the living conditions of the horses in the 3rd Infantry Regiment, also called the Old Guard, best known for guarding the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier.</description></item><item><title>New FBI documents link Saudi spy in California to 9/11 attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623430e744fcd7fe5a34ebdc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 07:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623430e744fcd7fe5a34ebdc/</guid><description>A new batch of previously secret FBI documents confirms that US authorities knew that a Saudi man who helped 9/11 hijackers was, in fact, a Saudi spy.
Highlights New FBI documents link Saudi spy in California to 9/11 attacks. FBI concluded five years ago that there was a &amp;ldquo;50/50 chance&amp;rdquo; that this Saudi spy knew ahead of time that the two Islamists he befriended were about to join the plot to hijack commercial jetliners and crash them into buildings in what turned out to be America&amp;rsquo;s deadliest terrorist attack.</description></item><item><title>Watchdog finds DHS identified threats prior to January 6 but did not widely share intelligence until after attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622846192ceb355fd1e97aad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 06:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622846192ceb355fd1e97aad/</guid><description>The Department of Homeland Security intelligence division had identified &amp;quot;specific&amp;quot; threats related to January 6, 2021, prior to the attack on the US Capitol, but did not widely share any intelligence it had gathered until two days after the riot, according to a new watchdog report.
Highlights DHS intelligence division had identified “specific” threats related to January 6, 2021, prior to the attack on the US Capitol, a new watchdog report says.</description></item><item><title>Florida mom finds toddler locked inside day care after workers left for the day</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62114f4e214d6ddc659c492c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62114f4e214d6ddc659c492c/</guid><description>Authorities are investigating a Florida day care center where a mother found her 2-year-old daughter alone and locked inside after workers left for the day,
Highlights Authorities are investigating a Florida day care center where a mother found her 2-year-old daughter alone and locked inside after workers left for the day. The case was being investigated by the local child protection agency. The day care worker responsible for checking out children left at 6:20 p.</description></item><item><title>Police Reports Detail Battery Allegations Against Chris Brown in Miami Beach</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e74f216d387819b310c08/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e74f216d387819b310c08/</guid><description>Miami Beach Police are investigating allegations of battery by two women against R&amp;amp;B singer Chris Brown, according to police reports obtained by NBC 6.
Highlights NBC 6 Investigators obtained copies of police reports which detail what both women said happened when they were with Brown while visiting Miami Beach. Both alleged assaults took place more than a year ago, with the first woman claiming she was drugged and raped by the 32-year-old singer while at a party on a yacht that was docked near Diddy&amp;rsquo;s home on Dec.</description></item><item><title>Pope Benedict XVI knew of abusive priests when he ran Munich archdiocese, investigators say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea7637a83375790c39bf3e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 09:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea7637a83375790c39bf3e/</guid><description>Pope Benedict XVI knew about priests who abused children but failed to act when he was archbishop of Munich from 1977 to 1982, an inquest found Thursday, rejecting Benedict&amp;rsquo;s long-standing denials in a damning judgment.
Summary Berlin (CNN) Pope Benedict XVI knew about priests who abused children but failed to act when he was archbishop of Munich from 1977 to 1982, an inquest found Thursday, rejecting Benedict&amp;rsquo;s long-standing denials in a damning judgment.</description></item><item><title>The world's 10 wealthiest men doubled their fortunes during the first two years of the coronavirus pandemic as poverty and inequality soared. Oxfam said the men's wealth jumped from $700 billion to $1.5 trillion, at an average rate of $1.3 billion per day</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5223c93e2d7f552f904bd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5223c93e2d7f552f904bd/</guid><description>The world&amp;rsquo;s 10 wealthiest men doubled their fortunes during the first two years of the coronavirus pandemic as poverty and inequality soared, a report said on Monday.
Summary Oxfam said the wealth of the world&amp;rsquo;s 10 richest men jumped from $700 billion to $1.5 trillion during the pandemicParis (AFP) – The world&amp;rsquo;s 10 wealthiest men doubled their fortunes during the first two years of the coronavirus pandemic as poverty and inequality soared, a report said on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Capitol Police intelligence official says she sounded alarm about potential violence days before January 6 riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</guid><description>&amp;quot;We knew there were going to be thousands of protesters. And we knew there were gonna be extremists there,&amp;quot; the official said.
Summary Three days before the January 6 riot, a top Capitol Police intelligence official sounded the alarm about potential violence at the U.S. Capitol. Julie Farnam, now the acting director of intelligence for the Capitol Police, had been with the department for 72 days when violent protestors attacked the Capitol on January 6th.</description></item><item><title>Police: 2nd person arrested after child says she was locked in closet for 25 days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7beade982a21ad8b2876e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 01:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7beade982a21ad8b2876e/</guid><description>Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant.
Summary Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant. JACKSONVILLE, Fla. – Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant.</description></item><item><title>Uber driver charged with raping passenger during Vegas ride</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c715e9017344910229fb6a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 13:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c715e9017344910229fb6a/</guid><description>An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police say fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las Vegas
Summary An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police say fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las VegasLAS VEGAS &amp;ndash; An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police said fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las Vegas.</description></item><item><title>Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. This increase was exacerbated during the Covid pandemic. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 13:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c472ebd145ec6ce6474775/</guid><description>Report calls for a “modest progressive wealth tax on global multimillionaires” in order to redistribute wealth.
Summary PARIS: The share of global wealth of the world’s richest people soared at a record pace during the Covid pandemic, a report on inequality showed on Tuesday. Since 1995, the slice held by billionaires has risen from one percent to three percent, according to the World Inequality Report. In fact, 2020 marked the steepest increase in global billionaires’ share of wealth on record,” the document said.</description></item></channel></rss>