<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>store on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/store/</link><description>Recent content in store on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/store/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unionized workers at Victoria Starbucks 'steaming mad' after wage increases not extended to location</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295db44674c7e1d585b02c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295db44674c7e1d585b02c1/</guid><description>Workers at a Starbucks in Victoria are calling out Starbucks Canada after the company refused to extend wage increases to the unionized staff at the Douglas Street location.
Highlights Workers at a Starbucks in Victoria are calling out Starbucks Canada after the company refused to extend wage increases to the unionized staff at the Douglas Street location. The Douglas Street store voted to unionize back in the summer of 2020, voting to become part of United Steelworkers District 3, which represents over 50,000 workers in Western Canada.</description></item><item><title>Once a retail giant, Kmart nears extinction after closure</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62548c76cae6950dffbf7046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 20:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62548c76cae6950dffbf7046/</guid><description>Kmart’s decline has been slow but steady, brought about by years of falling sales, changes in shopping habits and the looming shadow of Walmart.
Highlights The number of Kmarts in the U.S. will be down to three in the continental U.s. and a handful of stores elsewhere. Kmart cemented a place in American culture with its Blue Light Specials, a flashing blue orb affixed to a pole that would beckon shoppers to a flash sale in progress.</description></item><item><title>Comic book store owners are offering to ship banned Holocaust novel 'Maus' to Tennessee students for free</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fad73e1aeae2f9813f357d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 19:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fad73e1aeae2f9813f357d/</guid><description>After a Tennessee school board banned a graphic novel about the Holocaust from local middle schools, comic book store owners from near and far pledged to send students the book for free.
Highlights A Tennessee school board banned a graphic novel about the Holocaust from local middle schools. Comic book store owners from near and far pledged to send students the book for free. &amp;ldquo;Maus&amp;rdquo; tells the story of his parents in the 1940&amp;rsquo;s, following the Jewish family&amp;rsquo;s experience with rising anti-Semitism to their internment at the Auschwitz concentration camp.</description></item><item><title>Cleveland Starbucks workers file for unionization, aiming to be first Starbucks union in Ohio</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd0f102cec1e84f3d722a8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 05:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd0f102cec1e84f3d722a8/</guid><description>Workers at a Starbucks in Cleveland banded together and petitioned the National Labor Relation Board (NLRB) for unionization, pushing to become the coffee chain&amp;rsquo;s first union store in Ohio, according to the Starbucks Workers United union.
Summary CLEVELAND — Workers at a Starbucks in Cleveland banded together and petitioned the National Labor Relation Board (NLRB) for unionization, pushing to become the coffee chain&amp;rsquo;s first union store in Ohio, according to Starbucks Workers United union.</description></item></channel></rss>