<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fled on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fled/</link><description>Recent content in fled on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 21:13:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fled/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nine hospitalized after Texas authorities find dozens of undocumented workers in semi trailer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276e0d2c05fa0d06c16094c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 21:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276e0d2c05fa0d06c16094c/</guid><description>Nine people were treated for dehydration and scores of others fled the scene when authorities discovered up to 100 undocumented workers in the trailer of a broken-down semi in rural Texas, officials said Friday.
Highlights The truck became disabled on a rural highway about 2 miles north of the town of Ganado. When authorities investigated just after 7 a.m. CT, they discovered a packed trailer. They apprehended 10 people while others ran from the scene.</description></item><item><title>UN: Nearly two-thirds of Ukraine's children have fled homes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62557de95677b57e07c44078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62557de95677b57e07c44078/</guid><description>UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Nearly two-thirds of all Ukrainian children have fled their homes in the six weeks since Russia’s invasion, and the United Nations has verified the deaths of 142 youngsters, though the number is almost certainly much higher, the U.N.
Highlights Nearly two-thirds of all Ukrainian children have fled their homes in the six weeks since Russia’s invasion. The United Nations has verified the deaths of 142 youngsters, though the number is almost certainly much higher.</description></item></channel></rss>