<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weekly on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weekly/</link><description>Recent content in weekly on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 20:09:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weekly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mortgage demand falls to the lowest level in 22 years, amid rising rates and slowing home sales</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a101e77dec06735097b1d1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 20:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a101e77dec06735097b1d1/</guid><description>Mortgage demand continues to fall as interest rates rise further and affordability in the housing market weakens.
Highlights Mortgage demand continues to fall as interest rates rise further and affordability in housing market weakens. Average contract interest rate for 30-year fixed-rate mortgages with conforming loan balances $647,200 or less increased to 5.40% from 5.33%. Mortgage Bankers Association: Total mortgage application volume fell 6.5% last week. Refinance demand, which is most sensitive to weekly rate moves, fell another 6% for the week and was 75% lower than the same week one year ago.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks to require all U.S. workers get COVID-19 vaccine or tested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d436e8fd7216ad48be247d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d436e8fd7216ad48be247d/</guid><description>Citing Omicron variant, coffee chain says getting inoculated is the &amp;quot;best option&amp;quot; for containing the virus.
Summary Starbucks says it will require its U.S. workers be vaccinated against COVID-19 or be tested weekly as of February 9, in keeping with a federal mandate as the Omicron variant advances across the country. Starbucks Chief Operating Officer John Culver told the company&amp;rsquo;s domestic workforce of roughly 220,000 employees that they must disclose their vaccination status by January 10.</description></item></channel></rss>