<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>conspiracy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/conspiracy/</link><description>Recent content in conspiracy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/conspiracy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Praise for Uvalde shooter and call for copycats is growing online, Homeland Security warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1fef4957202de9e9fc98d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1fef4957202de9e9fc98d/</guid><description>In a U.S. Dept. of Homeland Security bulletin released Thursday, officials sounded the&amp;hellip;
Highlights Homeland Security officials say online forums known for hosting violent extremist content are encouraging copycat attacks in the U.S. Department of Homeland Security bulletin released Tuesday morning. The bulletin comes as evidence of law enforcement’s calamitous mishandling of the shooting continues to emerge. A lone gunman shot and killed 19 children and two teachers at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, on May 20, killing two teachers and 19 children.</description></item><item><title>Member of Georgia chapter of Oath Keepers pleads guilty to conspiracy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cc56062f2754f3d2d446f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 05:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cc56062f2754f3d2d446f/</guid><description>According to the Department of Justice, on April 29, a member of the Georgia chapter of Oath Keepers has pleaded guilty to seditious conspiracy and obstruction of an official proceeding for his actions before, during, and after the breach of the U. S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021. His and others’ actions disrupted a joint session of the U. S. Congress convened to ascertain and count the electoral votes related to the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>House Jan. 6 panel alleges Trump engaged in 'criminal conspiracy'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ccef23c77e8c46500c4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 14:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ccef23c77e8c46500c4e/</guid><description>The 221-page filing marks the committee’s most formal effort to link the former president to a federal crime, though the actual import of the filing is not clear since lawmakers do not have the power to bring charges on their own and can only make a referral to the Justice Department.
Highlights House committee says it found evidence that Trump and his associates engaged in a “criminal conspiracy” to prevent Congress from certifying the results of the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Judge tosses Zimmerman’s lawsuit against Trayvon’s parents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dab80865f28890b5b457c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620dab80865f28890b5b457c/</guid><description>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — A judge in Florida has dismissed a defamation and conspiracy lawsuit former neighborhood watch volunteer George Zimmerman had filed against the parents of Trayvon Martin, the teen he fatally shot almost a decade ago in a case that drew international attention about race and gun violence.
Highlights Zimmerman had filed a defamation and conspiracy lawsuit against the parents of Trayvon Martin. The lawsuit claimed that Trayvon Martin’s parents, along with attorney Ben Crump, participated in the conspiracy in an effort to get charges filed against Zimmerman.</description></item></channel></rss>