<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>level on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/level/</link><description>Recent content in level on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/level/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. traffic deaths hit highest level in 16 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62842c383463f9c0d99d8e24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62842c383463f9c0d99d8e24/</guid><description>An estimated 42,915 people died in motor vehicle traffic crashes in the U.S. in 2021.
Highlights An estimated 42,915 people died in motor vehicle traffic crashes in the U.S. in 2021, according to data released Tuesday from the Department of Transportation. The number represents a 10.5% increase from 2020, when 38,824 deaths were reported. Texas is estimated to have had the highest amount of deaths at 4,573, followed by California and Florida.</description></item><item><title>Cops: Body in barrel in Lake Mead was man who had been shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62725f7dc7f7a0fbfd0465d9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 11:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62725f7dc7f7a0fbfd0465d9/</guid><description>LAS VEGAS (AP) — The body found inside a barrel on the newly exposed bottom of Lake Mead after the lake&amp;rsquo;s level was depleted amid drought is that of a man who was shot, police said Tuesday. The killing probably happened between the mid-1970s and the early 1980s because the victim was wearing shoes that were manufactured during that period, said homicide Lt.
Highlights Cops: Body in barrel in Lake Mead was man who had been shot.</description></item><item><title>China says Taiwan is 'not Ukraine' as island raises alert level</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62165ddf75705c798f8da656/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62165ddf75705c798f8da656/</guid><description>Taiwan is &amp;quot;not Ukraine&amp;quot; and has always been an inalienable part of China, China&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry said on Wednesday, as Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen called for the island to beef up vigilance.
Highlights Taiwan is &amp;ldquo;not Ukraine&amp;rdquo; and has always been an inalienable part of China, China&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry says. Comments come as Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen calls for the island to beef up vigilance on military activities in response to the crisis.</description></item><item><title>Covid: Woman isolates in toilet for five hours after positive mid-flight test</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cee2cd3f58a6fb67682f8c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cee2cd3f58a6fb67682f8c/</guid><description>A US teacher says she spent five hours in the toilet after testing positive for Covid-19.
Summary According to the tracker of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the seven-day daily average of new cases is at 277,000 in the country, the highest level since the start of the pandemic. The rates of deaths and hospitalisations, however, remain relatively steady. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>