<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kids on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kids/</link><description>Recent content in kids on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 21:08:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Families of kids wounded in Uvalde school shooting sue suspected gunman’s estate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a10fb8699c26c11939e684/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 21:08:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a10fb8699c26c11939e684/</guid><description>The families of four students injured in the Uvalde school shooting filed a lawsuit against the suspected gunman&amp;rsquo;s estate.
Highlights The families of four students injured in the Uvalde, Texas, school shooting are suing the suspected gunman&amp;rsquo;s estate. Salvador Ramos, 18, allegedly killed 19 children and two teachers at Robb Elementary School on May 24. The plaintiffs suffered severe injuries to the face, leg, back and other parts of the body, resulting in having them undergo multiple surgeries, according to the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Christian school leader who taped students’ mouths shut says kids chose punishment over suspension</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256a29fd15e3ab9c5ccb1d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256a29fd15e3ab9c5ccb1d5/</guid><description>A Louisiana Christian school headmaster, a pastor and former &amp;quot;Survivor&amp;quot; contestant who was arrested last week after he taped students’ mouths shut as a form of discipline, is defending his actions, claiming the pupils were bullying their teacher.
Highlights John Raymond, 60, was arrested Thursday on three counts of cruelty to juveniles. He was arrested last week after he taped students’ mouths shut as a form of discipline. A police investigation found Raymond used a roll of packing tape to tape the mouths of three 13-year-old students shut.</description></item><item><title>Judge sides with 12 disabled kids seeking masks in schools</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e8607b8a7151655a1fece/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 03:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e8607b8a7151655a1fece/</guid><description>RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A federal judge has ruled that an executive order and new Virginia law allowing parents to opt their children out of classroom COVID-19 mask mandates cannot prevent 12 vulnerable students from seeking a “reasonable modification” that could include a requirement that their classmates wear masks.
Highlights A federal judge has ruled that an executive order and new Virginia law allowing parents to opt their children out of classroom COVID-19 mask mandates cannot prevent 12 vulnerable students from seeking a “reasonable modification” that could include a requirement that their classmates wear masks.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian kids with cancer evacuated from Poland to St. Jude Children's Hospital - CBS News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ba973f2e3fc6e9b2ad5c5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ba973f2e3fc6e9b2ad5c5/</guid><description>Four children with cancer — just 9 months to 9 years old— have been evacuated from Ukraine to St Jude Children&amp;rsquo;s Research Hospital in Memphis, the U.S. State Department said.
Highlights Four Ukrainian children, ages 9 months to 9 years, have been airlifted from Poland to Memphis. St. Jude is the first hospital in the U.S. to receive Ukrainian patients, the hospital said in a press release. The hospital said it will provide the children with cancer care and &amp;ldquo;trauma-informed psychosocial therapy&amp;rdquo; The State Department said it &amp;ldquo;supported airlift of these pediatric oncology patients and some of their immediate family members from Poland&amp;rdquo; to Memphis International Airport, but did not offer more details about the role it played.</description></item><item><title>Half of US adults exposed to harmful lead levels as kids</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226c9c65f6e8944ede0697d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226c9c65f6e8944ede0697d/</guid><description>Over 170 million U.S.-born people who were adults in 2015 were exposed to harmful levels of lead as children, a new study estimates. Researchers used blood-lead level, census and leaded gasoline consumption data to examine how widespread early childhood lead exposure was in the country between 1940 and 2015.
Highlights Over 170 million of people born in the United States who were adults in 2015 were exposed to harmful levels of lead as children, according to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences on Monday, March 7, 2022.</description></item></channel></rss>