<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lawyer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawyer/</link><description>Recent content in lawyer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 19:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawyer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. lawyer Avenatti sentenced to four years prison for defrauding Stormy Daniels</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62990aa5f3ebe74dd5886a42/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62990aa5f3ebe74dd5886a42/</guid><description>Michael Avenatti, the brash California lawyer who once took on then-President Donald Trump, was sentenced to four years in prison on Thursday for defrauding his best-known former client, the porn actress Stormy Daniels.
Highlights Michael Avenatti, the brash California lawyer who once took on then-President Donald Trump, was sentenced to four years in prison on Thursday. He was sentenced for defrauding his best-known former client, the porn actress Stormy Daniels. Avenatti took on the president of the United States in a bid to get a settlement from the White House.</description></item><item><title>Lev Parnas, an ex-Giuliani associate, to plead guilty to conspiracy charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622af667bab1936c9d322e87/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 07:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622af667bab1936c9d322e87/</guid><description>Lev Parnas, convicted in October on campaign finance charges, will plead guilty to a conspiracy count concerning his work at a fraud insurance company that former ally Rudy Giuliani also worked for.
Highlights Lev Parnas, convicted in October on campaign finance charges, will plead guilty to conspiracy count. Former ally Rudy Giuliani also worked for fraud insurance company Fraud Guarantee. Prosecutors said fraud Guarantee conned people into investing more than $2 million in their Florida start-up.</description></item></channel></rss>