<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>days on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/days/</link><description>Recent content in days on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 12:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/days/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian invaders have three days of supplies left, says Ukraine military</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b10e803132e104eab3649/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 12:22:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b10e803132e104eab3649/</guid><description>Ukrainian commanders say fuel, food and ammunition in short supply after breakdown in Russian supply chains
Highlights Claims of major shortages described as ‘plausible’ by western officials. Western officials said they were unable to corroborate the analysis. Report said to be consistent with evidence that the Russian advance had stalled. Pentagon official said there were continuing morale issues among Russian troops, with food and fuel shortages, as well as frostbite due to a lack of adequate clothing.</description></item><item><title>Nashville firefighter who called council members white supremacists suspended for 16 days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237989535641d06cf41d77d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237989535641d06cf41d77d/</guid><description>NFD concluded that Lipscomb had violated department policy and, pending a\u00a0hearing, he should be suspended for 16 days.
Highlights Nashville firefighter Josh Lipscomb, who performs as a comedian under the name Josh Black, called some council members “white supremacists” in a Feb. 3 tweet. An NFD panel concluded he violated department policy and should be suspended for 16 days. The suspension will begin on his next scheduled shift Monday, records show.</description></item><item><title>Delta loses $408 million; 8,000 employees contract Covid over the last four weeks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0bd331bbfc302012403ef/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0bd331bbfc302012403ef/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines lost $408 million in the final quarter of 2021, dragged down by a Covid-19 surge that rocked the airline in December, and the carrier predicted Thursday that it will suffer one more quarterly loss before travel perks up in spring and summer.
Summary CEO Ed Bastian said 8,000 employees have contracted Covid-19 over the last four weeks. Earlier this week, United Airlines CEO Scott Kirby sent a letter to employees saying that 3,000 employees had tested positive for Covid-19.</description></item><item><title>France's Bogdanoff TV twins die of Covid six days apart</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4d18fc17fa09c819f36f2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4d18fc17fa09c819f36f2/</guid><description>Grichka and Igor Bogdanoff had hosted a TV science and science-fiction show in the 1980s.
Summary Family friend Pierre-Jean Chalençon said they had left it too late to seek hospital treatment, deciding it was similar to flu. &amp;ldquo;People have said they were anti-vaxxers but they absolutely weren&amp;rsquo;t,&amp;rdquo; he told BFMTV. &amp;ldquo;Several friends told them to get themselves vaccinated but they felt because of their lifestyle and their [lack of] comorbidity, they weren&amp;rsquo;t at risk of Covid.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan rejects US CDC guidance on 5-day quarantine - Some Omicron cases still infectious up to 12 days after testing positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0eb30fcff74226b151d37/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0eb30fcff74226b151d37/</guid><description>Some Omicron cases still infectious up to 12 days after testing positive | 2021-12-30 18:59:00
Summary It also shortened the isolation period for vaccinated people who have been exposed to the virus to five days. During a press conference on Dec. 30, Philip Lo (羅一鈞), deputy head of the CECC’s medical response division, announced that a total of 59 imported Omicron cases have been detected in Taiwan. More than 80% of these cases were detected upon arrival in Taiwan, while the rest tested positive within six days after entering the country.</description></item><item><title>CDC shortens recommended Covid-19 isolation and quarantine time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</guid><description>The CDC shortened the recommended times that people should isolate when they&amp;rsquo;ve tested positive for Covid-19 from 10 days to five days if they don&amp;rsquo;t have symptoms &amp;ndash; and if they wear a mask around others for at least five more days.
Summary The CDC also shortened the recommended time for people to quarantine if they are exposed to the virus to a similar five days if they are vaccinated. People who are fully vaccinated and boosted may not need to quarantine at all, the CDC said.</description></item></channel></rss>