<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>days on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/days/</link><description>Recent content in days on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/days/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>France's Bogdanoff TV twins die of Covid six days apart</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4d18fc17fa09c819f36f2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4d18fc17fa09c819f36f2/</guid><description>Grichka and Igor Bogdanoff had hosted a TV science and science-fiction show in the 1980s.
Summary Family friend Pierre-Jean Chalençon said they had left it too late to seek hospital treatment, deciding it was similar to flu. &amp;ldquo;People have said they were anti-vaxxers but they absolutely weren&amp;rsquo;t,&amp;rdquo; he told BFMTV. &amp;ldquo;Several friends told them to get themselves vaccinated but they felt because of their lifestyle and their [lack of] comorbidity, they weren&amp;rsquo;t at risk of Covid.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan rejects US CDC guidance on 5-day quarantine - Some Omicron cases still infectious up to 12 days after testing positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0eb30fcff74226b151d37/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0eb30fcff74226b151d37/</guid><description>Some Omicron cases still infectious up to 12 days after testing positive | 2021-12-30 18:59:00
Summary It also shortened the isolation period for vaccinated people who have been exposed to the virus to five days. During a press conference on Dec. 30, Philip Lo (羅一鈞), deputy head of the CECC’s medical response division, announced that a total of 59 imported Omicron cases have been detected in Taiwan. More than 80% of these cases were detected upon arrival in Taiwan, while the rest tested positive within six days after entering the country.</description></item><item><title>CDC shortens recommended Covid-19 isolation and quarantine time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</guid><description>The CDC shortened the recommended times that people should isolate when they&amp;rsquo;ve tested positive for Covid-19 from 10 days to five days if they don&amp;rsquo;t have symptoms &amp;ndash; and if they wear a mask around others for at least five more days.
Summary The CDC also shortened the recommended time for people to quarantine if they are exposed to the virus to a similar five days if they are vaccinated.</description></item></channel></rss>