<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prisoner on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prisoner/</link><description>Recent content in prisoner on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prisoner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In Mariupol, the occupiers plan a war crime, a “parade of prisoners”. The Ukrainian serviceman remembers a similar “parade” in 2014 in Donetsk, and human rights activists explain how Russia will be punished for it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278b20bbde588aecb3df8d0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278b20bbde588aecb3df8d0/</guid><description>In Mariupol, the occupiers are planning to hold &amp;quot;parade of prisoners&amp;quot; on May 9. A similar one was held on August 24, 2014 in Donetsk. Vasyl Stasiev is planning the parad. Lawyers explain why it is a war crime.
Highlights Vasyl Stasiev was in captivity from August 13 to December 26, 2014. The only thing I remember from that &amp;ldquo;parade&amp;rdquo; is the beastly crowd. The feeling was that they were ready just to attack us and tear us apart.</description></item><item><title>Snake Island sailors freed in prisoner swap between Russia and Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d1171804af9bca08e97b2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:49:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d1171804af9bca08e97b2/</guid><description>Ukrainian soldiers at the Black Sea outpost made headlines at the start of the war by profanely defying threats from a Russian warship. Russia and Ukraine each exchanged 10 prisoners on Thursday.
Highlights Ukraine and Russia exchange 10 prisoners of war each on Thursday. The exchange also freed 19 Ukrainian civilian sailors captured as their ship tried to take Ukrainian troops off Snake Island. Ukraine released 11 Russian civilian sailors as part of the deal, Deputy Prime Minister Iryna Vereshchuk says.</description></item></channel></rss>