<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rape on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rape/</link><description>Recent content in rape on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 21:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rape/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>San Francisco DA drops charges against woman whose rape kit DNA linked her to a property crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eba52c21a59f1063e6f8d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 21:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eba52c21a59f1063e6f8d/</guid><description>District attorney Chesa Boudin said the charges violated constitutional protections against unreasonable searches and seizures
Highlights District attorney Chesa Boudin drops charges against a woman whose DNA collected from a rape kit was used to link her to a property crime. Officials said the practice violated the defendants’ fourth amendment protections against unreasonable searches and seizures by the government, and runs afoul of California’s Victims’ Bill of Rights. The district attorney also expressed concerns the practice would deter victims of sexual assault, which is widely underreported in the US, from coming forward.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana man is freed after new evidence uncovered in 1977 attempted rape conviction</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ba74d119ce1ce4a91404a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 13:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ba74d119ce1ce4a91404a/</guid><description>Vincent Simmons​ is a free man after decades in prison.
Highlights Vincent Simmons was convicted of attempted aggravated rape of twin sisters in 1977. He has been trying for years to get a new trial. A judge says he will not retry him, saying the time &amp;ldquo;has been overcome&amp;rdquo; by new evidence. Simmons&amp;rsquo; twin sisters, now 59, say they are the victims and that he is guilty. The girls&amp;rsquo; testimony to police initially told police they didn&amp;rsquo;t know who he was and that &amp;ldquo;all Black people look alike&amp;rdquo; and even used the N-word, defense lawyer says.</description></item></channel></rss>