<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>damage on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/damage/</link><description>Recent content in damage on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/damage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passengers scream as world’s longest cruise ship crashes into Jamaican pier</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295bf58be8e95faa111cf69/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295bf58be8e95faa111cf69/</guid><description>Investigation launched into alleged accident
Highlights The Harmony of the Seas crashed into a pier in Falmouth, Jamaica, on Thursday morning. The 227,000 tonne vessel was trying to dock at the busy port on the country&amp;rsquo;s northern shore. Video of the crash has attracted more than 500,000 views on social media. No injuries were reported - although the vessel sustained &amp;lsquo;cosmetic&amp;rsquo; damage. Port Authority of Jamaica has launched an investigation into the incident.</description></item><item><title>Tornado hits Gaylord, extensive damage reported</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62891d9deba5fa4f6a005c29/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62891d9deba5fa4f6a005c29/</guid><description>OTSEGO COUNTY, Mich. (WPBN/WGTU) &amp;ndash; The Gaylord community is assessing the damage after a powerful tornado hit. The National Weather Service confirmed a large and “extremely dangerous” tornado was located over Gaylord, moving northeast at 50 mph Friday around 3:45 p. m. Extensive damage was reported in Gaylord with buildings destroyed. Several roads are closed in the area due to downed power lines.
Highlights A large and &amp;ldquo;extremely dangerous&amp;rdquo; tornado was located over Gaylord, moving northeast at 50 mph.</description></item><item><title>A construction project caused damage to 100-million-year-old dinosaur tracks in Utah</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c6bb55e390136656ae5dc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 16:18:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c6bb55e390136656ae5dc/</guid><description>A project to replace the boardwalk at the Mill Canyon Dinosaur Tracksite in Moah, Utah, cause minor damage to tracks and trace fossils at the site, a Bureau of Land Management paleontologist found.
Highlights A project to replace the boardwalk at the Mill Canyon Dinosaur Tracksite in Moab, Utah, caused minor damage to dinosaur tracks. The site dates back more than 100 million years and contains more than 200 dinosaur tracks and traces of at least 10 different animals.</description></item></channel></rss>