<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>building on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/building/</link><description>Recent content in building on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 05:10:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/building/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Residents of luxury San Francisco apartment building, 33 Tehama, evacuated after flood hits every floor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a02f2d619f0edb77a653a8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 05:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a02f2d619f0edb77a653a8/</guid><description>Hundreds of residents of San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s 33 Tehama were evacuated with a moment&amp;rsquo;s notice from their homes Friday after a burst water pipe flooded the building.
Highlights Hundreds of residents of San Francisco&amp;rsquo;s 33 Tehama were evacuated with a moment&amp;rsquo;s notice from their homes on Friday after a burst water pipe flooded all 35 floors of the high-end SoMa tower. Residents say they have no idea when they may be able to return, or where they will live as they wait.</description></item><item><title>All 5 building blocks of DNA, RNA found in meteorites from Canada, U.S., Australia | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271382be1d7feddc0225012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271382be1d7feddc0225012/</guid><description>A fresh examination of meteorites that landed in the United States, Canada and Australia is bolstering the notion that early in Earth&amp;rsquo;s history, such objects may have delivered chemical ingredients vital for the advent of life.
Highlights Three meteorites that landed in U.S., Canada and Australia found to contain chemical ingredients needed for the advent of life. Researchers found two of the five chemical components needed to form DNA and RNA.</description></item><item><title>With U.S. approval, Trump name to come down from landmark Washington hotel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62402a7b8541f4fa48b65c4c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 09:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62402a7b8541f4fa48b65c4c/</guid><description>The U.S. government on Friday said it would allow former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s company to sell the rights to a luxury hotel in Washington to a Hilton affiliate, clearing the way for Trump&amp;rsquo;s name to come down off a building that served as a flashpoint during his presidency.
Highlights The U.S. government says it will allow Trump&amp;rsquo;s company to sell rights to a luxury hotel in Washington to a Hilton affiliate.</description></item><item><title>D.C. board rules that officer who committed suicide after Jan. 6 died in line of duty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ab0bdc8074f88ac32ee88/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 02:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ab0bdc8074f88ac32ee88/</guid><description>A District of Columbia retirement board has ruled that a police officer died in the line of duty when he took his own life due to injuries he suffered during the Jan. 6, 2021, riot at the U.S. Capitol, the Washington Post reported.
Highlights Washington&amp;rsquo;s Police and Firefighters&amp;rsquo; Retirement and Relief Board said in a letter on Monday that Jan. 6 was the &amp;ldquo;sole and direct cause&amp;rdquo; of Jeffrey Smith&amp;rsquo;s suicide.</description></item><item><title>The University of Alabama is renaming a building after its first Black student, removing the name of a Klansman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207dd1e7be3be647c909deb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 16:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207dd1e7be3be647c909deb/</guid><description>After a week of backlash, the University of Alabama System&amp;rsquo;s Board of Trustees voted Friday to name a building after the school&amp;rsquo;s first Black student instead of having her share the name with a Ku Klux Klan leader.
Highlights The University of Alabama System&amp;rsquo;s Board of Trustees reversed a February 3 decision to name the building Lucy-Graves Hall after its first Black student and civil rights activist Autherine Lucy Foster and Bibb Graves, a former Alabama governor and a Ku Klux Klan leader.</description></item><item><title>Satellite images show Russia still building up forces near Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6f9cbde48532e11530cce/</guid><description>New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.
Summary Dec 24 (Reuters) - New satellite images captured by a private U.S. company show that Russia has continued to build up its forces in annexed Crimea and near Ukraine in recent weeks while pressing the United States for talks over security guarantees it is seeking.</description></item></channel></rss>