<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>casey on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/casey/</link><description>Recent content in casey on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 02:22:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/casey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Casey White manhunt ends in Indiana, accomplice Vicky White hospitalized, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279cc3fdd92052d282307db/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 02:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279cc3fdd92052d282307db/</guid><description>Vicky White, a former Alabama corrections officer, died of self-inflicted gunshot wound, authorities say. Casey White and his suspected accomplice, Vicky, have been on the run since April 29. They were captured after a
Highlights Vicky White, a former Alabama corrections officer, died Monday night from self-inflicted gunshot wounds. Casey White, the fugitive inmate awaiting trial for capital murder, was arrested in Evansville, Indiana. The pair had been on the run since April 29 when the 56-year-old jailer told the Alabama jailer that she was transporting the inmate for a mental evaluation.</description></item><item><title>Florida First Lady Casey DeSantis Now Cancer-Free</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222119ef821199ff68e6360/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 13:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222119ef821199ff68e6360/</guid><description>Florida first lady Casey DeSantis is now cancer-free after battling breast cancer, she and Gov. Ron DeSantis announced Thursday.
Highlights Casey DeSantis&amp;rsquo; diagnosis was made public in October. She underwent surgery and received her final chemotherapy treatment in January. The first lady, 41, has played an active role in her husband&amp;rsquo;s administration. &amp;ldquo;There are no words to express how truly blessed, grateful and humbled I am to hear the words cancer free,&amp;rdquo; she said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>