<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attack on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attack/</link><description>Recent content in attack on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 18:17:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fox News cameraman killed by incoming fire outside of Kyiv</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230d801a84a88706f241942/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230d801a84a88706f241942/</guid><description>Pierre Zakrzewski had been travelling in a vehicle near Kyiv with correspondent Benjamin Hall, who was injured, and Ukrainian journalist Oleksandra Kuvshinova, who was also killed.
Highlights Pierre Zakrzewski was working with correspondent Benjamin Hall when his vehicle was hit. Ukrainian journalist Oleksandra Kuvshinova was also reported to be killed in the attack. Fox News producer Yonat Friling paid tribute to a &amp;lsquo;beautiful brave&amp;rsquo; woman. Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin said he was &amp;lsquo;deeply disturbed and saddened&amp;rsquo; by the killing.</description></item><item><title>No Charges for 5-Year-Old Who Left Teacher Hospitalized in Pembroke Pines School Attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622710a6e9e1974414c2c06d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622710a6e9e1974414c2c06d/</guid><description>A 5-year-old student who left a teacher hospitalized after he attacked her at an elementary school in Pembroke Pines won&amp;rsquo;t face charges, police said.
Highlights Incident happened Wednesday at Pines Lakes Elementary School in Pembroke Pines, Florida. A 5-year-old student who attacked a teacher left a teacher hospitalized after he attacked her at an elementary school. The incident began when two students, ages 4 and 5, started throwing things around the pre-K classroom and at the teachers, then started flipping over chairs.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin media: Ukraine preparing to attack, not Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2df1ba28cb0e739d8aa32/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2df1ba28cb0e739d8aa32/</guid><description>The threat of a Russian invasion is &amp;quot;imaginary&amp;quot;, and Ukraine is a failing state, says Russian TV.
Highlights As for the 100,000 Russian troops reportedly massed on the border with Ukraine, they get much less attention. When they do, the message is that Moscow is free to do whatever it likes with its own troops on its own territory. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>