<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attack on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attack/</link><description>Recent content in attack on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:34:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buffalo suspect's posts about attack plans could be seen online 30 minutes before mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628647371fc70d8a171b0473/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628647371fc70d8a171b0473/</guid><description>Thirty minutes before an 18-year-old White man allegedly carried out a racist mass shooting Saturday at a supermarket in a mostly Black enclave of Buffalo, New York, he revealed his monthslong plot to some on social media.
Highlights NEW: New York&amp;rsquo;s attorney general launches probe into social media companies used by alleged shooter. Payton S. Gendron, 18, is accused of killing 10 people and wounding three in a racist mass shooting in Buffalo, New York.</description></item><item><title>Proud Boys member pleads guilty for role in US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a1301f8848a840c5851bd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a1301f8848a840c5851bd/</guid><description>Plea agreement filed in federal court calls for Louis Enrique Colon to admit to a single felony charge and cooperate with prosecutors
Highlights Louis Enrique Colon pleads guilty to obstructing police officers in Washington, DC. Plea agreement calls for Colon to admit to a single felony charge and cooperate with prosecutors. Colon faces up to five years in prison and a fine of up to $250,000. One of the dozens of police officers injured during the insurrection testified on Wednesday that he didn’t punch or pick a fight with a retired New York police officer charged with attacking the officer.</description></item><item><title>'Stop the Steal' leader cooperating with DOJ's investigation of Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62528371898ee19979fffb00/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62528371898ee19979fffb00/</guid><description>Ali Alexander, a key figure in the &amp;quot;Stop the Steal&amp;quot; movement following the 2020 presidential election, says he has received a grand jury subpoena and has agreed to cooperate with the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s investigation of the January 6, 2021, attack on the US Capitol.
Highlights Ali Alexander says he has received a grand jury subpoena and has agreed to cooperate with the Justice Department’s investigation of the January 6, 2021, attack on the US Capitol.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina inmate convicted of killing toddler dies in prison attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d08b2d315fdb6375c1bac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 03:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d08b2d315fdb6375c1bac/</guid><description>Semajs Short, 24, was attacked in a housing area at Bertie Correctional Institution. He was convicted in the 2014 murder of 2-year-old Dy’Unanna Anderson. Short pleaded guilty to second-degree murder
Highlights Semajs Short, 24, was attacked in a housing area at Bertie Correctional Institution. He was convicted of second-degree murder in the 2014 murder of 2-year-old Dy&amp;rsquo;Unanna Anderson. Short was serving a 31-year prison sentence. Three other prisoners were injured in Tuesday’s assault, WCTI-TV reports.</description></item><item><title>Fox News cameraman killed by incoming fire outside of Kyiv</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230d801a84a88706f241942/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230d801a84a88706f241942/</guid><description>Pierre Zakrzewski had been travelling in a vehicle near Kyiv with correspondent Benjamin Hall, who was injured, and Ukrainian journalist Oleksandra Kuvshinova, who was also killed.
Highlights Pierre Zakrzewski was working with correspondent Benjamin Hall when his vehicle was hit. Ukrainian journalist Oleksandra Kuvshinova was also reported to be killed in the attack. Fox News producer Yonat Friling paid tribute to a &amp;lsquo;beautiful brave&amp;rsquo; woman. Irish Prime Minister Micheal Martin said he was &amp;lsquo;deeply disturbed and saddened&amp;rsquo; by the killing.</description></item><item><title>No Charges for 5-Year-Old Who Left Teacher Hospitalized in Pembroke Pines School Attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622710a6e9e1974414c2c06d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622710a6e9e1974414c2c06d/</guid><description>A 5-year-old student who left a teacher hospitalized after he attacked her at an elementary school in Pembroke Pines won&amp;rsquo;t face charges, police said.
Highlights Incident happened Wednesday at Pines Lakes Elementary School in Pembroke Pines, Florida. A 5-year-old student who attacked a teacher left a teacher hospitalized after he attacked her at an elementary school. The incident began when two students, ages 4 and 5, started throwing things around the pre-K classroom and at the teachers, then started flipping over chairs.</description></item><item><title>Kremlin media: Ukraine preparing to attack, not Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2df1ba28cb0e739d8aa32/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2df1ba28cb0e739d8aa32/</guid><description>The threat of a Russian invasion is &amp;quot;imaginary&amp;quot;, and Ukraine is a failing state, says Russian TV.
Highlights As for the 100,000 Russian troops reportedly massed on the border with Ukraine, they get much less attention. When they do, the message is that Moscow is free to do whatever it likes with its own troops on its own territory. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>