<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>keepers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/keepers/</link><description>Recent content in keepers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 05:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/keepers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Member of Georgia chapter of Oath Keepers pleads guilty to conspiracy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cc56062f2754f3d2d446f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 05:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626cc56062f2754f3d2d446f/</guid><description>According to the Department of Justice, on April 29, a member of the Georgia chapter of Oath Keepers has pleaded guilty to seditious conspiracy and obstruction of an official proceeding for his actions before, during, and after the breach of the U. S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021. His and others’ actions disrupted a joint session of the U. S. Congress convened to ascertain and count the electoral votes related to the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>Lawyer representing Proud Boys and Oath Keepers in Jan 6 cases has law licence revoked in Virginia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dd8ebc46fe8d90960310a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 18:17:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dd8ebc46fe8d90960310a/</guid><description>Court finds lawyer failed to follow ‘professional rules that govern safekeeping property’ and ‘meritorious claims and contentions’
Highlights Jonathon Moseley was disbarred by a three-judge panel in a Virginia state court on Friday following a two-hour hearing. He failed to follow ‘professional rules that govern safekeeping property’ and ‘meritorious claims and contentions’ The lawyer has represented a number of well-known Capitol riot defendants, such as one of the Oath Keepers who have been charged with seditious conspiracy and several people in the sights of the House select committee investigating the 6 January insurrection.</description></item></channel></rss>