<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pain on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pain/</link><description>Recent content in pain on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 23:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spain to allow girls over 16 to opt for abortions without parental consent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286ce2b4daea98526f3f117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 23:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286ce2b4daea98526f3f117/</guid><description>The approved draft bill allows abortions without parental consent for over-16s and paid menstrual leave.
Highlights The sexual and reproductive health bill also aims to give employees three days of sick leave for painful periods, draft says. The approved draft bill allows abortions without parental consent for over-16s and paid menstrual leave. The bill would also extend it to five days for particularly intense or incapacitating pain. It would also allow employees to have three days&amp;rsquo; sick leave, potentially extending it to a five-day period for especially intense pain.</description></item><item><title>Crocodiles turn on humans amid Iran water crisis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc4de1358c9c16e1e8e1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 12:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc4de1358c9c16e1e8e1ca/</guid><description>The creatures are attacking as their habitats shrink, a grim side-effect of Iran&amp;rsquo;s water shortages.
Summary Lying on the floor of his modest home, Siahouk was in excruciating pain from the injury to his right hand, the result of a nightmarish encounter. Just two days earlier, on a scorchingly hot August afternoon, the frail 70-year-old shepherd had gone to fetch water from a pond when he was pounced on by a gando, the local name for a mugger crocodile in Iran&amp;rsquo;s Baluchistan region.</description></item></channel></rss>