<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wasnt on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wasnt/</link><description>Recent content in wasnt on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:13:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wasnt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Louisiana girl, 4, dies after grandmother allegedly forced her to drink bottle of whiskey</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62640952c85330f1c8831916/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62640952c85330f1c8831916/</guid><description>A Louisiana child died after the girl’s grandmother forced her to drink a bottle of whiskey while her mother watched, authorities said Friday.
Highlights China Record, 4, was found with a blood alcohol level of.68 after officers were dispatched to a home east of Baton Rouge on Thursday morning. She was forced to drink half a bottle of whiskey while her mother watched, police said. Her cause of death was acute alcohol poisoning, the East Baton Rouge Coroner’s Office said.</description></item><item><title>Wrestling Legend Scott Hal (Razor Ramon) To Be Taken Off Life Support After Suffering Multiple Heart Attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f4d7d6adfb5c6f82aeb79/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 14:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f4d7d6adfb5c6f82aeb79/</guid><description>Kevin Nash revealed Sunday night that his long-time partner and best friend, Scott Hall, is being taken off life support.
Highlights Kevin Nash informed Sunday night that his long-time tag partner and best friend, Scott Hall, is being taken off life support. Hall was placed on life support Saturday after enduring three heart attacks. Hall underwent hip surgery last week, but reportedly suffered a setback when a blood clot got loose.</description></item><item><title>Sacramento church shooting leaves 5 dead, including 3 children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</guid><description>Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office confirmed.
Highlights Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento. The victims included three girls ages 9, 10 and 13, officials said. The shooter, who is unidentified, had a restraining order against him, an official said.</description></item></channel></rss>