<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>infections on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/infections/</link><description>Recent content in infections on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 20:16:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/infections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida judge overturns CDC mask mandate for public transit, planes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dc6fcfec3ce61fc6b3d84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 20:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dc6fcfec3ce61fc6b3d84/</guid><description>The court&amp;rsquo;s ruling comes less than a week after the CDC extended the mandate for 15 days, amid a rise in Covid infections nationwide due to the more contagious omicron BA.2 subvariant.
Highlights A judge in Florida vacated the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s national Covid mask mandate for planes and other forms of public transportation. The Health Freedom Defense Fund, a group that opposes public health mandates, and two individuals who argued that wearing masks while flying exacerbated their anxiety and panic attacks first filed the lawsuit in July 2021.</description></item><item><title>Shanghai Disney closes as city sees record surge in Covid cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238a77af0e46b8b5fcb6be2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 16:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238a77af0e46b8b5fcb6be2/</guid><description>China&amp;rsquo;s financial hub of Shanghai reported on Monday a record daily surge in local Covid-19 infections as authorities scrambled to test residents and rein in the Omicron variant, while closing its Disney resort until further notice.
Highlights Shanghai reported 24 new domestically transmitted Covid cases with confirmed symptoms for Sunday. It is the fourth consecutive day that Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s local asymptomatic infections have increased. Authorities scrambled to test residents and rein in the Omicron variant, while closing its Disney resort until further notice.</description></item></channel></rss>