<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>25 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/25/</link><description>Recent content in 25 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 23:13:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/25/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Netflix shares crater 20% after company reports it lost subscribers for the first time in more than 10 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f41f26abb2bb99f5e4761/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 23:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625f41f26abb2bb99f5e4761/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first time the streamer has reported a subscriber loss in more than a decade.
Highlights Netflix reported a loss of 200,000 subscribers during the first quarter. The company&amp;rsquo;s shares cratered more than 25% in extended hours after the report. Netflix is forecasting a global paid subscriber loss of 2 million for the second quarter. Co-CEO Reed Hastings said the company is exploring lower-priced, ad-supported tiers in a bid to bring in new subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Moscow braces for market meltdown Monday as new sanctions hit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c849b5fcf3096bfcf75a1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 08:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c849b5fcf3096bfcf75a1/</guid><description>Russian currency expected to plunge in first day’s trading since Swift ban and ECB says state-owned Sberbank subsidiaries are set to collapse
Highlights The U.S. and European Union announced unprecedented sanctions over the weekend. “There are no available measures with a realistic chance of restoring this. position at group level and in each of its subsidiaries within the. subsidiaries,” the company said in a statement. ‘I think for one of the largest.</description></item><item><title>1 in 15 people in London likely has COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d042613328107f90ab2c19/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d042613328107f90ab2c19/</guid><description>Summary LONDON (AP) — New figures from Britain’s official statistics body estimate that about 1 in 25 people in private households in England had COVID-19 in the week before Christmas, as the highly transmissible omicron variant spread rapidly across the country. The number jumped from 1 in 45 in the previous week, the Office for National Statistics said Friday. One in 25 is the equivalent of about 2 million people with coronavirus in England, the highest number since the statistics body began estimating infection levels in May 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>