<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>create on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/create/</link><description>Recent content in create on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 04:16:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/create/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UN agrees to create world's first-ever plastics pollution treaty in a blow to big oil</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62204102804c52a74a5df8c1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 04:16:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62204102804c52a74a5df8c1/</guid><description>The United Nations approved a landmark agreement to create the world&amp;rsquo;s first-ever global plastic pollution treaty on Wednesday, describing it as the most significant environmental deal since the 2015 Paris climate accord.
Highlights The United Nations approved a landmark agreement to create the world&amp;rsquo;s first-ever global plastic pollution treaty on Wednesday. The deal is the most significant environmental deal since the Paris climate accord. The agreement is due to be finalized by 2024 and will have ripple effects on businesses and the environment.</description></item><item><title>NATO won't create '2nd-class' allies to soothe Russia, alliance head says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8c60fcac41dd3e6c7be29/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8c60fcac41dd3e6c7be29/</guid><description>NATO has said it is ready for talks on reciprocal arms control with Moscow, but added that the alliance is united against the &amp;quot;real&amp;quot; risk of Russian aggression against Ukraine.
Summary NATO foreign ministers met by video conference Friday to discuss Russia&amp;rsquo;s military presence on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s borders, as alliance Secretary-General Jens Stoltenberg said the troop buildup continues. &amp;ldquo;We are ready to engage in arms control with Russia, conventional and nuclear, but that has to be reciprocal,&amp;rdquo; Stoltenberg said.</description></item></channel></rss>