<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>north on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/north/</link><description>Recent content in north on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 01:55:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/north/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>North Korea: Missile programme funded through stolen crypto, UN report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62007bf96c66ac62d8c6a158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 01:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62007bf96c66ac62d8c6a158/</guid><description>Investigators say cyber-attackers stole over $50 million in digital assets between 2020 and mid-2021.
Highlights UN report finds humanitarian situation in North Korea continuing to worsen. It said this was likely to be the result of the country&amp;rsquo;s decision to close its borders during the pandemic. Investigators say cyber-attackers stole over $50 million in digital assets between 2020 and mid-2021. UN report also found that North Korea&amp;rsquo;s humanitarian situation continues to worsen.</description></item><item><title>Son of North Carolina police officer shot by father has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</guid><description>The son of a Jacksonville police officer has died following an accidental shooting that occurred Dec. 27, involving his father.
Summary ONSLOW COUNTY, N.C. (WITN/Gray Media) - The 15-year-old son of a Jacksonville, North Carolina police officer has died after being shot last Monday at a home in Onslow County. Information released last week by authorities said the police officer accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head. Thursday afternoon, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said the teen has died.</description></item><item><title>North Korean officials demand handwriting samples of thousands of Pyongyang residents after graffiti appears calling Kim Jong-un a 'son of a bitch'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d56cc0b27b5c9d268d1312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d56cc0b27b5c9d268d1312/</guid><description>North Korean officials are demanding handwriting samples from thousands of Pyongyang residents after graffiti appeared insulting supreme leader Kim Jong-un, a rare sign of discontent among the elite in the capital.
Summary The message “Kim Jong-un, you son of a b&amp;mdash;-. Operated by dissidents and defectors, the Seoul-based media outlet has a network of undercover “citizen reporters” in North Korea and China. The UN’s Food and Agriculture Organisation has estimated North Korea is short 860,000 tonnes of produce this year alone, the equivalent to approximately 2.</description></item></channel></rss>