<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>north on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/north/</link><description>Recent content in north on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 13:33:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/north/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kim Jong Un mobilizes North Korea’s military in response to Covid-19 outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283a42282e8f574cd7061d1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 13:33:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283a42282e8f574cd7061d1/</guid><description>North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has mobilized the military to respond to the country&amp;rsquo;s first officially acknowledged outbreak of Covid-19, as the impoverished nation scrambles to address what state media has described as a &amp;quot;major national emergency.&amp;quot;
Highlights A further 392,920 new cases of &amp;ldquo;fever&amp;rdquo; and eight deaths were recorded between Saturday and Sunday evening. That brings the total number of reported cases to 1.2 million, with more than 648,000 recovered.</description></item><item><title>North Korea's Explosive Covid Outbreak: 820,620 Cases In 3 Days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280b6fc6525ae20f1350348/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 08:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280b6fc6525ae20f1350348/</guid><description>North Korea on Sunday reported 15 additional deaths from &amp;quot;fever&amp;quot; after the country recently announced its first-ever cases of Covid-19 and ordered nationwide lockdowns.
Highlights North Korea on Sunday reported 15 additional deaths from &amp;ldquo;fever&amp;rdquo; after the country recently announced its first-ever cases of Covid-19. State media KCNA said a total of 42 people had died, with 820,620 cases and at least 324,550 under medical treatment. Leader Kim Jong Un has said the outbreak has caused &amp;ldquo;great upheaval&amp;rdquo; in North Korea.</description></item><item><title>Family of Abducted Girl Claims Inaction of Dallas Police &amp;amp; Mavs in Sex Trafficking Case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e75d75ff24d07ddad92a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e75d75ff24d07ddad92a1/</guid><description>“The American Airlines Center (and the Dallas Mavericks) are grateful that the teenager has been found.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; - A statement from the Mavs.
Highlights 15-year-old girl from North Richland Hills is now home after being abducted by a man at an April 8 Dallas Mavericks game at American Airlines Center. Family still seeks answers, and is pressing the Mavs, AAC and Dallas Police for not acting swiftly enough regarding the crime. The girl&amp;rsquo;s father informed police at the game when he realized she was missing, but was told to report the allegations to his hometown North Richlands Hills Police.</description></item><item><title>U.S. boosts missile defense readiness in response to North Korea's "serious escalation" with recent missile tests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d28e057bb9cd386f34c81/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 23:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d28e057bb9cd386f34c81/</guid><description>Pentagon enhancing intelligence gathering and missile defense readiness in the region after Kim Jong Un regime tests components for a huge new missile.
Highlights U.S. intelligence agencies believe North Korea is testing components of its gigantic &amp;ldquo;Hwasong-17&amp;rdquo; intercontinental ballistic missile (ICBM) The new weapon was rolled out in a military parade in 2020, but as far as anyone knows, it has never been fired. If the missile works the way it has been designed to, it could potentially reach anywhere in the continental United States.</description></item><item><title>Deputy fired after putting knee on Black man's neck</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d1b196caa2a4d9e9dc43d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 22:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d1b196caa2a4d9e9dc43d/</guid><description>A North Carolina sheriff’s deputy has been fired after he was captured on video putting his knee on a Black man’s neck, and a state agency is looking into the incident
Highlights A North Carolina sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputy has been fired after he was captured on video putting his knee on a Black man&amp;rsquo;s neck. A state agency is looking into the incident. The family of the man provided video last week showing him being arrested on a charge of marijuana possession.</description></item><item><title>North Korea: Missile programme funded through stolen crypto, UN report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62007bf96c66ac62d8c6a158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 01:55:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62007bf96c66ac62d8c6a158/</guid><description>Investigators say cyber-attackers stole over $50 million in digital assets between 2020 and mid-2021.
Highlights UN report finds humanitarian situation in North Korea continuing to worsen. It said this was likely to be the result of the country&amp;rsquo;s decision to close its borders during the pandemic. Investigators say cyber-attackers stole over $50 million in digital assets between 2020 and mid-2021. UN report also found that North Korea&amp;rsquo;s humanitarian situation continues to worsen.</description></item><item><title>Son of North Carolina police officer shot by father has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</guid><description>The son of a Jacksonville police officer has died following an accidental shooting that occurred Dec. 27, involving his father.
Summary ONSLOW COUNTY, N.C. (WITN/Gray Media) - The 15-year-old son of a Jacksonville, North Carolina police officer has died after being shot last Monday at a home in Onslow County. Information released last week by authorities said the police officer accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head. Thursday afternoon, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said the teen has died.</description></item><item><title>North Korean officials demand handwriting samples of thousands of Pyongyang residents after graffiti appears calling Kim Jong-un a 'son of a bitch'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d56cc0b27b5c9d268d1312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d56cc0b27b5c9d268d1312/</guid><description>North Korean officials are demanding handwriting samples from thousands of Pyongyang residents after graffiti appeared insulting supreme leader Kim Jong-un, a rare sign of discontent among the elite in the capital.
Summary The message “Kim Jong-un, you son of a b&amp;mdash;-. Operated by dissidents and defectors, the Seoul-based media outlet has a network of undercover “citizen reporters” in North Korea and China. The UN’s Food and Agriculture Organisation has estimated North Korea is short 860,000 tonnes of produce this year alone, the equivalent to approximately 2.</description></item></channel></rss>