<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>alleged on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/alleged/</link><description>Recent content in alleged on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/alleged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK seeking return of Kevin Spacey from US to face sexual assault charges | UK news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62945427b648600d43992caf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 05:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62945427b648600d43992caf/</guid><description>Exclusive: Formal extradition is to be pursued if actor fails to come back to the country voluntarily
Highlights UK would seek formal extradition unless Spacey decides to come back voluntarily. US officials would have to be satisfied there is &amp;lsquo;probable cause&amp;rsquo; to detain Spacey. Spacey faces four charges of sexual assault relating to alleged attacks against three males between 2005 and 2013. Former head of extradition at the CPS says Spacey could be extradited in weeks if he does not contest extradition.</description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse sued in U.S. over alleged business related to oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d60f36784b3688d74faa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d60f36784b3688d74faa9/</guid><description>A group of people and entities have filed a class action lawsuit against Credit Suisse , alleging that the Swiss bank misled investors over business dealings related to Russian oligarchs, law firm Pomerantz LLP said.
Highlights Law firm Pomerantz LLP says Credit Suisse misled investors over dealings related to Russian oligarchs. Lawsuit filed in New York district court is on behalf of people and entities who acquired credit Suisse securities between March 19, 2021 and March 25, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Australia demands answers from China over alleged laser incident at sea</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214a93249d8433a0e9d3487/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214a93249d8433a0e9d3487/</guid><description>Australia is demanding China investigate the alleged use of a laser to &amp;quot;illuminate&amp;quot; an Australian jet in waters off the country&amp;rsquo;s north coast in an incident that threatens to worsen relations between the two countries.
Highlights Australia and China are at odds over the use of a laser to light up an Australian jet. The incident threatens to worsen relations between the two countries. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re the ones who need to explain, not just to think of all the countries in the region,&amp;rdquo; says Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison.</description></item><item><title>Police Reports Detail Battery Allegations Against Chris Brown in Miami Beach</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e74f216d387819b310c08/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e74f216d387819b310c08/</guid><description>Miami Beach Police are investigating allegations of battery by two women against R&amp;amp;B singer Chris Brown, according to police reports obtained by NBC 6.
Highlights NBC 6 Investigators obtained copies of police reports which detail what both women said happened when they were with Brown while visiting Miami Beach. Both alleged assaults took place more than a year ago, with the first woman claiming she was drugged and raped by the 32-year-old singer while at a party on a yacht that was docked near Diddy&amp;rsquo;s home on Dec.</description></item><item><title>2nd guilty plea planned in alleged plot to kidnap Whitmer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201bc14806c5f17d8b054fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:41:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201bc14806c5f17d8b054fd/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A man charged in an alleged plot to kidnap Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer has agreed to plead guilty, according to documents filed Monday, giving prosecutors another insider who could be a key witness at a March trial.
Highlights Kaleb Franks said he would join Ty Garbin as the second person to admit guilt in a scheme to snatch the Democratic governor before FBI agents arrested them in October 2020.</description></item><item><title>Ontario spent $133,866 trying to fire employee over alleged $2.99 theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd6c818dd457b34b3e027d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 18:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd6c818dd457b34b3e027d/</guid><description>The city of Ontario spent almost $134,000 in legal fees in its failed attempt to fire a civilian police records specialist. Gricelda Perez was accused of stealing a $2.99 energy bar from a convenience store in 2018.
Highlights Ontario spent almost $134,000 in legal fees in its failed attempt to fire a civilian police records specialist. Gricelda Perez was accused of stealing a $2.99 energy bar from a convenience store in 2018.</description></item></channel></rss>