<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>multiple on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/multiple/</link><description>Recent content in multiple on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 23:09:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/multiple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1 shot dead and multiple wounded after shooting at Graduation party in Thomaston - Fox3 Now</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ab8e160ed0e940f900ab/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 23:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292ab8e160ed0e940f900ab/</guid><description>ONE person is dead and two more are wounded after a gunman opened fire at a graduation party attended by 200 people in Thomaston Atlanta.
Highlights At least 200 people, mostly teens, were in the Park Lane Event Center when the shooting happened. Two people with serious injuries were taken by helicopter to a hospital in Macon, Georgia. Police have not made any arrests, but they think the suspects are not from the Thomaston area because only one of the victims lived there.</description></item><item><title>Man arrested in connection with "school shooter" signs found in 3 New Hampshire communities</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62926578dab7dc116d22fab7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 18:10:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62926578dab7dc116d22fab7/</guid><description>Multiple signs saying &amp;quot;school shooter&amp;quot; have been found in New Hampshire.
Highlights Man arrested after signs saying &amp;ldquo;school shooter&amp;rdquo; found in three communities. Guy Hanson, 61, of Pittsfield, New Hampshire, faces multiple charges. Department of Safety determined there is no credible threat at this time. Hanson is being held in Merrimack County Jail pending a hearing scheduled for Tuesday. No other suspects have been charged in relation to signs found in Barnstead, Epsom, and Pittsfields, N.</description></item><item><title>Multiple People Shot Outside Des Moines, IA Highschool - ABC</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226d8892f2d99553aef565d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 04:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226d8892f2d99553aef565d/</guid><description>Three teenagers were shot, according to police.
Highlights Two female East High School students, ages 16 and 18, are hospitalized in critical condition. The 15-year-old boy who died was not a student at the school. The gunfire appears to have come from a passing vehicle, police say. Potential suspects have been detained, but no charges have been filed at this time. The shooting occurred outside a high school in Des Moines, Iowa, police said Monday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Multiple sclerosis caused by Epstein-Barr-Virus — study: Researchers say Epstein-Barr-Virus is a main cause of MS, which affects 2.8 million people worldwide. New treatments and prevention may now be possible</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e166079eb8286c8eccaa6f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e166079eb8286c8eccaa6f/</guid><description>Researchers say Epstein-Barr-Virus is a main cause of MS, which affects 2.8 million people worldwide. New treatments and prevention may now be possible.
Summary Multiple sclerosis (MS) is an unpredictable condition — an autoimmune disease that attacks the central nervous system, the brain and spinal cord. The link between Epstein-Barr-Virus and MSIn a study conducted in the United States, researchers say they found that the Epstein-Barr-Virus (EBV) was definitely associated with all but one of 801 cases of multiple sclerosis.</description></item></channel></rss>