<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gas on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gas/</link><description>Recent content in gas on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 12:16:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In these locations, a gallon of gas costs more than the federal minimum wage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629606e726ccc29613515ee5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 12:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629606e726ccc29613515ee5/</guid><description>A handful of gas stations are charging $7.25 or more for a gallon of gas as fuel prices hit another record.
Highlights Gas prices are at a record $4.62 a gallon, up from $3.04 a month ago, AAA says. A gallon of regular fuel now costs as much as the federal minimum wage of $7.25. A handful of gas stations in California are charging more than the minimum wage at the pump.</description></item><item><title>BP profit more than doubles on 'exceptional' oil trading</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271edc2f525a1f988ce2916/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 03:07:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271edc2f525a1f988ce2916/</guid><description>BP took a hit of more than $24 billion from ditching its business in Russia but reported a huge jump in profit for the first quarter.
Highlights BP took a hit of more than $24 billion from ditching its business in Russia but reported a huge jump in profit for the first quarter. The UK-based energy giant said Tuesday that its underlying profit soared to $6.2 billion from $2.6 billion in the same period last year.</description></item><item><title>Sixteen states sue the Postal Service over plan to buy gas-powered vehicles.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c2b68205659c4f6f868bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c2b68205659c4f6f868bf/</guid><description>The lawsuits allege the Postal Service&amp;rsquo;s environmental analysis to justify spending up to $11.3 billion on gas-powered delivery trucks was deeply flawed.
Highlights 16 states sue U.S. Postal Service over its plan to replace its aging fleet with thousands of gas-powered delivery vehicles over the next decade. The lawsuits allege the agency&amp;rsquo;s environmental analysis to justify spending up to $11.3 billion on the gas trucks was deeply flawed. The Postal Service has about 230,000 vehicles, making up about one-third of the country&amp;rsquo;s entire federal fleet.</description></item><item><title>Russian oil tankers are vanishing off the map – transponders are turned off for hours at a time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245549b8dbd600257a6d926/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245549b8dbd600257a6d926/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine made the country a pariah in the global energy market. Since the war started, a de facto embargo on Russian oil has emerged, with oil companies, trading houses, shippers and banks backing away, all at the same time.
Highlights Dark activity among Russian-affiliated crude oil tankers is up by 600% compared with before the war began, a company says. Similar trends are playing out with other petroleum products, too.</description></item><item><title>Uber charging customers new fuel fee for rides, delivery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ed40557294e5f30e6f34b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 05:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ed40557294e5f30e6f34b/</guid><description>Citing record-high prices for gasoline, Uber is charging customers a new fuel fee to help offset costs for ride-hail and delivery drivers.
Highlights Uber is charging customers a new fuel fee to help offset costs for ride-hail and delivery drivers. The temporary surcharge will be either 45 cents or 55 cents for each Uber trip and 35 cents for Uber Eats order. All the money will go directly to drivers, San Francisco-based Uber said.</description></item><item><title>As inflation heats up, 64% of Americans are now living paycheck to paycheck</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</guid><description>The number of Americans living paycheck to paycheck is climbing, despite rising wages.
Highlights The cost of living is growing at the fastest annual pace in about four decades. At the start of 2022, 64% of the U.S. population was living paycheck to paycheck, up from 61% in December. Even among those earning six figures, 48% said they are now living paycheck-to-paycheck. When wages rise at a slower pace than inflation, those paychecks won&amp;rsquo;t go as far at the grocery store and at the gas pump.</description></item><item><title>Police fire tear gas as anti-Covid restrictions ‘Freedom Convoy’ enters Paris</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208d973ec5ce6a5c0210702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208d973ec5ce6a5c0210702/</guid><description>Police fired tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs-Élysées avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a &amp;quot;Freedom Convoy&amp;quot; protesting against Covid-19 restrictions made it into the French capital.
Highlights Police fire tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs-Élysées avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a &amp;ldquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rdquo; protesting against Covid-19 restrictions made it into the French capital. Police have mobilised thousands of officers, set up checkpoints and deployed armoured personnel carriers and water cannon trucks in preparation for the protests.</description></item></channel></rss>