<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gas on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gas/</link><description>Recent content in gas on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:18:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>As inflation heats up, 64% of Americans are now living paycheck to paycheck</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 16:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227819ffaa0facf7b42dca8/</guid><description>The number of Americans living paycheck to paycheck is climbing, despite rising wages.
Highlights The cost of living is growing at the fastest annual pace in about four decades. At the start of 2022, 64% of the U.S. population was living paycheck to paycheck, up from 61% in December. Even among those earning six figures, 48% said they are now living paycheck-to-paycheck. When wages rise at a slower pace than inflation, those paychecks won&amp;rsquo;t go as far at the grocery store and at the gas pump.</description></item><item><title>Police fire tear gas as anti-Covid restrictions ‘Freedom Convoy’ enters Paris</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208d973ec5ce6a5c0210702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208d973ec5ce6a5c0210702/</guid><description>Police fired tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs-Élysées avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a &amp;quot;Freedom Convoy&amp;quot; protesting against Covid-19 restrictions made it into the French capital.
Highlights Police fire tear gas at demonstrators on the Champs-Élysées avenue in Paris on Saturday shortly after a &amp;ldquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rdquo; protesting against Covid-19 restrictions made it into the French capital. Police have mobilised thousands of officers, set up checkpoints and deployed armoured personnel carriers and water cannon trucks in preparation for the protests.</description></item></channel></rss>