<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>forced on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/forced/</link><description>Recent content in forced on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 18:15:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/forced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine-Russia War: Russia forced to use outdated Soviet equipment - GUR</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626593af83114bc906291d66/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626593af83114bc906291d66/</guid><description>The majority of old Soviet-era equipment, held in storage since the 1970s, seems to be meant to shore up Russian artillery and missile capabilities.
Highlights Russian military is being forced to increasingly rely on outdated Soviet-made equipment in its ongoing invasion of Ukraine. The majority of old Soviet-era equipment seems to be meant to shore up Russian artillery and missile capabilities. In April alone, hundreds of weapons were taken out of GRAU&amp;rsquo;s storage for this purpose, including Msta-S anti-aircraft guns, Hurricane MLRSs and more.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas bartender robbed at gunpoint was forced to repay bosses stolen money, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620aa964de20c8dc82c39738/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 19:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620aa964de20c8dc82c39738/</guid><description>A Las Vegas bartender was robbed at gunpoint and then forced to repay his company the stolen money, according to a lawsuit filed by the employee.
Highlights A Las Vegas bartender was robbed at gunpoint and then forced to repay his company the stolen money, lawsuit says. Edward Parker was working at the Lodge Hualapai early Dec. 4, 2020, when a gunman entered and ordered him to kneel on the ground.</description></item><item><title>French lawmakers officially recognise China’s treatment of Uyghurs as ‘genocide’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e98727191a1e43ba67af92/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 16:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e98727191a1e43ba67af92/</guid><description>France&amp;rsquo;s parliament on Thursday denounced a &amp;quot;genocide&amp;quot; by China against its Uyghur Muslim population, in a resolution that risks straining ties between Paris and Beijing two weeks before the Winter O…
Summary It reads that the National Assembly &amp;ldquo;officially recognises the violence perpetrated by the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China against the Uyghurs as constituting crimes against humanity and genocide&amp;rdquo;. French MPs were also called to applaud Uyghurs refugees who had been invited to observe the parliamentary session.</description></item></channel></rss>