<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>campaign on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/campaign/</link><description>Recent content in campaign on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/campaign/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Australia election: conservative government voted out after nearly a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62890eee438ffbdadf2ff675/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 16:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62890eee438ffbdadf2ff675/</guid><description>Anthony Albanese’s Labor party defeats the ruling Coalition, but may lack the numbers to form majority government
Highlights Australia&amp;rsquo;s rightwing Coalition government has lost power after nearly a decade in office. Liberal leader Scott Morrison conceded defeat and announced he would step down as leader of his party. The biggest surprise of the night was the surge in support for the Greens. But Labor opposition failed to sweep to power in its own right, winning just 31.</description></item><item><title>New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin arrested on campaign finance fraud charges, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255eb63d4023367746611bb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 21:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255eb63d4023367746611bb/</guid><description>New York Lt. Gov. Brian Benjamin was arrested on charges related to a campaign finance fraud investigation, two people familiar with the matter told NBC New York.
Highlights Brian Benjamin surrendered to authorities and appeared before a federal judge in New York City on Tuesday. An indictment alleges that Benjamin was given campaign contributions from a Harlem real estate developer. In exchange, Benjamin obtained a $50,000 state grant for the developer&amp;rsquo;s business, the indictment states.</description></item><item><title>Trump aide Manafort removed from plane for revoked passport</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b55876002ef165478a08f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 17:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b55876002ef165478a08f/</guid><description>MIAMI (AP) — Former Trump adviser Paul Manafort was removed from a plane at Miami International Airport before it took off for Dubai because he carried a revoked passport, officials said Wednesday.
Highlights Paul Paul Paul was removed from a plane at Miami International Airport before it took off for Dubai because he carried a revoked passport, officials said Wednesday. Miami-Dade police confirmed Wednesday, March 23, 2022, that he was removed.</description></item><item><title>GoFundMe shuts down funding to 'Freedom Convoy'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fea21506ae11e36afd7b17/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 16:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fea21506ae11e36afd7b17/</guid><description>The platform said it would release the funds for a peaceful demonstration, but not for an occupation that has been linked to illegal activity.
Highlights GoFundMe pulls plug on campaign that had collected more than $10 million for &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; Convoy protest in Ottawa. Organizers say the protest by truckers and their supporters in Ottawa has become an occupation. The platform is allowing requests for donation refunds until Feb. A new fundraiser on Christian Crowdfunding site GiveSendGo had raised over $73,000 as of Friday evening.</description></item><item><title>US conservatives linked to rich donors wage campaign to ban books from schools | US news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eecd1882985717a68e550b/</guid><description>Experts warn trend is accelerating as groups push for bans of works that often address race, LGBTQ issues and marginalized people
Summary Conservative groups across the US, often linked to deep-pocketed rightwing donors, are carrying out a campaign to ban books from school libraries, often focused on works that address race, LGBTQ issues or marginalized communities. Groups purporting to be “grassroots” efforts have frequently led the charge, petitioning school boards or elected officials to remove certain books.</description></item></channel></rss>