<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>statue on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/statue/</link><description>Recent content in statue on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:09:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/statue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$2M relic stolen, angel statue beheaded at Brooklyn church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62953271df5c1f08a92da2fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62953271df5c1f08a92da2fa/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Police say someone busted into the altar at a New York City church, stole a $2 million gold relic and removed the head from a statue of an angel at some point late last week. The incident happened between 6:30 p.m.
Highlights Police: St. Augustine&amp;rsquo;s Roman Catholic Church in Brooklyn’s Park Slope neighborhood in New York. The tabernacle, a box containing Holy Communion items, was made of 18-carat gold and decorated with jewels.</description></item><item><title>Gaza farmer finds 4,500-year-old statue of Canaanite goddess</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268980629564048a6ef1085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 01:11:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268980629564048a6ef1085/</guid><description>The stone head the Canaanite goddess of beauty, love and war is unearthed in a Khan Younis field.
Highlights Farmer Nidal Abu Eid came across the head while cultivating his field. &amp;ldquo;We found it by chance. It was muddy and we washed it with water,&amp;rdquo; he said. The head the Canaanite goddess of beauty, love and war is unearthed in Khan Younis field. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Tibetan monks beaten, arrested for sharing Buddha statue destruction news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbd98c050b8410b7bfa3a0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbd98c050b8410b7bfa3a0/</guid><description>Chinese authorities last month destroyed a 99-foot tall Buddha statue, drawing a US State Department rebuke.
Summary The site of the demolished 99-foot Buddha statue in Drago in the Tibetan Autonomous Prefecture is shown in this Jan. 1, 2022 image. Authorities in western China’s Sichuan province are beating and arresting Tibetan monks suspected of informing outside contacts about the destruction of a sacred statue, Tibetan sources say. Monks from a local monastery and other Tibetan residents were forced to witness the destruction, an action experts called part of an ongoing campaign to eradicate Tibet’s distinct national culture and religion.</description></item></channel></rss>