<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>guilty on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/guilty/</link><description>Recent content in guilty on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 06:11:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/guilty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DC Man Pleads Guilty to Assaulting Asian Family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930e7dbc13a9e8c2ef267d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 06:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930e7dbc13a9e8c2ef267d/</guid><description>A D.C. man pleaded guilty Thursday to assaulting three adults of Chinese descent who were walking down a street in the Glover Park area of Washington, D.C., the&amp;hellip;
Highlights Patrick Trebat, 39, pleaded guilty to three counts of simple assault, including one with a hate-bias enhancement. Trebat attacked a man, a woman and their adult son because they appeared to be from another country and spoke a language Trebat didn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description></item><item><title>How to Murder Your Husband writer found guilty of murdering husband</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fcff95e196320db24e681/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 19:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fcff95e196320db24e681/</guid><description>Portland jury finds Nancy Crampton Brophy guilty of killing chef Daniel Brophy in June 2018
Highlights Nancy Crampton Brophy, 71, found guilty of second-degree murder of her husband. The self-published romance novelist wrote an essay titled How to Murder Your Husband. The essay detailed various options for committing an untraceable killing. It was written in the form of a brainstorming exercise for writers in 2011. Daniel Brophy was killed on 2 June 2018 as he prepared for work at the Oregon Culinary Institute in south-west Portland.</description></item><item><title>Man Arrested In Dave Chappelle Attack Charged With Attempted Murder In Alleged Stabbing Of Roommate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628776c582e2c8f1fb84784f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 11:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628776c582e2c8f1fb84784f/</guid><description>Isaiah Lee has been charged with attempted murder for allegedly stabbing his roommate at a transitional housing facility last year.
Highlights Isaiah Lee has pleaded not guilty to the felony charge and is due back in court June 2. Lee, 23, is accused of rushing Chappelle while carrying a replica gun that contained a switchblade. Lee is also accused of stabbing his roommate at a transitional housing facility in December. Lee remains jailed in lieu of $30,000 bail and is ordered to remain at least 100 yards away from the Hollywood Bowl and the comedian&amp;rsquo;s home.</description></item><item><title>Former Idaho lawmaker found guilty of raping intern</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c633c63a968bc26359e9f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 22:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c633c63a968bc26359e9f/</guid><description>BOISE, Idaho (AP) — A former Idaho lawmaker was convicted Friday of raping a 19-year-old legislative intern after a dramatic trial in which the young woman fled the witness stand during testimony, saying “I can’t do this.”
Highlights Former Idaho state Rep. Aaron von Ehlinger convicted Friday of raping a 19-year-old legislative intern after a dramatic trial in which the young woman fled the witness stand during testimony, saying “I can’t do this.</description></item><item><title>‘Monstrous, Monstrous Acts': Ex-Boston Police Union President Pleads Guilty to Child Rape</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626988a4dd8ada9810ac5526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 18:17:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626988a4dd8ada9810ac5526/</guid><description>A former head of Boston&amp;rsquo;s police union facing a total of 33 charges in connection with the rape and abuse of six children over various periods of time beginning&amp;hellip;
Highlights Patrick Rose pleads guilty to 21 counts of child rape and sexual assault over 27-year period. He was sentenced to 10 to 13 years in prison, plus 10 years probation following his release. Prosecutors said most of the charges date back to the 1990s, but at least one was within the last two years.</description></item><item><title>Jan. 6 rioter who said he wanted Trump's 'approval' found guilty by jury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</guid><description>A Donald Trump supporter who told jurors that he was &amp;quot;following presidential orders&amp;quot; when he stormed the Capitol was found guilty.
Highlights Dustin Thompson, 38, of Ohio, admitted he stole a coat rack and a bottle of liquor from the Capitol. He testified that he was seeking former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s “respect’ and “approval” on Jan. 6, 2021. Thompson&amp;rsquo;s attorney argued that “Donald Trump encouraged people like Dustin Thompson to storm the Capitol’s Capitol&amp;quot; District Judge Reggie Walton ordered Thompson detained until his sentencing, even though the government didn’t ask him to.</description></item><item><title>Kim Potter, ex-Minnesota officer, found guilty of manslaughter in death of Daunte Wright</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</guid><description>A Minneapolis jury reached an &amp;quot;outcome&amp;quot; in the trial of Kim Potter, a former police officer charged with fatally shooting Daunte Wright, a Black motorist.
Summary A Minneapolis jury on Thursday convicted former police officer Kim Potter on all charges she faced for fatally shooting Black motorist Daunte Wright — with a gun and not her Taser — earlier this year. Potter, 49, faces a maximum of 15 years in prison and is set to be sentenced Feb.</description></item></channel></rss>