<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>guilty on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/guilty/</link><description>Recent content in guilty on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/guilty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jan. 6 rioter who said he wanted Trump's 'approval' found guilty by jury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</guid><description>A Donald Trump supporter who told jurors that he was &amp;quot;following presidential orders&amp;quot; when he stormed the Capitol was found guilty.
Highlights Dustin Thompson, 38, of Ohio, admitted he stole a coat rack and a bottle of liquor from the Capitol. He testified that he was seeking former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s “respect’ and “approval” on Jan. 6, 2021. Thompson&amp;rsquo;s attorney argued that “Donald Trump encouraged people like Dustin Thompson to storm the Capitol’s Capitol&amp;quot; District Judge Reggie Walton ordered Thompson detained until his sentencing, even though the government didn’t ask him to.</description></item><item><title>Kim Potter, ex-Minnesota officer, found guilty of manslaughter in death of Daunte Wright</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</guid><description>A Minneapolis jury reached an &amp;quot;outcome&amp;quot; in the trial of Kim Potter, a former police officer charged with fatally shooting Daunte Wright, a Black motorist.
Summary A Minneapolis jury on Thursday convicted former police officer Kim Potter on all charges she faced for fatally shooting Black motorist Daunte Wright — with a gun and not her Taser — earlier this year. Potter, 49, faces a maximum of 15 years in prison and is set to be sentenced Feb.</description></item></channel></rss>