<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>signs on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/signs/</link><description>Recent content in signs on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/signs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York governor signs law raising age to own semiautomatic rifle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e7b1ced6b1d1a1926114c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 22:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e7b1ced6b1d1a1926114c/</guid><description>New Yorkers under age 21 will be prohibited from buying semiautomatic rifles under a new law signed Monday by Gov. Kathy Hochul.
Highlights New Yorkers under age 21 will be prohibited from buying semiautomatic rifles under a new law signed by Gov. Kathy Hochul. New York&amp;rsquo;s Legislature passed the bills last week, pushing the changes through after a pair of mass shootings involving 18-year-old gunmen using guns. One bill will require microstamping in new firearms, which could help law enforcement solve gun-related crimes.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma's Gov. Stitt signs bill restricting school bathrooms to birth sex, effective immediately</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fb63a1fd93b426ab09105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:18:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fb63a1fd93b426ab09105/</guid><description>The Oklahoma bill requires districts to restrict bathroom access by students&amp;rsquo; sex. If schools don&amp;rsquo;t comply, they face a 5% deduction in state funding.
Highlights Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt signs bill restricting school bathrooms to birth sex, effective immediately. School districts and charter schools that don&amp;rsquo;t comply face a 5% deduction in their state funding. The legislation follows months of debate over whether students should be allowed to use the restroom that matches their gender identity, not strictly their sex at birth.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee Gov. Bill Lee signs law adding criminal penalties to abortion pill distribution via mail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278ce21021783408abd9f42/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278ce21021783408abd9f42/</guid><description>The bill adds criminal penalties to abortion bill dispensation through telehealth or mail distribution means.
Highlights Tennessee Gov. Bill Lee signs law adding criminal penalties to abortion pill distribution via mail. The bill prohibits any distribution of abortion medication except when prescribing is done in person by a physician. The legislation also makes it a Class E felony punishable by a fine of up to $50,000 if that procedure is not followed.</description></item><item><title>Idaho governor signs abortion ban modeled on Texas law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cb55e76056edaa021b7c2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cb55e76056edaa021b7c2/</guid><description>BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho on Wednesday became the first state to enact a law modeled after a Texas statute banning abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy and allowing it to be enforced through lawsuits to avoid constitutional court challenges.
Highlights Idaho on Wednesday, March 23, 2022, became the first state to enact a law modeled after a Texas statute banning abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy. Republican Gov.</description></item><item><title>Ohio Gov. DeWine signs bill into law allowing people to carry concealed weapons without a permit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62302f1771a53a63925f7dcf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 06:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62302f1771a53a63925f7dcf/</guid><description>Ohio Governor Dewine signed Senate Bill 215 that allows eligible Ohioans 21 or older to carry a concealed weapon without a permit Monday.
Highlights Ohio Gov. DeWine signs bill into law allowing people to carry concealed weapons without a permit. Ohio House members voted 57-35 in favor of the bill on March 2. The bill would also reduce penalties if a gun owner does not properly notify law enforcement they have a firearm in their possession; it will go into effect in 90-days.</description></item><item><title>South Dakota governor signs 2022’s first trans athlete ban into law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc99629cc95d31550cff2a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 03:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc99629cc95d31550cff2a/</guid><description>South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem signed a bill Thursday that bans transgender girls and women from playing on female sports teams.
Highlights South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem signed a bill that bans transgender girls and women from playing on female sports teams. The state is the first this year — and the 10th nationwide — to enact such a bill into law. The bill applies to all state-accredited schools, generally includes both public and private schools.</description></item></channel></rss>