<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>santa on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/santa/</link><description>Recent content in santa on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 18:17:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/santa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>USPS services suspended in Santa Monica neighborhood after repeat attacks on carriers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625470a4c21b7b5c4f0c187f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 18:17:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625470a4c21b7b5c4f0c187f/</guid><description>The postal service left a notice for all the residents in the affected area, where they won&amp;rsquo;t be delivering mail in the near future.
Highlights A Santa Monica resident reported an assault on a mail carrier in the area. The incident happened in the early hours of Jan. The United States Postal Service has suspended their services for one block of residents. Residents are angry at the actions of a man who has not been charged with any crime.</description></item><item><title>Man breaks into home, takes bath, eats shrimp leaves $200 for damages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033135b9995d68c7af4c4e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 03:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033135b9995d68c7af4c4e/</guid><description>Teral Christesson, 34, was arrested Sunday for breaking into a home in New Mexico. He apologized, told the homeowner he just needed a warm place to sleep. Christesson told investigators he was “caught in a bl
Highlights Teral Christesson, 34, was arrested Sunday for breaking into a home in New Mexico. He apologized, told the homeowner he just needed a warm place to sleep and left the man $200 to repair the window.</description></item></channel></rss>