<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mandatory on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mandatory/</link><description>Recent content in mandatory on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 23:09:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mandatory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>USB Type-C will become mandatory for all phones, tablets and cameras sold in the EU</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fda8f0f130367c6047706/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 23:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629fda8f0f130367c6047706/</guid><description>This move is expected to save EU customers &amp;lsquo;250 million euro a year on unnecessary charger purchases&amp;rsquo;
Highlights USB Type-C will become mandatory for all phones, tablets and cameras sold in the EU. This move is seen as a major blow to Apple, who ship most of their devices with Lightning ports for charging and data transfer. This is expected to save EU customers &amp;lsquo;250 million euro a year on unnecessary charger purchases&amp;rsquo; The move is good news for consumers, as they should no longer need multiple chargers to charge all of their new devices.</description></item><item><title>Austria makes COVID-19 vaccination mandatory starting February.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5141c404a48f6bdad6630/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 07:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5141c404a48f6bdad6630/</guid><description>Austrian government presents mandatory vaccination law coming in next month
Summary “Without obligatory vaccination, we will always lag behind,” health minister Wolfgang Mueckstein said. “All experts believe that we will need high overall immunity in the population next fall as well,” Mueckstein said. If authorities judge vaccination progress still to be insufficient, they would then send reminders to people who remain unvaccinated, Nehammer said. If that still does not work, people would be sent a vaccination appointment and fined if they do not keep it.</description></item></channel></rss>