<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mahoney on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mahoney/</link><description>Recent content in mahoney on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 15:14:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mahoney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>South Carolina inmate picks firing squad over electric chair as execution looms, calling both options "unconstitutional"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625add1a2cb4d6ffa1bd38bf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 15:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625add1a2cb4d6ffa1bd38bf/</guid><description>If executed as scheduled on April 29, Richard Moore would be the first person put to death in the state since 2011.
Highlights Richard Moore, 57, is the first state prisoner to face the choice of execution methods after a law went into effect last year making electrocution the default. The new law was prompted by the decadelong break, which corrections officials attribute to an inability to procure the drugs needed to carry out lethal injections.</description></item><item><title>South Carolina schedules first execution after preparing death chamber for firing squad</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625187e649397847c8ac41c8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 13:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625187e649397847c8ac41c8/</guid><description>Richard Bernard Moore, 57, could face a choice between the electric chair and the firing squad.
Highlights Richard Moore, 57, has spent more than two decades on death row after he was convicted of killing convenience store clerk James Mahoney in 2001. Moore could face a choice between the electric chair and the firing squad, two options available to death row prisoners after legislators altered the state&amp;rsquo;s capital punishment law last year.</description></item></channel></rss>