<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>place on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/place/</link><description>Recent content in place on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 15:14:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/place/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twenty People Shot at Arkansas Car Show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623744bafa4229f7b8dac0b2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623744bafa4229f7b8dac0b2/</guid><description>A person was killed and at least 24 people were injured in a shooting at a car show in Dumas, Arkansas, on Saturday night, police said. “One suspect is in
Highlights A person was killed and at least 24 people were injured in a shooting at a car show in Dumas, Arkansas, on Saturday night. The event&amp;rsquo;s organizers, a nonprofit group called the Hoodnic Foundation, said it was “heartbroken and in shock at what took place” The conditions of the people injured and information about possible suspects was not immediately available.</description></item><item><title>Shooting at a Portland Protest Against Police Violence Leaves One Dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212bcc461ec54ddef583463/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212bcc461ec54ddef583463/</guid><description>Authorities describe confrontation in Normandale Park between homeowner and participants in police violence protest
Highlights One person killed and five wounded in Portland shooting at Normandale Park. Incident happened during confrontation between armed homeowner and armed protesters. Police responded to six shootings in nine hours on Thursday night and Friday morning. At the time of the shooting a march was planned for Amir Locke, a Black man shot dead by police in Minneapolis.</description></item></channel></rss>