<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>charged on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/charged/</link><description>Recent content in charged on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 11:09:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/charged/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man Arrested In Dave Chappelle Attack Charged With Attempted Murder In Alleged Stabbing Of Roommate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628776c582e2c8f1fb84784f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 11:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628776c582e2c8f1fb84784f/</guid><description>Isaiah Lee has been charged with attempted murder for allegedly stabbing his roommate at a transitional housing facility last year.
Highlights Isaiah Lee has pleaded not guilty to the felony charge and is due back in court June 2. Lee, 23, is accused of rushing Chappelle while carrying a replica gun that contained a switchblade. Lee is also accused of stabbing his roommate at a transitional housing facility in December. Lee remains jailed in lieu of $30,000 bail and is ordered to remain at least 100 yards away from the Hollywood Bowl and the comedian&amp;rsquo;s home.</description></item><item><title>Teen charged in 151-mph crash that killed 6 posted Instagram videos of himself racing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626365b9b86a764fe0678c3d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 02:35:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626365b9b86a764fe0678c3d/</guid><description>A Florida teenager has been charged in the deaths of six people in a violent 151-mph crash in January, and new court documents reveal he posted himself racing at 182 mph in his luxury BWM on social media just two weeks prior.
Highlights Noah Galle, 18, was formally charged Monday with six counts of vehicular homicide in the Jan. 27 crash that killed six farm employees leaving work in Delray Beach, Florida.</description></item><item><title>State trooper who shot, killed New Haven teen in 2020 arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62605af434eec5f93f8564ad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62605af434eec5f93f8564ad/</guid><description>It was unclear Tuesday evening what exactly the trooper was charged with. He turned&amp;hellip;
Highlights Brian North turned himself in to the inspector general at Troop I in Bethany around 7:30 p.m. Tuesday. He was released on a $50,000 bond and scheduled to appear in Superior Court in Milford on May 3. Mubarak Soulemane, 19, was shot and killed on Jan. 15, 2020, after he allegedly showed a knife at an AT&amp;amp;T store in Norwalk and carjacked a ride share driver.</description></item><item><title>Five students charged with hate crimes in 'racially motivated' incident, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 04:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d700ddef4b900045cdf8b/</guid><description>Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children while exclaiming “brown power!” — an incident police are calling a “racially-motivated crime.”
Highlights Five Florida middle school students were charged with hate crimes after allegedly attacking a different group of children. They allegedly yelled “It’s Opposite Day!” and “brown power!’ Police are calling the incident a racially motivated crime. In Florida, evidencing prejudice while committing a hate crime is considered a third-degree felony.</description></item><item><title>Family of Emmett Till want woman who made false accusation to be charged with murder for 1955 lynching</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cb86b831a55fb0c7b9e7d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cb86b831a55fb0c7b9e7d/</guid><description>Family members of Emmett Till are seeking justice for his 1955 death that helped launch the civil rights movement.
Highlights Family of Emmett Till want woman who made false accusation to be charged with murder. Carolyn Bryant Donham is the only living accomplice in the murder of Till, they said. Donham&amp;rsquo;s false accusations led to the 14-year-old&amp;rsquo;s kidnapping and lynching in the Delta region. The U.S. Department of Justice opened investigations into Till&amp;rsquo;s murder in 2004 and 2018; no new charges were announced in December.</description></item><item><title>Russian-American charged with acting as illegal Russian agent in the US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62286f8098282a7eb4eca6b8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 09:13:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62286f8098282a7eb4eca6b8/</guid><description>A dual Russian-American citizen has been charged with acting as a spy in the US, according to court filings that say she ran organizations that &amp;quot;sought to spread Russian propaganda.&amp;quot;
Highlights A dual Russian-American citizen has been charged with acting as a spy in the US. The complaint alleges that Elena Branson worked on behalf of the Russian government and Russian officials. Prosecutors allege she coordinated meetings for Russian officials to lobby US political officials and businesspeople.</description></item><item><title>4th Kansas Rep. charged in a year, Suzi Carlson charged with two counts after DUI arrest last month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62213d62d4636e71e7d9be1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 22:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62213d62d4636e71e7d9be1c/</guid><description>Rep. Suzi Carlson, R-Clay Center, is charged with two counts in relation to an arrest for allegedly\u00a0driving under the influence earlier this year.
Highlights Rep. Suzi Carlson charged with two counts after DUI arrest last month. Carlson was arrested on suspicion of driving under the influence with a blood alcohol concentration above 0.08 and failure to maintain a single lane. Carlson, 69, is a retired municipal court judge. She is the fourth Kansas lawmaker arrested in the past year, with another scheduled hearing scheduled for May.</description></item><item><title>Alleged ‘Proud Boy’ charged over calling woman ‘n-word’ before punching her in the face</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e1d309d61180b09a926cb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 13:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e1d309d61180b09a926cb/</guid><description>Police are investigating whether there are any links to Proud Boys ‘gang activity’
Highlights Andrew Walls, 26, charged with possessing firearm while intoxicated and assaulting 23-year-old woman Cameron Morgan. Victim&amp;rsquo;s father posted video online asking for help identifying the man. Police say they are looking into &amp;lsquo;awfully similar&amp;rsquo; images of who they say appears to be Walls. Police are investigating whether there are any links to Proud Boys ‘gang activity’ Mr Walls reportedly called himself the vice president of the Proud Boys’ Akron/Canton Chapter, the Akron Beacon Journal reported in a news story.</description></item><item><title>Local BLM chapter posts bail for man charged with attempted murder of mayoral candidate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f398145d88ce574f204e9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f398145d88ce574f204e9/</guid><description>LOUISVILLE, Ky. (TND) — A man who is charged with the attempted murder of a mayoral candidate in Louisville is no longer in jail after a local Black Lives Matter chapter teamed up with a community bail fund to post his bail. Quintez Brown, 21, who is said to be a &amp;quot;social justice activist&amp;quot; running as a candidate for Louisville&amp;rsquo;s metro council, allegedly tried to assassinate Democrat mayoral candidateCraig Greenberg.</description></item><item><title>MILWAUKEE -- The man who bought Kyle Rittenhouse an assault-style rifle when he was only 17 has agreed to plead no contest to contributing to the delinquency of a minor, a non-criminal citation, and avoid convictions on the two felonies he'd been facing.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc90663738cf593c49f462/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc90663738cf593c49f462/</guid><description>Dominick Black was charged with delivering a dangerous weapon to a minor, resulting in death.
Summary The two counts related to Joseph Rosenbaum and Anthony Huber, the protesters Rittenhouse fatally shot the night of Aug. 25, 2020, in Kenosha.Black was 18 when he purchased the rifle for Rittenhouse at a hardware store in Rusk County in May of that year. At 17, Rittenhouse was too young to legally purchase the weapon.</description></item><item><title>Idaho man charged with murder and cannibalism after body parts found in microwave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</guid><description>Description Summary CLARK FORK — A northern Idaho man faces serious charges after investigators say they found a dead man’s body parts in a microwave. Russell is charged with felony first-degree murder and felony cannibalism in an amended criminal complaint filed Wednesday. Deputies went to Flaget’s truck, where they found the body naked from the waist down positioned awkwardly in the passenger seat. Some of the tissue indicated heat had been applied, possibly in the microwave for one to two minutes, according to court documents.</description></item></channel></rss>