<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rich on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rich/</link><description>Recent content in rich on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 05:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rich/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'You got rich off our dead bodies' opioid victims tell Purdue's Sacklers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ada1d06819d4181840eb5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ada1d06819d4181840eb5/</guid><description>Victims of America&amp;rsquo;s opioid epidemic confronted members of the Sackler family that owns Purdue Pharma on Thursday with wrenching stories of suffering they said was caused by the painkillers that built the company fortune.
Highlights Victims of U.S. opioid epidemic confronted Sackler family that owns Purdue Pharma on Thursday with wrenching stories of suffering they said was caused by the painkillers that built the company fortune. &amp;ldquo;You got rich off our dead bodies and told us it was our own fault for dying,&amp;rdquo; Ryan Hampton told Richard Sackler, a former board member.</description></item><item><title>Over 100 millionaires call for higher taxes worldwide: 'Tax us now'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9088c247558d98d634f4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9088c247558d98d634f4e/</guid><description>A group of ultrawealthy people are asking governments around the world to make them pay more in taxes in order to help close a growing wealth gap.
Summary IRS TAX-FILING SEASON TO KICK OFF ON JAN. 24&amp;quot;As millionaires, we know that the current tax system is not fair,&amp;quot; they wrote. They argued the bedrock of a strong democracy is a fair tax system that bridges the gap between everyday people and the ultrawealthy.</description></item><item><title>Locked-out New Zealanders outraged as visa scheme for rich foreigners resumes. Critics say the wealthy will be able to buy their way in while citizens lose out on quarantine spots.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6b3794cfd4927f11a1805/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 06:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6b3794cfd4927f11a1805/</guid><description>Critics say the wealthy will be able to buy their way in while citizens lose out on quarantine spots
Summary With their visas in hand, investors may apply to compete for spots in New Zealand’s congested MIQ system. According to information released under the Official Information Act, New Zealand’s policy of granting visas to wealthy investors reached its height in 2016-2017 when 446 wealthy investors were granted visas. Due to the emergence of Covid-19 and the closing of New Zealand’s borders, just 51 investor visas were granted in 2020-2021.</description></item></channel></rss>