<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cup on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cup/</link><description>Recent content in cup on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Poland and Sweden refuse to play Russia in World Cup qualifiers because of Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b6c116f6ca2b76e5c5d86/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b6c116f6ca2b76e5c5d86/</guid><description>Polish and Bayern Munich star Robert Lewandowski said he can&amp;rsquo;t &amp;quot;imagine playing&amp;quot; against Russia while its military continues to attack Ukraine.
Highlights Poland and Sweden will not play Russia in World Cup playoff qualifiers. Poland&amp;rsquo;s football association president Cezary Kulesza said in a tweet it is &amp;ldquo;time to act!&amp;rdquo; The decision comes days after FIFA President Gianni Infantino failed to condemn the actions of Russian President Vladimir Putin. Russia was set to play Poland on March 24 in a semifinal playoff game in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>A Mexican woman reported a sexual assault in Qatar. She faces jail, 100 lashes.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62174c21f36484aa4d75ad52/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62174c21f36484aa4d75ad52/</guid><description>Mexican Paola Schietekat said she was sexually assaulted in Qatar where she worked but instead could face punishment if she goes back to the country she left.
Highlights Paola Schietekat was working in Qatar for the Supreme Committee for Delivery and Legacy. In June, she said she was assaulted in a violent incident by an acquaintance and fellow Latino who also worked in Qatar. The Mexican economist managed to leave Qatar with the help of Human Rights Watch and the World Cup body where she worked.</description></item></channel></rss>