<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wait on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wait/</link><description>Recent content in wait on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 04:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wait/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Federal agents entered Uvalde school to kill gunman despite local police initially asking them to wait</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291a14b959660ffebec7e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291a14b959660ffebec7e82/</guid><description>Federal agents who went to Robb Elementary in Uvalde, Tex., on Tuesday to confront a gunman were told by local police to wait, but chose to enter the school.
Highlights Federal agents who went to Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, on Tuesday to confront a gunman were told by local police to wait and not enter the school. After about half an hour, the federal agents opted of their own volition to lead the “stack” of officers inside the school and take down the shooter, two senior federal law enforcement officials say.</description></item><item><title>Dozens killed in attack on Kharkiv, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e6fb587e2dfca36fc716b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 19:11:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e6fb587e2dfca36fc716b/</guid><description>The cities of Kharkiv and Chernihiv suffer fierce shelling despite talks between Russia and Ukraine.
Highlights Kharkiv and Chernihiv suffer fierce shelling despite talks between Russia and Ukraine. In the north-west, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second-largest city has been pounded by suspected cluster munitions. Siege tactics used to devastating effect in Syria are being unleashed around the historic city of Chernihiv. But other Ukrainian cities give a glimpse of what may lie in wait for Kyiv, the country&amp;rsquo;s second largest city, according to a report by the Russian-backed anti-government forces in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Antonio Brown allegedly broke COVID protocol by sneaking date into hotel - ProFootballTalk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d863a51a9e8b9bab45d3c7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d863a51a9e8b9bab45d3c7/</guid><description>Summary Getty ImagesIf you thought the Antonio Brown saga couldn’t get any weirder, you were wrong. Someone named Ava Louise contends that she and Brown had sex in his room at the Jersey City, New Jersey Westin hotel, and that Brown ranted about the league’s COVID protocols. He also allegedly said, “I can’t wait for you to see what I do tomorrow. I can’t wait for you to see me tomorrow.</description></item></channel></rss>