<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>farm on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/farm/</link><description>Recent content in farm on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 19:12:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/farm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russians plunder $5M farm vehicles from Ukraine -- to find they've been remotely disabled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626edb655f10285f693a0d27/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626edb655f10285f693a0d27/</guid><description>Russian troops in the occupied city of Melitopol have stolen all the equipment from a farm equipment dealership &amp;ndash; and shipped it to Chechnya, according to a Ukrainian businessman in the area.
Highlights Russian troops in the occupied city of Melitopol have stolen all the equipment from a farm equipment dealership – and shipped it to Chechnya, according to a Ukrainian businessman. But after a journey of more than 700 miles, the thieves were unable to use any of the equipment – because it had been locked remotely.</description></item><item><title>Gang steal 1,600 kilos of cheese from Dutch dairy farm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e1eb425b0e5ec82798f2e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 23:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e1eb425b0e5ec82798f2e/</guid><description>Gang steal 1,600 kilos of cheese from Dutch dairy farm
Highlights Thieves stole 1,600 kilos of cheese worth €21,000 from a dairy farm in Noord Brabant. Almost all the cheese from the farm’s storage was taken and that has set the farm back some six months in income. Cheese farmers were plagued by a string of cheese thefts a couple of years ago and this week&amp;rsquo;s heist may be a sign of things to come, dairy farmer Theo Dekker said.</description></item></channel></rss>