<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>media on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/media/</link><description>Recent content in media on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 02:57:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Endangered sea turtle nest found at Galveston Island State Park for the first time in a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c498be90b4095e8c123a3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 02:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c498be90b4095e8c123a3/</guid><description>The nest contained more than one hundred eggs laid by a Kemp’s Ridley Sea Turtle &amp;ndash; one of the most endangered sea turtle species in the world.
Highlights The nest contained more than one hundred eggs laid by a Kemp&amp;rsquo;s Ridley sea turtle. Kemp&amp;rsquo;s is one of the most endangered sea turtle species in the world. The species was almost lost in the 1980s until intensive conservation efforts were implemented on nesting beaches and through fisheries management.</description></item><item><title>'Hands tied, shot in ear and limbs': Bodies of men tortured, killed by Russian forces found in Bucha grave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d89d9d06c5329b3acb3d6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 19:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d89d9d06c5329b3acb3d6/</guid><description>According to a Ukraine media reports, Ukrainian authorities filed criminal charges Thursday (April 28) against Russian soldiers allegedly involved in mass killings in Bucha.
Highlights Ukrainian authorities filed criminal charges Thursday (April 28) against Russian soldiers allegedly involved in mass killings in Bucha. According to police, on 29 April, a pit containing the bodies of three men who had been beaten up by Russian soldiers and then brutally killed was found.</description></item><item><title>Police open fire on vehicle in Paris, killing two people and injuring third - local media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626618c884e07209c5b48b3e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 03:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626618c884e07209c5b48b3e/</guid><description>It is believed that the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s driver, and a passenger sitting in the front seat, were those who died.
Highlights Police open fire on vehicle that tried to hit them - killing two occupants and injuring a third. The incident happened near the Pont Neuf - in the centre of the French capital - on Sunday night. It is believed that the vehicle&amp;rsquo;s driver, and a passenger sitting in the front seat, were those who died.</description></item><item><title>Teen is arrested after posting on social media with drugs, money, guns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62497366e3b2cc0b8df68d95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 10:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62497366e3b2cc0b8df68d95/</guid><description>SAN ANTONIO (WOAI) — Deputies arrested a teen after he posted images on social media with drugs, money and guns. Teen is arrested after posting on social media with drugs, money, and guns (Photo Courtesy of Bexar County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office) The incident happened Tuesday, March 29, when David Anakin Guerra, 17 posted on social media that he had THC cartridges, weapons and cash.
Highlights Deputies arrested a teen after he posted images on social media with drugs, money and guns.</description></item><item><title>Russia Said It Has Blocked Facebook</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 22:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</guid><description>Russia’s communications regulator said it blocked Facebook because of “discrimination against Russian media and information resources.&amp;quot; Twitter was blocked shortly after.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator blocks access to Facebook and Twitter. The move comes amid President Vladimir Putin’s ongoing military invasion of Ukraine. Facebook&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Meta, says it will keep its apps, including Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp, available to Russians. Last week, Meta president Nick Clegg said Russia had restricted use of the company&amp;rsquo;s services.</description></item><item><title>Freedom Convoy leader Pat King arrested live on social media.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210a6e8a8acd94012b9718d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 08:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210a6e8a8acd94012b9718d/</guid><description>“I am being arrested. We will talk to you guys soon.”
Highlights Pat King, one of the most vocal members of the “Freedom Convoy’s movement, went on social media Friday to livestream his arrest. King was approached in his vehicle by a police officer who said: “You are under arrest, sir.” “I am being arrested by this officer right now,” he told viewers to his live Facebook feed. ‘I have the right to a lawyer?</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong pro-democracy news site closes after raid, arrests | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd04ab89a30a5218870c65/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 01:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd04ab89a30a5218870c65/</guid><description>HONG KONG (AP) — A vocal pro-democracy website in Hong Kong shut down Wednesday after police raided its office and arrested seven current and former editors, board members and a journalist in a continuing crackdown on dissent in the semi-autonomous Chinese city.
Summary Editor of Stand News Patrick Lam, center, is escorted by police officers into a van after they searched evidence at his office in Hong Kong, Wednesday, Dec. 29, 2021.</description></item></channel></rss>