<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>action on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/action/</link><description>Recent content in action on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 03:39:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Doctors who ‘mislead’ on social media could soon face regulatory action</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268baefcb6e06e303b77a80/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 03:39:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268baefcb6e06e303b77a80/</guid><description>Planned new guidelines say online posts could be scrutinised by the General Medical Council
Highlights General Medical Council is to update its Good Medical Practice guide for the first time in almost a decade. Posts made on Twitter, Instagram and TikTok could be scrutinised if a doctor is reported. Doctors must ‘be honest and trustworthy, make clear the limits of their knowledge’ and make reasonable checks to make sure any information given is not misleading’ The document will also make it a doctor’s duty to act if they become aware of workplace bullying, as well as discrimination and sexual harassment.</description></item><item><title>Woman takes legal action after Met officer who called her ‘hot’ keeps job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 04:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</guid><description>Kristina O’Connor says detective who was investigating after men tried to steal her phone asked her out
Highlights Kristina O&amp;rsquo;Connor said she was sent inappropriate messages by DCI James Mason. The officer asked her out to dinner while taking her statement about an attempted robbery. A panel at a police misconduct hearing last year found him guilty of gross misconduct. The Met has confirmed he remains a serving officer. O’Connor is seeking a judicial review of how the investigation was handled by the force.</description></item><item><title>Biden says any Russian movement into Ukraine will be considered invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea21c7f4766d4415442f33/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea21c7f4766d4415442f33/</guid><description>U.S. President Joe Biden said on Thursday that he has made clear to Russian President Vladimir Putin that any Russian movement into Ukraine would be considered an invasion, after he earlier suggested allies were split over how to react to any &amp;quot;minor incursion.&amp;quot;
Summary REUTERS/Jonathan ErnstWASHINGTON, Jan 20 (Reuters) - U.S. President Joe Biden said on Thursday that he has made clear to Russian President Vladimir Putin that any Russian movement into Ukraine would be considered an invasion, after he earlier suggested allies were split over how to react to any &amp;ldquo;minor incursion.</description></item></channel></rss>