<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>threat on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threat/</link><description>Recent content in threat on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 04:25:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida fifth grader arrested after threatening a mass shooting, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295988d850718b5c5c3018c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 04:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295988d850718b5c5c3018c/</guid><description>A fifth grade student in Florida was arrested over the weekend and charged with sending a text message threatening to carry out a mass shooting, authorities
Highlights The Lee County Sheriff’s Office said it had learned earlier that day of a &amp;ldquo;threatening text message&amp;rdquo; sent by a student at an elementary school. It said its local school threat enforcement team was immediately notified and started investigating. The 10-year-old boy was interviewed and charged later with &amp;ldquo;making a written threat to conduct a mass shooting,&amp;rdquo; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said.</description></item><item><title>Armed female bystander kills man firing at party in West Virginia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62938ca685f11d9d4d61462b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62938ca685f11d9d4d61462b/</guid><description>A woman at a birthday party drew her pistol and left the gunman with multiple wounds, police say.
Highlights A woman at a birthday party drew her pistol and left the gunman with multiple wounds, police say. &amp;ldquo;Instead of running from the threat she engaged with the threat and saved several lives,&amp;rdquo; police say. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s just a member of the community who was carrying her weapon lawfully,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;And instead of running&amp;hellip; she engaged&amp;hellip; in the threat,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description></item><item><title>2 killed, 10 injured in Cedar Rapids club shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625356858cf8ff1b626f8e57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625356858cf8ff1b626f8e57/</guid><description>Two people were killed and another 10 injured after someone opened fire in a nightclub early Sunday morning in Cedar Rapids, Iowa.
Highlights Two people were killed and another 10 injured after someone opened fire in a nightclub early Sunday morning in Cedar Rapids, Iowa. Officers on a nearby patrol responded to the shooting around 1:27 a.m. Sunday morning at the Taboo Nightclub and Lounge. The two victims were not identified and police did not offer conditions on the injured.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine's growing reserve army 'getting ready' amid fears of Russian attack | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcf2e6f76291a3b787a8ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcf2e6f76291a3b787a8ec/</guid><description>An increasing number of Ukrainians are joining territorial defence groups designed to support the regular armed forces in the event of a Russian offensive - such as by protecting key locations like council buildings and bridges.
Summary &amp;ldquo;The &amp;lsquo;young blood&amp;rsquo; … are people who didn&amp;rsquo;t serve in the armed forces for different reasons but they passed our combat training&amp;hellip; His group, 130 Battalion of Territorial Defence of Kyiv, comprises some 320-330 reservists, aged between 21 and 56.</description></item></channel></rss>