<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deputies on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deputies/</link><description>Recent content in deputies on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 09:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deputies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$3M settlement reached in lawsuit over Black man fatally shot by N.C. deputies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a067353feeb3b7e9315403/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a067353feeb3b7e9315403/</guid><description>A North Carolina sheriff’s office announced a $3 million settlement on Monday in a lawsuit filed by the family of Andrew Brown Jr., a Black man who was shot and killed by sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputies.
Highlights Andrew Brown Jr. was killed on April 21 of last year by Pasquotank County sheriff’s deputies while they were serving drug-related warrants at his Elizabeth City home. The family had filed a $30 million civil rights lawsuit in 2021, saying the man died because officers showed “intentional and reckless disregard of his life” The settlement includes a special $1 million appropriation to go along with $2 million from the county&amp;rsquo;s insurance policy.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan to hold constitutional referendum that strips Nazarbayev's immunity and restricts power of president in the government</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ce73282833d835f2a2e57/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 14:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ce73282833d835f2a2e57/</guid><description>On June 5, Kazakhs will vote on a package of reforms intended to transform the country from a super-presidential system to a “presidential system with a strong parliament.”
Highlights Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s president Kassym-Jomart Tokayev called protesters terrorists and requested support from the Russian-backed Collective Security Treaty Organization to quell mass unrest. The vote will take place on June 5, just one month after the proposed reforms were released. The reform package addresses 33 separate articles – about one third of the total constitutional articles – and was developed by a working group.</description></item><item><title>Saturday night shootout at McDonald’s in Orange County after woman fires gun at deputies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fbcb55465308b3ca34e20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 11:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fbcb55465308b3ca34e20/</guid><description>Deputies responded to an armed robbery call at a McDonald’s on Saturday night. Deputies said the shooter, a woman in her 30s, fired a handgun inside and made threatening statements. All employees and customers were able to
Highlights Deputies responded to an armed robbery call at a McDonald’s on Saturday night. Deputies said the shooter, a woman in her 30s, fired a handgun inside and made threatening statements. All employees and customers were able to get out unharmed.</description></item><item><title>California teen who vanished three years ago is found alive in Utah</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b89183837cd3dea72ba0f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 03:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b89183837cd3dea72ba0f/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I never stopped looking for him. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t a day I wasn&amp;rsquo;t searching for him, in some form or fashion,&amp;quot; his mother said.
Highlights 19-year-old Connerjack Oswalt disappeared from his family&amp;rsquo;s home in California nearly three years ago. His family had searched for him for years, handing out fliers, scanning social media and desperately chasing down fruitless leads. &amp;ldquo;I never stopped looking for him. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t a day I wasn&amp;rsquo;t searching for him, in some form or fashion,&amp;rdquo; his mother says.</description></item><item><title>Driver, 59, dies after hitting 11-foot alligator on Florida roadway, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cfb48ff73e6d9cf8aa089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 23:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cfb48ff73e6d9cf8aa089/</guid><description>A man was killed after hitting an 11-foot alligator while driving in Florida early Thursday, authorities said.
Highlights John Hopkins, 59, was headed eastbound on Country Road 672, about two miles west of Country Road 39, in Lithia when he struck the alligator in the roadway at 12:30 a.m. The impact caused his car to veer off the road and flip into a ditch. A motorist passing through the area noticed the car in the ditch and called 911.</description></item><item><title>Florida man calls 911 to have meth tested for authenticity, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622dd135c6d79e5d88eaeb87/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622dd135c6d79e5d88eaeb87/</guid><description>A Spring Hill man is accused of calling 911 to have the methamphetamine he recently purchased from a man he met at an area bar tested because he believed it was really bath salts.
Highlights Thomas Eugene Colucci made the emergency call around 7 p.m. on Thursday. Colucci told deputies he wanted his methamphetamine tested because he did not want other people to purchase &amp;ldquo;fake&amp;rdquo; methamphetamine from the person who sold it to him.</description></item></channel></rss>