<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>amid on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/amid/</link><description>Recent content in amid on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 22:14:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/amid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. to welcome up to 100,000 Ukrainians fleeing war -sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ced3b4cc50e12b4ba60cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 22:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ced3b4cc50e12b4ba60cc/</guid><description>The United States plans to accept up to 100,000 Ukrainians fleeing Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion and is pledging $1 billion in new humanitarian aid, the Biden administration said on Thursday after a month of bombardments touched off Europe&amp;rsquo;s fastest-moving refugee crisis since the end of World War Two.
Highlights The United States plans to accept up to 100,000 Ukrainians fleeing Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion and is pledging $1 billion in new humanitarian aid. U.</description></item><item><title>Nations agree to release 60M barrels of oil amid Russian war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</guid><description>FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves — half of that from the United States — “to send a strong message to oil markets” that supplies won&amp;rsquo;t fall short after the Russian invasion of Ukraine .
Highlights The International Energy Agency’s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves.</description></item><item><title>National Guard fills in as nursing assistants amid healthcare worker shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62148c70730e0725cd0bff95/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 07:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62148c70730e0725cd0bff95/</guid><description>When Joenes Gellada joined the National Guard, he never imagined that would mean one day training as a nursing assistant.
Highlights The COVID-19 pandemic exacerbated an existing shortage of healthcare workers with about one in five quitting since February 2020. The next wave of 80 trainees will start work this week. The soldiers are only signed on until mid-March, though the healthcare workers hope they will be granted an extension.</description></item></channel></rss>