<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>amid on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/amid/</link><description>Recent content in amid on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 08:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/amid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amid boycotts, US scrambling to make Summit of the Americas a success</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62932aabe9234171a7654b98/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 08:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62932aabe9234171a7654b98/</guid><description>President Joe Biden is hosting the high-profile summit starting June 8 in Los Angeles.
Highlights The Summit of the Americas is slated to start June 8 in Los Angeles. Several leaders are threatening to boycott the summit because the U.S. has decided to not invite the governments of Venezuela and Nicaragua. The leaders of Bolivia, Antigua and Barbuda, and Guatemala have announced they will not attend. Mexico&amp;rsquo;s president Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has repeatedly said all of the region&amp;rsquo;s countries must be invited.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba lays off 40% of AliExpress Russia staff amid Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280e0192bfbb6f009e7a3ec/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280e0192bfbb6f009e7a3ec/</guid><description>AliExpress Russia, a joint venture launched in 2019 by Alibaba and Russian partners, operates domestic and cross-border transactions.
Highlights Alibaba Group Holding laid off about 40% of staff in Russian joint venture. China e-commerce giant could not be immediately reached for comment. Company depends on cross-border sales for more than three-quarters of its business. It has been slower to benefit from a pandemic-led ecommerce boom as supply chains adjust to new travel curbs.</description></item><item><title>Yuri Madvedev: Russian troops drive tank over own commander amid anger at high casualties</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fb5cec8981f2647a1505f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fb5cec8981f2647a1505f/</guid><description>Yuri Madvedev: Russian troops drive tank over own commander amid anger at high casualties
Highlights Colonel Yuri Medvedev is said to have suffered severe leg injuries in the attack. Almost half the troops in his brigade of 1,500 either died, or were wounded, in a series of clashes in the early weeks of the war. Chechen leader Ramzan Kadyrov appears to show the colonel being medically evacuated. He was airlifted to Belarus for emergency treatment and awarded a Russian military honour.</description></item><item><title>U.S. to welcome up to 100,000 Ukrainians fleeing war -sources</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ced3b4cc50e12b4ba60cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 22:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ced3b4cc50e12b4ba60cc/</guid><description>The United States plans to accept up to 100,000 Ukrainians fleeing Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion and is pledging $1 billion in new humanitarian aid, the Biden administration said on Thursday after a month of bombardments touched off Europe&amp;rsquo;s fastest-moving refugee crisis since the end of World War Two.
Highlights The United States plans to accept up to 100,000 Ukrainians fleeing Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion and is pledging $1 billion in new humanitarian aid. U.S. President Joe Biden is meeting with European leaders in Brussels to coordinate the Western response to the crisis.</description></item><item><title>Nations agree to release 60M barrels of oil amid Russian war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f60c70fe403765340d357/</guid><description>FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves — half of that from the United States — “to send a strong message to oil markets” that supplies won&amp;rsquo;t fall short after the Russian invasion of Ukraine .
Highlights The International Energy Agency’s 31 member countries agreed Tuesday to release 60 million barrels of oil from their strategic reserves.</description></item><item><title>National Guard fills in as nursing assistants amid healthcare worker shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62148c70730e0725cd0bff95/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 07:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62148c70730e0725cd0bff95/</guid><description>When Joenes Gellada joined the National Guard, he never imagined that would mean one day training as a nursing assistant.
Highlights The COVID-19 pandemic exacerbated an existing shortage of healthcare workers with about one in five quitting since February 2020. The next wave of 80 trainees will start work this week. The soldiers are only signed on until mid-March, though the healthcare workers hope they will be granted an extension. Wisconsin Dells Health Services, a long-term care facility for patients with dementia and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s, received aid from the National Guard in early February.</description></item></channel></rss>