<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>obtain on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/obtain/</link><description>Recent content in obtain on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:13:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/obtain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disney to help employees, their children obtain 'gender-affirming' procedures, per report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625212e372c06826bac574c6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 23:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625212e372c06826bac574c6/</guid><description>A Disney official said during a virtual conference on the company’s “Reimagine Tomorrow” initiative that they will be working with their benefits team to assist employees and their children with obtaining “gender-affirmation procedures. ” Such procedures typically include puberty blockers, breast removal, and genital reassignment surgery, according to Manhattan Institute senior fellow and a contributing editor at City Journal Christopher Rufo, who reported on the comments Thursday.
Highlights Disney to help employees and their children obtain &amp;lsquo;gender-affirming&amp;rsquo; procedures, per report.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi becomes 37th U.S. state to legalize medical marijuana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc28b32058cec7c9c20fb8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 19:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc28b32058cec7c9c20fb8/</guid><description>Mississippi joined 36 other U.S. states in legalizing marijuana for medical use on Wednesday, as the governor signed legislation permitting cannabis for treatment of severe, debilitating health conditions such as cancer, AIDS and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Highlights Mississippi joins 36 other U.S. states in legalizing marijuana for medical use on Wednesday. The governor signed legislation permitting cannabis for treatment of severe, debilitating health conditions such as cancer, AIDS and Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease. Governor Tate Reeves said the final version passed last week by the Republican-controlled legislature was designed to curb recreational marijuana use.</description></item></channel></rss>