<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>eastern on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/eastern/</link><description>Recent content in eastern on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/eastern/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian troops fought street by street with Kyiv's forces in battle for key Ukrainian city</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296301289ec1178364093fc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296301289ec1178364093fc/</guid><description>Russian troops pushed deeper into a key eastern Ukrainian city Monday, fighting street by street with Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s forces in a battle that has left Sievierodonetsk in ruins.
Highlights Russian troops advance into Sievierodonetsk, fighting street by street with Kyiv&amp;rsquo;s forces. Russian forces also shelled parts of Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northeast, and struggle continues for control of southern region. EU agrees to a partial oil embargo to pressure Moscow to end the war. Six civilians, including a French journalist, killed in fighting in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s second-largest city, also reported in Kharkarkarkiv.</description></item><item><title>Germany has 'betrayed' Ukraine, Kiev mayor Vitali Klitschko declares</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0e38eec650aed9f88b2c0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 06:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0e38eec650aed9f88b2c0/</guid><description>The ex-heavyweight champ today slated Germany for its &amp;lsquo;failure to provide assistance&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;betrayal of friends&amp;rsquo; as fears of a Russian invasion of Ukraine climb ever higher.
Summary Former world heavyweight boxing champion and Mayor of Kiev Vitali Klitschko has accused Germany of &amp;lsquo;betraying&amp;rsquo; Ukraine over its support of a Russian gas pipeline and refusal to export arms to his country. &amp;lsquo;There is huge disappointment in Ukraine that the federal government is sticking to Nord Stream 2 and that it does not want to supply defence weapons,&amp;rsquo; Klitschko wrote in Bild.</description></item><item><title>Biden Considers Sending Thousands of Troops, Including Warships and Aircraft, to Eastern Europe and Baltics Amid Fears of Russian Attack on Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee5c9b135932fdb2bf832c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee5c9b135932fdb2bf832c/</guid><description>The president is also considering deploying warships and aircraft to NATO allies, in what would be a major shift from its restrained stance on Ukraine.
Summary Thinning out staff at American embassies is a common precaution when conflicts or other crises arise that could put American diplomats in harm’s way. In his news conference last week, Mr. Biden said he had cautioned Mr. Putin that a Russian invasion of Ukraine would prompt Washington to send more troops to the region.</description></item></channel></rss>