<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>parents on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/parents/</link><description>Recent content in parents on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 12:20:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/parents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas Gov. orders state agencies to investigate gender-affirming care for trans kids as child abuse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621777f16bb4431580594e4c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 12:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621777f16bb4431580594e4c/</guid><description>Abbott wrote that doctors, nurses, teachers and anyone who comes into contact with a child has a requirement to report parents.
Highlights Texas Gov. Greg Abbott ordered state agencies to investigate gender-affirming care for transgender kids as child abuse. The order&amp;rsquo;s immediate impacts on transgender children&amp;rsquo;s access to treatments remain unclear. Experts and doctors fear an increase in mental health crises among transgender kids due to anti-trans bills introduced in state legislatures.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee parents, teachers push back against 'Maus' removal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207ea2c5593e891dc426a99/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207ea2c5593e891dc426a99/</guid><description>ATHENS, Tenn. (AP) — Growing up in rural eastern Tennessee, James Cockrum hadn&amp;rsquo;t given much thought to the possibility that one day he might find himself speaking about his Jewish heritage in front of a packed school board meeting.
Highlights The McMinn County School Board removed a Pulitzer Prize-winning graphic novel about the Holocaust from the district’s curriculum. The board voted unanimously to remove the book and directed teachers to find a suitable replacement.</description></item><item><title>Parents of worker killed in tornado that hit Amazon facility are suing the company for wrongful death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</guid><description>The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.
Summary (CNN) The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones lists $6.2 million in assets as judge adds new sanctions in Sandy Hook cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas — A Travis County judge imposed additional sanctions against Alex Jones on&amp;hellip;
Summary According to information Jones provided in December as part of the case, he listed more than $6.2 million in assets, including three properties worth about $2.35 million and about $458,000 in the bank. Free Speech Systems, according to Jones, has about $525,000 in the bank, inventory worth about $1.3 million and $2.1 million in fixed and intangible assets.</description></item></channel></rss>