<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>parents on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/parents/</link><description>Recent content in parents on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/parents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A father says he put 1,000 miles on his car to find specialty formula for premature infant daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a5242bb66ba91358270f6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a5242bb66ba91358270f6/</guid><description>Mac Jaehnert said he put 1,000 miles on his car in the last week looking for a specialty nutritional formula for daughter MacKenzie and other premature babies in his southeastern Washington state community.
Highlights Mac Jaehnert described empty store shelves in his search for Similac NeoSure in Richland, Washington state. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been a frustrating, heartbreaking, unnecessary challenge for a kid who has already overcome so much,&amp;rdquo; he said. The Biden administration has ordered the use of military aircraft to expedite the delivery of baby formula to the U.</description></item><item><title>Researchers Pinpoint Reason Infants Die From SIDS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cc251a8ff8a6061c42d90/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 08:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cc251a8ff8a6061c42d90/</guid><description>Researchers from The Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital Westmead in Sydney, Australia released a study that confirmed not only how infants die from sudden infant death syndrome, but why.
Highlights Sudden infant death syndrome accounts for 37% of sudden unexpected infant deaths a year in the U.S. Researchers from The Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital Westmead in Sydney, Australia released a study that confirmed not only how infants die from SIDS, but why. The study found activity of the enzyme butyryrylcholinesterase (BChE) was significantly lower in babies who died of SIDS compared to living infants and other non-SIDS infant deaths.</description></item><item><title>A 15-year-old boy died by suicide after relentless cyberbullying, and his parents say the Latin School could have done more to stop it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c3863494177b7445150f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c3863494177b7445150f7/</guid><description>A 15-year-old boy named Nate Bronstein was enrolled at one of the most prestigious private schools in Chicago and had a promising future — that is, until his parents say he became a victim of relentless cyberbullying by his classmates.
Highlights Nate Bronstein, 15, took his own life at the Latin School of Chicago. His parents say he was bullied by classmates at the prestigious private school. They say they were never told about the extent of the bullying.</description></item><item><title>Kindergartner brings tequila to school, shares with other students at snack time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e611e1fd41cb39e75d639/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 07:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e611e1fd41cb39e75d639/</guid><description>Some Michigan parents are upset because their kindergartners shared a bottle of tequila during snack time.
Highlights One of the students shared a bottle of Jose Cuervo mix with 10% alcohol content with her classmates. A teacher stopped it before a parent, Alexis Smith, got a call from her daughter&amp;rsquo;s school. School officials said they have addressed the situation, but can&amp;rsquo;t share the details because of student privacy laws. While school was closed Friday, Smith said her daughter will not be back on Monday for the first time since her first year of kindergarten was already cut short because of COVID and situations like this is making it worse,&amp;quot; she said.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook parents sue Alex Jones again, accuse him of trying to ‘shield assets’ in defamation cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625115a9ffdd0b673864fc31/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 05:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625115a9ffdd0b673864fc31/</guid><description>In the latest lawsuit, the families accuse the Infowars host of transferring&amp;hellip;
Highlights Four Sandy Hook parents who won two defamation suits against Alex Jones in Texas sue him. They say he &amp;ldquo;transferred millions of dollars from his fortune&amp;rdquo; to shield his assets from them. Jones, the host of the internet program “Infowars,” faces the first of three jury trials to award damages later this month in Texas. He called the 2012 shooting of 26 first-graders and educators at Sandy Hook Elementary School “staged” and “synthetic” Jones could not be reached for comment late Friday at his Texas-based “infowars” studio.</description></item><item><title>Florida house passes “don’t say gay” bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218e3a61831cfd71df2e441/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 14:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218e3a61831cfd71df2e441/</guid><description>Florida&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives passed a bill Thursday that would prohibit &amp;quot;classroom discussion about sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;quot; in the state’s
Highlights Florida&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives passed a bill that would prohibit &amp;ldquo;classroom discussion about sexual orientation or gender identity&amp;rdquo; in the state&amp;rsquo;s primary schools. The bill heads to the Republican-held Senate, where it is expected to pass. Critics have said the bill could open districts to lawsuits from parents who believe any conversation about LGBTQ people or issues to be inappropriate.</description></item><item><title>Texas Gov. orders state agencies to investigate gender-affirming care for trans kids as child abuse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621777f16bb4431580594e4c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 12:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621777f16bb4431580594e4c/</guid><description>Abbott wrote that doctors, nurses, teachers and anyone who comes into contact with a child has a requirement to report parents.
Highlights Texas Gov. Greg Abbott ordered state agencies to investigate gender-affirming care for transgender kids as child abuse. The order&amp;rsquo;s immediate impacts on transgender children&amp;rsquo;s access to treatments remain unclear. Experts and doctors fear an increase in mental health crises among transgender kids due to anti-trans bills introduced in state legislatures.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee parents, teachers push back against 'Maus' removal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207ea2c5593e891dc426a99/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207ea2c5593e891dc426a99/</guid><description>ATHENS, Tenn. (AP) — Growing up in rural eastern Tennessee, James Cockrum hadn&amp;rsquo;t given much thought to the possibility that one day he might find himself speaking about his Jewish heritage in front of a packed school board meeting.
Highlights The McMinn County School Board removed a Pulitzer Prize-winning graphic novel about the Holocaust from the district’s curriculum. The board voted unanimously to remove the book and directed teachers to find a suitable replacement.</description></item><item><title>Parents of worker killed in tornado that hit Amazon facility are suing the company for wrongful death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</guid><description>The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.
Summary (CNN) The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones lists $6.2 million in assets as judge adds new sanctions in Sandy Hook cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas — A Travis County judge imposed additional sanctions against Alex Jones on&amp;hellip;
Summary According to information Jones provided in December as part of the case, he listed more than $6.2 million in assets, including three properties worth about $2.35 million and about $458,000 in the bank. Free Speech Systems, according to Jones, has about $525,000 in the bank, inventory worth about $1.3 million and $2.1 million in fixed and intangible assets.</description></item></channel></rss>