<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>enforcement on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/enforcement/</link><description>Recent content in enforcement on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/enforcement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde police, school district no longer cooperating with Texas probe of shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296a0263f416bb99a7370bf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296a0263f416bb99a7370bf/</guid><description>Uvalde police and school district police are no longer cooperating with the Texas Dept. of Public Safety&amp;rsquo;s probe into the Robb Elementary School shooting, sources say.
Highlights Uv.C. police say they are no longer cooperating with the state&amp;rsquo;s response to the school shooting. The decision to stop cooperating occurred soon after the attack. The school was one of the worst school shootings in U.S. history, killing two people. The attack is believed to have been the result of a school shooting in Texas that took place at a school in May 2012, killing three people, including two children and two adults.</description></item><item><title>Police inaction moves to center of Uvalde shooting probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292819bd9f230e6013767f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292819bd9f230e6013767f9/</guid><description>The actions — or more notably, the inaction — of a school district police chief and other law enforcement officers have become the center of the investigation into this week&amp;rsquo;s shocking school shooting in Uvalde, Texas.
Highlights The actions of a school district police chief and other law enforcement officers have become the center of the investigation into this week’s shocking school shooting in Uvalde, Texas. The delay in confronting the shooter — who was inside the school for more than an hour — could lead to discipline, lawsuits and even criminal charges against police.</description></item><item><title>A woman was killed and nine officers injured in Phoenix shooting and barricade situation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091152376e25fb314a521a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 14:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62091152376e25fb314a521a/</guid><description>A woman was fatally shot and nine police officers were injured early Friday in a Phoenix suburb, police said.
Highlights Police identify the suspect as 36-year-old Morris Jones, 36, who was found dead inside the home. A woman was fatally shot and nine police officers were injured early Friday in a Phoenix suburb, police said. The officers were responding to a report of a shooting in Buckeye, west of Phoenix, Arizona.</description></item></channel></rss>