<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gunfire on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gunfire/</link><description>Recent content in gunfire on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:42:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gunfire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'They were shooting directly at the journalists': New evidence suggests Shireen Abu Akleh was killed in targeted attack by Israeli forces</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d7b5f2c39d56168a86f3f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:42:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d7b5f2c39d56168a86f3f/</guid><description>Witness testimony and videos obtained by CNN reveal how the veteran Palestinian-American journalist was shot dead in a targeted attack in the West Bank, while she was covering an Israeli raid with a group of other reporters.
Highlights Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh, 51, was killed by a bullet to the head at around 6:30 a.m. on May 11. She had been standing with a group of journalists near the entrance of Jenin refugee camp, where they had come to cover an Israeli raid.</description></item><item><title>'Dozens' killed by police overnight in Kazakhstan protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d74b150f2d85ecb558b660/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d74b150f2d85ecb558b660/</guid><description>Kazakhstan: Fresh gunfire heard in Almaty as deadly unrest continues
Summary Fresh gunfire was heard in Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s economic capital Almaty on Thursday afternoon, reported AFP, as violence continues to rock the Central Asian country. Azirbek said an &amp;ldquo;anti-terrorist&amp;rdquo; operation was underway in one of the districts of Almaty where the riots were most violent. Some of the cities in Kazakhstan where protests have been taking place. Following the government&amp;rsquo;s dismissal, Deputy prime minister Alikhan Smailov is to assume the role of interim prime minister until a new cabinet is formed.</description></item></channel></rss>