<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>meeting on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/meeting/</link><description>Recent content in meeting on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:43:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/meeting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Southern Baptists face push for public list of sex abusers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c29f47a1d2081514be8c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c29f47a1d2081514be8c1/</guid><description>A blistering report on the Southern Baptist Convention’s mishandling of sex abuse allegations is raising the prospect that the denomination, for the first time, will create a publicly accessible database of pastors and other church personnel known to be abusers.
Highlights A blistering report on the Southern Baptist Convention’s mishandling of sex abuse allegations, released on Sunday, May 23, 2022, is raising the prospect that the denomination, for the first time, will create a publicly accessible database of pastors and other church personnel known to be abusers.</description></item><item><title>Celebrity chef Mario Batali found not guilty of indecent assault, battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b8cb9af72e9ed3331e533/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 10:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b8cb9af72e9ed3331e533/</guid><description>Celebrity chef Mario Batali was being tried for a 2017 incident in Boston.
Highlights Mario Batali has been found not guilty of indecent assault and battery for a 2017 incident in Boston. Natalie Tene, 32, said Batali forcibly kissed her and grabbed her breasts, buttocks and groin after meeting him in a Boston bar in March 2017. Four women accused Batali of inappropriate touching in December 2017, which prompted him to leave the ABC daytime cooking show &amp;ldquo;The Chew&amp;rdquo; and remove himself from his restaurant business.</description></item><item><title>Actor Will Smith banned from attending Oscars for 10 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250a51e3c436a46c45715d2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 21:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250a51e3c436a46c45715d2/</guid><description>Will Smith will not be allowed to attend the Academy Awards for the next 10 years, as a result of his slapping comedian Chris Rock on stage during this year&amp;rsquo;s Oscar ceremony, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts &amp;amp; Sciences announced in a statement obtained by CNN.
Highlights Will Smith will not be allowed to attend the Academy Awards for the next 10 years. The decision was made during a Board of Governors meeting held earlier in the day in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>“Heartbroken” Will Smith Resigns From Academy Ahead Of Decision On His Future After Oscar Slap Of Chris Rock</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247b47cd1c46ee289a090ec/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 02:27:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6247b47cd1c46ee289a090ec/</guid><description>He will keep his King Richard award, but the former Fresh Prince will no longer be a member of the group that gave it to him on March 27
Highlights Will Smith has left the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences. Sources say he was told by the Academy that he likely could be expelled for a decade or more. Sources tell us that the traditional invite of the previous year’s Best Actor winner to hand out the Best Actress award had become a non-starter for Smith for the 95th Academy Awards.</description></item><item><title>Russian claims of bat bioweapon labs in Ukraine dismissed by US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236d3eb164a30f62ee6e9a5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 07:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236d3eb164a30f62ee6e9a5/</guid><description>Six countries with seats on the UN Security Council say Russia is spreading propaganda. They made the allegation at a meeting called at Russia&amp;rsquo;s request. Russia repeated its allegations that Ukraine has biological weapons program. The U.S. reiterated that Ukraine
Highlights Russia is using a UN Security Council meeting to spread its propaganda about its invasion of Ukraine, six Western members states say. The meeting was held at Russia&amp;rsquo;s request to discuss its allegations that Ukraine is developing biological weapons.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee parents, teachers push back against 'Maus' removal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207ea2c5593e891dc426a99/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207ea2c5593e891dc426a99/</guid><description>ATHENS, Tenn. (AP) — Growing up in rural eastern Tennessee, James Cockrum hadn&amp;rsquo;t given much thought to the possibility that one day he might find himself speaking about his Jewish heritage in front of a packed school board meeting.
Highlights The McMinn County School Board removed a Pulitzer Prize-winning graphic novel about the Holocaust from the district’s curriculum. The board voted unanimously to remove the book and directed teachers to find a suitable replacement.</description></item><item><title>Israeli PM announces plan to double the amount of settlers living in Golan Heights — a multimillion dollar project meant to further consolidate Israel's hold on the territory it captured from Syria more than five decades ago</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8d7eff9cd1fcdb7a049f2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8d7eff9cd1fcdb7a049f2/</guid><description>Israel says it plans to double the amount of settlers living in the Golan Heights and invest hundreds of millions of dollars developing the area
Summary Israel says it plans to double the amount of settlers living in the Golan Heights and invest hundreds of millions of dollars developing the areaMEVO HAMA, Golan Heights &amp;ndash; Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett said Sunday the country intends to double the amount of settlers living in the Israeli-controlled Golan Heights with a multimillion-dollar plan meant to further consolidate Israel’s hold on the territory it captured from Syria more than five decades ago.</description></item></channel></rss>