<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>indiana on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/indiana/</link><description>Recent content in indiana on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/indiana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Indiana firefighter killed when stranded motorist he stopped to help opened fire, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289e19826ed64cf3abb186d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289e19826ed64cf3abb186d/</guid><description>A firefighter was fatally shot and an officer was injured when a stranded motorist they stopped to help opened fire, Indiana State Police said.
Highlights Incident unfolded shortly before 9:30 p.m. Monday on SR 135 just south of Palmyra, Indiana. A firefighter was fatally shot and an officer was injured when a stranded motorist they stopped to help opened fire. The motorist, identified as Justin Moore of Owensboro, Kentucky, also died after he was shot by the officer.</description></item><item><title>Shooting along Indiana highway where SUV was stopped kills 2</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284f8df15f536294c60de2b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 13:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284f8df15f536294c60de2b/</guid><description>Authorities say two men were fatally shot after a police officer and two good Samaritans stopped along a southern Indiana highway to help a driver who was stopped in the roadway
Highlights Police officer and two good Samaritans stopped along a southern Indiana highway to help a driver who was stopped in the roadway. The shooting happened Monday night after an officer with the Palmyra Police Department stopped to assist the “apparent stranded motorist” Indiana State Police didn’t say what precipitated the gunfire or who fired the shots.</description></item></channel></rss>