<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>colorado on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/colorado/</link><description>Recent content in colorado on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 21:12:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/colorado/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colorado now guarantees the right to abortion in state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b5f2d7987f31f92c4ddf3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b5f2d7987f31f92c4ddf3/</guid><description>Abortion access is now guaranteed in Colorado law after Gov. Jared Polis signed a bill enshrining that right Monday.
Highlights The bill passed out of the Colorado legislature last month on a party-line vote. It would ban local and state governments from interfering in that care. It also would prevent a fertilized egg, embryo or fetus from having independent rights under state law. 15 other states and the District of Columbia have codified abortion into law with the “Reproductive Health Equity Act’s” The bill signed by Jared Polis, a Democrat of Pueblo, was passed by the House of Representatives last week.</description></item><item><title>Workers at nearly 80 Kroger's King Soopers go on strike as talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03e92708b1033bb719187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e03e92708b1033bb719187/</guid><description>More than 8,000 workers at nearly 80 King Soopers stores went on strike for better wages on Wednesday as negotiations stalled, but the stores stayed open as the Kroger Co-owned Colorado chain hired temporary staff and promoted online ordering.
Summary A union member raises a sign outside a Kroger&amp;rsquo;s King Soopers store during a protest as workers go on strike in Denver, Colorado, U.S., January 12, 2022. The striking workers are employed at King Soopers stores in the Denver metropolitan area, Boulder, Parker and Broomfield cities of Colorado, among others.</description></item><item><title>110 Year Sentence For Truck Driver Being Reconsidered</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2e927679e9dc44622769a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 09:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2e927679e9dc44622769a/</guid><description>Description Civil rights advocates are calling for Colorado Gov. Jared Polis to intervene after a truck driver was sentenced to 110 years for a fatal crash after his brakes failed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;As Colorado law required the imposition of the sentence in this case, the law also permits the Court to reconsider its sentence in an exceptional case involving unusual and extenuating circumstances,&amp;rdquo; the motion says. According to The Associated Press, police said that after his brakes failed, Mederos drove past a truck ramp before the crash.</description></item></channel></rss>