<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stake on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stake/</link><description>Recent content in stake on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk decides not to join Twitter board, says CEO Parag Agrawal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253ffcf02c6c04468c2468f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253ffcf02c6c04468c2468f/</guid><description>Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk abandoned his plans to join the board of Twitter after buying a 9% stake.
Highlights Tesla CEO Elon Musk has abandoned plans to join the board of Twitter. Musk proposed changes to Twitter&amp;rsquo;s subscription service, including price changes. Musk remains the largest shareholder of the social media company. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s stock briefly tumbled over 8% to less than $43 a share Monday, before recovering slightly. Musk&amp;rsquo;s appointment would have started on Saturday, &amp;ldquo;contingent on a background check and formal acceptance,&amp;rdquo; Twitter CEO says.</description></item><item><title>Brad Pitt sues Angelina Jolie over sale of stake in French vineyard Chateau Miraval to Russian oligarch</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620fc64afe72d78276696274/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620fc64afe72d78276696274/</guid><description>Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt bought the Chateau Miraval estate in the village of Correns, in southeastern France, in 2008, and were married there six years later. According to court documents, both agreed never to sell their respective interests without the other&amp;rsquo;s consent.
Highlights Angelina Jolie sold stake in Chateau Miraval SA company to a Russian oligarch, lawsuit claims. Jolie and Brad Pitt bought the estate in the village of Correns, in southeastern France, in 2008.</description></item></channel></rss>