<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>womens on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/womens/</link><description>Recent content in womens on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:09:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/womens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Soccer equalizes pay in milestone with women, men</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62856e8f3d71bf8b8b420f14/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62856e8f3d71bf8b8b420f14/</guid><description>The U.S. Soccer Federation reached milestone agreements to pay its men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams equally, making the American national governing body the first in the sport to promise both sexes matching money.
Highlights The U.S. Soccer Federation reached milestone agreements to pay its men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams equally. The federation on Wednesday announced separate collective bargaining agreements through December 2028 with the unions for both national teams. The deals grew partly out of a push by players on the more successful women’s team, including stars like Alex Morgan and Megan Rapinoe, who were at the forefront of the gender equity fight.</description></item><item><title>16 UPenn swimmers ask school not to challenge transgender policy that could block teammate Lia Thomas from competing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd79f118918c9a0ff5d84f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 19:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd79f118918c9a0ff5d84f/</guid><description>Letter on behalf of 16 members of UPenn swim team asks school to not challenge NCAA transgender athlete policy
Highlights Letter asks school and Ivy League not to challenge NCAA&amp;rsquo;s new transgender athlete participation policies. The letter was written by Olympic champion in swimming on behalf of 16 members of the Penn swim team. University of Pennsylvania swimmer Lia Thomas won the women&amp;rsquo;s 100- and 200-yard freestyle at Harvard last month.</description></item><item><title>Taliban forces have fired pepper spray at a group of women protesting in Afghanistan’s capital to demand rights to work and education. The Taliban authorities have blocked female public sector employees from returning to work, many secondary schools have still not reopened for girls.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e54c5923213e546a33c184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e54c5923213e546a33c184/</guid><description>One woman reportedly taken to hospital after protest calling for right to work and education is stopped
Summary Taliban forces have fired pepper spray at a group of women protesting in Afghanistan’s capital to demand rights to work and education. Since seizing control of the country by force in August, the Taliban authorities have imposed creeping restrictions on Afghans, especially on women. About 20 women gathered in front of Kabul University on Sunday, chanting “equality and justice” and carrying banners that read “women’s rights, human rights”, an AFP correspondent reported.</description></item><item><title>Taliban Reportedly Opens Fire On Women Protesting Against Restrictions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</guid><description>Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women.
Summary Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women. Taliban officials did not immediately respond to requests from RFE/RL for comment.</description></item></channel></rss>