<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>end on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/end/</link><description>Recent content in end on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/end/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protesters enter southern Alberta school, demand end of mask rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</guid><description>School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday where the gathering called for an end to mask mandates.
Highlights School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday. The gathering called for an end to mask mandates. The protest was quickly de-escalated by school officials and protestors were peacefully escorted out of the building.</description></item><item><title>Too little, too late: 500K nurses are leaving the bedside by the end of 2022</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd884ee25e4e8cf8ac6b62/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd884ee25e4e8cf8ac6b62/</guid><description>The pandemic accelerated an anticipated nurse shortage by 20 years. What does it mean for the future of healthcare?
Highlights Before the pandemic, Brittany Kennedy was working for a family and their child, picking up shifts as she — and they — needed. The added strain caused many healthcare workers to lose the passion they previously had for the job. The U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics projects that 500,000 seasoned nurses are expected to retire between now and the end of 2022, creating a shortage of 1.</description></item></channel></rss>