<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ran on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ran/</link><description>Recent content in ran on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:33:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ran/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Family of 6-year-old who ran marathon visited by child protective services, parents speak out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b3c812d118f06e767e883/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b3c812d118f06e767e883/</guid><description>The parents of a 6-year-old marathoner are speaking out after they say child protective services paid their family an unannounced visit.
Highlights Parents of 6-year-old marathoner say child protective services visited their home. Ben and Kami Crawford shared a photo of one of their children being interviewed by CPS. The Crawfords made headlines last week after they let their children, including their son Rainier, run the Flying Pig Marathon in Cincinnati.</description></item><item><title>Mutinous Russian troops ran over their own commander, say western officials | Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f81cdd6e3b5752fcfd59a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 21:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f81cdd6e3b5752fcfd59a/</guid><description>Officials describe reported incident during fighting in Ukraine as sign of ‘morale challenges’ faced by invading forces
Highlights Western officials say incident is sign of&amp;rsquo;morale challenges&amp;rsquo; faced by invading forces. Some reports said colonel of 37th separate guards motor rifle brigade was run over by tank. Western officials retracted claim in light of conflicting evidence on social media. They said key point was that he was a victim of a mutiny, not whether he had been killed or not.</description></item><item><title>Woman runs onto Phoenix tarmac to stop plane she missed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccda7dfd57757688763a88/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccda7dfd57757688763a88/</guid><description>Instead of waiting for the next flight, police say she ran through the glass doors separating the passenger area and the secure airfield.
Summary PHOENIX (Gray News) – A woman is facing charges after running onto the tarmac at Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport. According to the police report, the door to the jetway was already secured when Vickie Meyers, of St. Louis, Missouri, tried to catch a flight Sunday afternoon.</description></item></channel></rss>