<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>firing on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/firing/</link><description>Recent content in firing on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 13:20:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/firing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>South Carolina schedules first execution after preparing death chamber for firing squad</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625187e649397847c8ac41c8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 13:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625187e649397847c8ac41c8/</guid><description>Richard Bernard Moore, 57, could face a choice between the electric chair and the firing squad.
Highlights Richard Moore, 57, has spent more than two decades on death row after he was convicted of killing convenience store clerk James Mahoney in 2001. Moore could face a choice between the electric chair and the firing squad, two options available to death row prisoners after legislators altered the state&amp;rsquo;s capital punishment law last year.</description></item><item><title>Firing Upheld for LAPD Officers Playing Pokémon Go Instead of Responding to Robbery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddb7b9ebaf91cd881521ad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ddb7b9ebaf91cd881521ad/</guid><description>A California appellate court has ruled that two Los Angeles police officers were properly fired for playing Pokémon Go instead of responding to a robbery.
Summary A California appellate court has ruled that two Los Angeles police officers were properly fired for playing Pokémon Go instead of responding to a robbery. The court ruled on Friday that the LAPD was justified in firing Louis Lozano and Eric Mitchell for misconduct in 2017, the Sacramento Bee reported Monday.</description></item><item><title>Protesters call for firing of officer in fatal Florida dirt bike traffic stop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd3ced4379b3f93d073956/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd3ced4379b3f93d073956/</guid><description>Demonstrators outside the Boynton Beach, Florida police headquarters also demanded transparency about how Stanley David Jr. died.
Summary Demonstrators outside police headquarters in Boynton Beach, Florida, Tuesday night called for the firing of the officer involved in the death of a 13-year old boy on a dirt bike during an attempted traffic stop Sunday, CBS West Palm Beach affiliate WPEC-TV reports. Demonstrators outside Boynton Beach, Florida police headquarters on night of December 29, 2021 pressed for the firing of the officer in a fatal attempted dirt bike traffic stop two days before.</description></item></channel></rss>