<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>leaving on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/leaving/</link><description>Recent content in leaving on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/leaving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Companies leaving Russia cost 45% of national GDP - Investment Monitor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b41c19834196bf1dd8472/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b41c19834196bf1dd8472/</guid><description>Research from Yale shows that companies exiting Russia are taking with them revenues equal to almost half of Russia&amp;rsquo;s GDP.
Highlights Yale research shows that companies withdrawing from Russia are taking with them revenues equal to 45% of Russia&amp;rsquo;s GDP. Foreign direct investment (FDI) only accounted for 0.63% of the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP in 2020. Russian exports of oil and oil products are equivalent to only approximately 12% of GDP. Imports into Russia, on balance, are a net exporter, even as it is forced to sell oil and gas at highly discounted prices.</description></item><item><title>Rabbi who backed Abramovich's citizenship banned from leaving Portugal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e09decf41e0a6763748b6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 15:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e09decf41e0a6763748b6/</guid><description>A rabbi responsible for the certification that allowed Russian billionaire Roman Abramovich and others to obtain Portuguese citizenship is not allowed to leave the country and must present himself to authorities when required, Lusa news agency said on Saturday.
Highlights Roman Abramovich granted Portuguese citizenship last year based on a law offering naturalisation to descendants of Sephardic Jews. Abramovich has been sanctioned by British government over links to Putin and Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>