<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>food on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/food/</link><description>Recent content in food on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 14:13:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pussy Riot band member Maria Alyokhina escapes Russia dressed as food courier after criticising Putin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bc47ef7cd5a24c7fbe324/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 14:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bc47ef7cd5a24c7fbe324/</guid><description>In 2012, Pussy Riot came to the attention of Russian authorities after staging a protest inside a Moscow cathedral. Maria Alyokhina was arrested but she has continued to oppose the Russian president.
Highlights Maria Alyokhina was arrested in 2012 after staging a protest in a Moscow cathedral. The 33-year-old was sentenced to two years in prison for her activism. She has continued to speak out against the Russian president after she was placed under house arrest.</description></item><item><title>45-year-old Yan Zhiwen shot to death delivering food on scooter in Forest Hills, Queens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f6bce45bb712a5072ec94/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 05:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f6bce45bb712a5072ec94/</guid><description>It happened hours after Mayor Adams met with NYPD officials to address surging crime.
Highlights Yan Zhiwen, a food delivery worker, was shot and killed while on his scooter Saturday night in Queens. It happened near 108th Street and 67th Drive in Forest Hills at around 9:30 p.m. It happened hours after Mayor Eric Adams met with NYPD officials to address surging crime. Police are asking for help finding the shooter, who they say drove off in a light gray or tan Lexus.</description></item><item><title>States scale back food stamp benefits even as prices soar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b947da2706af828f6d48d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 04:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b947da2706af828f6d48d/</guid><description>DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Month by month, more of the roughly 40 million Americans who get help buying groceries through the federal food stamp program are seeing their benefits plunge even as the nation struggles with the biggest increase in food costs in decades.
Highlights The U.S. Department of Agriculture began offering the increased benefit in April 2020 in response to surging unemployment after the COVID-19 pandemic swept over the country.</description></item><item><title>Lebanon faces food crisis with ‘no wheat orders since Ukraine war began’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62362ab5d61fcd74f8a3a478/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 19:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62362ab5d61fcd74f8a3a478/</guid><description>As global prices soar, millers tell ‘The National’ that suppliers have no interest in selling to cash-strapped Lebanon
Highlights Wheat prices have soared since the start of the war in Ukraine, one of the world’s largest producers. Lebanon normally buys 96 per cent of its wheat from Russia and Ukraine. Importers are struggling to get dollars from a subsidy programme to buy wheat from new suppliers. The cost of the country&amp;rsquo;s largely imported food increased by 2,076 per cent between 2018 and 2021 due to the crash of the local currency.</description></item><item><title>Mariupol under siege: 'We are being completely cut off'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62212f29183110b42cb8a023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 21:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62212f29183110b42cb8a023/</guid><description>Residents of the south-eastern city tell the BBC they are being cut off by relentless Russian shelling.
Highlights Residents of south-eastern city say they are being cut off by relentless Russian shelling. &amp;ldquo;There is still some bread at the shop near us, but we don&amp;rsquo;t know when the food supply will end,&amp;rdquo; one resident says. &amp;ldquo;What will happen when we run out of our water? What will happen to my phone battery die?</description></item><item><title>World food prices jumped toward a record last month | Food News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd0937a0f9f1b4e05eae51/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd0937a0f9f1b4e05eae51/</guid><description>The United Nations’ index of prices rose 1.1 percent in January, pushed up by more pricey vegetable oils and dairy.
Highlights The United Nations’ index of prices rose 1.1% in January. The gauge is edging closer to 2011’s all-time high. The latest leg higher in the food index could further stretch household budgets. The poorest “segments in the population will feel the pinch the most,” a UN official says. Sugar marked the only commodity that eased during the month, while costs for meat, grain, dairy and vegetable oils rose.</description></item><item><title>Food disruptions feared in UK as new Brexit rules kick in</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d282ebd7a102723b0588f2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d282ebd7a102723b0588f2/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — New post-Brexit custom rules for goods arriving from the European Union to Britain are taking effect on Saturday, and a leading food industry body has warned that the new border controls could lead to food shortages.
Summary Beginning on Jan. 1, importers must make a full customs declaration on goods entering the U.K. from the EU or other countries. Beginning on Jan. 1, importers must make a full customs declaration on goods entering the U.</description></item><item><title>One year on, most voters say Brexit has gone badly. An Opinium poll also found that 42% of people who voted Leave in 2016 had a negative view of how it had turned out.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c859611b96cf1df48262a6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c859611b96cf1df48262a6/</guid><description>An Opinium poll on the anniversary of Britain quitting the EU also found that 42% of people who voted Leave in 2016 had a negative view of how it had turned out
Summary More than six out of 10 voters believe Brexit has either gone badly or worse than they expected – a year after the UK left the EU, according to an anniversary poll for the Observer. 26% of Leave supporters said it had gone worse than they expected, while 16% of those who voted for Brexit said they had expected it to go badly and had been proved right.</description></item></channel></rss>