<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>member on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/member/</link><description>Recent content in member on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:09:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Armed female bystander kills man firing at party in West Virginia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62938ca685f11d9d4d61462b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 15:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62938ca685f11d9d4d61462b/</guid><description>A woman at a birthday party drew her pistol and left the gunman with multiple wounds, police say.
Highlights A woman at a birthday party drew her pistol and left the gunman with multiple wounds, police say. &amp;ldquo;Instead of running from the threat she engaged with the threat and saved several lives,&amp;rdquo; police say. &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s just a member of the community who was carrying her weapon lawfully,&amp;rdquo; he said. &amp;ldquo;And instead of running&amp;hellip; she engaged&amp;hellip; in the threat,&amp;rdquo; he added.</description></item><item><title>'Can we just go set Marsha Blackburn on fire:' Nashville school board member caught on hot mic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624627651d7da3c72da0d937/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 22:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624627651d7da3c72da0d937/</guid><description>The comment about Marsha Blackburn from Sharon Gentry, some say, is just the latest example of extreme comments from Nashville school board members.
Highlights Nashville school board member Sharon Gentry was caught on hot mic criticizing Sen. Marsha Blackburn. Gentry criticized Blackburn for questioning Supreme Court nominee Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson. Other members of the heavily Democratic Nashville board didn&amp;rsquo;t appear to question Gentry&amp;rsquo;s comments. Board has a long history of dysfunction and condemnation from the public.</description></item></channel></rss>