<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>workplace on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/workplace/</link><description>Recent content in workplace on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 15:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/workplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man told employer not to celebrate his birthday. He was awarded $450,000 after unwanted party.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d8042d8e005b421df1328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d8042d8e005b421df1328/</guid><description>A Kentucky man with an anxiety disorder asked his employer not to celebrate his birthday because it would trigger a panic attack.
Highlights Kevin Berling asked his employer not to celebrate his birthday because it would trigger a panic attack. When the company, Gravity Diagnostics, ignored his request and had a surprise lunchtime celebration for him on Aug. 7, 2019, he got upset. A jury awarded him $450,000 on March 31, a jury found that Berling suffered an &amp;ldquo;adverse employment action&amp;rdquo; because of his anxiety disability.</description></item><item><title>Federal vaccine mandate for employers with 100 or more staff now in effect</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd474638760bd14c6b703a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd474638760bd14c6b703a/</guid><description>Should the employee choose to not get the shot, they must undergo weekly testing and wear a mask at the place of employment.
Summary The Biden Administrations new federal vaccine mandate for employers will 100 or more employees goes into effect on Monday. The 100 or more employee tally is for each entire company, no matter how many employees are at individual worksites. Fully remote workers and staff members who work outside exclusively should be included in the 100 or more employee tally, however, they are not subject to the federal vaccine mandate requirements.</description></item></channel></rss>