<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>soviet on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soviet/</link><description>Recent content in soviet on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 16:21:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soviet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian ambassador to Poland hit with red paint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62793f5e21b3920489fb9c32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 16:21:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62793f5e21b3920489fb9c32/</guid><description>Protesters have thrown red paint on the Russian ambassador to Poland as he arrived at a cemetery in Warsaw to pay respects to Red Army soldiers who died during World War II
Highlights Protesters throw red paint on Russian ambassador to Poland as he arrives at a cemetery in Warsaw to pay respects to Red Army soldiers who died during World War II. Ambassador Sergey Andreev arrived at the Soviet soldiers&amp;rsquo; cemetery to lay flowers on Victory Day.</description></item><item><title>Russia warns Czechia against supplying Ukraine with weapons of Soviet origin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3158957c06c6ce758141/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 21:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3158957c06c6ce758141/</guid><description>As the Czech Republic continues to arm Ukraine, Russia has told the country that it cannot transfer Soviet-made weapons without its consent.
Highlights Russia has told the Czech Republic that it cannot transfer Soviet-made weapons without its consent. Czech Republic continues to arm Ukraine. Russia has also said it will be unable to prevent this sabotage, Czech Republic says. &amp;ldquo;We interpret this as a clear threat that Russia itself was and is preparing sabotage,&amp;rdquo; Czech minister says.</description></item><item><title>‘Red Dawn’ hits Ukraine after destroyed Russian armor gets tagged with ‘Wolverines’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251a3d1b9537cb907086159/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 15:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251a3d1b9537cb907086159/</guid><description>A recent photo from Ukraine shows an abandoned Russian BMP-2 graffitied with &amp;quot;Wolverines&amp;quot; in an apparent reference to the movie &amp;quot;Red Dawn.&amp;quot;
Highlights A photo shows an abandoned Russian BMP-2 with the word “Wolverines” scrawled on the side in white spray paint in an apparent homage to the 1984 Cold War-era action flick “Red Dawn’s” A Ukrainian oil and gas company head snapped a photo of the vehicle. The photo was shared to Twitter on Thursday in response to a tweet by NPR&amp;rsquo;s White House correspondent, Scott Detrow, who wrote that “We were driving too fast to get a clear picture – but we just drove past a destroyed Russian tank with WOLVERINES spraypainted across it.</description></item></channel></rss>