<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>passenger on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/passenger/</link><description>Recent content in passenger on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/passenger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An American Airlines flight was diverted to Kansas City due to an 'unruly passenger'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209f34b2022a813384b0d08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 06:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209f34b2022a813384b0d08/</guid><description>An American Airlines flight was diverted to Kansas City International Airport in Missouri on Sunday afternoon because of &amp;quot;an unruly passenger,&amp;quot; the airline said in a statement.
Highlights Flight 1775 with service from Los Angeles (LAX) to Washington, D.C. diverted to Kansas City (MCI) due to an unruly passenger. The FBI confirmed the incident in a statement to CNN, adding the individual in question had been taken into custody. The flight landed safely at MCI at 2:28 p.</description></item><item><title>Delta CEO repeats call for a 'no-fly' list for unruly passengers in letter to US attorney general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff2d6cdd06d48a7de1254e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:08:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff2d6cdd06d48a7de1254e/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian sent a letter to US Attorney General Merrick Garland on Friday reiterating his call for the Justice Department to prosecute unruly passengers and place them on a &amp;quot;no-fly&amp;quot; list.
Highlights Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian reiterates his call for the Justice Department to prosecute unruly passengers and place them on a &amp;ldquo;no-fly&amp;rdquo; list. Last year was the worst on record for unruly airplane passenger behavior in the United States, according to FAA data.</description></item><item><title>American Airlines flight to London returns to Miami after passenger refuses to wear mask</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9bf5eb4864e4bbe4a08b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 20:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9bf5eb4864e4bbe4a08b1/</guid><description>American Airlines Flight 38 was heading to London with 129 passengers on board when it had to turn back.
Summary An American Airlines flight from Miami had to turn around on Wednesday night after a disruptive passenger refused to wear a mask, the airline said. American Airlines Flight 38 was heading to London with 129 passengers on board when it had to turn back. &amp;ldquo;Everyone was shocked,&amp;rdquo; one passenger told WFOR-TV.</description></item></channel></rss>