<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sheriffs on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sheriffs/</link><description>Recent content in sheriffs on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:24:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sheriffs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Andy Dick Arrested On Suspicion Of Sexual Battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d4296538f1b17bd656504/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:24:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d4296538f1b17bd656504/</guid><description>Comedian Andy Dick was arrested Wednesday at a campground in Orange County, California, on suspicion of sexual battery, authorities said.
Highlights Comedian Andy Dick was arrested Wednesday at a campground in Orange County, California, on suspicion of sexual battery. The Orange County Sheriff’s Department responded to O’Neill Regional Park around 9 a.m. after the adult male victim called authorities about a possible sexual assault. It was not immediately clear whether Dick had an attorney who could speak on his behalf in the incident.</description></item><item><title>Alabama woman killed by pack of dogs; owner charged with manslaughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f140b41f5665ecd718a0b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 23:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f140b41f5665ecd718a0b/</guid><description>An employee of the Alabama Department of Public Health was killed by a pack of dogs in the northwestern part of the state last week as she was responding to a
Highlights Jacqueline Summer Beard was pronounced dead Friday by the Franklin County coroner after local residents called the police to report a suspicious vehicle. Officers found the car with Beard&amp;rsquo;s body inside it in a rural area outside Red Bay, near the Mississippi line.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles County is investigating sheriff's department's 'deputy gangs'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e13e3fb821f84cdff1470/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e13e3fb821f84cdff1470/</guid><description>The Los Angeles County Civilian Oversight Commission (COC) is launching an investigation into &amp;quot;deputy gangs&amp;quot; or groups participating in gang-like activity at the Los Angeles County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department, the Commission said Thursday.
Highlights The Commission was created by the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors to &amp;ldquo;improve public transparency and accountability&amp;rdquo; in the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department. The Commission will look at how many gangs are currently in operation and their effects on the community.</description></item><item><title>At least 34 people rescued after they became stranded on a floating chunk of ice in Green Bay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc3c105f2b12ea8f8a868d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc3c105f2b12ea8f8a868d/</guid><description>At least 34 people were rescued on Saturday after being stranded on a large chunk of floating ice off the shore of Point Comfort on Green Bay, according to the Brown County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office in Wisconsin.
Summary (CNN) At least 34 people were rescued on Saturday after being stranded on a large chunk of floating ice off the shore of Point Comfort on Green Bay, according to the Brown County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office in Wisconsin.</description></item></channel></rss>