<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>federation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/federation/</link><description>Recent content in federation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:09:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/federation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Soccer equalizes pay in milestone with women, men</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62856e8f3d71bf8b8b420f14/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 22:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62856e8f3d71bf8b8b420f14/</guid><description>The U.S. Soccer Federation reached milestone agreements to pay its men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams equally, making the American national governing body the first in the sport to promise both sexes matching money.
Highlights The U.S. Soccer Federation reached milestone agreements to pay its men&amp;rsquo;s and women&amp;rsquo;s teams equally. The federation on Wednesday announced separate collective bargaining agreements through December 2028 with the unions for both national teams. The deals grew partly out of a push by players on the more successful women’s team, including stars like Alex Morgan and Megan Rapinoe, who were at the forefront of the gender equity fight.</description></item><item><title>No amount of alcohol is good for the heart, new report says, but critics disagree on science</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee95261e32d5dbcf7bdef2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 12:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee95261e32d5dbcf7bdef2/</guid><description>No amount of alcohol is good for the heart according to a new policy report by the World Health Federation, fueling an ongoing debate on what role drinking might play in heart heatlh.
Summary (CNN) In a bold move, the World Heart Federation released a policy brief Thursday saying that no amount of alcohol is good for the heart. &amp;ldquo;At the World Heart Federation, we decided that it was imperative that we speak up about alcohol and the damages to health, as well as the social and economic harms, because there is an impression in the population in general, and even among health care professionals, that it is good for the heart,&amp;rdquo; said Beatriz Champagne, chair of the advocacy committee that produced the report.</description></item></channel></rss>