<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>source on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/source/</link><description>Recent content in source on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 07:14:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/source/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>World's top oil trader will stop buying Russian crude</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62591b1ce54fe8adfc3b47df/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 07:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62591b1ce54fe8adfc3b47df/</guid><description>Vitol Group, the world&amp;rsquo;s top independent oil merchant, will stop trading Russian crude oil and products by the end of the year, a source with knowledge of the situation told CNN.
Highlights Vitol Group will stop trading Russian crude oil and products by the end of the year. The Dutch energy and commodities trading company will also not enter into any new Russian crude and product transactions. The U.S., UK, Canada and Australia have all announced bans on Russian oil since Russia invaded Ukraine in February.</description></item><item><title>US reveals claims of Russian 'kill list' if Moscow occupies Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214b78b133666247b1f02ff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 10:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214b78b133666247b1f02ff/</guid><description>The US says it has &amp;quot;credible information&amp;quot; that Russia is creating lists of Ukrainians to be killed.
Highlights The letter is the latest salvo in Washington&amp;rsquo;s attempts to expose what it says are Moscow&amp;rsquo;s plans for Ukraine. It is not clear how far any such plans might have progressed, or what scenarios would lead to them being put into action. The purpose of exposing such information is partly to act as a deterrent to Russian behaviour - and some officials acknowledge that they cannot be totally confident what will unfold.</description></item></channel></rss>