<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attorney on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attorney/</link><description>Recent content in attorney on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 17:15:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attorney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Philadelphia toddler dies after being shot at drugs deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626585a0ae6503a079253902/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626585a0ae6503a079253902/</guid><description>The district attorney said there is reason to believe the cause of death was due to the original injuries from the shooting in 2019.
Highlights Yaseem Jenkins, who was just 11 months at the time of the shooting, died on Tuesday, according to a statement by his family. The district attorney said they are awaiting an inquest report to establish the cause of death, but said they have reason to believe the three-year-old died due to his original injuries from the incident three years ago.</description></item><item><title>Former cop who stormed Capitol guilty on all six counts in second Jan. 6 jury trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254cdb066d8fa4371484ca9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254cdb066d8fa4371484ca9/</guid><description>Thomas Robertson, a former police officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia, was found guilty on all six charges on Monday.
Highlights Thomas Robertson was an officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia, when he entered the Capitol on Jan. He faced six charges, including obstruction of an official proceeding, civil disorder and entering a restricted building or grounds while carrying a deadly or dangerous weapon. Robertson was the second defendant to take his case to a jury, after Guy Reffitt was convicted on all counts last month.</description></item><item><title>US disrupts global ‘botnet’ controlled by Russian military intelligence, DoJ says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ef163a3c291e3a4badefb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 14:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ef163a3c291e3a4badefb/</guid><description>Attorney general also announces charges against Russian oligarch Konstantin Malofeyev for sanctions violations
Highlights US has disrupted a global “botnet’ controlled by Russia’s military intelligence agency. Attorney General Merrick Garland also announced charges against Russian oligarch Konstantin Malofeyev for sanctions violations. TV producer John Hanick, 71, a US citizen charged with violations of sanctions and false statements. The indictment is the first of a Russian oligarchs in the US since the Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>This Texas mom says she's moving her family to California to protect her transgender daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bcc9d691bb37a9156666c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 19:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bcc9d691bb37a9156666c/</guid><description>A Texas mom is doing whatever it takes to keep her transgender child safe &amp;ndash; even if that requires picking up their lives, leaving family and friends behind and moving hundreds of miles west.
Highlights Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton declared that gender-affirming surgical procedures in children and prescribing drugs that affect puberty are to be considered &amp;ldquo;child abuse&amp;rdquo; Five Texas District Attorneys issued a joint statement on Thursday calling the directives from the governor and attorney general cruel, life-threatening and un-American.</description></item><item><title>3 officers found guilty on federal charges in George Floyd’s killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218393e9285cd3dae3fde40/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 02:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218393e9285cd3dae3fde40/</guid><description>A federal jury has reached a verdict in the trial of three former Minneapolis police officers charged with violating the civil rights of George Floyd.
Highlights Three Minneapolis police officers convicted of violating civil rights of George Floyd. Floyd&amp;rsquo;s brother: &amp;ldquo;It can never be justice because I can never get George back&amp;rdquo; Former officers J. Alexander Kueng, Thomas Lane and Tou Thao found guilty of depriving Floyd of his civil rights.</description></item><item><title>Overtime fraud charges hit dozens of California officers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f9c013a04401641d91867/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 13:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620f9c013a04401641d91867/</guid><description>Dozens of current and former Highway Patrol officers have been charged with racking up more than $226,000 in phony hours in an overtime fraud scheme, California’s attorney general said.
Highlights The California Highway Patrol has been accused of overcharging more than $200,000. The officers are accused of using illegal funds to pay for their overtime. The funds were used to pay off large amounts of overtime, officials said in the past.</description></item><item><title>Delta CEO repeats call for a 'no-fly' list for unruly passengers in letter to US attorney general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff2d6cdd06d48a7de1254e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:08:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff2d6cdd06d48a7de1254e/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian sent a letter to US Attorney General Merrick Garland on Friday reiterating his call for the Justice Department to prosecute unruly passengers and place them on a &amp;quot;no-fly&amp;quot; list.
Highlights Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian reiterates his call for the Justice Department to prosecute unruly passengers and place them on a &amp;ldquo;no-fly&amp;rdquo; list. Last year was the worst on record for unruly airplane passenger behavior in the United States, according to FAA data.</description></item><item><title>Gov. Newsom signs executive order outlawing price gouging of COVID-19 at-home test kits in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc4a1070867ba32c1e3bbe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc4a1070867ba32c1e3bbe/</guid><description>Gov. Gavin Newsom signed an executive order aimed at preventing price gouging of at-home COVID-19 test kits.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos COVID-19 testing continued at many Los Angeles Unified School District campuses on Sunday, Jan. 9, 2022, as students, teachers and staff prepared to return from winter break. SACRAMENTO, Calif. (KABC) &amp;ndash; Gov. Gavin Newsom has signed an executive order aimed at preventing price gouging of at-home COVID-19 test kits.</description></item></channel></rss>