<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>know on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/know/</link><description>Recent content in know on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 12:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/know/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Brittney Griner home from Russia is WNBA's 'top priority,' commissioner says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256c04184937dc807fa25cb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256c04184937dc807fa25cb/</guid><description>In consecutive statements this week, the WNBA voiced support for the Houston all-star who&amp;hellip;
Highlights Brittney Griner&amp;rsquo;s detainment in Russia remains a &amp;ldquo;top priority&amp;rdquo; for the WNBA, Commissioner Cathy Engelbert said. Nneka Ogwumike, president of the Los Angeles Sparks team, seemed to confirm this during a Tuesday interview with ABC News&amp;rsquo; Robin Roberts on &amp;ldquo;Good Morning America&amp;rdquo; The two-time Olympic gold medalist has been detained in Russia since mid-February after authorities accused her of carrying vape cartridges containing cannabis oil in her luggage at a Moscow airport.</description></item><item><title>Seattle Kraken fan called a hero after noticing Canucks staffer's cancerous mole during game</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d169ba61c6e97258bcc758/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 09:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d169ba61c6e97258bcc758/</guid><description>A Seattle Kraken fan is being praised as a hero after helping the assistant equipment manager of the Vancouver Canucks identify a cancerous mole on his neck in the middle of a game.
Summary A Seattle Kraken fan is being praised as a hero — and awarded $10,000 — after helping the assistant equipment manager of the Vancouver Canucks identify a cancerous mole on his neck in the middle of a game.</description></item></channel></rss>