<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>social on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/social/</link><description>Recent content in social on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 13:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Millions in Bitcoin pouring into Ukraine from donors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b79632c14cf4697ef1bad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b79632c14cf4697ef1bad/</guid><description>Thousands of anonymous donations are being made to the Ukrainian military in Bitcoin.
Highlights Thousands of anonymous donations are being made to the Ukrainian military in Bitcoin. At least one social media post was found to copy a legitimate tweet from an NGO, but with the author swapping the Bitcoin address, presumably for one of their own. The author of the post is believed to have swapped Bitcoin address for that of his own, according to Elliptic.</description></item><item><title>False trampling death rumours a sign of misinformation campaign, say police | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212317433487e095ed1496c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212317433487e095ed1496c/</guid><description>Officers on horseback rode down Rideau Street in Ottawa late Friday afternoon, leading to two people being knocked over — and a persistent yet false social media rumour that one woman had been trampled.
Highlights Mounted officers on horseback rode down Rideau Street in Ottawa late Friday afternoon. Two people were knocked over during the operation, leading to a persistent yet false rumour that one woman had been trampled. Fox News contributor with 1.</description></item><item><title>Israel to open first LGBT shelter for Arab youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201dfc784df80ceb5249e0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201dfc784df80ceb5249e0d/</guid><description>Lawmaker hopes move will ‘break taboos’ * Two centers for LGBT Arab Israeli adults to open in Haifa
Highlights Israel is set to open its first shelter designated for LGBT Arab Israeli youth, in a move hailed as “historic” by one of the lawmakers who led the initiative. The new shelter will be established in an area with a large Arab population, though the exact location has not yet been decided.</description></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather sued by investors over alleged crypto scam</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df87d1dc5106ca49ff2b0b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df87d1dc5106ca49ff2b0b/</guid><description>A class action lawsuit accuses Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather of artificially inflating the price of the cryptocurrency EthereumMax.
Summary Kim Kardashian arrives for the 2018 Met Gala on May 7, 2018, at the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York. Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather are being sued over allegations they misled investors when promoting a little-known cryptocurrency called EthereumMax to their millions of social media followers. Kardashian caused a stir last year when she made an Instagram post promoting the EthereumMax token.</description></item><item><title>Passengers who filmed themselves partying maskless aboard a chartered Sunwing Airlines flight from Montreal to Mexico last week have become pariahs and now face being stranded</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6afb8a9bf544e7bd4c282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6afb8a9bf544e7bd4c282/</guid><description>Passengers who filmed themselves partying maskless aboard a chartered Sunwing Airlines flight from Montreal to Mexico last week have become pariahs and now face being stranded after two more airlines announced Wednesday they will not fly them home to Canada.
Summary She said she tested positive for COVID-19 Wednesday and is now in isolation in Tulum, south of Cancun. In one video, a large bottle of vodka appears to be passed among passengers, and later a woman appears to be smoking an electronic cigarette.</description></item></channel></rss>