<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>social on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/social/</link><description>Recent content in social on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 13:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laws restricting lessons on racism make it hard for teachers to discuss the massacre in Buffalo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288e730b5b9dd23d19a5a5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288e730b5b9dd23d19a5a5c/</guid><description>After a gunman killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, teachers are grappling with anti-critical race theory laws that limit what they can discuss with students.
Highlights Teachers fear for their jobs because of state laws limiting how they can discuss racism. Educators took to social media and wrote essays debating how to talk about the Buffalo shooting. Experts describe social studies and history courses as a potential antidote to extremist ideologies that appear to have motivated the suspect in Buffalo, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Two key tech execs quit Truth Social after troubled app launch</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c24018cf52f42faad182e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 11:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c24018cf52f42faad182e/</guid><description>The two Southern tech entrepreneurs had the two qualities that Donald Trump’s startup needed: tech-industry expertise and a worldview aligned with the former president.
Highlights Truth Social co-founders Josh Adams and Billy Boozer quit their senior posts at a critical juncture for the company’s smartphone-app release plans, according to two sources familiar with the venture. The departures followed the troubled launch of the company&amp;rsquo;s iPhone app on Feb. Truth Social is part of a growing sector of tech firms catering to conservatives and marketing themselves as free-speech champions.</description></item><item><title>Facebook fails to label 80% of posts promoting bioweapons conspiracy theory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245ab8f36c6bcab5d73fcd7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 13:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245ab8f36c6bcab5d73fcd7/</guid><description>A study found that external articles shared on the bioweapons myth were not labeled as ‘false information’ or ‘missing context’
Highlights Facebook failed to label 80% of posts promoting a conspiracy theory that the US is funding the use of bioweapons in Ukraine. Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH) studied a sample of posts from between 24 February and 14 March. The White House has condemned the myth, saying it may have been manufactured by Moscow to justify a possible use of chemical weapons against Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Mayor orders New York’s homeless camps dismantled ‘within two weeks’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fe51114fbb0e5908645e6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 04:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623fe51114fbb0e5908645e6/</guid><description>Eric Adams says officials will place people in ‘healthy living conditions with wraparound services’ as homelessness debate swirls
Highlights Eric Adams says homeless people will be placed in &amp;lsquo;healthy living conditions&amp;rsquo; with wraparound services, he says. The number of people living in parks and on the streets is estimated at around 1,100. The issue of homelessness in New York has arisen amid a crime spike in the city and a series of high-profile violent attacks, though advocates point out that the city – and its homeless population – has been caught in a crisis over inadequate mental health services for many years.</description></item><item><title>Some Russians are breaking through Putin’s digital iron curtain — leading to fights with friends and family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62369bde183a44924df36dbd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62369bde183a44924df36dbd/</guid><description>Putin&amp;rsquo;s digital iron curtain has fallen heavily on Russia, but many tech-savvy citizens can access outside news and social media easily. It&amp;rsquo;s leading to conflict over what&amp;rsquo;s true and what&amp;rsquo;s not between friends and family.
Highlights Some Russians are trying to pierce Russian President Vladimir Putin’s propaganda bubble, at times leaving them at odds with their own families, friends and co-workers. The war in Ukraine is only deepening the divide between young, tech-savvy people and an older generation who gets their news mostly from TV.</description></item><item><title>Five people killed in Russian hit on Kyiv TV tower – video | World news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f7b32a27f2a44bc06a5d9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f7b32a27f2a44bc06a5d9/</guid><description>Five people have been killed and several wounded in a Russian attack on a TV tower in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s capital, Kyiv, according to reports
Highlights Two explosions heard in Borshchahivka and Dorohozhychi areas, reports say. Several channels were knocked off air, knocking several channels off air. The incident was first reported on social media by the Ukrainian interior ministry adviser, Anton Herashchenko, moments after Russia warned Kyiv residents to evacuate military and intelligence infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Millions in Bitcoin pouring into Ukraine from donors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b79632c14cf4697ef1bad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 13:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b79632c14cf4697ef1bad/</guid><description>Thousands of anonymous donations are being made to the Ukrainian military in Bitcoin.
Highlights Thousands of anonymous donations are being made to the Ukrainian military in Bitcoin. At least one social media post was found to copy a legitimate tweet from an NGO, but with the author swapping the Bitcoin address, presumably for one of their own. The author of the post is believed to have swapped Bitcoin address for that of his own, according to Elliptic.</description></item><item><title>False trampling death rumours a sign of misinformation campaign, say police | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212317433487e095ed1496c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212317433487e095ed1496c/</guid><description>Officers on horseback rode down Rideau Street in Ottawa late Friday afternoon, leading to two people being knocked over — and a persistent yet false social media rumour that one woman had been trampled.
Highlights Mounted officers on horseback rode down Rideau Street in Ottawa late Friday afternoon. Two people were knocked over during the operation, leading to a persistent yet false rumour that one woman had been trampled. Fox News contributor with 1.</description></item><item><title>Israel to open first LGBT shelter for Arab youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201dfc784df80ceb5249e0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201dfc784df80ceb5249e0d/</guid><description>Lawmaker hopes move will ‘break taboos’ * Two centers for LGBT Arab Israeli adults to open in Haifa
Highlights Israel is set to open its first shelter designated for LGBT Arab Israeli youth, in a move hailed as “historic” by one of the lawmakers who led the initiative. The new shelter will be established in an area with a large Arab population, though the exact location has not yet been decided.</description></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather sued by investors over alleged crypto scam</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df87d1dc5106ca49ff2b0b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df87d1dc5106ca49ff2b0b/</guid><description>A class action lawsuit accuses Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather of artificially inflating the price of the cryptocurrency EthereumMax.
Summary Kim Kardashian arrives for the 2018 Met Gala on May 7, 2018, at the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York. Kim Kardashian and Floyd Mayweather are being sued over allegations they misled investors when promoting a little-known cryptocurrency called EthereumMax to their millions of social media followers. Kardashian caused a stir last year when she made an Instagram post promoting the EthereumMax token.</description></item><item><title>Passengers who filmed themselves partying maskless aboard a chartered Sunwing Airlines flight from Montreal to Mexico last week have become pariahs and now face being stranded</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6afb8a9bf544e7bd4c282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6afb8a9bf544e7bd4c282/</guid><description>Passengers who filmed themselves partying maskless aboard a chartered Sunwing Airlines flight from Montreal to Mexico last week have become pariahs and now face being stranded after two more airlines announced Wednesday they will not fly them home to Canada.
Summary She said she tested positive for COVID-19 Wednesday and is now in isolation in Tulum, south of Cancun. In one video, a large bottle of vodka appears to be passed among passengers, and later a woman appears to be smoking an electronic cigarette.</description></item></channel></rss>