<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>questions on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/questions/</link><description>Recent content in questions on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:30:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/questions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justice Dept. to review response to Texas school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294482e2f8a584828810c6d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294482e2f8a584828810c6d/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — The Justice Department said Sunday it will review the law enforcement response to the Texas school shooting, an unusual federal look back prompted by questions about the shifting and at times contradictory information from authorities that have enraged a community in shock and sorrow.
Highlights The Justice Department will review the law enforcement response to the Texas school shooting. The review will be conducted in a fair, impartial and independent manner and the findings will be made public.</description></item><item><title>Russian warship destroyed in occupied port of Berdyansk, says Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c8abcb189988ba8184aad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 15:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c8abcb189988ba8184aad/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s navy says the Orsk, which was used to ferry Russian troops, was hit in Berdyansk.
Highlights Lucy Hockings will be hosting a Your Questions Answered on Friday at 11:30GMT. This will be on World TV and the News Channel and will cover the war in Ukraine. You can get in touch on Twitter using the hashtag BBC Your Questions - and email us at YourQuestions@bbc.co.uk. We&amp;rsquo;ll also take a look at the human consequences of the conflict in Ukraine on Friday night at 1130GMT and on Saturday morning on the News and World TV at 11.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones lists $6.2 million in assets as judge adds new sanctions in Sandy Hook cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44157b52f104b3224a288/</guid><description>AUSTIN, Texas — A Travis County judge imposed additional sanctions against Alex Jones on&amp;hellip;
Summary According to information Jones provided in December as part of the case, he listed more than $6.2 million in assets, including three properties worth about $2.35 million and about $458,000 in the bank. Free Speech Systems, according to Jones, has about $525,000 in the bank, inventory worth about $1.3 million and $2.1 million in fixed and intangible assets.</description></item></channel></rss>