<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sister on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sister/</link><description>Recent content in sister on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:55:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sister/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>14-year old girl was accidentally shot by another child, says sheriff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e36603cf5629272aefb85/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e36603cf5629272aefb85/</guid><description>Alexis Sky Pierson, 14, died after being shot Tuesday when another child picked up what was believed to be an unloaded weapon and fired it towards her.
Highlights Alexis Sky Pierson, 14, died after being shot by another child in Hancock County, Mississippi. A 10-year-old picked up what appeared to be an unloaded weapon and fired it towards her. A bullet was discharged from the weapon, striking the girl just below her left eye.</description></item><item><title>Mum has arms ripped off, dies stopping pit bull from attacking 4-year-old son</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c294cdb11f41efe73d1b8f/</guid><description>Description A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says.
Summary A mother from Wisconsin in the US had her arms ripped apart by a pit bull while saving her four-year-old son from the dog and later died, her sister says. She said, ‘I have no arms, and I’m dying,’” Ms Pingel’s sister, Shannon Pingel, told the Wausau Daily Herald.</description></item></channel></rss>