<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>infant on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/infant/</link><description>Recent content in infant on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/infant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First baby formula shipment arrives from Europe on U.S. military plane</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b33d9a5124cbf494c0190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b33d9a5124cbf494c0190/</guid><description>A military cargo plane carrying the first shipment of infant formula from Europe to help address a critical shortage in the United States landed in Indianapolis on Sunday, and the White House said a second flight had been arranged.
Highlights A military cargo plane carrying the first shipment of infant formula from Europe landed in Indianapolis on Sunday. The White House said a second flight carrying formula would leave from Ramstein Air Base in Germany in coming days.</description></item><item><title>Formula maker: 'This is a crisis. We can't flip a switch and make a lot more formula'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d0e5ee5f7c31bc229b0bc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d0e5ee5f7c31bc229b0bc/</guid><description>Laura Modi is fielding dozens of emails, calls, and texts daily from anxious parents asking about how they can get baby formula.
Highlights Demand for baby formula is outstripping supply in the U.S. New York-based company is scrambling to meet demand. The situation has been exacerbated by potential bacterial infections in recent weeks. The company is producing at full capacity and making as much formula as they can. It is not the first time the company has been forced to withdraw from its formula production program, a spokesperson for the company says.</description></item><item><title>Infant formula recall expanded following child's death, FDA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ebf110fc0069c1457d86a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ebf110fc0069c1457d86a/</guid><description>Abbott Laboratories recalled some Similac PM 60/40 cans and cases produced at a Michigan facility, after an infant who was exposed to the powdered baby formula died.
Highlights Abbott recalled some Similac PM 60/40 cans and cases produced at a Michigan facility. An infant who was exposed to the powdered baby formula died, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Monday. A few days earlier, Abbott recalled certain baby formula made at the facility in Sturgis city following complaints about bacterial infections in infants who consumed the products.</description></item><item><title>TSA officer saves infant who stopped breathing at airport</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c723f80bfe68399f712d00/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 14:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c723f80bfe68399f712d00/</guid><description>NEWARK, N.J. (AP) — A security officer leapt over conveyor belt rollers and saved a 2-month-old boy who stopped breathing at a security checkpoint at Newark Liberty International Airport in New Jersey, newly released video shows.
Summary (Transportation Security Administration via AP)NEWARK, N.J. (AP) — A security officer leapt over conveyor belt rollers and saved a 2-month-old boy who stopped breathing at a security checkpoint at Newark Liberty International Airport in New Jersey, newly released video shows.</description></item></channel></rss>