<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>teachers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teachers/</link><description>Recent content in teachers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 22:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teachers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More than 800 Houston ISD teachers say they won't be returning to the classroom next year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293ef235eea5a7c3472ef91/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293ef235eea5a7c3472ef91/</guid><description>Houston Teacher’s United tweeted that 1 in 12 teachers in Houston Independent School District have given notice that they won’t be returning next year.
Highlights More than 800 Houston ISD teachers say they won&amp;rsquo;t be returning to the classroom next year. Houston Teacher’s United tweeted that 1 in 12 teachers in Houston Independent School District have given notice that they won’t be returning next year. The number of new applicants for HISD teacher positions is up 40% over this time last year.</description></item><item><title>Missouri high school bans LGBTQ support stickers and cards</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62695deaaabc7f02d509426a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 15:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62695deaaabc7f02d509426a/</guid><description>The school board of suburban Kansas City high school has told its teachers to remove cards and stickers that show they are allies of LGBTQ students.
Highlights School board of suburban Kansas City high school has told teachers to remove cards and stickers that show they are allies of LGBTQ students. The directive came after members received “a concern” about the cards. The email said the district remains committed to helping create a safe and inclusive environment, but the cards were “not appropriate at this time.</description></item></channel></rss>