<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>treatment on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/treatment/</link><description>Recent content in treatment on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:26:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/treatment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Putin treated for advanced cancer and survived assassination attempt, US intelligence reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a0be5b285cfc26cd10605/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a0be5b285cfc26cd10605/</guid><description>The Russian president has received treatment for advanced cancer and was targeted in an assassination attempt, three intelligence sources have told Newsweek
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin received treatment for advanced cancer in April, three US intelligence sources have told Newsweek. The report also confirmed an assassination plot against Mr Putin in March, the organisation said. Rumours have been swirling in the past few months that Mr Putin was suffering from cancer or was in bad health as pictures of him in a debilitated state emerged.</description></item><item><title>Palestinian baby dies after treatment delayed by Israeli blockade of Gaza</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62480629b2eefebe79cfac36/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62480629b2eefebe79cfac36/</guid><description>Fatima al-Masri, a 19-month-old with a hole in her heart, waited five months for Israel to issue a permit to allow her to travel to Jerusalem for treatment
Highlights Fatima al-Masri, 19 months, died in Gaza after waiting for five months for a permit to leave the blockaded enclave for treatment. She was diagnosed last year with a hole in the heart and died on Friday. Human rights groups say Israel’s blockade of Gaza was responsible for her death.</description></item><item><title>Iditarod punishes 3 mushers for sheltering dogs in windstorm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241a86252d5014a73844d98/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 12:22:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241a86252d5014a73844d98/</guid><description>The Iditarod has punished three mushers for taking their dogs inside shelter cabins during fierce storms at the tail end of this year&amp;rsquo;s race
Highlights Three mushers were penalized for leaving their dogs in a shelter during a winter storm. Porsild and Phillips were fined $1,000 each for doing so. The dogs were huddled inside a shelter at the end of the race in Nome, Alaska. The decision was made by race officials, but no charges were filed against the mushers.</description></item><item><title>Arkansas jail sued over ivermectin treatments has alleged history of leaving ailing inmates "harmed and worse off"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb8ecbb70d6ed393be6bc5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 08:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb8ecbb70d6ed393be6bc5/</guid><description>At least 37 federal lawsuits have been filed against the jail and/or its doctor since his contract began in 2016.
Highlights Walt Kelly was taken to Washington County Detention Center in Arkansas in November 2017 for two counts of delivering an ounce of marijuana. Kelly, 49, was undergoing treatment for bipolar disorder. Kelly said he was left &amp;ldquo;left to die in my own misery, in my mental health nightmare&amp;rdquo; last year.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer pill becomes 1st US-authorized home COVID treatment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c480fac70a799e60dad67e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 14:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c480fac70a799e60dad67e/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health regulators on Wednesday authorized the first pill against COVID-19, a Pfizer drug that Americans will be able to take at home to head off the worst effects of the virus.
Summary This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)WASHINGTON (AP) — U.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer pill becomes 1st US-authorized home COVID treatment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3a002b485b06b08d59d9e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3a002b485b06b08d59d9e/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. health regulators on Wednesday authorized the first pill against COVID-19, a Pfizer drug that Americans will be able to take at home to head off the worst effects of the virus.
Summary This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)This image provided by Pfizer in October 2021 shows the company&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Paxlovid pills. (Pfizer via AP)WASHINGTON (AP) — U.</description></item></channel></rss>