<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jet on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jet/</link><description>Recent content in jet on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 13:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>China Eastern Airlines Boeing 737 crashes in China with 133 passengers onboard</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62387bef7930b27c75f7bf5e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 13:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62387bef7930b27c75f7bf5e/</guid><description>A China Eastern Airlines Boeing 737-800 with 132 people on board crashed in mountains in southern China on a domestic flight on Monday after a sudden descent from cruising altitude. Media said there were no signs of survivors.
Highlights NEW: Chinese media show dashcam footage apparently showing jet diving to the ground behind trees. NEW: China Eastern Airlines grounded its fleet of 737-800 planes after the crash, state media reported. The plane was en route from the southwestern city of Kunming, capital of Yunnan province, to Guangzhou, China&amp;rsquo;s Guangdong, bordering Hong Kong, when it crashed.</description></item><item><title>The teenager that tracked Elon Musk's jet is now tracking Russian oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</guid><description>Jack Sweeney, a Florida teen who tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online has a new aviation-themed target: Russian oligarchs and billionaires.
Highlights Jack Sweeney, 19, tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online. He recently launched two new automated Twitter handles — @RUOligarchJets and @Putinjet — following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The two profiles have amassed nearly 300,000 followers combined and provide nearly live updates of the private jets&amp;rsquo; movements. Russia&amp;rsquo;s oligarchs face economic chaos at home and punishment by the West after President Vladimir Putin ordered his troops into Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>