<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>china on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/china/</link><description>Recent content in china on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:51:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia has requested military and economic assistance from China, US officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fe2fcb78c52ee299bcc3f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fe2fcb78c52ee299bcc3f/</guid><description>Russia has asked China for military support, including drones, as well as economic assistance for its unprovoked invasion of Ukraine, according to conversations CNN had with two US officials.
Highlights NEW: China says it was not asked by Russia for military equipment or other assistance. NEW: Chinese and Russian governments deny that the request happened. Russia expanded its offensive to western Ukraine on Sunday, firing missiles near Lviv and hitting a large military base.</description></item><item><title>China daily local symptomatic COVID cases more than triple</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e5e11487dedd8afa1f35a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 21:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e5e11487dedd8afa1f35a/</guid><description>Mainland China reported 1,807 new local symptomatic COVID-19 cases on Sunday, the highest daily figure in two years and more than triple the caseload of the previous day, as surging infections in a northeastern province squeeze health resources.
Highlights Mainland China reported 1,807 new local symptomatic COVID-19 cases on Sunday. Surge prompted health authorities to allow the public to buy rapid self-test kits for the first time to help detect infections quickly.</description></item><item><title>China state-backed hackers compromised networks of at least 6 U.S. state governments, research finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228d35b65abde91c7f7c77c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 16:19:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228d35b65abde91c7f7c77c/</guid><description>The China state-sponsored group called APT41 allegedly took advantage of software flaws and exploited security vulnerabilities.
Highlights Cybersecurity firm Mandiant says Chinese hackers took advantage of software flaws and exploited security vulnerabilities. The group, known as APT41, allegedly exploited vulnerabilities in web applications to get their initial foothold into state government networks. The U.S., European Union, NATO and other allies blamed China for massive cyberattack on Microsoft Exchange servers last year.</description></item><item><title>US-born figure skater Zhu Yi under attack after fall on Olympic debut for China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62006a7c6c503473c9f73125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62006a7c6c503473c9f73125/</guid><description>Representing China, California-born figure skater Zhu Yi is facing a firestorm of attack on Chinese social media after she fell flat on the ice and finished last in a women&amp;rsquo;s short program team event Sunday.
Highlights The hashtag &amp;ldquo;Zhu Yi has fallen&amp;rdquo; gained 200 million views in just a few hours on China&amp;rsquo;s Twitter-like platform. Many questioned why Zhu, an American-born skater, was picked to represent China at the expense of an athlete born in the country.</description></item><item><title>China gives 'Fight Club' new ending where authorities win</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f07309aae16bc7fe0b0773/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 22:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f07309aae16bc7fe0b0773/</guid><description>BEIJING - The first rule of Fight Club in China? Don&amp;rsquo;t mention the original ending. The second rule of Fight Club in China? Change it so the police win.
Summary China gives &amp;lsquo;Fight Club&amp;rsquo; new ending where authorities winChina has some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most restrictive censorship rules with authorities only approving a handful of foreign films for release each yearBEIJING - The first rule of Fight Club in China? Don&amp;rsquo;t mention the original ending.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan to invest $200m in Lithuania to offset Beijing’s sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6da03a14f72f1b76cbf1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6da03a14f72f1b76cbf1c/</guid><description>Taiwan is planning to invest 200 million US dollars in Lithuania, in an effort to shield the country from China&amp;rsquo;s pressu&amp;hellip;
Summary Taiwan is planning to invest 200 million US dollars in Lithuania, in an effort to shield the country from China&amp;rsquo;s pressure. The money will come from Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s National Development Fund as well as private investors. Lithuania has been a subject of undeclared economic sanctions from China after it opened the Taiwanese office.</description></item></channel></rss>