<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>korean on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/korean/</link><description>Recent content in korean on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 07:14:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/korean/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Korean marine deserts to serve as Ukrainian foreign legion saying 'I choose meaningful death than meaningless one'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ac8a8484ae9a730d666e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 07:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ac8a8484ae9a730d666e9/</guid><description>(ATTN: CHANGES headline, lead; UPDATES with new info in paras 2-3, minor edits in paras 4-&amp;hellip;
Highlights Marine attempted to enter Ukraine from Poland but was denied entry at a border checkpoint, official says. Ukraine authorities are set to transfer his custody to South Korean officials in Poland. The Marine is set to be transferred to South Korea by Ukraine authorities in South Korea, official said. Marine&amp;rsquo;s custody will be transferred in Poland, the official said, adding the Ukraine authorities will transfer it to his South Korean counterparts.</description></item><item><title>A viewer called to criticize a TV anchor in Missouri over being 'very Asian'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5c0e15220d37632ccb954/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5c0e15220d37632ccb954/</guid><description>A news anchor in Missouri was deeply hurt when a viewer criticized her for being &amp;quot;very Asian&amp;quot; but within hours, Asian Americans across the country stood up for her.
Summary (CNN) A news anchor in Missouri was deeply hurt when a viewer criticized her for being &amp;ldquo;very Asian&amp;rdquo; but within hours, Asian Americans across the country stood up for her. Last week, an unidentified woman called CNN affiliate KSDK in St.</description></item></channel></rss>