<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>doctors on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/doctors/</link><description>Recent content in doctors on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 02:16:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/doctors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US Woman Shocked After Being Charged $40 "For Crying" During Doctor's Visit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62884b487bd9a49f5329298a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62884b487bd9a49f5329298a/</guid><description>A US woman recently shared that her sister was charged $40 (early Rs 3,100) &amp;quot;for crying&amp;quot; at a doctor&amp;rsquo;s appointment. The photo of the medical bill has gone viral with more than 486,000 likes and thousands of comments.
Highlights Camille Johnson shared a picture of her sister&amp;rsquo;s medical bill on Twitter. She highlighted a segment of the bill that docked her sibling for a “brief emotional/behavioural assessment” The photo has gone viral with more than 486,000 likes and thousands of comments.</description></item><item><title>Alcohol should have cancer warning labels, say doctors and researchers pushing to raise awareness of risk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db4ceec450f920d000aba5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db4ceec450f920d000aba5/</guid><description>Advocates of warning labels want Canadians to understand that alcohol is classified as a Group 1 carcinogen and one of the top causes of preventable cancer.
Summary Stockwell wants to change that, and he and other health experts are advocating for cancer warning labels on alcohol containers. Tim Stockwell, a senior scientist with the Canadian Institute for Substance Use Research at the University of Victoria, is among the researchers and doctors pushing for cancer warning labels on alcohol.</description></item></channel></rss>