<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>canada on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/canada/</link><description>Recent content in canada on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/canada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unionized workers at Victoria Starbucks 'steaming mad' after wage increases not extended to location</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295db44674c7e1d585b02c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295db44674c7e1d585b02c1/</guid><description>Workers at a Starbucks in Victoria are calling out Starbucks Canada after the company refused to extend wage increases to the unionized staff at the Douglas Street location.
Highlights Workers at a Starbucks in Victoria are calling out Starbucks Canada after the company refused to extend wage increases to the unionized staff at the Douglas Street location. The Douglas Street store voted to unionize back in the summer of 2020, voting to become part of United Steelworkers District 3, which represents over 50,000 workers in Western Canada.</description></item><item><title>Canada will ensure border officials know Americans can travel for abortion: Mendicino - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273793e0a6766d19586bfc8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 07:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273793e0a6766d19586bfc8/</guid><description>If a leaked draft ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court becomes a decision, Roe v. Wade could be overturned. Americans can travel to Canada for abortions as needed, officials say.
Highlights Public Safety Minister Marco Mendicino says he will be speaking with the Canada Border Services Agency to make sure Americans seeking abortions can come to Canada. A leaked draft ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court suggested earlier this week that Roe v.</description></item><item><title>Canada prepared to welcome an unlimited number of Ukrainians fleeing war, minister says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622248ec8170757842306465/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 17:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622248ec8170757842306465/</guid><description>Immigration Minister Sean Fraser announced Thursday the federal government has created two new pathways for Ukrainians fleeing their war-torn country to come to Canada — part of a plan to accept an &amp;quot;unlimited number&amp;quot; of people who want to leave.
Highlights Immigration Minister Sean Fraser announced Thursday the federal government has created two new pathways for Ukrainians fleeing their war-torn country to come to Canada. Some critics, including NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh, have called on the government to drop the visa requirement altogether to allow all Ukrainians to travel to Canada unencumbered.</description></item><item><title>Second of five whales brought from Canada to US aquarium dies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a2b1fa2799ab5779ee84f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 10:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a2b1fa2799ab5779ee84f/</guid><description>Female was receiving intensive care for multiple health issues but died early Friday morning, and a male beluga died in August
Highlights The female whale had been receiving intensive care for health issues but died early Friday morning. A necropsy was to be performed to determine the cause of death. A male beluga that had been named Havok, who had a pre-existing gastrointestinal issue, died in August. The two whales were among five brought to Mystic last spring from Marineland, a themed zoo and amusement park, in Niagara Falls, Ontario, after a lengthy battle to obtain permits from both US and Canadian authorities.</description></item><item><title>'I thought it was a joke': Canada Post employee sent home for wearing N95 mask instead of company-provided cloth or disposable mask</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</guid><description>A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks.
Summary WINNIPEG -A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks. &amp;ldquo;Right away a supervisor came up to me and told me I can&amp;rsquo;t wear that mask,&amp;rdquo; said Gallagher.</description></item><item><title>Canada reaches agreement to compensate indigenous children taken from families</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db772d15b46499f71f75fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db772d15b46499f71f75fc/</guid><description>Canada announced on Tuesday two agreements totaling $31.5 billion (40 billion Canadian dollars) to compensate First Nations children who were taken from their families and put into the child welfare system and to reform the system that removed them and deprived them of services they needed.
Summary Toronto, Canada Canada announced on Tuesday two agreements totaling $31.5 billion (40 billion Canadian dollars) to compensate First Nations children who were taken from their families and put into the child welfare system and to reform the system that removed them and deprived them of services they needed.</description></item><item><title>Grocers pressured to bring back 'hero pay' amid Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</guid><description>The head of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union says the refusal by the country&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;quot;hero pay&amp;quot; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;quot;about greed, period.&amp;quot;
Summary The failure of Canada&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;ldquo;hero pay&amp;rdquo; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;ldquo;about greed, period,&amp;rdquo; the head of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union said Friday. While each chain has sporadically reintroduced either wage bonuses or other incentives, it appears none have offered workers pay premiums as a result of the Omicron surge.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau says China ‘playing’ Western states against each other</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7f6eb62614417bb46ab34/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7f6eb62614417bb46ab34/</guid><description>Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said China has been “playing” Western states against each other and that democracies should present a “united front”
Summary Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said China has been “playing” Western states against each other and that democracies should present a “united front” in response. Advertisement“We’ve been competing, and China has been from time to time very cleverly playing us off each other in an open-market, competitive way,” Trudeau said.</description></item></channel></rss>