<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>canada on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/canada/</link><description>Recent content in canada on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/canada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'I thought it was a joke': Canada Post employee sent home for wearing N95 mask instead of company-provided cloth or disposable mask</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</guid><description>A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks.
Summary WINNIPEG -A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks. &amp;ldquo;Right away a supervisor came up to me and told me I can&amp;rsquo;t wear that mask,&amp;rdquo; said Gallagher.</description></item><item><title>Canada reaches agreement to compensate indigenous children taken from families</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db772d15b46499f71f75fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db772d15b46499f71f75fc/</guid><description>Canada announced on Tuesday two agreements totaling $31.5 billion (40 billion Canadian dollars) to compensate First Nations children who were taken from their families and put into the child welfare system and to reform the system that removed them and deprived them of services they needed.
Summary Toronto, Canada Canada announced on Tuesday two agreements totaling $31.5 billion (40 billion Canadian dollars) to compensate First Nations children who were taken from their families and put into the child welfare system and to reform the system that removed them and deprived them of services they needed.</description></item><item><title>Grocers pressured to bring back 'hero pay' amid Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d96ecf526bedeffb931e82/</guid><description>The head of Canada&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union says the refusal by the country&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;quot;hero pay&amp;quot; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;quot;about greed, period.&amp;quot;
Summary The failure of Canada&amp;rsquo;s grocers to reinstate &amp;ldquo;hero pay&amp;rdquo; for employees amid an exponential rise in COVID-19 cases is &amp;ldquo;about greed, period,&amp;rdquo; the head of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest private-sector union said Friday. While each chain has sporadically reintroduced either wage bonuses or other incentives, it appears none have offered workers pay premiums as a result of the Omicron surge.</description></item><item><title>Trudeau says China ‘playing’ Western states against each other</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7f6eb62614417bb46ab34/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7f6eb62614417bb46ab34/</guid><description>Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said China has been “playing” Western states against each other and that democracies should present a “united front”
Summary Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said China has been “playing” Western states against each other and that democracies should present a “united front” in response. Advertisement“We’ve been competing, and China has been from time to time very cleverly playing us off each other in an open-market, competitive way,” Trudeau said.</description></item></channel></rss>