<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>age on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/age/</link><description>Recent content in age on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:11:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/age/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NY passes bill raising age to buy, own semi-automatic rifles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299c2088113d87ae45f8024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299c2088113d87ae45f8024/</guid><description>ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — New York&amp;rsquo;s legislature voted Thursday to ban anyone under age 21 from buying or possessing a semi-automatic rifle, a major change to state firearm laws pushed through less than three weeks after an 18-year-old used one of the guns to kill 10 people at a supermarket in Buffalo.
Highlights The age limit bill passed the Senate along party lines, 43-20, and in the Assembly 102-47, and will now head to Hochul’s desk for her signature.</description></item><item><title>Denmark stocks up on iodine pills to bolster nuclear emergency plan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254fd1a5bcf24a56997c2c8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254fd1a5bcf24a56997c2c8/</guid><description>Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Health Agency, concerned by the war in Ukraine, will buy 2 million iodine tablets to protect people in the event of a nuclear accident close to the Nordic country, it said on Monday.
Highlights Denmark&amp;rsquo;s Health Agency will buy 2 million iodine tablets to protect people in the event of a nuclear accident close to the Nordic country. The first deliveries are expected within two to three months. Denmark is more than 900 kilometres from the nearest nuclear plants in Ukraine, according to the health agency.</description></item><item><title>Turkmenistan’s despot finds a worthy successor: his son - "A horse-obsessed personality cult becomes a dynasty"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62120608cc39a745a2c049ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62120608cc39a745a2c049ee/</guid><description>A horse-obsessed personality cult becomes a dynasty | Asia
Highlights Gurbanguly Berdymukhamedov, Turkmenistan’s president, is still a spring chicken by the standards of his contemporaries. Islam Karimov ruled Uzbekistan until his death at 78 in 2016. Nursultan Nazarbayev, the former president of Kazakhstan, was the same age before he made way, in 2019, for a younger leader. A snap election will be held on March 12th. The stage has been set for Central Asia&amp;rsquo;s first hereditary succession since the era of the Khans.</description></item><item><title>Son of Sinéad O’Connor dies at age of 17 after going missing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9d13e3fc8393448a6f76d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9d13e3fc8393448a6f76d/</guid><description>Irish musician says Shane O’Connor, last seen on Friday morning, ‘was the very light of my life’
Summary Sinéad O’Connor’s 17-year-old son has died, two days after he was reported missing. The musician shared the news on social media, writing that he “decided to end his earthly struggle” and asked that “no one follows his example”. In the early hours of Saturday morning, O’Connor tweeted: “My beautiful son, Nevi’im Nesta Ali Shane O’Connor, the very light of my life, decided to end his earthly struggle today and is now with God.</description></item></channel></rss>