<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ontario on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ontario/</link><description>Recent content in ontario on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 23:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ontario/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ottawa: police use pepper spray and stun grenades to clear trucker protest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211795717f05bdace1ac286/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 23:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211795717f05bdace1ac286/</guid><description>‘We told you to leave,’ police say on Twitter, before confronting protesters against Covid mandates and Trudeau government
Highlights Police used pepper spray and stun grenades to break up the blockade of trucks and demonstrators in downtown Ottawa. Truckers have been protesting against Covid-19 vaccine requirements for truck drivers in Canada for more than three weeks. Police, who were accused of using heavy-handed tactics, deployed Mounties on horseback, claimed there were no serious injuries.</description></item><item><title>Truck blockade at U.S.-Canadian border shuts auto plants</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057198cf5ec5624e0d195b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 20:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057198cf5ec5624e0d195b/</guid><description>The truck blockade at the U.S. border by Canadians protesting the country’s COVID-19 restrictions is tightening the screws on the auto industry, forcing Ford, Toyota and General Motors to shut down plants or otherwise curtail production
Highlights The U.S. braced for the possibility of similar truck-borne protests inspired by the Canadians. The bumper-to-bumper demonstration by the self-proclaimed Freedom Convoy entered its fourth day Thursday at the Ambassador Bridge connecting Windsor, Ontario, to Detroit, disrupting the flow of auto parts and other products between the two countries.</description></item></channel></rss>