<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>beach on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/beach/</link><description>Recent content in beach on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 16:20:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/beach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>14-year-old accused of raping Mastic Beach woman in front of daughter during home invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272a7a15fe30ec3b2b7d535/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 16:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272a7a15fe30ec3b2b7d535/</guid><description>The 14-year-old, because of his juvenile status, faces a maximum of 10 years behind bars.
Highlights The suspect is a 14-year-old youth, police say. The victim, 23, was strangled, stabbed, robbed and brutally raped on April 19. Police say the video they distributed of the perpetrators led to tips and eventually a DNA profile that matched the violent rape scene. The suspect was arraigned and, because of his juvenile status, faces a maximum of 10 years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Coastal Panel Staff Advises Against Huntington Beach Desalination Plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fcd74951274a79e6720e9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:24:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fcd74951274a79e6720e9/</guid><description>A proposed California desalination plant that would produce 50 million gallons of drinking water per day failed a crucial regulatory hurdle on Monday, possibly dooming a project that had been promoted as a partial solution for sustained drought.
Highlights Staff of the California Coastal Commission recommended denying approval of the Huntington Beach plant proposed by Poseidon Water. The plant is expected to produce 50 million gallons of drinking water per day, enough for 16% of the homes in the Orange County Water District, where 2.</description></item></channel></rss>