<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>student on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/student/</link><description>Recent content in student on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 00:50:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/student/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest "Don't say gay" bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222b39fd32798c94fe12cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 00:50:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222b39fd32798c94fe12cce/</guid><description>Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest “Don’t say gay” bill. Bill would keep schools from encouraging conversations about sexual orientation and gender identity. Measure has drawn heavy opposition from groups that have repeatedly argued it singles
Highlights Students across Southwest Florida walk out to protest “Don’t say gay” bill. The bill would keep schools from encouraging conversations about sexual orientation and gender identity. The measure has drawn heavy opposition from groups that have repeatedly argued it singles out LGBTQ people.</description></item><item><title>5 Texas Christian School Admins Arrested Today for Covering Up the Sexual Assault of a Freshman by the Baseball Team</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d9927531b13641a8936b7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d9927531b13641a8936b7/</guid><description>Two coaches and three administrators have been charged after Midland Police say a student was sexually assaulted during a baseball practice.
Highlights Three administrators and two coaches at Midland Christian School were arrested and charged with Failure To Report With Intent To Conceal Neglect Or Abuse. Barry Russell, Gregory McClenden, Matthew Counts, Jared Lee and Dana Ellis were all interviewed regarding a sexual assault at the school. The assault reportedly took place at Christensen Stadium around January 20, 2022 during a baseball practice.</description></item><item><title>Pause on student loan payments is extended through May 1</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4486cb98d38c767bbcd63/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4486cb98d38c767bbcd63/</guid><description>Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1.
Summary WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;ndash; The Biden administration is extending a student loan moratorium that has allowed millions of Americans to put off debt payments during the pandemic. Under the action Wednesday, payments on federal student loans will remain paused through May 1. Interest rates will remain at 0% during that period, and debt collection efforts will be suspended.</description></item></channel></rss>