<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>called on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/called/</link><description>Recent content in called on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/called/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teenage girl traumatised after police strip-search, says mum</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c849dc18a28627fe2e717/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c849dc18a28627fe2e717/</guid><description>A 14-year-old girl who was strip-searched by police was traumatised by the incident, her mum says.
Highlights Olivia was strip-searched by police after an argument with two boys. She was searched by police at the scene and nothing was discovered. The 14-year-old was traumatised by the incident, her mother said. She said Olivia had been out with friends when they had an argument. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Nashville firefighter who called council members white supremacists suspended for 16 days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237989535641d06cf41d77d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237989535641d06cf41d77d/</guid><description>NFD concluded that Lipscomb had violated department policy and, pending a\u00a0hearing, he should be suspended for 16 days.
Highlights Nashville firefighter Josh Lipscomb, who performs as a comedian under the name Josh Black, called some council members “white supremacists” in a Feb. 3 tweet. An NFD panel concluded he violated department policy and should be suspended for 16 days. The suspension will begin on his next scheduled shift Monday, records show.</description></item><item><title>Michigan activist swallows mail-order abortion pill on live TV</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0c76d89ac470764fd3efb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 04:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0c76d89ac470764fd3efb/</guid><description>Summary The Food and Drug Administration lifted a restriction on abortion pills in December that allows people to obtain them through the mail and at pharmacies. Related: Most abortions happen in first trimester, and other facts about Michigan abortion ratesBlackmore said she took the first abortion pill on live television to confront stigma surrounding abortions and call attention to the mail-order pills. Related: Anti-abortion advocates rally at Michigan Capitol, express hope Roe v.</description></item></channel></rss>