<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>intoxication on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/intoxication/</link><description>Recent content in intoxication on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 19:11:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/intoxication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Woman arrested after crashing car, fleeing on foot showed signs of intoxication before bribing deputy with sex to let her go, Pct. 4 says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62644f470d537231b2b9d013/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 19:11:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62644f470d537231b2b9d013/</guid><description>As Ortiz was being taken to jail, she attempted to bribe the deputy by offering him “sexual acts and cash in exchange to be let go,” authorities reported.
Highlights Dulce Ortiz was arrested after crashing car, fleeing on foot, and showing signs of intoxication before bribing deputy with sex to let her go, authorities say. Ortiz was charged with Failure to Stop and Give Information. As Ortiz was being taken to jail, she attempted to bribe the deputy by offering him “sexual acts and cash in exchange to be let go,” authorities report.</description></item><item><title>US House candidate apologizes to girls after sleepover</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A U.S. House candidate in Oklahoma has apologized after reports that she became intoxicated at a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day weekend sleepover for middle-school-aged girls, berated several of the children and vomited in a hamper.
Highlights Democrat Abby Broyles is apologizing after reports that she became intoxicated, berated several middle-school-aged girls at a sleepover and vomited in a hamper. Broyles told television station KFOR that she had an adverse reaction after drinking wine and taking medication given to her by a friend.</description></item></channel></rss>