<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ottawa on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ottawa/</link><description>Recent content in ottawa on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:12:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ottawa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canada parliament backs Trudeau on emergency powers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621551992b2ffa3ec7b47b5c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:12:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621551992b2ffa3ec7b47b5c/</guid><description>PM Justin Trudeau invoked the Emergencies Act last week over protests against Covid restrictions.
Highlights Emergencies Act invoked last week over protests against Covid restrictions. It has been used over the past week to impose bans on public assembly in some areas of Ottawa. It also gives authorities the ability to freeze bank accounts, among other measures. PM Justin Trudeau invoked the Act last week following the protests against the Covid ban in Ottawa.</description></item><item><title>'Battle of Billings Bridge' attracts hundreds of volunteers, traps convoy for hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c7a64973ec3a26d413439/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 04:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c7a64973ec3a26d413439/</guid><description>&amp;quot;It just happened. I have never seen anything like it.&amp;quot;
Highlights Hundreds of volunteers block the intersection of Bank Street and Riverside Drive, detaining the convoy for a short time. The convoy was released after nine hours, but some have dubbed it &amp;rsquo;the Battle of Billings Bridge&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;The look on their faces when they were taking down their flags was one of defeat, not of pride,” said Andrea Harden, who has training in de-escalation techniques and non-violent civil disobedience.</description></item><item><title>‘Freedom Convoy’ protesters shut down third border crossing as Ottawa police warn of arrests ‘without a warrant’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620653efcdee5ffe18c39374/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 12:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620653efcdee5ffe18c39374/</guid><description>Raucous protests against vaccine mandates and coronavirus restrictions blocked a third border crossing with the United States.
Highlights The mayor of Windsor, Ontario, says the city and auto groups are seeking an injunction to end a blockade by protesters. The self-styled “Freedom Convoy,” now heading into its third weekend, has paralyzed the Canadian capital. The White House says it is “monitoring” the situation at the border “very closely” and that Cabinet officials are “engaged around the clock’ to bring this to a swift end” The protests started in opposition to U.</description></item><item><title>Ontario court freezes access to donations for truckers' protest from GiveSendGo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62062887f3b1516ce37754b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 09:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62062887f3b1516ce37754b6/</guid><description>The Ontario government says it has successfully petitioned a court to freeze access to millions of dollars donated through online fundraising platform GiveSendGo to the convoy protesting COVID-19 restrictions in Ottawa and at several border crossings.
Highlights Ontario government successfully petitioned a court to freeze access to millions of dollars donated through online fundraising platform GiveSendGo to the convoy protesting COVID-19 restrictions in Ottawa and at several border crossings. The province obtained an order from the Superior Court of Justice that prohibits anyone from distributing donations made through the website&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Freedom Convoy 2022&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Adopt-a-Trucker&amp;rdquo; campaign pages.</description></item><item><title>Trucker convoy: Ottawa ‘under siege’ amid ‘nation-wide insurrection,’ officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffe51e5b54cf0e447e764a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 15:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffe51e5b54cf0e447e764a/</guid><description>Tensions are high as thousands of additional convoy supporters are expected to arrive this weekend, leading to a potentially ‘volatile’ mix says Ottawa’s former police chief.
Highlights More than 100 people gathered outside City Hall on Saturday afternoon to demand convoy supporters go home. Police Chief Peter Sloly said that the legal rules in place for police conduct “were never intended to deal with a city under siege,” he said. The trucker convoy has dug in over the past nine days amid what the chair of the police services board called a “nation-wide insurrection” Sloly, himself, and the Ontario premier have called an “occupation.</description></item></channel></rss>