<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arrest on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arrest/</link><description>Recent content in arrest on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 23:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arrest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A 15-year-old suspect has been arrested in the shooting death of an 11-year-old girl in the Bronx, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62897134ced30d853be4fa0a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 23:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62897134ced30d853be4fa0a/</guid><description>A 15-year-old was arrested Friday in connection with the fatal shooting of an 11-year-old girl in New York City&amp;rsquo;s Bronx neighborhood earlier this week, police said.
Highlights Kyhara Tay, 11, was shot in the abdomen with a stray bullet in the Bronx on Monday. A 15-year-old was arrested Friday in connection with the shooting, police say. The shooting comes as New York City grapples with an uptick of gun violence that has reached even the city’s youngest.</description></item><item><title>Reward grows to $22,500 for arrest of escaped inmate serving life for murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280f0e03ac5ff8dc8bd0c21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280f0e03ac5ff8dc8bd0c21/</guid><description>A Texas inmate serving life for murder managed to break free from his shackles, overpower a bus driver and escape from custody, officials said.
Highlights Gonzalo Lopez, 46, was on a transport bus en route from Gatesville to Huntsville for a medical appointment when he escaped. Lopez cut out the bottom of a door that separates inmates and the driver, Texas Department of Criminal Justice says. Lopez is serving a life sentence for a capital murder in Hidalgo County and an attempted capital murder.</description></item><item><title>4th Kansas Rep. charged in a year, Suzi Carlson charged with two counts after DUI arrest last month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62213d62d4636e71e7d9be1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 22:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62213d62d4636e71e7d9be1c/</guid><description>Rep. Suzi Carlson, R-Clay Center, is charged with two counts in relation to an arrest for allegedly\u00a0driving under the influence earlier this year.
Highlights Rep. Suzi Carlson charged with two counts after DUI arrest last month. Carlson was arrested on suspicion of driving under the influence with a blood alcohol concentration above 0.08 and failure to maintain a single lane. Carlson, 69, is a retired municipal court judge. She is the fourth Kansas lawmaker arrested in the past year, with another scheduled hearing scheduled for May.</description></item><item><title>5 Texas Christian School Admins Arrested Today for Covering Up the Sexual Assault of a Freshman by the Baseball Team</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d9927531b13641a8936b7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d9927531b13641a8936b7/</guid><description>Two coaches and three administrators have been charged after Midland Police say a student was sexually assaulted during a baseball practice.
Highlights Three administrators and two coaches at Midland Christian School were arrested and charged with Failure To Report With Intent To Conceal Neglect Or Abuse. Barry Russell, Gregory McClenden, Matthew Counts, Jared Lee and Dana Ellis were all interviewed regarding a sexual assault at the school. The assault reportedly took place at Christensen Stadium around January 20, 2022 during a baseball practice.</description></item><item><title>Long Island Man Claims Cops Ripped Off His Prosthetic Leg During Wrongful Arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bdeb635335c404035e218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 17:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bdeb635335c404035e218/</guid><description>A man with a prosthetic leg is seeking millions in damages from the Suffolk County Police Department, after claiming he was wrongfully arrested and injured by&amp;hellip;
Highlights Long Island man is seeking millions in damages from the Suffolk County Police Department. He claims he was wrongfully arrested and injured by cops. Police officers ripped off his prosthetic leg during wrongful arrest, he says. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Auburn man arrested for leaving flowers at fiancé's grave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057fa87d384d8a5f85ebf5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057fa87d384d8a5f85ebf5/</guid><description>An arrest warrant for Winchester Hagans is signed by his fiancés father Tom Ford. The charge: littering.
Highlights Winchester Hagans lost his fiancé, Hannah Ford, in a car crash in January 2021. She died one month after he proposed to her. Hagans built a flower box filled with her favorite flowers and decorated it with pictures of the two of them to put by her grave. Last month, Hagans was arrested for littering after putting the box of flowers on her grave.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioter ordered back to jail after DWI arrest, AR-15 rifle discovered in car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8d048cb6990eaabe4cbcc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 03:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8d048cb6990eaabe4cbcc/</guid><description>An accused Capitol rioter has been ordered to be returned to federal custody after he tried to flee an arrest for suspected drunk driving last month and police discovered an AR-15 rifle in his car.
Summary James Tate Grant, who is accused of attacking a Capitol Police officer in the Jan. 6, 2021, riot. As he was being arrested, Grant tried to flee, the filing said. In Grant’s car, police recovered an AR-15 assault rifle, 60 rounds of ammunition, weapon accessories and combat fatigues, court documents said.</description></item><item><title>Russian dissident Alexei Navalny says he has 'no regrets': After spending a year behind bars, Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: "Don't be afraid of anything."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</guid><description>After spending a year behind bars, the prominent Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: &amp;quot;Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of anything.&amp;quot;
Summary His return and arrest led to protests and a monthslong crackdown on his political network. Navalny on Monday took to social media to share his sentiments on the anniversary of his arrest on charges he has maintained are politically motivated. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t regret it for a second,&amp;rdquo; Navalny said of his decision to return to Russia, only to be arrested.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones' wife arrested on domestic violence charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7ccbc52d7e6bc69448489/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7ccbc52d7e6bc69448489/</guid><description>The wife of conspiracy theorist Alex Jones was arrested Christmas Eve on a domestic violence charge that the right-wing provocateur says stems from a “medication imbalance.”
Summary The wife of conspiracy theorist Alex Jones was arrested Christmas Eve on a domestic violence charge that the right-wing provocateur says stems from a “medication imbalance.”DALLAS &amp;ndash; The wife of conspiracy theorist Alex Jones was arrested Christmas Eve on a domestic violence charge that the right-wing provocateur said stems from a &amp;ldquo;medication imbalance.</description></item></channel></rss>