<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nuclear on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nuclear/</link><description>Recent content in nuclear on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 11:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nuclear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Macron bets on nuclear in carbon-neutrality push, announces new reactors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62064443f7f9253d0041c9e0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 11:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62064443f7f9253d0041c9e0/</guid><description>France will build at least six new nuclear reactors in the decades to come, President Emmanuel Macron said on Thursday, placing nuclear power at the heart of his country&amp;rsquo;s drive for carbon neutrality by 2050.
Highlights French President Emmanuel Macron says nuclear power is key to reaching carbon-neutrality by 2050. The first new reactor, an evolution of the European Pressurised Reactor (EPR), would come online by 2035. France will also increase its solar power capacity tenfold by 2050 to more than 100 gigawatts (GW) EDF estimates the cost of six new reactors at about 50 billion euros ($57.</description></item><item><title>‘No one can win a nuclear war’: Superpowers release rare joint statement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d371fdf6709c474ae2fcfe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d371fdf6709c474ae2fcfe/</guid><description>China, Russia, the UK, the United States and France release a joint statement agreeing that a further spread of nuclear arms should be avoided.
Summary China, Russia, the UK, the United States and France have agreed that a further spread of nuclear arms and a nuclear war should be avoided. According to a joint statement released on Tuesday morning (AEDT), the five countries – the permanent members of the United Nations Security Council – said they considered it their primary responsibility to avoid war between the nuclear states and to reduce strategic risks, while aiming to work to create an atmosphere of security.</description></item></channel></rss>