<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>opinion on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/opinion/</link><description>Recent content in opinion on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 23:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Crowds protest at Supreme Court after leak of Roe opinion draft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271b72354c6deddee3ee156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 23:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271b72354c6deddee3ee156/</guid><description>Activists expect a larger turnout Tuesday afternoon and evening, with protests planned in state capitals across the country.
Highlights More than 100 supporters of abortion rights and a smaller number of opponents continued to voice their reactions to a leaked opinion by the court signaling it was positioned to overturn Roe v. Wade. The two groups were separated by police barricades, but many of the antiabortion demonstrators present earlier Tuesday had left.</description></item><item><title>Abortion clinic at center of Mississippi case may move to N.M. if Roe is overturned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62719b0210cd8daa73c987d1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 21:14:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62719b0210cd8daa73c987d1/</guid><description>Shannon Brewer, the director of Mississippi’s only abortion clinic, said she is prepared to move to New Mexico if the Supreme Court overturns Roe v. Wade.
Highlights The director of Jackson Women’s Health Organization, Mississippi&amp;rsquo;s only abortion clinic, said she is prepared to move to New Mexico if the Supreme Court overturns Roe v. Wade. Shannon Brewer said she&amp;rsquo;s also making a plan for how she can continue providing abortion access to women.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court potential shock move on abortion sends protesters onto Washington streets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270e682e170eb5e76ac974c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 08:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270e682e170eb5e76ac974c/</guid><description>Anti-abortion activists and pro-abortion rights supporters took to the streets of Washington on Tuesday after news that the U.S. Supreme Court may overturn the 1973 Roe v Wade ruling that legalized abortion.
Highlights A leaked initial draft majority opinion suggests the court has voted to overturn Roe v. Wade. The ruling would be the court&amp;rsquo;s most sweeping since former President Donald Trump succeeded in naming three justices to the court, cementing a 6-3 conservative majority.</description></item></channel></rss>