<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>israeli on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/israeli/</link><description>Recent content in israeli on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:12:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/israeli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israeli nationalists chant racist slogans in Jerusalem march</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62946e4dfdbc1eb185c174f1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62946e4dfdbc1eb185c174f1/</guid><description>Thousands of Israeli nationalists, some of them chanting “Death to Arabs,” have begun parading through the heart of the main Palestinian thoroughfare in Jerusalem’s Old City
Highlights Thousands of Israeli nationalists, some of them chanting “Death to Arabs,” have begun parading through the heart of the main Palestinian thoroughfare in Jerusalem’s Old City. The crowds, who were overwhelmingly young Orthodox Jewish men, were celebrating Jerusalem Day &amp;ndash; an Israeli holiday that marks the capture of the Old City in the 1967 Mideast war.</description></item><item><title>Syria's air defences confront 'Israeli aggression', state media report | Reuters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252d9796b3070546000ca04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 13:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252d9796b3070546000ca04/</guid><description>Syrian air defences confronted an &amp;quot;Israeli air aggression&amp;quot; on Saturday in the country&amp;rsquo;s central region, Syrian state media reported.
Highlights Syrian air defences confronted an &amp;ldquo;Israeli air aggression&amp;rdquo; in the country&amp;rsquo;s central region, state media reported. Israel&amp;rsquo;s military declined to comment on the reported air strikes in Syria. Syria state media: &amp;ldquo;The Israeli enemy launched an air aggression from the north of Lebanon, targeting some points in the central region,&amp;rdquo; state media said citing a military source.</description></item><item><title>UAE sentences Israeli woman to death for cocaine possession - CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e024ef9bfbde8df20e1fc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e024ef9bfbde8df20e1fc/</guid><description>A court in the United Arab Emirates has sentenced an Israeli woman to death, after she was found guilty of possessing 500 grams of cocaine. The woman &amp;ndash; named by Israeli media as 43-year old Fidaa Kiwan &amp;ndash; is appealing the sentence.
Highlights A court in the United Arab Emirates has sentenced an Israeli woman to death, after she was found guilty of possessing 500 grams of cocaine. The woman &amp;ndash; named by Israeli media as 43-year-old Fidaa Kiwan &amp;ndash; is appealing the sentence.</description></item><item><title>Israeli attack over Damascus kills two -Syrian State Media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622749ea068e2734fc60ad23/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 12:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622749ea068e2734fc60ad23/</guid><description>An Israeli attack over the Syrian capital Damascus on Monday killed two civilians and left some material damage, Syrian State Media reported citing a military source.
Highlights Israel has mounted frequent attacks against what it has described as Iranian targets in Syria. Tehran-backed forces including Lebanon&amp;rsquo;s Hezbollah have deployed over the last decade to support President Bashar al-Assad in Syria&amp;rsquo;s war. &amp;ldquo;Our air defences downed most of the Israeli missiles,&amp;rdquo; the military source said.</description></item><item><title>4-year-old Israeli child tests positive for polio, first case since 1989</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62268352c4ca42fae2677c3e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 22:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62268352c4ca42fae2677c3e/</guid><description>The case in Jerusalem comes after a reported outbreak in Malawi, which was linked to one circulating in Pakistan, where it is still endemic.
Highlights A four-year-old Israeli child from Jerusalem tested positive for polio after it was revealed he was not vaccinated against the life-threatening disease. The patient seems to have been infected with a strain that has undergone a change and could cause disease in those who are not vaccinated.</description></item></channel></rss>