<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>israeli on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/israeli/</link><description>Recent content in israeli on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 12:20:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/israeli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Israeli attack over Damascus kills two -Syrian State Media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622749ea068e2734fc60ad23/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 12:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622749ea068e2734fc60ad23/</guid><description>An Israeli attack over the Syrian capital Damascus on Monday killed two civilians and left some material damage, Syrian State Media reported citing a military source.
Highlights Israel has mounted frequent attacks against what it has described as Iranian targets in Syria. Tehran-backed forces including Lebanon&amp;rsquo;s Hezbollah have deployed over the last decade to support President Bashar al-Assad in Syria&amp;rsquo;s war. &amp;ldquo;Our air defences downed most of the Israeli missiles,&amp;rdquo; the military source said.</description></item><item><title>4-year-old Israeli child tests positive for polio, first case since 1989</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62268352c4ca42fae2677c3e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 22:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62268352c4ca42fae2677c3e/</guid><description>The case in Jerusalem comes after a reported outbreak in Malawi, which was linked to one circulating in Pakistan, where it is still endemic.
Highlights A four-year-old Israeli child from Jerusalem tested positive for polio after it was revealed he was not vaccinated against the life-threatening disease. The patient seems to have been infected with a strain that has undergone a change and could cause disease in those who are not vaccinated.</description></item></channel></rss>