<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>say on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/say/</link><description>Recent content in say on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/say/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colorado wildfire: Marshall fire may have destroyed 1,000 homes in Boulder County, officials say</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</guid><description>The Marshall fire that tore through parts of Superior and Louisville may have destroyed up to 1,000 homes, Gov. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle said Friday.
Summary The winter wildfire, which exploded amid bone-dry conditions fueled by climate warming, quickly became the most destructive wildfire in Colorado history. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle estimated up to 1,000 homes in Superior and Louisville may have been destroyed as the roaring wildfire decimated entire subdivisions with shocking speed.</description></item><item><title>California man driving to White House to kill leaders on 'hit list' arrested in Iowa, officials say</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</guid><description>A heavily armed California man was arrested in Iowa after he told law enforcement officers that he would &amp;quot;do whatever it takes&amp;quot; to kill government leaders on
Summary The man, Kuachua Brillion Xiong, 25, has been held in the Pottawattamie County Jail in Council Bluffs since Thursday, according to sheriff&amp;rsquo;s records. Xiong had been driving from his home near Sacramento, California, since Dec. 18 &amp;ldquo;with the intention of driving straight to the White House &amp;hellip; to kill persons in power,&amp;rdquo; Larson wrote.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina officer accidentally shoots son in the head, authorities say</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cbf97b9f7774fa6b661a1b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 06:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cbf97b9f7774fa6b661a1b/</guid><description>A Jacksonville police officer is under investigation after authorities said he accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head.
Summary Authorities in North Carolina said a 15-year-old male was seriously hurt after his father, a police officer, shot him in the head. The father and the son were not immediately identified, though investigators said the father is a part of the nearby Jacksonville Police Department. The review was not comprehensive, due to the sheer number of U.</description></item><item><title>Teen in dressing room fatally shot by LA police firing at assault suspect, officials say</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</guid><description>A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday,
Summary LOS ANGELES — A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday, authorities said. The 14-year-old girl was found dead behind the dressing room wall, which was penetrated by gunfire, Los Angeles police officials said.</description></item></channel></rss>