<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>say on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/say/</link><description>Recent content in say on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 22:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/say/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More than 800 Houston ISD teachers say they won't be returning to the classroom next year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293ef235eea5a7c3472ef91/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293ef235eea5a7c3472ef91/</guid><description>Houston Teacher’s United tweeted that 1 in 12 teachers in Houston Independent School District have given notice that they won’t be returning next year.
Highlights More than 800 Houston ISD teachers say they won&amp;rsquo;t be returning to the classroom next year. Houston Teacher’s United tweeted that 1 in 12 teachers in Houston Independent School District have given notice that they won’t be returning next year. The number of new applicants for HISD teacher positions is up 40% over this time last year.</description></item><item><title>Dallas Koreatown hair salon shooting suspect had 'delusional fear of Asians,' police records say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287a110643c452b8397ccf9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 14:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287a110643c452b8397ccf9/</guid><description>The arrest warrant affidavit says Jeremy Smith admitted he was in the area on the day of the shooting. His girlfriend told investigators he has panic attacks around people of Asian descent ever since a car crash with an Asian man two years ago.
Highlights Jeremy Smith, 36, was arrested for shooting three women at a Dallas Koreatown hair salon. Police say he was in the area on the day of the shooting and admitted he was looking for a business to repair a panel of broken glass for a garage door.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families can resume defamation lawsuits vs InfoWars owner, attorneys say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fe4567c322dfc0e69381c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 17:18:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fe4567c322dfc0e69381c/</guid><description>Families of the victims of the 2012 Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre will be dismissed from the InfoWars bankruptcy case, allowing them to resume their defamation lawsuits against the website&amp;rsquo;s owner, conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, attorneys said in court on Friday.
Highlights Families of the victims of the 2012 Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre will be dismissed from the InfoWars bankruptcy case. They will be able to resume their defamation lawsuits against the website&amp;rsquo;s owner, conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, attorneys said in court on Friday.</description></item><item><title>Office of anti-abortion organization in Wisconsin targeted in arson attack, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62784e9cb026ef10a4d96828/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 23:14:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62784e9cb026ef10a4d96828/</guid><description>The office of a conservative political organization that lobbies against abortion rights was vandalized and damaged by fire on Sunday morning in Madison, Wisconsin, in what police are investigating as arson.
Highlights Wisconsin Family Action is a political action committee that lobbies against abortion rights. A Molotov cocktail was thrown inside the building, police say. Police chief says WFA appears to have been targeted because of its beliefs. Fire investigators believe the fire was intentionally set and are investigating the incident as arson, fire department says.</description></item><item><title>Woman with 3 kids in car charged in road-rage shooting that injured teen, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62718d26ace47f441a71142b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 20:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62718d26ace47f441a71142b/</guid><description>A woman is in custody following a road rage incident in Georgia that left a teenage victim injured, police said.
Highlights A 17-year-old was shot in the face Sunday afternoon while inside a vehicle on Interstate 20. Brittney Griffith has been charged with four counts of aggravated assault, three counts of cruelty to children and one count of possession of a firearm during commission of a felony. Griffith&amp;rsquo;s three children, ages 4 to 6, were in the car with her when she shot at the victim’s vehicle, police said.</description></item><item><title>Apple store in Maryland becomes third to launch union drive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717ea261fb248308b43d1f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 19:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62717ea261fb248308b43d1f/</guid><description>Employees at the Towson Mall store say they want a voice on coronavirus safety, scheduling, pay and other topics.
Highlights Workers at the Towson Mall store near Baltimore have been drumming up support for nearly a year. They say they have signatures from more than 65 percent of employees who are likely to be eligible, giving them a “supermajority” that would be difficult for the company to overcome. The union drive is the latest sign of a reinvigorated labor movement.</description></item><item><title>A 15-year-old boy died by suicide after relentless cyberbullying, and his parents say the Latin School could have done more to stop it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c3863494177b7445150f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c3863494177b7445150f7/</guid><description>A 15-year-old boy named Nate Bronstein was enrolled at one of the most prestigious private schools in Chicago and had a promising future — that is, until his parents say he became a victim of relentless cyberbullying by his classmates.
Highlights Nate Bronstein, 15, took his own life at the Latin School of Chicago. His parents say he was bullied by classmates at the prestigious private school. They say they were never told about the extent of the bullying.</description></item><item><title>In NYC, ads for jobs will have to say what they pay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a97e291fd58c3e737d5cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 13:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a97e291fd58c3e737d5cc/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Help wanted. The job: putting one of the nation’s most far-reaching salary disclosure laws into practice. Location: New York City. Just four months ago, city lawmakers overwhelmingly voted to require many ads for jobs in the nation’s most populous city to include salary ranges, in the name of giving job applicants — particularly women and people of color — a better shot at fair pay.
Highlights In NYC, ads for jobs will have to say what they pay in job postings.</description></item><item><title>Two Russian oligarchs and their families found dead within 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62671d0b922f34fab2d58845/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 22:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62671d0b922f34fab2d58845/</guid><description>Two Russian gas executives found dead within 24 hours. Investigators say it&amp;rsquo;s unclear whether two were in contact before they were found dead. Two Russian oligarchs and their families found dead in Russia.
Highlights Two Russian gas executives and their families found dead within 24 hours. Investigators say it&amp;rsquo;s unclear whether two were in contact before they, along with their families, were found dead. Investigators: It&amp;rsquo;s unclear if two gas executives had been in contact with each other before they died.</description></item><item><title>Knife-wielding 14-year-old Massachusetts girl scares intruder out of her home and helps apprehend him, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c90f2f7478229458ed019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 22:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c90f2f7478229458ed019/</guid><description>The girl&amp;rsquo;s mother said she was armed with two steak knives when she confronted the man and scared him away.
Highlights A 14-year-old Massachusetts girl scared off a man who allegedly broke into her home Friday morning. Police said the girl, identified as Avery Cormier, was armed with two steak knives when she confronted the intruder. Joseph Ridge, 58, was charged with aggravated breaking and entering during the daytime, trespassing and disorderly conduct.</description></item><item><title>Trafficking ring moved nearly 300 guns from Georgia to Pennsylvania, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555144638320951fd70caf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62555144638320951fd70caf/</guid><description>Atlanta rapper Fredrick Norman, aka “Slowkey Fred,&amp;quot; is one of 11 people facing federal charges in connection with an alleged straw-purchasing scheme, according to records and interviews.
Highlights ATF agents traced nearly 300 firearms purchased in Georgia from dozens of gun retailers to the suspects. Some were found at crime scenes and in the possession of convicted felons in Philadelphia. 11 suspects in Georgia and Pennsylvania are accused of trafficking guns from Georgia to Pennsylvania.</description></item><item><title>Chairman of Russian metals company calls for Bucha probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62522b1d9ecd65f4abcd34ab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62522b1d9ecd65f4abcd34ab/</guid><description>The board chairman of Russian metals company Rusal has called for an investigation into events in the Kyiv suburb of Bucha, where Ukrainian officials say Russian troops killed civilians
Highlights Board chairman of Russian metals company Rusal has called for an investigation into events in the Kyiv suburb of Bucha. Ukrainian forces and journalists discovered scores of bodies on streets and in mass graves after Russian troops withdrew. The Kremlin has said the deaths were staged by the Ukrainians to denigrate Russian forces.</description></item><item><title>Alabama legislature passes 'Don't Say Gay,' trans care and bathroom ban bills</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625060280f64251b5da48776/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625060280f64251b5da48776/</guid><description>Two bills targeting the LGBTQ community passed on Thursday.
Highlights Two bills targeting the LGBTQ community passed on Thursday. SB 184, the Vulnerable Child Protection Act, would ban gender-affirming care to minors under 18. HB 322 would ban trans students from using bathrooms and locker rooms that align with their gender identity. The Trevor Project has condemned the passage of such bills as an attack on bodily autonomy for trans youth and their families.</description></item><item><title>BuzzFeed investors have pushed CEO Jonah Peretti to shut down entire newsroom, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b396eb62c81f8568ce93c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 15:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b396eb62c81f8568ce93c/</guid><description>BuzzFeed&amp;rsquo;s news organization has about 100 employees and loses roughly $10 million a year, according to people familiar with the matter.
Highlights The news division loses $10 million a year, people familiar with it say. The decision to shut down the division could add up to $300 million to the $2 billion loss. BuzzFeed has offered a voluntary buyout to more than 30 staff members. The company has won several awards for its work, including a Pulitzer and an award for excellence in its content, a source says.</description></item><item><title>Shootings targeting homeless men in New York and Washington, DC are linked, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f1575fe7d1eee65919de9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f1575fe7d1eee65919de9/</guid><description>A series of shootings targeting homeless men in New York City and Washington, DC, were carried out by the same suspect, officials said Sunday.
Highlights Five shootings targeting homeless men in New York City and Washington, DC, were carried out by the same suspect, police say. The five shootings left two men dead and took place over a nine-day period this month. The mayors of both cities issued a joint statement Sunday night saying a &amp;ldquo;cold-blooded killer on the loose&amp;rdquo; Authorities are offering a total of $55,000 for information leading to the arrest of the suspect, with the MPD offering a reward of up to $10,000 to $20,000, leading to up to a $25,000.</description></item><item><title>China Asked Russia to Delay Ukraine War Until After Olympics, U.S. Officials Say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622024296fff817336c459c6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 02:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622024296fff817336c459c6/</guid><description>A Western intelligence report indicates that Chinese officials had some level of direct knowledge about President Vladimir V. Putin’s war plans or intentions.
Highlights The ambitious joint statement that the two nations issued during that meeting alarmed American and European officials. It was the first time China had explicitly sided with Russia on issues concerning NATO and European security. A Western intelligence report indicates that Chinese officials had some level of direct knowledge about President Vladimir V.</description></item><item><title>Mom decapitates 6 year old son and dog. Claims devil was speaking to her.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e4a6a443cdff855e0645a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e4a6a443cdff855e0645a/</guid><description>Police say a mother decapitated her 6-year-old child and the family dog Tuesday night in Kansas City.
Highlights Police say a mother decapitated her 6-year-old child and the family dog Tuesday night in Kansas City. Tasha Haefs, 35, has been charged with first-degree murder and armed criminal action. Police say they also found a decapitated dog in the basement of the home. Prosecutors have requested that she be held without bond.</description></item><item><title>Bus driver shot in the head while transporting kids in north Minneapolis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 07:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204baa85cf878b657c0f088/</guid><description>Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis.
Highlights Police say a bus driver is expected to recover after he was shot in the head Wednesday afternoon in north Minneapolis. Police say they have not apprehended any suspects. Three children younger than 10 were on board the bus at the time of the shooting. Minneapolis Public Schools released a statement in response to the school bus shooting as well as a separate shooting in which a student was shot, which read, in part: “… We recognize the deep impact this has on our students, staff and families.</description></item><item><title>Girl under 10 is youngest person to die of COVID-19 in Houston, city health officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</guid><description>A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday.
Summary The nations COVID-19 death toll stands at around 800,000 as the anniversary of the U.S. vaccine rollout arrives. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke, File)HOUSTON – A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday. Privacy laws prevent the health department from providing any other identifiable information.</description></item><item><title>‘Say no to Putin’: Ukrainians support protests in Kazakhstan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</guid><description>Demonstrators in Kyiv fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots.
Summary Demonstrators in Kyiv and Kharkov fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots. Kyiv, Ukraine – With their country’s fate being discussed at this week’s US-Russia talks, Ukrainians took to the streets over the weekend to defend their independence and champion an additional cause – that of Kazakhstan’s protests.</description></item><item><title>Novak Djokovic pictured with young players the day after lawyers say he tested positive for COVID | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da17978f86b29d4bd88492/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da17978f86b29d4bd88492/</guid><description>A photograph taken by the Tennis Association of Serbia showed the world number one meeting with the youngsters but it is not clear if he knew he had coronavirus at the time.
Summary World tennis number one Novak Djokovic appears to have been photographed with young players the day after his lawyers said he tested positive for COVID-19. Djokovic is currently being held in an immigration detention centre in Australia after arriving in the country without proof of vaccination.</description></item><item><title>US shatters its average daily Covid-19 case record again. Experts describe coming weeks as a 'tidal wave' and 'blizzard'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d14da23edfd48be438c6ab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 07:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d14da23edfd48be438c6ab/</guid><description>A day after reporting its highest average daily Covid-19 case number, the US shattered the record Thursday, with an average of 355,990 infections reported every day in the past week, according to Johns Hopkins University.
Summary (CNN) A day after reporting its highest average daily Covid-19 case number, the US shattered the record Thursday, with an average of 355,990 infections reported every day in the past week, according to Johns Hopkins University.</description></item><item><title>Colorado wildfire: Marshall fire may have destroyed 1,000 homes in Boulder County, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</guid><description>The Marshall fire that tore through parts of Superior and Louisville may have destroyed up to 1,000 homes, Gov. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle said Friday.
Summary The winter wildfire, which exploded amid bone-dry conditions fueled by climate warming, quickly became the most destructive wildfire in Colorado history. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle estimated up to 1,000 homes in Superior and Louisville may have been destroyed as the roaring wildfire decimated entire subdivisions with shocking speed.</description></item><item><title>California man driving to White House to kill leaders on 'hit list' arrested in Iowa, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</guid><description>A heavily armed California man was arrested in Iowa after he told law enforcement officers that he would &amp;quot;do whatever it takes&amp;quot; to kill government leaders on
Summary The man, Kuachua Brillion Xiong, 25, has been held in the Pottawattamie County Jail in Council Bluffs since Thursday, according to sheriff&amp;rsquo;s records. Xiong had been driving from his home near Sacramento, California, since Dec. 18 &amp;ldquo;with the intention of driving straight to the White House &amp;hellip; to kill persons in power,&amp;rdquo; Larson wrote.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina officer accidentally shoots son in the head, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbf97b9f7774fa6b661a1b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 06:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbf97b9f7774fa6b661a1b/</guid><description>A Jacksonville police officer is under investigation after authorities said he accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head.
Summary Authorities in North Carolina said a 15-year-old male was seriously hurt after his father, a police officer, shot him in the head. The father and the son were not immediately identified, though investigators said the father is a part of the nearby Jacksonville Police Department. The review was not comprehensive, due to the sheer number of U.</description></item><item><title>Teen in dressing room fatally shot by LA police firing at assault suspect, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</guid><description>A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday,
Summary LOS ANGELES — A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday, authorities said. The 14-year-old girl was found dead behind the dressing room wall, which was penetrated by gunfire, Los Angeles police officials said.</description></item></channel></rss>