<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ivermectin on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ivermectin/</link><description>Recent content in ivermectin on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 16:16:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ivermectin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ivermectin does not prevent severe COVID-19, study finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621117d3166debb3aa5e613b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 16:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621117d3166debb3aa5e613b/</guid><description>Treatment with the dewormer drug ivermectin failed to prevent patients with mild to moderate COVID-19 from progressing to serious illness, a study published Friday by JAMA Internal Medicine found.
Highlights Treatment with dewormer drug ivermectin failed to prevent patients with mild to moderate COVID-19 progressing to serious illness. 43 of 249 patients, or 17%, who received &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; treatment progressed to severe illness, researchers say. Study compared the safety and effectiveness of the drug to standard care in 480 Malaysian patients.</description></item><item><title>Arkansas doctor sued for allegedly giving inmates ivermectin without their consent recognized by local leaders for "job well done"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202a521237a41fc9d175b2f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202a521237a41fc9d175b2f/</guid><description>The doctor has also been sued dozens of times for allegedly providing inadequate medical care to detainees, including for mistreating broken bones.
Highlights Dr. Robert Karas has been accused of treating COVID-positive detainees with anti-parasitic drug ivermectin. The ACLU has sued Karas on behalf of four inmates for the alleged treatment. Local officials agreed to commend Karas for a &amp;ldquo;job well done&amp;rdquo; in his handling of the coronavirus pandemic. The local doctor has not shied away from touting the use of the drug to treat COVID, despite the CDC and other agencies advising against doing so.</description></item></channel></rss>