<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elderly on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elderly/</link><description>Recent content in elderly on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 12:27:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elderly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Horror in Shanghai as elderly man taken to morgue in body bag while still alive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272711640e9c85e802d4f69/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 12:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272711640e9c85e802d4f69/</guid><description>An elderly Shanghai resident was mistakenly declared dead and taken to a morgue in a body bag, in the latest sign of dysfunction in the Covid-stricken city where millions of people remain under government-enforced lockdown.
Highlights Video shows the head of the man appearing from a yellow body bag. It is the latest sign of dysfunction in China&amp;rsquo;s most progressive and modern city. The video has since gone viral on China&amp;rsquo;s Twitter-like platform Weibo.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo, N.Y., police officers cleared of wrongdoing after shoving elderly man to ground at protest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253648afd9b40f53552fe11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 23:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253648afd9b40f53552fe11/</guid><description>Two police officers will be reinstated after an arbitrator ruled they didn&amp;rsquo;t violate use-of-force guidelines when they pushed a 75-year-old protester to the ground at a June 2020 protest over the murder of George Floyd.
Highlights Martin Gugino, 75, was pushed to the ground by two Buffalo police officers in June 2020. The incident occurred during racial injustice protests over the murder of George Floyd in Minneapolis. A news crew captured video of the incident in downtown Buffalo.</description></item><item><title>FBI: Americans Lost $1 Billion to Romance Scams in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bd563650f6c85d32cc422/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bd563650f6c85d32cc422/</guid><description>Organized Crime and Corruption Reporting Project
Highlights Romance scams have been on the rise since the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic and cost Americans more than US$1 billion in 2021 alone. Perpetrators mainly target women over 40 who are widowed, divorced, elderly or disabled. “The victim just wants connection and companionship. The bad guy generally wants cold hard cash,” the FBI warned. Phishing attacks and social engineering, like romance scams, remain two of the most common crimes on the web.</description></item></channel></rss>