<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>harm on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/harm/</link><description>Recent content in harm on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/harm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>South Africa court blocks Shell's oil exploration</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cd752dd98c5e0a5f17b170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cd752dd98c5e0a5f17b170/</guid><description>Environmentalists hail the ruling as a victory in their efforts to protect marine life.
Summary Shell had begun surveying the 6,000-sq-km area at the beginning of December after an earlier court judgement said it could go ahead. In that case, the judge said that those who wanted to prevent the survey had not provided enough evidence to show the environmental harm. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Court halts Shell’s offshore seismic survey along South Africa’s Wild Coast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cbb3289803cb49658c7deb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cbb3289803cb49658c7deb/</guid><description>The Grahamstown High Court in Makhanda on Tuesday granted an interdict against Shell’s seismic survey along the Wild Coast
Summary PRETORIA - The Grahamstown High Court in Makhanda on Tuesday granted an interdict against Shell’s seismic survey along the Wild CoastThis a second application made in the same court to stop oil multinational Shell’s seismic survey along South Africa’s Wild Coast. On Tuesday, Judge Gerald Bloem granted the applicants Amadiba, Dwesa-Cwebe, Port St Johns and Kei Mouth communities an interdict against Shell.</description></item></channel></rss>