<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>spike on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spike/</link><description>Recent content in spike on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spike/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Tsunami' of woes: U.S. school shootings spike amid pandemic stress</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620047a35716c231273334ce/</guid><description>Signs are emerging that the challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers studying the phenomenon worry it will only grow.
Highlights Signs are emerging that the stresses and challenges of the pandemic are worsening gun violence in American schools. Researchers who are studying the phenomenon worry it will only get worse. Already, campuses have been the site of 141 shootings so far during the 2021-22 school year - more than at any point in the previous decade.</description></item><item><title>Thieves in LA are looting freight trains filled with packages from UPS, FedEx and Amazon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e29b6261b3231b8530b60a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 10:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e29b6261b3231b8530b60a/</guid><description>Photos and videos showing piles of empty boxes littered alongside rail tracks in Los Angeles County, California have gone viral as shipping companies say they&amp;rsquo;ve seen a dramatic spike in railroad theft. Some of the boxes are packages from companies like UPS, Amazon and FedEx.
Summary Washington, DC (CNN) Photos and videos showing piles of empty boxes littered alongside rail tracks in Los Angeles County, California have gone viral as shipping companies say they&amp;rsquo;ve seen a dramatic spike in railroad theft.</description></item></channel></rss>