<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>week on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/week/</link><description>Recent content in week on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 10:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/week/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas power use to break all-time high next week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299de08d07c4d299e8f970b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 10:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299de08d07c4d299e8f970b/</guid><description>Power demand in Texas will break the all-time high next week as economic growth boosts overall usage and hot weather causes homes and businesses to crank up their air conditioners, the state&amp;rsquo;s power grid operator forecast on Thursday.
Highlights Power demand in Texas will break the all-time high next week as economic growth boosts overall usage and hot weather causes homes and businesses to crank up their air conditioners. High temperatures in Houston would remain in the low to mid 90s Fahrenheit (33.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine pleads for weapons as Russian onslaught threatens to turn the tide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293382d8d3ce6188618bced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 09:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293382d8d3ce6188618bced/</guid><description>As support among some European allies appears to waver, Kyiv calls for advanced rocket systems to hit Russia’s supply lines
Highlights US has agreed to provide more military weapons to Ukraine this week. Russia has threatened to use its own military equipment against rebels in Ukraine. But Britain and other European countries are yet to agree on a plan to provide weapons to Russia. Russian President Vladimir Putin is expected to meet with US President George W Bush on the sidelines of the war.</description></item><item><title>Average price of gas in Canada tops $2 a litre for first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284d4e5dc65dad40d988853/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 11:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284d4e5dc65dad40d988853/</guid><description>Gasoline prices are showing no signs of letting up as the average price in Canada tops $2 a litre for the first time. Natural Resources Canada says the average price across the country for regular gasoline hit $2.06 per litre on Monday for an all-time high.
Highlights Natural Resources Canada says the average price across the country for regular gasoline hit $2.06 per litre on Monday for an all-time high. The average was a nine-cent jump from the $1.</description></item><item><title>‘Potentially historic’ wildfire event threatens New Mexico, Southwest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277984aa8daed53f2b16f57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 10:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277984aa8daed53f2b16f57/</guid><description>The entire state of New Mexico is under a red flag warning for dangerous fire conditions
Highlights The National Weather Service is calling it a “dangerous, long duration and potentially historic critical fire weather event” Tinderbox conditions conducive to the rapid spread of blazes are expected to persist well into next week. New ignitions are also anticipated, which could rapidly grow out of control. The Calf Canyon fire became New Mexico’s second-largest on record this week, now the state&amp;rsquo;s second largest on record.</description></item><item><title>Russia threatens legal action if forced into sovereign debt default</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253c806eebc388546f07c2b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 06:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253c806eebc388546f07c2b/</guid><description>Finance Minister Anton Siluanov&amp;rsquo;s remarks to the pro-Kremlin Izvestia newspaper on Monday sharpened Moscow&amp;rsquo;s tone in its financial wrestling with the West.
Highlights Russia will take legal action if the West tries to force it to default on its sovereign debt, Finance Minister Anton Siluanov told the pro-Kremlin Izvestia newspaper. Russia faces its first sovereign external default in more than a century after it made arrangements to make an international bond repayment in roubles earlier this week, even though the payment was due in U.</description></item><item><title>Texas School District approves 4-day school week to deal with staffing shortages and funding issues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624df484773834ef80e5d0f2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 20:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624df484773834ef80e5d0f2/</guid><description>Officials said the decision was made in the hopes of retaining educators amid a national&amp;hellip;
Highlights Jasper ISD will shift to a four-day school week for the 2022-23 school year. The move is part of a larger effort to lower costs and improve the well-being of teachers. In 2016 Olfen ISD became the first Texas school district to change its schedule. Dime Box ISD in Central Texas opted to institute a four day school week, carving out Mondays as a &amp;ldquo;flex day&amp;rdquo; for students and staff.</description></item><item><title>Buddy, the cat mauled by two dogs in Frankford, heads to foster care</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249b9967a171534a1420b65/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249b9967a171534a1420b65/</guid><description>Buddy, the cat who was mauled by two dogs in Frankford, was taken into foster care Friday morning by a veterinarian who tended to him at the BluePearl Pet Hospital in Philadelphia. The pet will be monitored at his foster home before the Pennsylvania SPCA possibly puts him up for adoption.
Highlights The Pennsylvania SPCA said it will monitor Buddy&amp;rsquo;s progress at his foster home before possibly putting him up for adoption.</description></item><item><title>Ford, GM to halt production at two Michigan plants due to parts shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624733bbd66db14bbfec9a70/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 17:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624733bbd66db14bbfec9a70/</guid><description>Ford Motor Co and General Motors will each halt production next week at a Michigan plant due to parts shortages, the two companies said separately on Thursday.
Highlights Ford Motor Co and General Motors will each halt production next week at a Michigan plant due to parts shortages. The auto industry is grappling with a global chip shortage triggered by the COVID-19 pandemic, forcing companies to cut production. Ford said it would suspend production at its Flat Rock Assembly Plant next week, where it builds the Mustang, due to the global semiconductor shortage.</description></item><item><title>Disney workers plan walkout to protest 'Don't Say Gay' bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232364020ca781b0a00ff01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 19:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232364020ca781b0a00ff01/</guid><description>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — Disney workers are planning walkouts during their breaks every day this week to protest CEO Bob Chapek’s slow response in publicly criticizing Florida legislation that critics have dubbed the “Don’t Say Gay” bill.
Highlights Disney workers are planning walkouts during their breaks every day this week to protest CEO Bob Chapek’s slow response in publicly criticizing Florida legislation that critics have dubbed the “Don’t Say Gay” bill.</description></item><item><title>Colombia decriminalizes abortion in historic ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62147f667f240bddea38d20a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 06:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62147f667f240bddea38d20a/</guid><description>Colombian court decriminalizes abortion for first 24 weeks of pregnancy. Restrictions will remain in place if women request an abortion after the 24th week of gestation. Women’s rights organizations had been asking to decriminalize abortion for years.
Highlights Women in Colombia are free to end pregnancies until the 24th week after insemination. Women were only allowed to abort pregnancies in cases of rape, or if the life of the mother or unborn baby was seriously compromised.</description></item><item><title>YouTube permanently bans Fox News host Dan Bongino</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f23658373f3d0dddf913cb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 06:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f23658373f3d0dddf913cb/</guid><description>Fox News Channel host Dan Bongino on Wednesday became among the most-followed conservative personalities to be permanently banned from YouTube, a week after the Google-owned video service said he had posted COVID-19 misinformation.
Summary REUTERS/Jonathan ErnstJan 26 (Reuters) - Fox News Channel host Dan Bongino on Wednesday became among the most-followed conservative personalities to be permanently banned from YouTube, a week after the Google-owned (GOOGL.O) video service said he had posted COVID-19 misinformation.</description></item><item><title>DA for Atlanta area granted special grand jury to probe Trump's election interference</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efe681c9882968645f49e5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efe681c9882968645f49e5/</guid><description>An Atlanta-area district attorney investigating former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s efforts to overturn the 2020 election results in Georgia will be allowed to seat a special grand jury this spring.
Summary (CNN) An Atlanta-area district attorney investigating former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s efforts to overturn the 2020 election results in Georgia will be allowed to seat a special grand jury this spring. Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis requested last week to seat a special grand jury starting May 2.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 patient whose family sued to keep him on ventilator dies after transfer from Mercy Hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 07:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee4eb7926641bf797c50be/</guid><description>Scott Quiner, a COVID-19 patient from Buffalo, Minnesota, whose wife sued Mercy Hospital in Coon Rapids to keep him on a ventilator, died Saturday morning at a Texas hospital, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney confirmed.
Summary &amp;ldquo;On behalf of the family of Scott Quiner, I would like to thank the public for the outpouring of love and support during this difficult time,&amp;rdquo; Holsten said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;The family now requests privacy while they grieve the loss of their beloved husband and father.</description></item><item><title>A 74-year-old woman spent 27 years in prison for a murder she didn't commit. This week she was exonerated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3ded572a871c2c5157005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e3ded572a871c2c5157005/</guid><description>A Tennessee woman who was wrongfully convicted of murdering her great-niece and spent 27 years in prison, was exonerated this week.
Summary (CNN) A Tennessee woman who was wrongfully convicted of murdering her great-niece and spent 27 years in prison, was exonerated this week. On June 26, 1987, Joyce Watkins, now 74, and her boyfriend at the time, Charlie Dunn, went to pick up Watkins four-year-old great-niece, Brandi, in Kentucky, according to a report filed with the Davidson County Criminal Court.</description></item><item><title>Chicago schools cancel classes for fourth day as union fight hits second week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc743e876618a0aae5455a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc743e876618a0aae5455a/</guid><description>Chicago school leaders canceled classes for the fourth day Monday as a standoff with the local teachers&amp;rsquo; union over Covid-19 protocols entered its second week.
Summary Chicago school leaders canceled classes for the fourth consecutive day on Monday as a standoff with the local teachers&amp;rsquo; union over remote learning and other Covid-19 safety protocols entered its second week. Later that day, however, Lightfoot appeared to strike a different tone, tweeting that teachers&amp;rsquo; union leaders were &amp;ldquo;not listening.</description></item><item><title>US children hospitalized with COVID in record numbers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</guid><description>The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers
Summary The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbersSEATTLE &amp;ndash; The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers, and experts lament that most of the youngsters are not vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Myanmar model-actor Paing Takhon named world's 'Most Handsome Face,' sentenced to jail in same week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8e70700b2c026cf5ff96/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8e70700b2c026cf5ff96/</guid><description>Model and actor Paing Takhon was sentenced to three years in jail for speaking out during protests in Myanmar, in the same week he was named the “Most Handsome Face” of 2021 by entertainment site TC Candler. Takhon was named the world’s “Most Handsome Face” of 2021, coinciding with the model and actor’s sentencing this week for his support of the anti-coup protests in Myanmar earlier this year. Takhon rose to global prominence at the beginning of 2021 when he became known as the “hot monk” through viral social media posts.</description></item><item><title>Massachusetts state trooper fired over Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID vaccine mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 09:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</guid><description>Summary A Massachusetts state trooper was fired this week for not complying with Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate, which required more than 40,000 Executive Department employees to be fully immunized by mid-October. The development comes a week after MassLive reported the state had fired at least 60 Department of Correction workers for noncompliance. A volunteer at the Edith Nourse Rogers Memorial Veterans Hospital and the Special Olympics, the fired trooper “was never disciplined in any way shape or form” by the Massachusetts State Police prior to Baker’s vaccine mandate, SPAM said.</description></item></channel></rss>