<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>week on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/week/</link><description>Recent content in week on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/week/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US children hospitalized with COVID in record numbers</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d07aa14b85b0c2f444f897/</guid><description>The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers
Summary The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbersSEATTLE &amp;ndash; The omicron-fueled surge that is sending COVID-19 cases rocketing in the U.S. is putting children in the hospital in record numbers, and experts lament that most of the youngsters are not vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Myanmar model-actor Paing Takhon named world's 'Most Handsome Face,' sentenced to jail in same week</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ce8e70700b2c026cf5ff96/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ce8e70700b2c026cf5ff96/</guid><description>Model and actor Paing Takhon was sentenced to three years in jail for speaking out during protests in Myanmar, in the same week he was named the “Most Handsome Face” of 2021 by entertainment site TC Candler. Takhon was named the world’s “Most Handsome Face” of 2021, coinciding with the model and actor’s sentencing this week for his support of the anti-coup protests in Myanmar earlier this year. Takhon rose to global prominence at the beginning of 2021 when he became known as the “hot monk” through viral social media posts.</description></item><item><title>Massachusetts state trooper fired over Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID vaccine mandate</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 09:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c82f2a0b7c21a03f8b4d56/</guid><description>Summary A Massachusetts state trooper was fired this week for not complying with Gov. Charlie Baker’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate, which required more than 40,000 Executive Department employees to be fully immunized by mid-October. The development comes a week after MassLive reported the state had fired at least 60 Department of Correction workers for noncompliance. A volunteer at the Edith Nourse Rogers Memorial Veterans Hospital and the Special Olympics, the fired trooper “was never disciplined in any way shape or form” by the Massachusetts State Police prior to Baker’s vaccine mandate, SPAM said.</description></item></channel></rss>