<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>article on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/article/</link><description>Recent content in article on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 17:13:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian Media: "Vladimir Putin has assumed a historic responsibility for the final solution of the Ukrainian question"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623760a5871577f2f340a45a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 17:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623760a5871577f2f340a45a/</guid><description>A quickly deleted article referred to the independence of Belarus and Ukraine as a &amp;quot;terrible catastrophe.&amp;quot;
Highlights Opinion piece seemingly published by Russian news agency RIA Novosti before being quickly taken down. Petr Akopov wrote that Russia is &amp;ldquo;restoring its unity&amp;rdquo; and providing a &amp;ldquo;solution to the Ukrainian question&amp;rdquo; in its invasion of Ukraine. The article was recorded by the Internet Archive&amp;rsquo;s Wayback Machine before it was taken offline. It referred to the 1991 declarations of independence by Belarus and Ukraine as a &amp;ldquo;terrible catastrophe&amp;rdquo; and an &amp;ldquo;unnatural dislocation&amp;rdquo; Author theorized that Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s statehood would not be liquidated if Russia succeeds in its goals, but would instead be &amp;ldquo;reorganized, re-established and returned to its natural state&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Omicron was in Nova Scotia wastewater before it was identified in South Africa</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd555f1aa833d1cef889ca/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd555f1aa833d1cef889ca/</guid><description>&amp;lsquo;Our team detected Omicron, retrospectively, in Nova Scotia wastewater in mid-November,&amp;rsquo; Dalhousie researchers say
Summary Share this Story: Omicron was in Nova Scotia wastewater before it was identified in South AfricaOmicron was in Nova Scotia wastewater before it was identified in South Africa &amp;lsquo;Our team detected Omicron, retrospectively, in Nova Scotia wastewater in mid-November,&amp;rsquo; Dalhousie researchers say Photo by Andrew Vaughan / Canadian PressArticle content New data from researchers at Dalhousie University show that Omicron was in Nova Scotia wastewater weeks before it was identified by the province — and even before the new COVID-19 variant was reported by South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Calgary therapists hail 'legalization' of medicinal psychedelic drugs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dab258abc2b2c546fb3c9c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dab258abc2b2c546fb3c9c/</guid><description>Local therapists say Ottawa’s move allowing physicians to prescribe psychedelics is a “seismic shift” towards legalizing their medicinal use.
Summary Share this Story: Therapists hail &amp;rsquo;legalization&amp;rsquo; of medicinal psychedelic drugsTherapists hail &amp;rsquo;legalization&amp;rsquo; of medicinal psychedelic drugs Photo by Jim Wells/PostmediaArticle content Local therapists say Ottawa’s move allowing physicians to prescribe psychedelics is a “seismic shift” towards legalizing their medicinal use. Advertisement Story continues below This advertisement has not loaded yet, but your article continues below.</description></item></channel></rss>