<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weeks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weeks/</link><description>Recent content in weeks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 05:17:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weeks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde school district police chief won't be sworn in Tuesday as city council meeting is postponed for funerals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295a4d71f33fbe27fc809f3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 05:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295a4d71f33fbe27fc809f3/</guid><description>With funerals for victims of last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting now taking place in Uvalde, Texas, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor has postponed a city council meeting at which new members &amp;ndash; including school district police chief Pedro &amp;quot;Pete&amp;quot; Arredondo &amp;ndash; were to be sworn in.
Highlights With funerals for victims of last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting now taking place in Uvalde, Texas, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor postpones a city council meeting. Mayor Don McLaughlin: &amp;ldquo;Our focus on Tuesday is on our families who lost loved ones&amp;rdquo; 19 school children and two teachers were killed in two adjoining classrooms at Robb Elementary by an 18-year-old gunman.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma passes bill banning most abortions after conception.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287d9d47d9a377375d72171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 18:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287d9d47d9a377375d72171/</guid><description>The state&amp;rsquo;s ban, its third in recent months, has been called the strictest in the US.
Highlights The state&amp;rsquo;s ban, its third in recent months, has been called the strictest in the US. It is around the time cardiac activity can be detected in the embryo, and before many women realise they are pregnant. But the bill bans abortion even earlier than Texas, where it is not legal after six weeks.</description></item><item><title>Weekly jobless claims fell to 166,000 last week, the lowest level since 1968</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f2a38e74597f29f4fe741/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 18:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f2a38e74597f29f4fe741/</guid><description>Initial filings for unemployment dropped to 166,000, well below the Dow Jones estimate of 200,000 and 5,000 below the previous week&amp;rsquo;s total
Highlights Initial filings for unemployment dropped to 166,000, well below the Dow Jones estimate of 200,000 and 5,000 below the previous week&amp;rsquo;s total. The Labor Department revised claims from 2017 to 2021 and changed the seasonal factors it is using to calculate the numbers. The numbers nevertheless reflect a jobs market that is subject to a severe worker shortage.</description></item><item><title>Missing hiker's body found in LA park with dog by his side</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624948e4e125d5c23b8798db/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624948e4e125d5c23b8798db/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — A hiker who went missing two weeks ago was found dead in Griffith&amp;hellip;
Highlights Oscar Alejandro Hernandez, 29, was reported missing on March 16. His body was found Thursday night in a remote area of the sprawling urban park. His dog, King, was alive but emaciated. Hernandez was found with his dog by his side, authorities said. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>4-year-old Israeli child tests positive for polio, first case since 1989</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62268352c4ca42fae2677c3e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 22:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62268352c4ca42fae2677c3e/</guid><description>The case in Jerusalem comes after a reported outbreak in Malawi, which was linked to one circulating in Pakistan, where it is still endemic.
Highlights A four-year-old Israeli child from Jerusalem tested positive for polio after it was revealed he was not vaccinated against the life-threatening disease. The patient seems to have been infected with a strain that has undergone a change and could cause disease in those who are not vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>CDC to consider increasing time between vaccine doses to lower risk of heart inflammation – Boston 25 News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204e5372ded2e107ea07b72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204e5372ded2e107ea07b72/</guid><description>CDC is considering changing vaccine guidance to lengthen the time in between doses of certain vaccines. Time between the first two doses of the mRNA COVID-19 vaccines appears to reduce the risk of myocarditis, a rare type of heart
Highlights The CDC is considering changing vaccine guidance to lengthen the time in between doses of certain vaccines. The changes would apply to the Pfizer and Moderna COVID-19 vaccines, which use the mRNA technology.</description></item><item><title>Taking a step back: US colleges returning to online classes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</guid><description>With COVID-19 cases surging just as students are about to return from winter break, dozens of U.S. colleges are moving classes online again for at least the first week or so of the semester — and some warn it could stretch longer if the wave of infection doesn’t subside soon.
Summary The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online. The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online.</description></item></channel></rss>