<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>18 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/18/</link><description>Recent content in 18 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:13:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/18/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Official Age of Adulthood in Japan Lowered to 18</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</guid><description>The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. This makes it possible for 18- or 19-year-olds to sign a smartphone contract or take out a loan without parental consent, but also means that they need to take responsibility for such decisions.
Highlights The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. It means that 18- or 19-year-olds will be able to sign a contract for a smartphone or credit card, lease an apartment, or enter an expensive loan contract for an automobile or English conversation school, without parental consent.</description></item><item><title>‘Bloodthirsty’ squirrel attacks 18 people in Welsh village in two-day Christmas rampage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccb04f8c4b2de752610c49/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 19:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccb04f8c4b2de752610c49/</guid><description>‘Those teeth could bite right through a child’s tiny finger’, said the woman who put an end to the attacks
Summary A squirrel’s reign of terror over a sleepy Welsh village has been brought to an end after it bit 18 residents leaving some too scared to leave their homes. The attacks were ended when Ms Reynolds set out a cage in her garden leaving a handful of peanuts, Stripe’s favourite snack, as bait.</description></item></channel></rss>