<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>europe on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/europe/</link><description>Recent content in europe on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Expert: Monkeypox likely spread by sex at 2 raves in Europe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bea51aa880e9a5f5f75a6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bea51aa880e9a5f5f75a6/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — A leading adviser to the World Health Organization described the unprecedented outbreak of monkeypox in developed countries as “a random event” that might be explained by sexual behavior at two recent raves in Europe.
Highlights Leading doctor who chairs a World Health Organization expert group described the unprecedented outbreak of monkeypox in developed countries as “a random event” that might be explained by risky sexual behavior at two recent mass events in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Russian market cracks 17% as Ukraine tensions intensify</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62155feede8b75074051dd03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 22:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62155feede8b75074051dd03/</guid><description>Russia warned there were no firm plans for a summit between US President Joe Biden and Putin. In another development, reports emerged that Russian forces killed a group of five saboteurs who breached the country&amp;rsquo;s southwest border from Ukraine on Monday.
Highlights Russian stock market sank 17 per cent in Monday&amp;rsquo;s trade as President Vladimir Putin said his country was mulling recognising the independence of east Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s two separatist republics. Russia is one of the biggest producers of Crude oil, and the status can lead to a sharp spike of more than $100 and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Germany halts approval of gas pipeline Nord Stream 2 after Russia’s actions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214fdb97c3918e03af23774/</guid><description>Germany on Tuesday halted the certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline designed to bring natural gas from Russia directly to Europe.
Highlights Germany halts certification of the Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline to bring gas to Europe. The pipeline is designed to bring natural gas directly to Europe from Russia. Germany&amp;rsquo;s president said the country would not accept the recognition of the two pro-Russian separatist regions in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Germany has 'betrayed' Ukraine, Kiev mayor Vitali Klitschko declares</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0e38eec650aed9f88b2c0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 06:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0e38eec650aed9f88b2c0/</guid><description>The ex-heavyweight champ today slated Germany for its &amp;lsquo;failure to provide assistance&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;betrayal of friends&amp;rsquo; as fears of a Russian invasion of Ukraine climb ever higher.
Summary Former world heavyweight boxing champion and Mayor of Kiev Vitali Klitschko has accused Germany of &amp;lsquo;betraying&amp;rsquo; Ukraine over its support of a Russian gas pipeline and refusal to export arms to his country. &amp;lsquo;There is huge disappointment in Ukraine that the federal government is sticking to Nord Stream 2 and that it does not want to supply defence weapons,&amp;rsquo; Klitschko wrote in Bild.</description></item><item><title>Djokovic travelled across Europe before Australia trip, at odds with declaration</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dea6bf88b0796e258e0ab3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dea6bf88b0796e258e0ab3/</guid><description>Novak Djokovic was in Serbia in the two weeks before flying to the Australian Open from Spain, according to three Belgrade residents, whose accounts to Reuters backed social media posts that contradict information contained in his immigration declaration on arrival in Melbourne.
Summary Djokovic, the world number one in men&amp;rsquo;s tennis, is in Australia to play in next week&amp;rsquo;s Australian Open. Three separate social media posts have purported to show Djokovic photos and video of Djokovic in Belgrade and were posted on Dec.</description></item></channel></rss>