<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>weapons on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weapons/</link><description>Recent content in weapons on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 22:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/weapons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US ‘doomsday plane’ made four-hour flight following Putin’s nuclear weapons threat</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621febe0ac02ebb02812087d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 22:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621febe0ac02ebb02812087d/</guid><description>The Boeing 747 modified to provide a flying command centre in the event of a nuclear conflict conducted a mission with other early warning jets but Washington has underlined it sees &amp;rsquo;no reason&amp;rsquo; to change its nuclear posture
Highlights $200m ‘doomsday plane’ designed to act as a flying control centre in the event of a nuclear conflict was sent on a four-hour training sortie on Monday. The modified Boeing 747 has the call sign “GORDO15” and conducted a mission with other early warning jets.</description></item><item><title>Russia moves more troops westward amid Ukraine tensions | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 09:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7d32f6d51a0a1bb96fb5e/</guid><description>MOSCOW (AP) — Russia is a sending an unspecified number of troops from the country’s far east to Belarus for major war games, officials said Tuesday, a deployment that will further beef up Russian military presence near Ukraine amid Western fears of a planned invasion.
Summary Russia has concentrated an estimated 100,000 troops with tanks and other heavy weapons near Ukraine in what the West fears could be a prelude to an invasion.</description></item></channel></rss>