<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>block on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/block/</link><description>Recent content in block on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:12:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/block/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supreme Court declines to block elite high school’s new admissions policy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269250de27efce9be21a1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269250de27efce9be21a1ca/</guid><description>The Supreme Court declined to block a top-rated high school from using an admissions plan that a community group says discriminates against Asian Americans.
Highlights Thomas Jefferson High School for Science and Technology changed its admission system two years ago. The school did away with a requirement to take three standardized tests, submit an essay and get teacher recommendations. The new system requires applicants to have taken a rigorous load of middle school courses with a high grade-point average.</description></item><item><title>Crypto exchanges resist call to block Russian users</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ea87bda4813d65713911d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 23:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ea87bda4813d65713911d/</guid><description>Some large exchanges have said blanket bans on Russia-based addresses would unfairly hurt innocent Russians.
Highlights Binance, Kraken and Kraken have said they will comply with U.S. sanctions. Some exchanges say blanket bans on Russia-based addresses would unfairly hurt innocent Russians. Some experts say the focus on crypto as a platform for sanctions evasion is misguided. Still, the markets are not big enough to absorb sanctions-abating levels of currency, says Chainalysis&amp;rsquo; co-head of public policy at Chainalysis.</description></item></channel></rss>