<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dead on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dead/</link><description>Recent content in dead on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 23:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Driver, 59, dies after hitting 11-foot alligator on Florida roadway, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cfb48ff73e6d9cf8aa089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 23:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cfb48ff73e6d9cf8aa089/</guid><description>A man was killed after hitting an 11-foot alligator while driving in Florida early Thursday, authorities said.
Highlights John Hopkins, 59, was headed eastbound on Country Road 672, about two miles west of Country Road 39, in Lithia when he struck the alligator in the roadway at 12:30 a.m. The impact caused his car to veer off the road and flip into a ditch. A motorist passing through the area noticed the car in the ditch and called 911.</description></item><item><title>Bernie Madoff’s sister and her husband found dead in apparent murder-suicide | US crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621357b98eb210085db2d598/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621357b98eb210085db2d598/</guid><description>Palm Beach county sheriff says Sondra Wiener, 87, and 90-year-old husband Marvin Wiener found dead on Thursday
Highlights Sondra Wiener, 87, and her 90-year-old husband Marvin Wiener were found unresponsive with gunshot wounds on Thursday afternoon. Palm Beach county sheriff’s office says it appears to be a murder-suicide. Madoff was known for orchestrating a massive Ponzi scheme that wiped out people&amp;rsquo;s fortunes and ruined charities. After pleading guilty in 2009 to fraud and other charges, he was sentenced to 150 years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Jean-Luc Brunel: Jeffrey Epstein associate is found dead in French prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211408fadc97a9c84686948/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 19:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211408fadc97a9c84686948/</guid><description>Brunel went to ground after Epstein&amp;rsquo;s death, but in October 2019 he, and Epstein&amp;rsquo;s former girlfriend Ghislaine Maxwell, were traced to the Brazilian Riviera - and he was arrested the following year in Paris.
Highlights Jean-Luc Brunel, 76, was detained in December 2020 as part of an inquiry into allegations of rape, sexual assault and sexual harassment. Brunel had founded a modelling management company with Jeffrey Epstein but he had denied any wrongdoing related to his association with him.</description></item></channel></rss>