<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dead on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dead/</link><description>Recent content in dead on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:07:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dead/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apparent active shooter at medical facility in Tulsa, Oklahoma.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298295f44b6a5935a8f8576/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 03:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298295f44b6a5935a8f8576/</guid><description>UPDATE: Saint Francis Health System has released the following statement concerning the shooting: Saint Francis Health System is grieving the loss of four members of our family. As a faith based organization, the only recourse we have at this moment is to pray while we navigate this tragedy. Out of respect for the families, we are not commenting on or releasing names of those lost or injured at this time.</description></item><item><title>Rosaries, bouquets and tiny caskets: Uvalde begins to bury its dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295f7758062616263523ef6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295f7758062616263523ef6/</guid><description>In a Texas town scarred by gun massacre, anger and grief gives way to a relentless cycle of mourning as two weeks of funerals begin.
Highlights Funeral home in U.S. reopens for mourners for victims of U.N. school shooting. “There’s going to be a lot of tears and sadness, but as we continue to celebrate their lives, they will turn into tears of joy,” priest says. Funeral director: “It&amp;rsquo;s okay to be angry.</description></item><item><title>Agency: 1 dead, 7 injured in Oklahoma festival shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293b7385dbbf70e01ae1e39/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 18:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6293b7385dbbf70e01ae1e39/</guid><description>Authorities say one person was killed and seven were injured in a shooting early Sunday at an outdoor festival in eastern Oklahoma
Highlights One person killed, seven injured in shooting early Sunday at outdoor festival in eastern Oklahoma. Two juveniles among those shot at Memorial Day event near Taft, about 10 miles (16 kilometers) southeast of Tulsa. Witness describes frantic people running for cover as gunfire erupted. Witnesses said argument preceded the gunfire just after midnight, Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigation says.</description></item><item><title>11-Year-Old Survivor of Uvalde Massacre Put Blood on Herself and Played Dead, Aunt Says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62914c1a3d3d46f2e3d4ba80/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 22:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62914c1a3d3d46f2e3d4ba80/</guid><description>The family of a girl who survived the school shooting in Uvalde, Texas says the 4th grader put blood on herself and played dead after the gunman entered her&amp;hellip;
Highlights Miah Cerrillo, 11, survived the massacre at Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, on Tuesday. Her aunt and godmother said the 4th grader is struggling to cope and telling them what she witnessed during the shooting. Blanca Rivera said Miah&amp;rsquo;s teacher, Irma Garcia, was one of the two teachers killed.</description></item><item><title>4 people fall off California cliff; 1 dead and 2 badly hurt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628caef268ea097dc6f90e4b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628caef268ea097dc6f90e4b/</guid><description>Authorities say four people fell off a Southern California ocean cliff in the early morning darkness
Highlights Four people fell off a Southern California ocean cliff before dawn Monday morning. A 25-year-old man from Los Angeles died at the scene, police say. A fourth person, a man who suffered minor injuries, managed to climb back up from the beach below and alert a passing officer. Two women were airlifted from beach and each hospitalized in critical condition.</description></item><item><title>As many as 8 dead in mass shooting at upstate New York supermarket: Law enforcement source - ABC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628029c58f94ee832d1c0140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 22:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628029c58f94ee832d1c0140/</guid><description>Reported mass shooting in upstate New York TOPS Friendly Markets
Highlights At least 10 people are dead and another 3 wounded after a mass shooting at a supermarket in Buffalo, New York, police say. The 18-year-old male suspect entered the supermarket shortly after 2:30 p.m. and fired a rifle, law enforcement officials say. One of the victims was a retired Buffalo police officer working security at the store, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Pittsburgh Mass Shooting: 11 shot, 2 juveniles dead in Easter shooting at Airbnb in East Allegheny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c3dbfdd6f8ad9f68532c1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c3dbfdd6f8ad9f68532c1/</guid><description>Pittsburgh Police received multiple ShotSpotter alerts just after 12:30 a.m. in the 800 block of Suismon Street in the East Allegheny neighborhood of the North Side. Police say a large party was happening at the Airbnb
Highlights Pittsburgh Police received multiple ShotSpotter alerts just after 12:30 a.m. in the 800 block of Suismon Street. Police say a large party was happening at the Airbnb with as many as 200 people in attendance.</description></item><item><title>Red is dead: Russian anti-war protesters fly a new flag for peace</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ab6d3694adbf4ade88e50/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 09:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ab6d3694adbf4ade88e50/</guid><description>Seeing the tricolour as tainted, they took the ‘blood’ out to leave blue and white, then found others had done so too
Highlights When Putin’s forces invaded Ukraine, anti-war Russians joined protests around the world. Kai Katonina and his friends came up with a white, blue and white striped flag. It has since been embraced on social media as well as by Russian protesters on the streets. The new Russian flag has also drawn the ire of the Kremlin, and officials last week proposed banning it as an “extremist” symbol.</description></item><item><title>Driver, 59, dies after hitting 11-foot alligator on Florida roadway, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cfb48ff73e6d9cf8aa089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 23:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cfb48ff73e6d9cf8aa089/</guid><description>A man was killed after hitting an 11-foot alligator while driving in Florida early Thursday, authorities said.
Highlights John Hopkins, 59, was headed eastbound on Country Road 672, about two miles west of Country Road 39, in Lithia when he struck the alligator in the roadway at 12:30 a.m. The impact caused his car to veer off the road and flip into a ditch. A motorist passing through the area noticed the car in the ditch and called 911.</description></item><item><title>Bernie Madoff’s sister and her husband found dead in apparent murder-suicide | US crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621357b98eb210085db2d598/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 09:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621357b98eb210085db2d598/</guid><description>Palm Beach county sheriff says Sondra Wiener, 87, and 90-year-old husband Marvin Wiener found dead on Thursday
Highlights Sondra Wiener, 87, and her 90-year-old husband Marvin Wiener were found unresponsive with gunshot wounds on Thursday afternoon. Palm Beach county sheriff’s office says it appears to be a murder-suicide. Madoff was known for orchestrating a massive Ponzi scheme that wiped out people&amp;rsquo;s fortunes and ruined charities. After pleading guilty in 2009 to fraud and other charges, he was sentenced to 150 years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Jean-Luc Brunel: Jeffrey Epstein associate is found dead in French prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211408fadc97a9c84686948/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 19:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211408fadc97a9c84686948/</guid><description>Brunel went to ground after Epstein&amp;rsquo;s death, but in October 2019 he, and Epstein&amp;rsquo;s former girlfriend Ghislaine Maxwell, were traced to the Brazilian Riviera - and he was arrested the following year in Paris.
Highlights Jean-Luc Brunel, 76, was detained in December 2020 as part of an inquiry into allegations of rape, sexual assault and sexual harassment. Brunel had founded a modelling management company with Jeffrey Epstein but he had denied any wrongdoing related to his association with him.</description></item></channel></rss>