<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>meta on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/meta/</link><description>Recent content in meta on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 11:12:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Meta and YouTube block Russian state media from monetizing on its platforms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b5c60bfd32b9f3d9e6d9f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 11:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b5c60bfd32b9f3d9e6d9f/</guid><description>YouTube said Saturday that it will temporarily halt the ability of a number of Russian channels, including state-sponsored RT, to monetize their content on the platform.
Highlights YouTube said it will temporarily halt the ability of a number of Russian channels, including state-sponsored RT, to monetize their content on the platform. It will also be &amp;ldquo;significantly limiting&amp;rdquo; recommendations to those channels. The company said the channels are affiliated with recent sanctions, and that it has restricted access to RT and other channels in Ukraine in response to a request from that country&amp;rsquo;s government.</description></item><item><title>Lawsuit aiming to break up Facebook group Meta can go ahead, US court rules | Meta</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfea45e2a3897f563787aa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfea45e2a3897f563787aa/</guid><description>The Federal Trade Commission wants to force sale of Instagram and WhatsApp
Summary The US competition watchdog can proceed with a breakup lawsuit against Facebook’s owner, a federal judge has ruled. Mark Zuckerberg’s Meta, the parent of Facebook, Instagram and WhatsApp, had asked a court to dismiss an antitrust complaint brought by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) for the second time. However, Judge James Boasberg said on Tuesday that the FTC’s revised lawsuit should be allowed to proceed.</description></item></channel></rss>