<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deadly on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deadly/</link><description>Recent content in deadly on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 06:12:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deadly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Governor saw deadly arrest video months before prosecutors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291bd2b9981fdbc4f19f1ed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 06:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291bd2b9981fdbc4f19f1ed/</guid><description>BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — With racial tensions still simmering over the killing of George Floyd, Louisiana Gov. John Bel Edwards and his top lawyers gathered in a state police conference room in October 2020 to prepare for the fallout from a troubling case closer to home: troopers’ deadly arrest of Ronald Greene.
Highlights Governor saw deadly arrest video months before prosecutors had video, AP finds. Video showed a bruised and bloody Ronald Greene going limp and drawing his final breaths.</description></item><item><title>Shooting with 'multiple' victims reported at Kissimmee-area Target</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a5b0a486829444faea2f0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 09:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a5b0a486829444faea2f0/</guid><description>One person is dead, and three others were injured after a shooting at a Target store Wednesday night in Kissimmee, Florida.
Highlights One person is dead, and three others injured after a shooting at a Target store in Kissimmee, Florida. Two of Osceola County Sheriff Marcos R. Lopez said two of his deputies were involved in the shooting and are OK. The parking lot was blocked off with yellow investigative tape and more than a dozen vehicles were in the area, according to a FOX 35 crew.</description></item><item><title>Houston Police: Woman shoots ex when he shows up with new girlfriend to child custody exchange</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62590def26affbddb9ca6bf4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62590def26affbddb9ca6bf4/</guid><description>According to investigators, Harris and the man were in a prior dating relationship and have two children together when the victim was bringing on the children back from a visit and had his current girlfriend in the car.
Highlights Keshante Shamirra Harris, 27, is charged with aggravated robbery with a deadly weapon and deadly conduct. Harris and Aaron Konte Williams were in a prior dating relationship and have two children together.</description></item><item><title>The next Covid variant will be more contagious than omicron, but the question is whether it will be more deadly, WHO says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</guid><description>A top WHO official warned against theories that the virus will continue to mutate into milder strains that make people less sick than earlier variants.
Summary RT: Maria Van Kerkhove, Head a.i. Emerging Diseases and Zoonosis at the World Health Organization (WHO), speaks during a news conference on the situation of the coronavirus at the United Nations in Geneva, Switzerland, January 29, 2020. The next Covid-19 variant that will rise to world attention will be more contagious than omicron, but the real question scientists need to answer is whether or not it will be more deadly, World Health Organization officials said Tuesday.</description></item></channel></rss>