<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bolsonaro on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bolsonaro/</link><description>Recent content in bolsonaro on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bolsonaro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Covid ‘denialist’ and Bolsonaro ally Olavo de Carvalho died of virus, says daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f08f2a2016ec4c10350c28/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f08f2a2016ec4c10350c28/</guid><description>Rightwing radical was a towering figure in Brazil who was adored and abhorred in equal measure by millions of followers and foes
Summary Olavo de Carvalho, the coronavirus-denying mentor of Jair Bolsonaro and Brazil’s radical right, has died in the United States, with one of his children citing Covid-19 as the cause. The statement did not say how Carvalho – a former astrologer who repeatedly trivialized Covid as the “moronavirus” – had died.</description></item><item><title>President Bolsonaro admitted to São Paulo hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d39c3079c839bfce5cb49e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d39c3079c839bfce5cb49e/</guid><description>Bolsonaro left the Santa Catarina coast by helicopter bound for Joinville, plane with his wife Michelle Bolsonaro
Summary The President&amp;rsquo;s doctor says he was hospitalized early this morning with suspected intestinal obstruction. RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL - Bolsonaro left the Santa Catarina coast by helicopter bound for Joinville, where he boarded the presidential plane with his wife Michelle Bolsonaro and daughter Laura. According to reports, Bolsonaro is in the Vila Nova Star Hospital in São Paulo.</description></item></channel></rss>