<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>court on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/court/</link><description>Recent content in court on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 15:09:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/court/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Donald Trump to testify in New York investigation into his business practices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a20cf9652e920c28a272d5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 15:09:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a20cf9652e920c28a272d5/</guid><description>Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr will also testify in attorney general Letitia James’ inquiry into Trump Organization
Highlights Former president Donald Trump will testify under oath on 15 July in New York attorney general Letitia James’s investigation into his business practices. His daughter Ivanka Trump and son Donald Trump Jr will also testify in the investigation. The investigation has homed in on whether the Trump Organization misstated the values of its real estate properties to obtain favorable loans and tax deductions.</description></item><item><title>U.S. wins case to seize Russian superyacht in Fiji, sails away</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a04b163ca29fca583efa9d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a04b163ca29fca583efa9d/</guid><description>The United States won a legal battle on Tuesday to seize a Russian-owned superyacht in Fiji and wasted no time in taking command of the $325 million vessel.
Highlights Fiji&amp;rsquo;s Supreme Court lifts a stay order preventing the U.S. from seizing the superyacht Amadea. The Justice Department removed the motorized vessel within an hour or two of the court’s ruling, possibly to ensure the yacht didn’t get entangled in any further legal action.</description></item><item><title>California bees can be fish and have the same protections, a court has ruled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f159efb36cf783ac93b07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:09:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f159efb36cf783ac93b07/</guid><description>A fishy ruling from California: A California court has ruled bees can legally be considered fish under specific circumstances.
Highlights The ruling reversed an earlier judgment which found bumblebees could not be considered &amp;ldquo;fish&amp;rdquo; under the California Endangered Species Act. Notably, invertebrates are absent from the list of protected species. California&amp;rsquo;s Third District Court of Appeal ruled bees can legally be considered fish under specific circumstances. The ruling reverses an earlier ruling which found the bumblebee was not allowed to be classified as a fish under the endangered species Act of 2062 and 2067.</description></item><item><title>Harvey Weinstein’s rape conviction upheld by appeals court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629919579f8d18e53b7203d8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629919579f8d18e53b7203d8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A New York appeals court on Thursday upheld Harvey Weinstein’s rape conviction and 23-year prison sentence, rejecting the former movie mogul’s claim that the judge at his landmark #MeToo trial unfairly allowed women to testify about allegations that weren’t part of the case.
Highlights Harvey Weinstein was convicted in New York in February 2020 of forcibly performing oral sex on a TV and film production assistant, Mimi Haley, in 2006 and raping an aspiring actress in 2013.</description></item><item><title>Hinckley, who shot Reagan in 1981, granted full freedom</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62989a5e0d1e3dc84e8f576b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 11:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62989a5e0d1e3dc84e8f576b/</guid><description>A federal judge on Wednesday granted John Hinckley, the man who shot and wounded President Ronald Reagan and three others in a 1981 assassination attempt, unconditional release from the remaining restrictions he faced, U.S. media reported.
Highlights John Hinckley Jr. shot and wounded President Ronald Reagan and three others in 1981 assassination attempt. Judge lifts travel and internet usage restrictions against Hinckleys, who has been living on his own in Virginia.</description></item><item><title>No state charge for billionaire Sanford in child porn probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629202d97e3a77c81363f68a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 11:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629202d97e3a77c81363f68a/</guid><description>SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — The South Dakota attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office has declined to file charges against billionaire T. Denny Sanford following an investigation into possible possession of child pornography, saying it found no “prosecutable offenses” within the state&amp;rsquo;s jurisdiction, according to a court document filed Friday.
Highlights South Dakota attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office has declined to file charges against Sanford following an investigation into possible possession of child pornography, saying it found no “prosecutable offenses” within the state’s jurisdiction.</description></item><item><title>An appeals court finds Florida's social media law unconstitutional</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d03c3e2cada4724b26a66/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d03c3e2cada4724b26a66/</guid><description>In a blow to Gov. Ron DeSantis, a three-judge panel of the 11th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals said social media companies&amp;rsquo; moderation and curation efforts were protected by the First Amendment.
Highlights An appeals court finds Florida&amp;rsquo;s social media law unconstitutional. The law would require large social media companies to publish standards on how it decides to &amp;ldquo;censor, deplatform, and shadow ban&amp;rdquo; The law was signed by GOP Gov. Ron DeSantis in 2021.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine court jails Russian soldier for life in war crimes trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b959de21b1e4548374c15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 14:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b959de21b1e4548374c15/</guid><description>A Ukrainian court sentenced a Russian soldier to life in prison on Monday for killing an unarmed civilian in the first war crimes trial arising from Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion.
Highlights Ukrainian court sentences Russian tank commander Vadim Shishimarin to life in prison for killing unarmed civilian. 21-year-old tank commander pleaded guilty to killing Oleksandr Shelipov in the northeastern Ukrainian village of Chupakhivka on Feb. 28, four days after the invasion. Russia denies targeting civilians or involvement in war crimes while it carries out what it calls a &amp;ldquo;special military operation&amp;rdquo; in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones back on the hook for damages after bankruptcy judge sends Sandy Hook cases to Texas court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62886660069aa21ece71281f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 04:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62886660069aa21ece71281f/</guid><description>The bankruptcy judge’s ruling means the Texas trial to determine what Alex Jones owes&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; defamation cases are sent back to state court in Texas, where the parents of two boys slain in the Sandy Hook massacre await jury trials to see how much Jones owes them. Jones&amp;rsquo; bankruptcy filing put on hold the two trials in Texas and the third in Connecticut, since federal court trumps state proceedings.</description></item><item><title>Federal Court Orders ‘All’ ISPs to Block Film-Piracy Websites — Setting An Interesting Precedent for the Music Industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276eee686a2499e9025b948/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 22:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276eee686a2499e9025b948/</guid><description>ISPs must block multiple piracy websites that infringed upon media, a court has ruled in a significant judgement for the music industry.
Highlights A federal court has ordered internet service providers (ISPs) to block access to multiple television- and film-piracy websites. The decision sets an interesting precedent for the music industry. The judge also imposed a $7.65 million damages bill for copyright infringement as well as “pre-judgment interest on all monetary relief,” at nine percent, from late December onward.</description></item><item><title>U.S. eyes emergency contraception grants if top court cuts abortion rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273958d4f285b3e829a540a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273958d4f285b3e829a540a/</guid><description>U.S. President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration was looking at grants to help fund expanding access to emergency contraception as a possible response if the Supreme Court overturns a 1973 decision that legalized abortion nationwide, White House spokesperson Jen Psaki said on Wednesday.
Highlights U.S. President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration looking at grants to help fund expanding access to emergency contraception as a possible response if the Supreme Court overturns a 1973 decision that legalized abortion nationwide.</description></item><item><title>Man who assaulted flight attendants, was duct taped on Frontier flight, sentenced to jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271d0a2e28beb284f598fca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 01:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271d0a2e28beb284f598fca/</guid><description>Man who assaulted flight attendants, was duct taped on Frontier flight, sentenced to jail.
Highlights Max Berry pleaded guilty to three counts of assault within maritime and territorial jurisdiction and faced 1.5 years and a $15,000 fine. He had been drinking on a Frontier Airlines flight in August from Philadelphia to Miami when he spilled his drink on himself and a flight attendant. Berry went to the bathroom without his shirt and groped two flight attendants.</description></item><item><title>Sex worker gets 30 years for fatally drugging men for ‘a few quick dollars’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270131fe020ba2ae06fd4c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 17:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270131fe020ba2ae06fd4c8/</guid><description>Angelina Barini’s pattern was nearly identical, authorities said. In motel rooms in Queens, she gave four men high doses of drugs, robbed them and left them unresponsive.
Highlights Angelina Barini, 43, met with clients at motels in New York City before giving them drugs that incapacitated them. Then, she would rob the men and leave with their personal belongings. Four of them, including a prominent Italian chef, died of overdoses from the drugs, court records state.</description></item><item><title>Colombia court says 5,733 people killed, disappeared in campaign against left-wing party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626621a4a8618f5dd51b323d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 04:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626621a4a8618f5dd51b323d/</guid><description>Some 5,733 people were killed or disappeared in Colombia as part of a campaign against the left-wing Patriotic Union (UP) party between 1984 and 2016, acts linked to paramilitaries with military backing, the country&amp;rsquo;s transitional justice tribunal said on Friday.
Highlights Some 5,733 people were killed or disappeared in Colombia as part of a campaign against the left-wing Patriotic Union (UP) party between 1984 and 2016. The attacks were often carried out by right-wing paramilitary gunmen, although there was also evidence of involvement of state agents.</description></item><item><title>US supreme court rules against air force officer who refused Covid vaccine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eef9755e81ec0cd1136f1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eef9755e81ec0cd1136f1/</guid><description>Majority of court sides with Pentagon over challenge by lieutenant colonel who cited religious grounds for refusal to get vaccine
Highlights Lt Col Jonathan Dunn cited religious grounds for his refusal to get the Covid-19 vaccine. He cited a speech given by Joe Biden that led him to conclude that “the vaccine ceased to be merely a medical invention and took on a symbolic and even sacramental quality” The court ruled in March that the US navy had the authority to determine the job assignments of 35 service members who refused to get vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Feds say towing company illegally sold service members’ cars</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c9f23992f913350bb012e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c9f23992f913350bb012e/</guid><description>Federal prosecutors have filed a lawsuit accusing a Virginia company of illegally taking and selling service members’ vehicles.
Highlights Federal prosecutors file lawsuit accusing Virginia company of illegally taking and selling service members’ vehicles. Lawsuit seeks damages for affected service members, a civil penalty, and a court order barring the company from auctioning off vehicles without court orders. Federal prosecutors say the move violates the law requiring towing companies to get court orders before taking off service members&amp;rsquo; vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk ‘funding secured’ tweets ruled false new court filing suggests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bccb2253ad4a6eff826a8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 08:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bccb2253ad4a6eff826a8/</guid><description>A court filing out Friday suggests a judge ruled that CEO Elon Musk knowingly made false statements when he tweeted about a take-private deal for Tesla in 2018.
Highlights Court filing suggests a judge ruled that Tesla CEO Elon Musk knowingly made false statements about a take-private deal for Tesla in 2018. The shareholders are suing Tesla over money they lost after Musk tweeted in 2018 that he was considering taking his electric vehicle company private at $420 per share and said he had funding secured to do so.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma lawmakers pass bill to make performing an abortion illegal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d8624a9d39d0aa19d9ffe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 12:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d8624a9d39d0aa19d9ffe/</guid><description>State house approves bill that would make performing an abortion a felony, and is one in raft of GOP bills to restrict or ban abortion
Highlights Oklahoma lawmakers overwhelmingly passed a bill to make performing an abortion a felony punishable by 10 years in prison and a $100,000 fine. The bill is one in a raft of Republican bills to severely restrict or ban abortion. Thousands of pregnant Texans have relied on legal abortion in Oklahoma since Texas outlawed abortion after six weeks gestation in September 2021.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court backs Navy in fight with anti-vaccine SEALs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f49a299b5b8509d718b49/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f49a299b5b8509d718b49/</guid><description>The U.S. Supreme Court on Friday granted a request by President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration to let the Navy decline to deploy SEALs and other special operations forces personnel who refused mandatory COVID-19 vaccination due to religious objections.
Highlights The U.S. Supreme Court granted a request by President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration to let the Navy decline to deploy SEALs and other special operations forces personnel who refused mandatory COVID-19 vaccination due to religious objections.</description></item><item><title>Navalny sentenced to 9 years in prison by Russian court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623aac2bf0e30c61d1634fbf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 05:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623aac2bf0e30c61d1634fbf/</guid><description>A Russian court has convicted top opposition leader Alexei Navalny of fraud and contempt of court, sentencing him to nine more years in prison in a move seen as an
Highlights Russian court convicts Alexei Navalny of fraud and contempt of court. Sentenced him to nine more years in prison in a move seen as an attempt to keep him behind bars for as long as possible. Navalny was convicted of contempt and fraud and sentenced to nine years behind bars.</description></item><item><title>'You got rich off our dead bodies' opioid victims tell Purdue's Sacklers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ada1d06819d4181840eb5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ada1d06819d4181840eb5/</guid><description>Victims of America&amp;rsquo;s opioid epidemic confronted members of the Sackler family that owns Purdue Pharma on Thursday with wrenching stories of suffering they said was caused by the painkillers that built the company fortune.
Highlights Victims of U.S. opioid epidemic confronted Sackler family that owns Purdue Pharma on Thursday with wrenching stories of suffering they said was caused by the painkillers that built the company fortune. &amp;ldquo;You got rich off our dead bodies and told us it was our own fault for dying,&amp;rdquo; Ryan Hampton told Richard Sackler, a former board member.</description></item><item><title>SF judge tosses plea deals for CA militia members linked to man who killed Oakland federal guard</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621767ccc0414357cf1f26f6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 11:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621767ccc0414357cf1f26f6/</guid><description>A San Francisco judge throws out the guilty pleas for three members of &amp;quot;Grizzly Scouts&amp;quot; who made plans to target police with Steve Carrillo.
Highlights Steven Carrillo, a Santa Cruz County Air Force sergeant, pleaded guilty Friday to fatally shooting Pat Underwood at Oakland federal building. Judge threw out guilty pleas for three members of an armed, anti-government militia who made plans to target law enforcement. The Grizzly Scouts used a Facebook account named &amp;ldquo;they say the west won&amp;rsquo;t boog&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;This is the beginning of the boog,&amp;rdquo; court records show.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court rejects Trump's bid to shield January 6 records, bringing end to legal battle</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62152846663c5b6e90e95e31/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62152846663c5b6e90e95e31/</guid><description>The Supreme Court already rejected Trump&amp;rsquo;s emergency request to block the release of his records to the January 6 select committee.
Highlights The Supreme Court turned away the former president&amp;rsquo;s legal fight with the House select committee investigating the January 6 assault on the U.S. Capitol. The panel received more than 700 pages of records sought by the panel earlier this month. Trump asserted executive privilege over more than 750 pages of documents related to the events of January 6, including presidential diaries, visitor logs, handwritten notes from then-White House chief of staff Mark Meadows, binders from then White House press secretary Kayleigh McEnany, and a draft executive order on election integrity.</description></item><item><title>4 Alberta border protesters charged with conspiring to murder RCMP officers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d14abe3b73fe54fc2fbe8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d14abe3b73fe54fc2fbe8/</guid><description>The first 11 protesters to be arrested in connection to the Coutts, Alta., border blockade made their first court appearance Tuesday afternoon on charges that include conspiracy to murder, mischief and possession of a weapon.
Highlights At least 13 people have been arrested at the Coutts, Alta., border crossing in southern Alberta. Most face charges of mischief to property over $5,000 and possession of a weapon. A total of 13 have been charged with conspiracy to murder in relation to a protest against pandemic restrictions near the main U.</description></item><item><title>Tina Peters arrested for allegedly recording court proceeding</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62063690260f4b0a138baf56/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62063690260f4b0a138baf56/</guid><description>Mesa County Clerk and Recorder Tina Peters was arrested in Grand Junction Tuesday, and a judge signed a search warrant to obtain a video recording from her iPad that was allegedly taken by Peters during a court hearing Monday involving her deputy clerk’s burglary and cybercrime charges.
Highlights Mesa County Clerk and Recorder Tina Peters was arrested in Grand Junction Tuesday. A judge signed a search warrant to obtain a video recording from her iPad that was allegedly taken by Peters during a court hearing Monday.</description></item><item><title>Judge sides with Britney Spears in ongoing court battle with her father over finances</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea682cd29919af438972e7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 08:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea682cd29919af438972e7/</guid><description>Although Britney Spears&amp;rsquo; 13-year conservatorship has ended, the legal battle over her finances is still going on.
Summary (CNN) Although Britney Spears&amp;rsquo; 13-year conservatorship has ended, the legal battle over her finances is still going on. The singer&amp;rsquo;s attorney, Mathew Rosengart, faced off in court on Wednesday against attorney Alex Weingarten, who now represents the pop star&amp;rsquo;s father, Jamie Spears. Judge Brenda Penny ruled against a request from the elder Spears for Britney Spears to set aside money from her $60 million estate in a reserve to potentially cover legal fees, which would include her father&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Ohio's high court overturns new congressional map saying it 'unduly favors' Republicans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e263310c9630cf76136ffc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e263310c9630cf76136ffc/</guid><description>Ohio&amp;rsquo;s state supreme court ruled Friday that the state&amp;rsquo;s newly-drawn congressional map, which was passed by the GOP-controlled legislature, violates the state constitution because it &amp;quot;unduly favors the Republican Party and disfavors the Democratic Party.&amp;quot;
Summary (CNN) Ohio&amp;rsquo;s state supreme court ruled Friday that the state&amp;rsquo;s newly-drawn congressional map, which was passed by the GOP-controlled legislature, violates the state constitution because it &amp;ldquo;unduly favors the Republican Party and disfavors the Democratic Party.</description></item><item><title>Murphy signs bill enshrining abortion into NJ state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e19e4d69dd4e34eac0ed3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 16:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e19e4d69dd4e34eac0ed3d/</guid><description>TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — New Jersey Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy, anticipating possible changes to the Roe v. Wade ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court, signed a bill Thursday enshrining the right to an abortion into state law.
Summary Phil Murphy, anticipating possible changes to the Roe v. Wade ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court, signed a bill Thursday enshrining the right to an abortion into state law. ADVERTISEMENTIn addition to abortion rights, the bill also specifically outlines a right to access contraception, as well as to carry a pregnancy to term.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families who won defamation suit against Alex Jones subpoena Facebook as trial nears</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1903629059753f4d85456/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1903629059753f4d85456/</guid><description>The Sandy Hook families who won a defamation suit against extremist Alex Jones in&amp;hellip;
Summary NEWTOWN — The Sandy Hook families who won a defamation suit against extremist Alex Jones in Connecticut want to know whether the “Infowars” host used Facebook to amplify conspiracy theories as both sides prepare for a trial to establish damages. But since Facebook deactivated Jones’ accounts in 2018, his lawyers said they had no access to the social media data the families seek, according to court records.</description></item><item><title>New York attorney general asks court to enforce subpoenas of Trump children in tax fraud probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d452fd8a045bb351269367/</guid><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization.
Summary New York Attorney General Letitia James has subpoenaed Ivanka Trump and Donald Trump Jr. as part of her civil tax fraud investigation into the Trump Organization, court filings made public Monday reveal. The state attorney general &amp;ldquo;is engaged in a criminal investigation that has an active grand jury.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew makes 'unprecedented' request for all witness testimony in sex abuse case to be kept secret</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce643ed24df844e06c718b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce643ed24df844e06c718b/</guid><description>The request was made in a letter submitted to court as part of a fresh attempt to get the civil proceedings thrown out
Summary Share this Story: Prince Andrew makes &amp;lsquo;unprecedented&amp;rsquo; request for all witness testimony in sex abuse case to be kept secretPrince Andrew makes &amp;lsquo;unprecedented&amp;rsquo; request for all witness testimony in sex abuse case to be kept secret The request was made in a letter submitted to court as part of a fresh attempt to get the civil proceedings thrown out Photo by Steve Parsons/PA Wire/Pool via Reuters/FileArticle content LONDON — Prince Andrew, the Duke of York, has made an “unprecedented” request for all witness testimony taken in his sexual abuse case to be kept secret, it has emerged.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Weddington, attorney who won Roe v Wade abortion case, dies aged 76</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca296dd5ad42077375fcf2/</guid><description>Texan lawyer and Linda Coffee won landmark 1973 case, safeguarding right now under threat from US supreme court
Summary Sarah Weddington, an attorney who argued and won the Roe v Wade supreme court case which established the right to abortion in the US, has died. “With Linda Coffee, she filed the first case of her legal career, Roe v Wade, fresh out of law school. Sarah Weddington poses with a signed copy of the Roe v Wade decision in front of the US supreme court in 2005.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4b942ce300bd25bd3fdeb/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6. The ruling Wednesday comes one day after he asked a federal judge in Florida for a temporary restraining order, and it&amp;rsquo;s the first quick response to a lawsuit from a House witness, after several went to court to try to invalidate the committee and block the House from pursuing their phone records.</description></item></channel></rss>