<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>severed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/severed/</link><description>Recent content in severed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 21:10:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/severed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Paralysed man with severed spine walks thanks to implant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62018aafcdd999939b083649/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 21:10:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62018aafcdd999939b083649/</guid><description>Michel Roccati tells the BBC he &amp;quot;almost has a normal life&amp;quot; again thanks to an electrical implant.
Highlights Nine people have received the implant and regained the ability to walk. None of them use it to help them walk in their everyday lives - because it&amp;rsquo;s too complicated at this stage. Instead, the implant exercises their muscles, improves their health and often restores a little bit of movement. Michel Roccati tells the BBC he &amp;ldquo;almost has a normal life&amp;rdquo; again thanks to an electrical implant.</description></item><item><title>Undersea Cable Connecting Norway With Arctic Satellite Station Has Been Mysteriously Severed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de527ce8f0a4e0f7c23d41/</guid><description>The cables run through a highly strategic stretch of water near where the Barents and Norwegian Sea meet.
Summary Bjoertvedt/Wikimedia Commons The Svalbard Satellite Station atop the mountain of Platåberget on the island of Spitsbergen in Svalbard, Norway. Known as the Svalbard Undersea Cable System, the dual communication cable runs between Longyearbyen and Andøya in northern Norway, each stretching more than 800 miles. Nsandel/Wikimedia Commons The Cable Innovator was one of the cable-laying vessels involved in laying the Svalbard Undersea Cable System.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutor: Ethan Crumbley tortured animals, kept severed bird head in bedroom for six months</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d93694f3d554e5f99961ca/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d93694f3d554e5f99961ca/</guid><description>Summary Friday&amp;rsquo;s bond hearing for the Crumbley parents. Beginning in March, Keast said Ethan Crumbley texted his mother multiple times that he believed there was a demon or ghost inside the house. In May, he filmed himself torturing and killing animals and kept a bird&amp;rsquo;s severed head in a jar in his room for six months. Prosecutors also presented new details about the Crumbley parents&amp;rsquo; behavior in several days following the shooting.</description></item></channel></rss>