<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>win on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/win/</link><description>Recent content in win on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 16:17:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/win/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mississippi fire chief dies hours after legal win allowing use of Ivermectin to treat COVID</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62053a81c1761200de2c8037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62053a81c1761200de2c8037/</guid><description>Wayne Doyle died Tuesday afternoon at North Mississippi Medical Center in Tupelo.
Highlights Wayne Doyle died Tuesday afternoon at North Mississippi Medical Center in Tupelo. He was given Ivermectin, which is not approved to treat the virus. Doyle died after he was moved out of the hospital to receive the drug. The drug has been at the center of attention during the pandemic of the virus in the U.S. Some used it for treatment, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not approved by the federal government and some use it to treat parasites in humans and animals.</description></item><item><title>Bills become the first team in NFL history to pitch a 'perfect' offensive game in playoff win over Patriots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e55a71f6c19446734d41fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 12:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e55a71f6c19446734d41fc/</guid><description>The Bills didn&amp;rsquo;t punt, kick a field goal, nor turn the ball over in the blowout win
Summary The Buffalo Bills had an offensive performance for the ages on Saturday night, a feat that has never been executed in NFL history. The Bills scored on their first seven possessions, the first team in NFL playoff history to accomplish that feat. The only other team to accomplish that feat was the 2019 Kansas City Chiefs in the AFC Divisional Playoffs against the Houston Texans.</description></item><item><title>‘No one can win a nuclear war’: Superpowers release rare joint statement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d371fdf6709c474ae2fcfe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d371fdf6709c474ae2fcfe/</guid><description>China, Russia, the UK, the United States and France release a joint statement agreeing that a further spread of nuclear arms should be avoided.
Summary China, Russia, the UK, the United States and France have agreed that a further spread of nuclear arms and a nuclear war should be avoided. According to a joint statement released on Tuesday morning (AEDT), the five countries – the permanent members of the United Nations Security Council – said they considered it their primary responsibility to avoid war between the nuclear states and to reduce strategic risks, while aiming to work to create an atmosphere of security.</description></item></channel></rss>