<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sparks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sparks/</link><description>Recent content in sparks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 16:19:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sparks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>China internet censors scramble as lockdown frustration sparks ‘creative’ wave of dissent | China</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260325993c0910a2895d4ec/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 16:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260325993c0910a2895d4ec/</guid><description>Experts say volume of dissent from Shanghai over zero-Covid measures challenging attempts to control information
Highlights China&amp;rsquo;s strict system of censorship is struggling against the onslaught of complaints from Shanghai. Residents find creative ways to get around bans on words, hashtags and even lyrics from the national anthem. Government has urged residents to harness “positive energy” in response to weeks-long lockdown. On WeChat, groups have shared the names and stories of people who died, either with Covid or because the lockdown delayed their access to healthcare.</description></item><item><title>Video of police stopping fight at NJ mall sparks excessive force investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d4c6f3af054a299cb3af4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 19:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620d4c6f3af054a299cb3af4/</guid><description>A video posted on social media of police breaking up a fight between a Black and white teen at Bridgewater Commons mall has prompted an investigation.
Highlights Video shows two male teens, one Black and the other white, having an argument before pointing fingers at each other. The video shows no sign of resistance from the Black teen. A female voice is heard saying, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s cause he&amp;rsquo;s Black, racially motivated,&amp;rdquo; a female voice heard saying in the video.</description></item></channel></rss>