<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>personal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/personal/</link><description>Recent content in personal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 19:08:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cambridge Analytica scandal: Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg sued by Washington, DC AG</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bdb8debec35554468dbda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 19:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bdb8debec35554468dbda/</guid><description>The lawsuit accuses Mark Zuckerberg of misrepresenting the protection of user data and their blatant disregard and misuse of sensitive, personal data belonging to residents of Washington District of Columbia.
Highlights The case seeks to hold Zuckerberg accountable for his role in. misrepresenting the protection of user data. The personal data of more than 70 million US. users that Cambridge Analytica used to manipulate the election accounted for more than half the total votes during the 2016 presidential elections.</description></item><item><title>Sheriff claims deputies didn’t search lacrosse team’s personal items, body camera shows otherwise</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c350d3838f0326a4277d3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 22:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c350d3838f0326a4277d3/</guid><description>An incident that involved players from a university’s lacrosse team and deputies in Georgia remains under investigation.
Highlights Delaware State University President Tony Allen released a statement on Monday responding to the incident that reportedly happened on April 20 in Georgia. Georgia law enforcement stopped a bus for a minor traffic violation with the Delaware State Lacrosse team on board. Deputies searched the belongings of the student-athletes, including suitcases with drug-sniffing dogs.</description></item><item><title>Biden says he'd consider slapping Putin with personal sanctions if Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f28ac59ed72783ee509b72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f28ac59ed72783ee509b72/</guid><description>Russia has warned that sanctioning Vladimir Putin would lead to US-Russia ties being cut. Leaked documents suggest Putin has secret assets abroad.
Highlights Joe Biden said a Russian invasion of Ukraine could be the &amp;ldquo;largest invasion since World War II.&amp;rdquo; Biden said the US could sanction Vladimir Putin personally if an invasion went ahead. He said that if Russia invaded Ukraine, it would have &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; and could be the &amp;ldquo;largest invasion since World War II.</description></item></channel></rss>