<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jackson on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jackson/</link><description>Recent content in jackson on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 11:13:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jackson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 Suspects Arrested in South Street Mass Shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a082e350af779fa99d0a70/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 11:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a082e350af779fa99d0a70/</guid><description>Two people are in custody in connection to the mass shooting that killed three people and wounded 11 others on South Street in Philadelphia over the weekend.
Highlights Rashaan Vereen, 34, is charged with attempted murder, aggravated assault, simple assault, recklessly endangering another person, conspiracy, violation of the uniforms firearms act, possession of an instrument of crime, tampering of evidence and obstruction of justice. Quran Garner, 18, was arrested and charged with two counts of aggravated assault.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas discharged from hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1f087b14606ea959599d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 14:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1f087b14606ea959599d/</guid><description>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was discharged from the hospital, a week after being admitted with an infection.
Highlights Thomas was treated with antibiotics at Sibley Memorial Hospital in Washington, D.C., after &amp;ldquo;flu-like symptoms&amp;rdquo; Thomas was discharged less than a day after news outlets revealed his wife, Virginia Thomas, sent an array of text messages urging then-President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s top aide to try to overturn the 2020 election. Thomas is currently the longest-serving justice on the high court, and the second oldest, behind the 83-year-old Breyer, who is retiring.</description></item><item><title>Teen honored after using his Make-A-Wish to feed homeless in Jackson</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da33b687ed3f55535f8f10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da33b687ed3f55535f8f10/</guid><description>A Jackson teen is being honored for giving back to his community and helping the homeless.
Summary Teen honored after using his Make-A-Wish to feed homeless in JacksonTeen honored after using his Make-A-Wish to feed homeless in JacksonPEARL, Miss. (WLBT) - A Jackson teen is being honored for giving back to his community and helping the homeless. We introduced you to 13-year-old Abraham last year after he used his Make-A-Wish to feed the homeless in Jackson.</description></item></channel></rss>