<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>takes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/takes/</link><description>Recent content in takes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:35:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/takes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alabama ban on gender-affirming care for transgender youth takes effect</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62791893fb2f9e68b3b85713/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62791893fb2f9e68b3b85713/</guid><description>An Alabama law that makes it a felony to provide gender-affirming medical treatment to transgender youth went into effect on Sunday while a federal judge weighs whether to grant a motion to put a temporary hold on it.
Highlights Alabama law that makes it a felony to provide gender-affirming medical treatment to transgender youth went into effect on Sunday. A federal judge weighs whether to grant a motion to put a temporary hold on it.</description></item><item><title>A large Russian cargo plane took a lengthy, unexpected, and unexplained route over central and southern Finland on Saturday night, passing over Finland's Air Force headquarters and a military intelligence unit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7003a1a2afff60d9e9272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7003a1a2afff60d9e9272/</guid><description>The incident comes as political tensions continue to rise in the Baltic region.
Summary A large Russian cargo plane took an lengthy, unexpected and unexplained route over central and southern Finland on Saturday night, passing over Finland&amp;rsquo;s Air Force headquarters and a military intelligence unit. The cargo plane took off from Moscow at about 7.26pm Finnish time on Saturday evening and flew towards the city of Murmansk in northwestern Russia. The cargo plane also passed close to the Halli military airport in Jämsä, Central Finland.</description></item><item><title>MILWAUKEE -- The man who bought Kyle Rittenhouse an assault-style rifle when he was only 17 has agreed to plead no contest to contributing to the delinquency of a minor, a non-criminal citation, and avoid convictions on the two felonies he'd been facing.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc90663738cf593c49f462/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc90663738cf593c49f462/</guid><description>Dominick Black was charged with delivering a dangerous weapon to a minor, resulting in death.
Summary The two counts related to Joseph Rosenbaum and Anthony Huber, the protesters Rittenhouse fatally shot the night of Aug. 25, 2020, in Kenosha.Black was 18 when he purchased the rifle for Rittenhouse at a hardware store in Rusk County in May of that year. At 17, Rittenhouse was too young to legally purchase the weapon.</description></item></channel></rss>