<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>transmission on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transmission/</link><description>Recent content in transmission on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 11:11:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/transmission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CDC to significantly ease pandemic mask guidelines Friday | WTOP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218b92ed831908d2b2228a7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 11:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218b92ed831908d2b2228a7/</guid><description>The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday, according to two people familiar with the matter, meaning most Americans will no longer be advised to wear masks in indoor public settings.
Highlights The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday. The change comes as the Biden administration moves to shift its focus to preventing serious illness and death from the virus, rather than all instances of infection.</description></item><item><title>1 in 50 Manhattan Residents Infected With COVID in the Last Week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</guid><description>The omicron variant outbreak of COVID-19 in New York City is growing so quickly, 2% of all Manhattan residents were infected in just the last week.
Summary As the omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread out of control in New York City, transmission rates are soaring, with 2% of all Manhattan residents infected in the last week and nearing that level in the other boroughs. About 2,012 of every 100,000 Manhattan residents tested positive in the last seven days, according to the latest transmission data posted by the city.</description></item></channel></rss>