<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thats on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/categories/thats/</link><description>Recent content in thats on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.com/categories/thats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Omicron is ‘not the same disease’ as earlier Covid waves, says UK scientist | Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</guid><description>Sir John Bell says disease ‘appears less severe’ as other scientists criticise lack of new restrictions in England
Summary Omicron is “not the same disease we were seeing a year ago” and high Covid death rates in the UK are “now history”, a leading immunologist has said. Fewer patients were needing high-flow oxygen and the average length of stay was down to three days, he said. George Eustice, the environment secretary, said the government was keeping the level of Covid hospital admissions under “very close review”.</description></item><item><title>Fauci says U.S. should consider vaccine mandate for domestic air travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.com/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</guid><description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said in an interview on MSNBC that such a requirement should be &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot; considered.
Summary The federal government should consider requiring Covid-19 vaccines for domestic flights, the nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said Monday. &amp;ldquo;If you want to do that with domestic flights, I think that&amp;rsquo;s something that seriously should be considered.&amp;rdquo; There is no indication at this point that a vaccine mandate is on its way for U.</description></item></channel></rss>