<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thats on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/thats/</link><description>Recent content in thats on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:18:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/thats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Someone Shot The Johnny Cash Water Tower In Kingsland, Arkansas, And Now It’s Taking A Leak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62833e17482ab39c59261f00/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62833e17482ab39c59261f00/</guid><description>Ok, well that&amp;rsquo;s just hilarious. Kingsland, Arkansas, is a tiny little town in Cleveland County, that&amp;rsquo;s not known for anything really&amp;hellip; except being the birthplace of Johnny Cash. And in honor of the Man In Black, Kingsland&amp;rsquo;s water tower features a silhouette of Johnny holding a guitar. However, according to the Arkansas Democrat Gazette, somebody recently put
Highlights In honor of the Man In Black, Kingsland’s water tower features a silhouette of Johnny Cash holding a guitar.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Sweden and Finland confirm Nato plans in historic shift</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62825c6169eab7af7ed7a53a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62825c6169eab7af7ed7a53a/</guid><description>Traditionally both countries favour neutrality but the shift comes after Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights Mr Blinken said he had heard strong support for the Nordic countries. Traditionally both countries favour neutrality but the shift comes after Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. He said he is confident the countries will reach consensus on joining Nato if they choose to do. He has held talks with his Turkish counterpart about joining Nato in the hope of a deal being reached by the end of the year.</description></item><item><title>Couple wakes up to find strange dog sleeping with them in their bed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ccff5863ac5dd88864ec2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ccff5863ac5dd88864ec2/</guid><description>Jimmy Johnson opened his eyes and didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize the dog sleeping in their bed in Polk County, Tennessee.
Highlights Jimmy Johnson opened his eyes and didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize the dog sleeping in their bed. After a post on Facebook went viral, someone recognized the dog named Nala. The couple thinks the back door was left open by accident and their new furry roommate just wandered in. Nala traveled almost two miles and the adventure eventually ended when the dog wanted some company.</description></item><item><title>Celebrity chef's Ukraine charity kitchen destroyed by Russian missile</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e53d70a5aa310872f5e20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 06:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e53d70a5aa310872f5e20/</guid><description>One of the restaurant partners of the World Central Kitchen (WCK) was struck on Saturday, according to the nonprofit kitchen&amp;rsquo;s CEO Nate Mook, who confirmed the news on Twitter, revealing that four staff members had been injured in the blast.
Highlights One of the World Central Kitchen&amp;rsquo;s partners in Ukraine has been hit by a Russian missile. Four staff members were injured in the blast, according to the charity&amp;rsquo;s Twitter account.</description></item><item><title>Police say Burger King employee shot at customer who threw mayonnaise at her</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623512441f7f04756b53d0f6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 23:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623512441f7f04756b53d0f6/</guid><description>A Burger King employee has been arrested for shooting at a customer at a northwest Miami-Dade Burger King on Thursday afternoon.
Highlights Police identified the woman as Shateasha Hicks, 30, who was arrested for shooting at a Miami-Dade Burger King on Thursday afternoon. Witnesses say Hicks left the restaurant and grabbed a gun out of her car. Police said she fired five rounds at the car as the man drove away.</description></item><item><title>Joe Rogan apologises for using N-word and racist Planet of the Apes story</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61febdeb00e68aa9f8162afe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 18:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61febdeb00e68aa9f8162afe/</guid><description>Podcast host apologises for ‘shameful’ matter, but says comments were taken out of context
Highlights Comedian says clips were &amp;rsquo;taken out of context&amp;rsquo; and is&amp;rsquo;sincere and humble&amp;rsquo; He says he was quoting other people or referring to a Richard Pryor comedy album. Rogan has come under fire for suggesting that the healthy should not get vaccinated. The 54-year-old also said he had deleted his popular podcast The Joe Rogan Experience because it was &amp;lsquo;an idiotic thing to say&amp;rsquo; He said: &amp;lsquo;I certainly wasn’t trying to be racist, and I certainly wasn&amp;rsquo;t trying to offend someone for entertainment with something as stupid as racism&amp;rsquo; He has also apologised for saying he thought the word was in context when he mentioned it in his podcast.</description></item><item><title>Omicron is ‘not the same disease’ as earlier Covid waves, says UK scientist | Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 18:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb50c7d6229523246d9048/</guid><description>Sir John Bell says disease ‘appears less severe’ as other scientists criticise lack of new restrictions in England
Summary Omicron is “not the same disease we were seeing a year ago” and high Covid death rates in the UK are “now history”, a leading immunologist has said. Fewer patients were needing high-flow oxygen and the average length of stay was down to three days, he said. George Eustice, the environment secretary, said the government was keeping the level of Covid hospital admissions under “very close review”.</description></item><item><title>Fauci says U.S. should consider vaccine mandate for domestic air travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cad24786c7639db24dbd68/</guid><description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said in an interview on MSNBC that such a requirement should be &amp;quot;seriously&amp;quot; considered.
Summary The federal government should consider requiring Covid-19 vaccines for domestic flights, the nation&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert said Monday. &amp;ldquo;If you want to do that with domestic flights, I think that&amp;rsquo;s something that seriously should be considered.&amp;rdquo; There is no indication at this point that a vaccine mandate is on its way for U.</description></item></channel></rss>