<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>best on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/best/</link><description>Recent content in best on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 03:06:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/best/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia tests nuclear-capable ballistic missile that Putin says has no peer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260ca2406bc58abffb7cc1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 03:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260ca2406bc58abffb7cc1c/</guid><description>In a show of strength two months into its assault on Ukraine, Russia test-launched a new nuclear-capable intercontinental ballistic missile which President Vladimir Putin said on Wednesday would make Moscow&amp;rsquo;s enemies stop and think.
Highlights Russia test-launched a new nuclear-capable intercontinental ballistic missile which President Vladimir Putin said on Wednesday would make Moscow&amp;rsquo;s enemies stop and think. Putin was shown on TV being told by the military that the long-awaited Sarmat missile had been test launched for the first time from Plesetsk in northwest Russia and hit targets in the Kamchatka peninsula, nearly 6,000 km (3,700 miles) away.</description></item><item><title>Academy condemns Will Smith's actions, launches review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624241029131b5dbacbf29d3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 23:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624241029131b5dbacbf29d3/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences on Monday condemned the actions of Will Smith during Sunday night’s Oscars and launched an inquiry into his slapping of presenter Chris Rock .
Highlights The Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences condemns the actions of Will Smith during Sunday night’s Oscars. The film academy has launched an inquiry into his slapping of presenter Chris Rock. Smith stunned the Dolby Theatre crowd and viewers at home when he took the stage during Rock&amp;rsquo;s remarks after the comedian made a joke about Jada Pinkett Smith, Smith&amp;rsquo;s wife.</description></item><item><title>Will Smith, Chris Rock confrontation shocks Oscar audience</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62414400daa329aafadad8fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 05:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62414400daa329aafadad8fc/</guid><description>It was a big night for “CODA” at the 94th Academy Awards, which picked up three major wins at Sunday&amp;rsquo;s show. But most were talking about another Oscars moment. Here&amp;rsquo;s a rundown of what happened at Sunday&amp;rsquo;s show.
Highlights Will Smith slapped presenter Chris Rock on stage after he joked about a sequel to &amp;ldquo;G.I. Jane&amp;rdquo; Smith later apologized to the academy and his fellow nominees. Apple TV+ scored its first best picture Academy Award on Sunday, less than three years after launching the service.</description></item></channel></rss>