<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>illinois on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/illinois/</link><description>Recent content in illinois on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 02:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/illinois/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Illinois found to be routinely housing wards of the state in Chicago’s jail for kids</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a00f5d77bcd758689a5a8c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 02:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a00f5d77bcd758689a5a8c/</guid><description>The state’s child welfare agency says it has nowhere else to put the children. Opponents call it cruel, and a civil rights violation.
Highlights WBEZ first reported on the crisis in 2015. 84 children in the care of the Illinois Department of Children and Family Services were left in the juvenile detention center after a judge ordered their release. One boy, originally detained on a robbery case, is still being held more than eight months after he was released.</description></item><item><title>'A tragedy': Closure of 150-year-old college underscores toll of ransomware attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a034fe95e395bb24ca612/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 06:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a034fe95e395bb24ca612/</guid><description>Lincoln College is scheduled to close its doors Friday, becoming the first U.S. institution of higher learning to shut down in part due to a ransomware attack.
Highlights Lincoln College is scheduled to close its doors Friday, becoming the first U.S. institution of higher learning to shut down in part due to a ransomware attack. The Illinois school is one of only a handful of rural American colleges that qualify as predominantly Black institutions by the Department of Education.</description></item></channel></rss>