<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>francisco on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/francisco/</link><description>Recent content in francisco on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/francisco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leaning San Francisco skyscraper is tilting 3 inches per year as engineers rush to fix it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1d66a2d83a32304afe2c5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 20:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1d66a2d83a32304afe2c5/</guid><description>The engineer trying to stabilize the Millennium Tower, a luxury residential skyscraper in San Francisco that is sinking into the ground and now leaning over
Summary The engineer trying to stabilize the Millennium Tower, a luxury residential skyscraper in San Francisco that is sinking into the ground and now leaning over two feet off of center, said the building is now tilting three inches per year. Hamburger made the comments Thursday at a city hearing in which he pitched an updated fix for the building&amp;rsquo;s foundation, NBC Bay Area reported.</description></item><item><title>Police arrest 76-year-old man in cold case of 1978 strangling death of teen in San Francisco</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 10:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2f746a69e297307727f2d/</guid><description>Description Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City
Summary Police in San Francisco say they arrested a 76-year-old man and charged him with murder for the 1978 strangling death of Marissa Rolf Harvey, a New York City teen who was found dead after visiting Golden Gate Park. Mark Stanley Personette, of Conifer, Colorado, was arrested Dec.</description></item></channel></rss>