<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>men on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/men/</link><description>Recent content in men on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 08:16:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/men/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gas theft ring in Florida stole at least $60K of fuel from stations to resell at half price, sheriff says.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bfad785affa04abbc68ee/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 08:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bfad785affa04abbc68ee/</guid><description>Six men accused of stealing thousands of dollars of gasoline from Florida gas stations have been arrested, officials said Monday.
Highlights Six men are accused of stealing thousands of dollars of gasoline from Florida gas stations. A seventh man, Willian Penate-Arencibia, who is alleged to be their ringleader, is still at large. The suspects were selling the gas for half the price to truck drivers, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office alleged. The six men are charged with racketeering, conspiracy to commit racketeering and grand theft, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Driver falls asleep at wheel, kills 2 men changing tire on Florida interstate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f77b3e141b53bb0ff66e0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 17:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f77b3e141b53bb0ff66e0/</guid><description>The Florida Highway Patrol says two men who were changing a tire on the side of an interstate were killed when a passing driver fell asleep at the wheel and hit them.
Highlights The men were killed Sunday on Interstate 275 in Tampa, the Florida Highway Patrol said. Troopers said a 73-year-old man pulled over onto the road&amp;rsquo;s shoulder after a left front tire blew out. A friend of the man arrived a short time later to help him with the tire.</description></item><item><title>‘COVID started everything:’ Jury set in trial of 4 men accused of plotting Gov. Whitmer’s kidnapping over coronavirus orders</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228a92cfe47503d84ca8235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 13:19:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228a92cfe47503d84ca8235/</guid><description>Four men accused of plotting to kidnap Gov. Gretchen Whitmer at her Michigan summer home. Opening statements are set for Wednesday morning. Defendants say they were part of a militia, the Wolverine Watchmen, whose members conspired to kidnap
Highlights Four men accused of plotting to kidnap Gov. Gretchen Whitmer over her response to the pandemic. The defendants say that undercover FBI agents and paid informants pushed the defendants to take part in crimes.</description></item><item><title>The world's 10 wealthiest men doubled their fortunes during the first two years of the coronavirus pandemic as poverty and inequality soared. Oxfam said the men's wealth jumped from $700 billion to $1.5 trillion, at an average rate of $1.3 billion per day</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5223c93e2d7f552f904bd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5223c93e2d7f552f904bd/</guid><description>The world&amp;rsquo;s 10 wealthiest men doubled their fortunes during the first two years of the coronavirus pandemic as poverty and inequality soared, a report said on Monday.
Summary Oxfam said the wealth of the world&amp;rsquo;s 10 richest men jumped from $700 billion to $1.5 trillion during the pandemicParis (AFP) – The world&amp;rsquo;s 10 wealthiest men doubled their fortunes during the first two years of the coronavirus pandemic as poverty and inequality soared, a report said on Monday.</description></item></channel></rss>