<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>citizens on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/citizens/</link><description>Recent content in citizens on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 18:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/citizens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Attacks by Boston youth ‘terrorizing unsuspecting citizens’ continue downtown; police can’t make arrests because many suspects ‘too young’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62701ffa2bb077417f6e68b8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62701ffa2bb077417f6e68b8/</guid><description>At least five violent attacks involving juveniles &amp;quot;terrorizing unsuspecting citizens&amp;quot; that have occurred across Boston. The most recent attack happened on Wednesday night when Boston police were dispatched to Boston Common shortly after 6:30 p.m. Two women claimed
Highlights At least five violent attacks involving juveniles have occurred across Boston. The apparent ringleader of the group — a slim 5-foot-3-inch girl is “well known to Officers as she has been terrorizing unsuspecting citizens of Downtown Boston,” authorities said.</description></item><item><title>UAE to ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan. 10</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d22e8c3e1379b736c3ed73/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d22e8c3e1379b736c3ed73/</guid><description>The United Arab Emirates will ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan. 10, the state news agency WAM reported on Saturday, citing the foreign ministry and the National Emergency Crisis and Disaster Management Authority.
Summary A family walks at Dubai International Airport, as Emirates airline resumed limited outbound passenger flights amid outbreak of the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) in Dubai, UAE April 27, 2020. REUTERS/Ahmed JadallahCAIRO, Jan 1 (Reuters) - The United Arab Emirates will ban non-vaccinated citizens from traveling abroad from Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>