<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>milwaukee on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/milwaukee/</link><description>Recent content in milwaukee on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:39:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/milwaukee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multiple People Injured in Shooting at Wisconsin Cemetery During Funeral</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299825f123574c57d4870c3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299825f123574c57d4870c3/</guid><description>A shooting at a cemetery south of Milwaukee on Thursday afternoon resulted in multiple victims, police said.
Highlights Police say multiple shots were fired at Graceland Cemetery in Racine, about 30 miles (48 kilometers) south of Milwaukee. The shooting occurred at the interment for Da’Shontay L. King Sr. who was fatally shot by Racine police May 20, his sister says. Residents say they heard 20 to 30 shots fired at the cemetery.</description></item><item><title>21 people were injured in shootings in downtown Milwaukee; Mayor Johnson imposes curfew Saturday night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628127e5baac9bf6b4717134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628127e5baac9bf6b4717134/</guid><description>Eleven people are in custody, 10 guns were recovered and all the victims are expected to survive after three shootings near the Deer District and Water Street in Milwaukee following the Bucks Game 6 playoff game.
Highlights Milwaukee Mayor Cavalier Johnson imposes curfew Saturday night for under-21s. Mayor: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re going to do something about what happened here in this neighborhood last night&amp;rdquo; 11 people, ranging in age from 19 to 30, were arrested and 10 guns were recovered.</description></item></channel></rss>