<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sex on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sex/</link><description>Recent content in sex on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Expert: Monkeypox likely spread by sex at 2 raves in Europe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bea51aa880e9a5f5f75a6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bea51aa880e9a5f5f75a6/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — A leading adviser to the World Health Organization described the unprecedented outbreak of monkeypox in developed countries as “a random event” that might be explained by sexual behavior at two recent raves in Europe.
Highlights Leading doctor who chairs a World Health Organization expert group described the unprecedented outbreak of monkeypox in developed countries as “a random event” that might be explained by risky sexual behavior at two recent mass events in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Actress Zara Phythian and husband jailed for child sex offences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62846d4a580b1f6ec9fc7d83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 03:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62846d4a580b1f6ec9fc7d83/</guid><description>Zara Phythian - who appeared in Doctor Strange - abused a girl with husband Victor Marke.
Highlights We and our partners use technologies such as cookies to give you the best online experience. We store some limited information on your device without your consent. We use local storage to store your consent preferences. You can choose not to receive personalised ads by clicking ‘Reject data collection and continue” below. You may be asked to set these settings again when you visit non-AMP pages.</description></item><item><title>City employee fired gun over 20 times after Iowa juvenile refused to perform sex act</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c196c30b87d6889aeab51/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c196c30b87d6889aeab51/</guid><description>Police say he shot more than 20 rounds toward the Raccoon River.
Highlights Michael Teeples allegedly asked one of the girls to perform a sex act in exchange for money. When she refused, he showed a handgun and threatened to shoot out their tires if they left. He then tried to grab the victims in the vehicle they were driving. He later fired the weapon in the victims’ direction. Police say he shot more than 20 rounds toward the Raccoon River.</description></item><item><title>Sex worker gets 30 years for fatally drugging men for ‘a few quick dollars’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270131fe020ba2ae06fd4c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 17:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270131fe020ba2ae06fd4c8/</guid><description>Angelina Barini’s pattern was nearly identical, authorities said. In motel rooms in Queens, she gave four men high doses of drugs, robbed them and left them unresponsive.
Highlights Angelina Barini, 43, met with clients at motels in New York City before giving them drugs that incapacitated them. Then, she would rob the men and leave with their personal belongings. Four of them, including a prominent Italian chef, died of overdoses from the drugs, court records state.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee woman accused of 23 sex crimes involving 9 students at a high school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233f9bf5a9fc19d3e8aadd5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233f9bf5a9fc19d3e8aadd5/</guid><description>A 38-year-old Tennessee woman is facing 23 counts of sex crimes involving nine minors at a high school.
Highlights Melissa Blair, 38, was indicted on 23 charges, including 18 counts of aggravated statutory rape. She is accused of setting up meetings with the victims through social media and offering items in return for sexual favors. The alleged crimes occurred from early in 2020 to late 2021, McMinn County Sheriff Joe Guy said.</description></item><item><title>Representative Matt Gaetz's ex-girlfriend granted immunity in sex trafficking probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</guid><description>The woman testified in front of a federal grand jury last week hearing evidence in the Gaetz investigation.
Summary Gaetz has been under investigation to determine if he violated sex trafficking laws and obstructed justice in that probe. Gaetz has previously denied all wrongdoing, and has said he has never paid for sex nor had sex with an underage girl. One of the sources said she has information related to the investigation of both the sex trafficking and obstruction allegations.</description></item></channel></rss>