<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sex on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sex/</link><description>Recent content in sex on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 03:17:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/sex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tennessee woman accused of 23 sex crimes involving 9 students at a high school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233f9bf5a9fc19d3e8aadd5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233f9bf5a9fc19d3e8aadd5/</guid><description>A 38-year-old Tennessee woman is facing 23 counts of sex crimes involving nine minors at a high school.
Highlights Melissa Blair, 38, was indicted on 23 charges, including 18 counts of aggravated statutory rape. She is accused of setting up meetings with the victims through social media and offering items in return for sexual favors. The alleged crimes occurred from early in 2020 to late 2021, McMinn County Sheriff Joe Guy said.</description></item><item><title>Representative Matt Gaetz's ex-girlfriend granted immunity in sex trafficking probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</guid><description>The woman testified in front of a federal grand jury last week hearing evidence in the Gaetz investigation.
Summary Gaetz has been under investigation to determine if he violated sex trafficking laws and obstructed justice in that probe. Gaetz has previously denied all wrongdoing, and has said he has never paid for sex nor had sex with an underage girl. One of the sources said she has information related to the investigation of both the sex trafficking and obstruction allegations.</description></item></channel></rss>