<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>return on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/return/</link><description>Recent content in return on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/return/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shkreli ordered to return $64M, is barred from drug industry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e20ec922339ac0b5dd0dc6/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — Martin Shkreli must return $64.6 million in profits he and his former company reaped from jacking up the price and monopolizing the market for a lifesaving drug, a federal judge ruled Friday while also barring the provocative, imprisoned ex-CEO from the pharmaceutical industry for the rest of his life.
Summary FILE - Former Turing Pharmaceuticals CEO Martin Shkreli attends the House Committee on Oversight and Reform Committee hearing on Capitol Hill in Washington, Feb.</description></item><item><title>62,000 Los Angeles students and staff test positive for Covid ahead of return to school Tuesday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 07:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd2b33190fd690ef36f36e/</guid><description>As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show.
Summary (CNN) As Los Angeles students and staff prepare to return to school Tuesday, about 62,000 have tested positive for Covid-19, school district data show. The Los Angeles Unified School District (LAUSD) is requiring all students and employees to show a negative test result before returning. It is the nation&amp;rsquo;s second largest district, with more than 640,000 students in grades K-12.</description></item><item><title>Chicago schools cancel classes for fourth day as union fight hits second week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc743e876618a0aae5455a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc743e876618a0aae5455a/</guid><description>Chicago school leaders canceled classes for the fourth day Monday as a standoff with the local teachers' union over Covid-19 protocols entered its second week.
Summary Chicago school leaders canceled classes for the fourth consecutive day on Monday as a standoff with the local teachers' union over remote learning and other Covid-19 safety protocols entered its second week. Later that day, however, Lightfoot appeared to strike a different tone, tweeting that teachers' union leaders were &amp;ldquo;not listening.</description></item></channel></rss>