<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rally on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rally/</link><description>Recent content in rally on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 18:16:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rally/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comedians Rally Around Chris Rock, Express Concern About Violence – Deadline</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62434cc14c792519e0319e81/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 18:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62434cc14c792519e0319e81/</guid><description>Comedians Rally Around Chris Rock, Express Concern About Violence Towards Comics: &amp;quot;Now We All Have To Worry&amp;quot;
Highlights Comedians react to Will Smith&amp;rsquo;s Oscar slap on Chris Rock at the Oscars. Howard Stern: &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t hit people over speech, certainly not at the Academy Awards&amp;rdquo; Kathy Griffin: &amp;ldquo;It’s a very bad practice to walk up on stage and physically assault a Comedian&amp;rdquo; Rosie O&amp;rsquo;Donnell: &amp;ldquo;Bravo to Chris Rock – for not eviscerating will smith [sic.</description></item><item><title>Trucker convoy protest in Washington DC flops as no-one shows up</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f9862dd030b92f5dad1ce/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 16:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f9862dd030b92f5dad1ce/</guid><description>Organisers had expected thousands of people to attend Freedom Convoy event
Highlights National Parks Service had given permission for the demonstration at the Sylvan Theater. Organisers expected several thousand people to rally against Covid-19 mandates. Organiser Kyle Sefcik is an MMA fighter and independent candidate for governor in Maryland. Several trucker convoys are still on their way to DC to oppose Covid mandates. Meanwhile, a security fence has been put in place around the US Capitol grounds as Joe Biden gives his first State of the Union address on Tuesday evening, with Joe Biden giving his first S.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones met with 1/6 committee and says he pleaded the Fifth ‘almost 100 times’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0b94e81066c404de9d405/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 03:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0b94e81066c404de9d405/</guid><description>Summary By Annie Grayer and Oliver Darcy, CNNRight-wing conspiracy theorist Alex Jones met virtually on Monday with the House select committee investigating the January 6 insurrection, he announced on his broadcast. “I just had a very intense experience being interrogated by the January 6 committee,” Jones said on his broadcast on Monday. Jones also relayed on Monday that the committee had asked him whether he had heard of any plans for violence on January 6.</description></item></channel></rss>