<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>allegedly on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/allegedly/</link><description>Recent content in allegedly on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 18:19:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/allegedly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buffalo 911 dispatcher who allegedly hung up on shooting call put on leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62868a20852b80382efd95fe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 18:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62868a20852b80382efd95fe/</guid><description>A 911 dispatcher is on leave and may lose her job after allegedly hanging up on an supermarket employee hiding during this weekend&amp;rsquo;s shooting rampage in Buffalo, New York.
Highlights A 911 dispatcher has been placed on leave and may lose her job after allegedly hanging up on an supermarket employee hiding during this weekend’s shooting rampage in Buffalo, New York. The store employee alleges the dispatcher shouted at her, asked why she was whispering — then hung up.</description></item><item><title>Justice Department charges 12 medical professionals for allegedly fueling the opioid epidemic in Appalachian region</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62733de66bf74f4d6b235120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 03:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62733de66bf74f4d6b235120/</guid><description>A 24-year-old patient died from a morphine overdose after a dentist allegedly wrote three opioid prescriptions for the patient in five days.
Highlights A dozen defendants across eight federal districts have been charged in connection with the illegal prescription and distribution of 5.1 million pills. The defendants span seven states and account for approximately $7 million in opioid-related fraud loss, the Justice Department says. One pharmacist in Florida allegedly sold 219,567 pills of oxycodone and 112,840 pills of hydromorphone on the black market between 2019 and 2021.</description></item><item><title>Florida family Makarenkos allegedly beat, blinded gay man after he 'made' their son gay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62631a67743e163aaeb2b5f5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62631a67743e163aaeb2b5f5/</guid><description>“Unfortunately, your son’s gay,” the 31-year-old Florida man told the Makarenkos, including his alleged lover, as they allegedly attacked him last year, according to records obtained by The Washington Post.
Highlights A Florida man was brutally beaten and blinded by members of his boyfriend’s family because they believed the man “made” their son gay, according to court documents. Prosecutors allege that Inna Makarenko, 44; Yevhen Makarenkos, 43; and two of their adult sons, Oleh, 21, and Vladyslav, 25, ambushed the man at his apartment in Pompano Beach last August and beat him so badly that they left him severely injured in a pool of his own blood for about 14 hours.</description></item><item><title>Two men allegedly impersonated federal agents to get access to Secret Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f882e0a796d814d38aa67/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:56:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f882e0a796d814d38aa67/</guid><description>The two allegedly used fake credentials to get closer to members of federal law enforcement agencies, including Secret Service agents assigned to the first lady.
Highlights Arian Taherzadeh, 40, and Haider Ali, 35, have been arrested for allegedly impersonating federal agents. The two allegedly obtained paraphernalia, handguns and assault rifles used by federal law enforcement agencies. Four Secret Service agents have been placed on administrative leave amid the investigation. The men were discovered on March 14, when the U.</description></item><item><title>Man accused of hiding in woman's attic, secretly filming her after meeting on OnlyFans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622280bbfc3ec51580e8f23a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 21:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622280bbfc3ec51580e8f23a/</guid><description>A Pennsylvania man is accused of breaking into a New Hampshire woman&amp;rsquo;s home and hiding out in her attic after they met through her OnlyFans account, according
Highlights Mauricio Damian Guerrero, 20, from Bensalem, was arrested and charged with four counts of burglary. Guerrero allegedly broke into the woman&amp;rsquo;s Somersworth home early in the morning on Feb. The woman said she met Guerrero through her OnlyFans account and gave him her address because he said he wanted to buy her a television and fireplace.</description></item><item><title>Florida woman charged with murder after allegedly stabbing husband 140 times</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62133b70e8991d2bc69fd4ea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 07:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62133b70e8991d2bc69fd4ea/</guid><description>A Florida woman has been charged with first-degree murder after police say she allegedly stabbed her husband more than 140 times.
Highlights Joan Burke, 61, who is being held without bond, appeared before a Palm Beach County judge on Sunday via video conference. Police say they responded to Burke&amp;rsquo;s home on the evening of February 11 after receiving a call from a man who identified himself as the son of the suspect.</description></item><item><title>Mom sues social media giants for allegedly driving her 11-year-old daughter to suicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5102d956e5f086b4eb3f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5102d956e5f086b4eb3f/</guid><description>A Connecticut mother filed a lawsuit last month against Meta and Snap for allegedly causing the death of her 11-year-old daughter.
Highlights Selena Rodriguez, 11, died by suicide last July. A Connecticut mom filed a lawsuit against Meta Platforms Inc. and Snap for allegedly causing her daughter&amp;rsquo;s death. Selena suffered &amp;ldquo;severe mental harm, leading to physical injury,&amp;rdquo; according to the lawsuit. Experts have been debating the effects social media has on children and teens.</description></item></channel></rss>