<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mom on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mom/</link><description>Recent content in mom on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 03:50:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Woman charged after gun in son's backpack goes off at school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285be822b25508e3f9fff64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 03:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285be822b25508e3f9fff64/</guid><description>Chicago police say a mother has been charged with child endangerment after a gun in her second grader’s backpack accidentally discharged at school, injuring a 7-year-old classmate
Highlights Chicago police say a gun in a second grader’s backpack accidentally discharged at school. The 28-year-old woman appeared in court on Wednesday on three misdemeanor child endangerment counts. A judge ordered her release from Cook County Jail on $1,000 bond. The bullet ricocheted off the floor and grazed the child&amp;rsquo;s abdomen, police said.</description></item><item><title>Vermont man accused of killing mom, grandfather in attempt to get millions in inheritance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bac21884a163cd02193aa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:29:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bac21884a163cd02193aa/</guid><description>A 28-year-old Vermont man is accused of killing his grandfather to obtain trust fund money and later killing his mother while they were at sea for a purported
Highlights Nathan Carman, 28, is accused of killing his grandfather to obtain trust fund money. His mother, Linda, disappeared during a 2016 fishing trip on her son&amp;rsquo;s boat, prosecutors say. He is expected to be arraigned Wednesday in U.S. District Court in Rutland, Vermont.</description></item><item><title>Florida mom finds toddler locked inside day care after workers left for the day</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62114f4e214d6ddc659c492c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62114f4e214d6ddc659c492c/</guid><description>Authorities are investigating a Florida day care center where a mother found her 2-year-old daughter alone and locked inside after workers left for the day,
Highlights Authorities are investigating a Florida day care center where a mother found her 2-year-old daughter alone and locked inside after workers left for the day. The case was being investigated by the local child protection agency. The day care worker responsible for checking out children left at 6:20 p.</description></item><item><title>Mom sues social media giants for allegedly driving her 11-year-old daughter to suicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5102d956e5f086b4eb3f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5102d956e5f086b4eb3f/</guid><description>A Connecticut mother filed a lawsuit last month against Meta and Snap for allegedly causing the death of her 11-year-old daughter.
Highlights Selena Rodriguez, 11, died by suicide last July. A Connecticut mom filed a lawsuit against Meta Platforms Inc. and Snap for allegedly causing her daughter&amp;rsquo;s death. Selena suffered &amp;ldquo;severe mental harm, leading to physical injury,&amp;rdquo; according to the lawsuit. Experts have been debating the effects social media has on children and teens.</description></item><item><title>Mom who took her child into Capitol during riot gets prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d90c7b8e0e41a7ab1aeb9e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d90c7b8e0e41a7ab1aeb9e/</guid><description>A North Carolina woman who brought her 14-year-old son into the U.S. Capitol during last year&amp;rsquo;s riot was sentenced Friday to three months imprisonment. U.S. District Judge Colleen Kollar-Kotelly said she finds it “very hard to comprehend” why Virginia Marie Spencer and her husband took their child into the building during a violent insurrection.
Summary Mom who took her child into Capitol during riot gets prisonFILE - Violent protesters, loyal to President Donald Trump, storm the Capitol in Washington on Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>