<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>change on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/change/</link><description>Recent content in change on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 20:14:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Fossil fuels are choking humanity’: Major UN report sounds the alarm on climate impacts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d2d0583ddef185fb07540/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 20:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d2d0583ddef185fb07540/</guid><description>The IPCC&amp;rsquo;s latest report examines the impacts of the climate emergency on nature and people around the world.
Highlights The world faces unavoidable climate hazards in the next two decades with global heating of 1.5 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels. The U.N. &amp;rsquo;s Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, approved by 195 member states, makes clear that minor, reactive or incremental changes are no longer sufficient to tackle the climate emergency. The analysis provides world leaders with a gold standard summation of modern climate science at a time when there are fears Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine could distract policymakers from taking coordinated action.</description></item><item><title>CDC to significantly ease pandemic mask guidelines Friday | WTOP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218b92ed831908d2b2228a7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 11:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218b92ed831908d2b2228a7/</guid><description>The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday, according to two people familiar with the matter, meaning most Americans will no longer be advised to wear masks in indoor public settings.
Highlights The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday. The change comes as the Biden administration moves to shift its focus to preventing serious illness and death from the virus, rather than all instances of infection.</description></item><item><title>New Virginia Governor Youngkin to Lift School Mask Mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 09:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</guid><description>New Virginia governor Glenn Youngkin says he’s against school mask and vaccine mandates, plus will change COVID-19 policies after his 2022 inauguration.
Summary What to Know Virginia&amp;rsquo;s incoming governor, Glenn Youngkin, said he will rescind the statewide K-12 mask mandate. The removal of the school mask mandate may disproportionately affect low-income residents and communities of color, a political science professor said. Glenn Youngkin said after he was sworn in that he signed an executive order lifting the statewide school mask mandate.</description></item></channel></rss>