<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>banned on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/banned/</link><description>Recent content in banned on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 12:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/banned/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tory MP arrested on suspicion of rape and banned from Commons – reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284e5d3247053e9feca08f9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 12:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284e5d3247053e9feca08f9/</guid><description>MP arrested on suspicion of indecent assault, sexual assault, rape, abuse of position of trust and misconduct
Highlights MP arrested on suspicion of indecent assault, sexual assault, rape, abuse of position of trust and misconduct in public office. Metropolitan Police said offences are alleged to have taken place between 2002 and 2009. MP&amp;rsquo;s arrest followed a two-year investigation and remains in custody. Whips’ Office has asked MP not to come to parliament while investigation is ongoing.</description></item><item><title>Actor Will Smith banned from attending Oscars for 10 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250a51e3c436a46c45715d2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 21:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250a51e3c436a46c45715d2/</guid><description>Will Smith will not be allowed to attend the Academy Awards for the next 10 years, as a result of his slapping comedian Chris Rock on stage during this year&amp;rsquo;s Oscar ceremony, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts &amp;amp; Sciences announced in a statement obtained by CNN.
Highlights Will Smith will not be allowed to attend the Academy Awards for the next 10 years. The decision was made during a Board of Governors meeting held earlier in the day in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>Two students and ACLU sue Missouri school district over removing 8 books from libraries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210ed2b43aeb25326800481/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 13:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210ed2b43aeb25326800481/</guid><description>Two students have sued a Missouri school district over its decision to remove eight books from school libraries, arguing the novels were banned because they discuss issues surrounding race, gender and sexual identity.
Highlights Two students have sued a Missouri school district over its decision to remove eight books from school libraries. The ACLU argues the novels were banned because they discuss issues surrounding race, gender and sexual identity. The lawsuit was filed Tuesday by the American Civil Liberties Union of Missouri (ACLU) against the Wentzville School District on behalf of the students who are minors and not named in the complaint.</description></item><item><title>Hymen repair surgery and virginity testing to be banned in UK</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f056fcbc6075efe2a185ff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f056fcbc6075efe2a185ff/</guid><description>The practice is linked to virginity in some cultures and has been described as a form of violence.
Summary She moved to the UK in 2017 but when she found out her daughter was not a virgin, she says she was very nervous and worried and they discussed the surgery. But after working with MEWso, she said she realised she should not impose the same injustice on her daughter. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>