<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ceo on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ceo/</link><description>Recent content in ceo on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ceo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk decides not to join Twitter board, says CEO Parag Agrawal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253ffcf02c6c04468c2468f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253ffcf02c6c04468c2468f/</guid><description>Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk abandoned his plans to join the board of Twitter after buying a 9% stake.
Highlights Tesla CEO Elon Musk has abandoned plans to join the board of Twitter. Musk proposed changes to Twitter&amp;rsquo;s subscription service, including price changes. Musk remains the largest shareholder of the social media company. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s stock briefly tumbled over 8% to less than $43 a share Monday, before recovering slightly. Musk&amp;rsquo;s appointment would have started on Saturday, &amp;ldquo;contingent on a background check and formal acceptance,&amp;rdquo; Twitter CEO says.</description></item><item><title>Spotify CEO condemns Rogan's use of racial slurs, but says company won't be 'silencing' him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200e28519f8be851f2333a1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 09:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200e28519f8be851f2333a1/</guid><description>Daniel Ek, the chief executive of Spotify, addressed Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s past use of racial slurs on Sunday night, telling staff in a memo that while he found the comments &amp;quot;incredibly hurtful&amp;quot; and inconsistent with company values, he did not believe &amp;quot;silencing&amp;quot; the podcaster was the answer.
Highlights Daniel Ek, the chief executive of Spotify, addressed Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s past use of racial slurs on Sunday night. He told staff in a memo that while he found the comments &amp;ldquo;incredibly hurtful&amp;rdquo; and inconsistent with company values, he did not believe &amp;ldquo;silencing&amp;rdquo; the podcaster was the answer.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer CEO says two Covid vaccine doses aren’t ‘enough for omicron’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dde1f3795b81724024aa32/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dde1f3795b81724024aa32/</guid><description>Bourla said the two-dose vaccine has lost its protective power against infection and its ability to prevent hospitalization has also dropped.
Summary John Thys | AFP | Getty ImagesPfizer CEO Albert Bourla on Monday said two doses of the company&amp;rsquo;s vaccine may not provide strong protection against infection from the Covid omicron variant, and the original shots have also lost some of their efficacy at preventing hospitalization. Bourla, in an interview at J.</description></item><item><title>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records were subpoenaed by House Jan. 6 committee</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6e80ff951d68b8d8b3f15/</guid><description>MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell says his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol.
Summary My Pillow CEO Michael Lindell is seen outside the door of the West Wing at the White House on Friday, Jan 15, 2021 in Washington, DC. MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell, an ally of former President Donald Trump, said his phone records have been subpoenaed by the House committee investigating the origins of the deadly riot that took place on Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>