<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>father on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/father/</link><description>Recent content in father on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/father/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mother charged after Florida toddler fatally shoots father</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f23d4a496fbce80d7a5bd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f23d4a496fbce80d7a5bd/</guid><description>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — A 2-year old boy fatally shot his father in an accident after finding a gun, and the boy&amp;rsquo;s mother is now facing criminal charges, authorities in Florida said Monday. Reggie Mabry, 26, was fatally shot late last month while he was playing a video game.
Highlights Reggie Mabry, 26, was fatally shot late last month while he was playing a video game. The gun was fired by his 2-year-old son in the home he shared with his wife and their three children.</description></item><item><title>A man who attacked and blamed an Asian family for Covid-19 pleaded guilty to hate crimes charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217cb5c0f3d6d9f7c376611/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217cb5c0f3d6d9f7c376611/</guid><description>A 21-year-old Texas man pleaded guilty to federal hate crime charges after he brutally attacked and blamed an Asian family whom he believed to be Chinese for the Covid-19 pandemic, prosecutors announced Wednesday.
Highlights Jose Gomez III saw a Burmese family with three young children enter a Sam’s Club in Texas. He followed them into the store and attacked the family, slashing the father and a child who was then 6 years old.</description></item><item><title>Britney Spears says father took millions during conservatorship</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8a622c23a6aadc3b45934/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8a622c23a6aadc3b45934/</guid><description>Britney Spears&amp;rsquo; legal team said her father, Jamie Spears, should be able to pay his own legal fees because he “enriched himself” by “taking more than $6
Summary Jamie Spears, 69, made $6,314,307.99 throughout the controversial conservatorship, which was terminated in November, the legal team said in documents filed by Britney Spears’ attorney, Matthew Rosengart. The documents also accuse Jamie Spears of having used some of the earnings to pitch his own television show.</description></item></channel></rss>