<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>special on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/special/</link><description>Recent content in special on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/special/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Father and son craft 19 custom caskets for the Uvalde shooting victims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a15dbebefacfc4bf0b0e2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 14:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a15dbebefacfc4bf0b0e2/</guid><description>Each caskets is carefully handpainted and decorated to relect the child&amp;rsquo;s interests and personality.
Highlights Trey Ganem, 50, and his son Billy, 25, have been working around the clock to craft a custom casket for each of the children killed in last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting in Uvalde, Texas. Each casket is carefully handpainted and decorated to relect the child&amp;rsquo;s interests and personality. Ganem has donated the caskets to the families, making sure they have one less thing to think about.</description></item><item><title>Dave Chappelle attacked onstage at L.A.'s Hollywood Bowl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728101493ebf3bc464a6af/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 13:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728101493ebf3bc464a6af/</guid><description>The controversial comic laughed off the incident after being tackled, and video appeared to show the person who charged him being beaten onstage.
Highlights Comedian Dave Chappelle was attacked onstage Tuesday night as he performed at Los Angeles&amp;rsquo; Hollywood Bowl arena. A man appeared to run onto the stage and tackle the comic before he was set upon by multiple people onstage. The motivation for the attack remained unclear, and there was no immediate response from the L.</description></item><item><title>Kidnapped Ukrainian mayor freed in 'special operation,' officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233a429752aecd02bb0c39f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233a429752aecd02bb0c39f/</guid><description>The mayor of Melitopol was allegedly abducted by Russian forces on March 11.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky calls for release of Melitopol&amp;rsquo;s mayor. Mayor Ivan Fedorov has been freed in a &amp;ldquo;special operation,&amp;rdquo; an adviser to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s presidential office says. Russian forces allegedly abducted the mayor on March 11. The Russian-controlled separatists then announced they were bringing charges against him for &amp;ldquo;aiding terrorism&amp;rdquo; A pro-Russian lawmaker says a &amp;ldquo;committee of the chosen&amp;rdquo; is now taking over the running of the city, a lawmaker tells people not to allow pro-Ukrainian activists to &amp;ldquo;destabilize&amp;rdquo; the situation.</description></item><item><title>Three Canadian Special Forces members under investigation for protest involvement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a55d822339ab1effef365/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 13:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a55d822339ab1effef365/</guid><description>Three members of the Canadian Special Operations Forces are under investigation for allegedly supporting the protests against COVID-19 restrictions in Ottawa, the Department of National Defence said on Sunday.
Highlights Three members of the Canadian Special Operations Forces are under investigation for allegedly supporting the protests against COVID-19 restrictions in Ottawa. The department did not detail how the three unidentified members were involved in the demonstrations. The &amp;ldquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rdquo; protests, started in the national capital Ottawa by Canadian truckers opposing a vaccinate-or-quarantine mandate for cross-border drivers, entered its 17th day on Sunday.</description></item></channel></rss>