<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>emergency on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/emergency/</link><description>Recent content in emergency on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:15:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/emergency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. eyes emergency contraception grants if top court cuts abortion rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273958d4f285b3e829a540a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273958d4f285b3e829a540a/</guid><description>U.S. President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration was looking at grants to help fund expanding access to emergency contraception as a possible response if the Supreme Court overturns a 1973 decision that legalized abortion nationwide, White House spokesperson Jen Psaki said on Wednesday.
Highlights U.S. President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s administration looking at grants to help fund expanding access to emergency contraception as a possible response if the Supreme Court overturns a 1973 decision that legalized abortion nationwide.</description></item><item><title>Canadian police secure downtown Ottawa as truckers’ protest ends</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621390c49fd93b849866b945/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 13:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621390c49fd93b849866b945/</guid><description>Three-week occupation over Covid precautions and Trudeau government ends with 76 vehicles towed and 191 arrests
Highlights Police secure downtown core of Ottawa with fencing after two days of tense standoffs and 191 arrests. Police used pepper spray and stun grenades on protesters, clearing most of the area in front of parliament. Prime Minister Justin Trudeau invoked emergency powers to give his government wider authority to stop the protests. Protesters initially wanted an end to cross-border Covid-19 vaccine mandates for truck drivers but the blockade turned into a demonstration against Trudeau.</description></item></channel></rss>