<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>central on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/central/</link><description>Recent content in central on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 16:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/central/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Turkey’s inflation soars to 73%, a 23-year high, as food and energy costs skyrocket</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a32e2543aa6618f383dc0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 16:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a32e2543aa6618f383dc0/</guid><description>Economic analysts expect Turkey&amp;rsquo;s inflation will only get worse as the country grapples with President Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s unorthodox strategy on monetary policy.
Highlights Turkey&amp;rsquo;s inflation for the month of May rose by an eye-watering 73.5% year on year. Food prices in the country of 84 million rose 91.6% in May. President Erdogan has for years refused to meaningfully raise rates to cool the resulting inflation. He instructed the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank to repeatedly slash borrowing rates last year even as inflation continued to rise.</description></item><item><title>Apple workers at New York's Grand Central store take steps to unionize</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625df010eb1bf025bee91249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 23:11:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625df010eb1bf025bee91249/</guid><description>Apple workers at the company&amp;rsquo;s Grand Central store in Manhattan have begun collecting signatures from workers, according to a website created by organizers.
Highlights Workers at Apple&amp;rsquo;s flagship Grand Central Terminal retail store in New York City are taking steps to unionize. Organizers are in the process of collecting signatures from workers, according to a website. Apple says it offers &amp;ldquo;very strong compensation and benefits&amp;rdquo; for full-time and part-time employees. Amazon workers at a Staten Island warehouse voted in the company&amp;rsquo;s first U.</description></item></channel></rss>