<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>identity on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/identity/</link><description>Recent content in identity on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:23:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Yorkers can now choose an 'X' gender marker on their state IDs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292f524f64f5f4a0137f934/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292f524f64f5f4a0137f934/</guid><description>Residents of New York can now choose an &amp;quot;X&amp;quot; marker for their gender on state identification cards
Highlights Residents of New York can now choose an &amp;ldquo;X&amp;rdquo; marker for their gender on state identification cards. The Gender Recognition Act will go into full effect on June 24. The legislation will allow people to attest to their own gender identity when petitioning a court or updating an identification document. It will also eliminate the requirement to publish name changes in a local newspaper, and allow parents the choice to be designated as &amp;ldquo;father,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;mother&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;parent&amp;rdquo; on their child&amp;rsquo;s birth certificate, the legislation will also allow parents to be named &amp;ldquo;father&amp;rdquo; on the birth certificate of their child, among other things, the act will go to full effect.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell to reveal identity of ‘8 John Does’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4f80e917579524bf69b14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 05:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4f80e917579524bf69b14/</guid><description>Convicted sex-trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell will no longer fight to protect the identity of eight men who allegedly had sex with young women she and her billionaire paedophile pal Jeffrey Epstein procured for them.
Summary The British socialite and convicted sex-trafficker has ended her fight to keep the identity of eight “John Does” a secret, her lawyer said in a letter. Convicted sex-trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell will no longer fight to protect the identity of eight men who allegedly had sex with young women she and her billionaire paedophile pal Jeffrey Epstein procured for them.</description></item></channel></rss>