<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>travel on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/travel/</link><description>Recent content in travel on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 18:18:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canada and Mexico prepare to accept Americans seeking abortions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d4f522e375b4d4f7a7420/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 18:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d4f522e375b4d4f7a7420/</guid><description>If the US supreme court does vote to overthrow Roe v Wade, many Americans in need of surgical abortions could be forced to travel to Canada or Mexico
Highlights Leaked draft decision indicates U.S. Supreme Court could overturn Roe v Wade. An estimated 26 states are likely to ban abortion, according to Guttmacher Institute. Canada&amp;rsquo;s minister of families, Karina Gould, reaffirmed that Americans can access abortion services in Canada. Americans without immigration status in Canada are charged about C$500 (US$388) for a surgical abortion.</description></item><item><title>Tesla will pay travel costs for staff seeking abortion services</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62768cd15e97503a68e64e08/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62768cd15e97503a68e64e08/</guid><description>Tesla is covering travel costs for employees seeking out-of-state abortions, joining the ranks of major companies who’ve introduced a similar policy to benefit
Highlights Tesla is covering travel costs for employees seeking out-of-state abortions. The car maker expanded its Safety Net program and health insurance offerings last year to include “travel and lodging support for those who may need to seek healthcare services that are unavailable in their home state” The company moved its corporate headquarters last year from Silicon Valley to Texas, which passed a law banning abortions at roughly six weeks of pregnancy.</description></item><item><title>L.A. bans official travel to Florida and Texas over parents' rights bill, LGBTQ+ policies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fd3388a2df1d47de220b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 06:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fd3388a2df1d47de220b6/</guid><description>TheLos Angeles County Board of Supervisors voted unanimously on Tuesday to suspend all official travel to both Florida and Texas. The travel ban was proposed and passed in response to legislationenacted in Florida and Texas. Critics, including the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors, claim those bills target LGBTQ+ youth and families. The board reportedly voted in support of the ban in order to support &amp;quot;affirming care and inclusion for LGBTQ+ youth and their families.</description></item><item><title>Citigroup to cover travel expenses for abortions as U.S. states curb access</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62338838c3f71afefd0801dc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 19:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62338838c3f71afefd0801dc/</guid><description>Citigroup Inc has started covering travel expenses for employees who go out of state for abortions because of newly enacted restrictions in Texas and other places, becoming the first major U.S. bank to make that commitment.
Highlights Citigroup Inc has started covering travel expenses for employees who go out of state for abortions because of newly enacted restrictions in Texas and other places. The new policy is &amp;ldquo;in response to changes in reproductive healthcare laws in certain states in the U.</description></item><item><title>Citi's response to abortion bans: We'll pay for workers to travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623299d241630a7aa830e455/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 02:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623299d241630a7aa830e455/</guid><description>After a number of US states passed laws severely restricting access to abortions, Citigroup this week said it is providing employees with travel benefits to facilitate access to abortion clinics.
Highlights Citigroup&amp;rsquo;s new policy covers employees&amp;rsquo; expenses when traveling to seek an abortion, according to a person with knowledge of the matter. The company declined to comment beyond what it published in its proxy statement. Several states have recently passed laws that make many abortions illegal.</description></item><item><title>US State Department issues 'do not travel' warning for Ukraine as embassy staff is told to leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee326a11fc5601404430b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee326a11fc5601404430b2/</guid><description>The U.S. State Department has ordered the evacuation of American citizens in Ukraine amid the threat of Russian military action.
Summary The U.S. State Department has ordered the evacuation of American citizens in Ukraine amid the threat of Russian military action. &amp;ldquo;U.S. citizens in Ukraine should be aware that Russian military action anywhere in Ukraine would severely impact the U.S. Embassy’s ability to provide consular services, including assistance to U.S. citizens in departing Ukraine,&amp;rdquo; the State Department said in a travel advisory.</description></item><item><title>Australia cancels visa of tennis No.1 Djokovic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6a1bb196081507306385f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6a1bb196081507306385f/</guid><description>But a decision on whether to deport the Serbian tennis star will only happen on Monday.
Summary The decision infuriated many in a country that has seen a surge in Covid-19 cases, and where over 90% of those over 16 are fully vaccinated. People have also had to endure some of the world&amp;rsquo;s strictest restrictions, and some still cannot travel between states or leave the country. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>CDC: 'Avoid cruise travel, regardless of vaccination status'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ced4bcbc79f23f80e7e9b0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ced4bcbc79f23f80e7e9b0/</guid><description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Thursday urged all travelers — vaccinated and unvaccinated — to avoid cruise ship travel due to the omicron variant
Summary The CDC said the coronavirus &amp;ldquo;spreads easily between people in close quarters on board ships, and the chance of getting COVID-19 on cruise ships is very high.&amp;rdquo; It said the travel health notice upgrade from level 3 to level 4 &amp;ldquo;reflects increases in cases onboard cruise ships since identification of the omicron variant.</description></item><item><title>Major airlines are cancelling Christmas Eve flights as their crews call in sick</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c67b3a03a92b41b14d4b45/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 02:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c67b3a03a92b41b14d4b45/</guid><description>At least three major airlines have reported cancelling dozens of flights as illnesses largely tied to the Omicron variant of the coronavirus take a toll on flight crew numbers during the busy holiday travel season.
Summary Delta Air Lines and United Airlines said they cancelled dozens of flights because of staff shortages tied to the Omicron variant. &amp;ldquo;The difference between airline staff and most other businesses is that when you work on a plane, you can&amp;rsquo;t work from home.</description></item></channel></rss>