<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>defamation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/defamation/</link><description>Recent content in defamation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:21:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/defamation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandy Hook families’ defamation damages trial against Alex Jones to move forward in CT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628daebfb0b099bc309dc2b2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:21:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628daebfb0b099bc309dc2b2/</guid><description>Representatives for Alex Jones and the Sandy Hook families reached an agreement in&amp;hellip;
Highlights A federal judge clears the way for Sandy Hook families to have the defamation lawsuit they won against Alex Jones released from bankruptcy protection. The families&amp;rsquo; target will be Jones himself and his parent company Free Speech Systems. A trial to determine the damages Jones must pay for calling the worst crime in Connecticut history “staged,’ “synthetic,” “manufactured,“ and “a giant hoax” A federal bankruptcy judge in Texas released Jones from Chapter 11 protection and sent his defamation cases back to state court in Texas.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families can resume defamation lawsuits vs InfoWars owner, attorneys say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fe4567c322dfc0e69381c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 17:18:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fe4567c322dfc0e69381c/</guid><description>Families of the victims of the 2012 Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre will be dismissed from the InfoWars bankruptcy case, allowing them to resume their defamation lawsuits against the website&amp;rsquo;s owner, conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, attorneys said in court on Friday.
Highlights Families of the victims of the 2012 Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre will be dismissed from the InfoWars bankruptcy case. They will be able to resume their defamation lawsuits against the website&amp;rsquo;s owner, conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, attorneys said in court on Friday.</description></item><item><title>Trump ally Devin Nunes loses CNN defamation appeal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625880d192352602c15715a4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 20:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625880d192352602c15715a4/</guid><description>A federal appeals court said Devin Nunes, the former California congressman and an ally of former U.S. President Donald Trump, cannot revive his defamation lawsuit against CNN over reports he was involved in efforts to uncover damaging Ukraine-related information about Joe Biden.
Highlights A federal appeals court said Devin Nunes cannot revive his defamation lawsuit against CNN. The 2nd U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Manhattan said Nunes failed to seek a correction fast enough, or show he deserved &amp;ldquo;special damages&amp;rdquo; for economic loss.</description></item></channel></rss>