<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>thought on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/thought/</link><description>Recent content in thought on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 06:14:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Whoopi Goldberg Returns To ‘The View’ After Two-Week Suspension: “We’re Going To Keep Having Tough Conversations”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211dc314fb9d5f74a9e6e88/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 06:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211dc314fb9d5f74a9e6e88/</guid><description>Whoopi Goldberg returned to The View on Monday after a two-week suspension, opening the show by telling viewers, &amp;quot;Yes, I am back.&amp;quot;
Highlights Whoopi Goldberg returned to The View on Monday after a two-week suspension over comments she made about the Holocaust. Goldberg had apologized, but ABC News president Kim Godwin called her comments “wrong and hurtful” The Anti Defamation League condemned the remarks, and she later issued a written apology.</description></item><item><title>'I thought it was a joke': Canada Post employee sent home for wearing N95 mask instead of company-provided cloth or disposable mask</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e96af87fea95a78491e972/</guid><description>A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks.
Summary WINNIPEG -A Winnipeg man who works for Canada Post as a mail carrier said he was sent home for the type of mask he was wearing, despite it being better than the company&amp;rsquo;s masks. &amp;ldquo;Right away a supervisor came up to me and told me I can&amp;rsquo;t wear that mask,&amp;rdquo; said Gallagher.</description></item></channel></rss>