<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>newspaper on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/newspaper/</link><description>Recent content in newspaper on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:12:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/newspaper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia seizes Audemars Piguet watches in apparent retaliation for Swiss sanctions | Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241981752d946f2cb236505/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241981752d946f2cb236505/</guid><description>Timepieces worth millions of dollars were taken by FSB agents in Moscow, according to a Swiss paper
Highlights Russian agents seize millions of dollars worth of Audemars Piguet watches in Moscow. Swiss paper says move was &amp;rsquo;likely an arbitrary repressive measure in response to sanctions&amp;rsquo; Swiss foreign affairs department officials said the move was ‘most likely an arbitrary measure’ Russia was the 17th-biggest export market for Swiss watches in 2021, accounting for 260m Swiss francs of shipments.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Palin loses defamation case against New York Times</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ad3933e58e89ba58acef7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 22:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ad3933e58e89ba58acef7/</guid><description>A U.S. judge on Monday said he will throw out Sarah Palin&amp;rsquo;s defamation lawsuit against the New York Times after concluding that the newspaper did not in an editorial maliciously link the former Alaska governor and 2008 Republican U.S. vice presidential candidate to a mass murder.
Highlights Sarah Palin&amp;rsquo;s defamation lawsuit against the New York Times will be thrown out, U.S. District Judge Jed Rakoff says. The judge says Palin failed to show the Times acted with &amp;ldquo;actual malice&amp;rdquo; in a June 2017 editorial.</description></item></channel></rss>