<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>walk on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/walk/</link><description>Recent content in walk on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:18:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/walk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Musk threatens to walk away from Twitter deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ed188f0b9e51e26078786/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ed188f0b9e51e26078786/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — Elon Musk is threatening to walk away from his $44 billion bid to buy Twitter, accusing the company of refusing to give him information about its spam bot and fake accounts .
Highlights Elon Musk is threatening to end his $44 billion agreement to buy Twitter. Lawyers for the Tesla and SpaceX CEO made the threat in a letter to Twitter dated Monday, June 6, 2022 that the social platform included in a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission.</description></item><item><title>‘Extremely disappointed’: New 40-ton arches collapse onto bridge in downtown Hickory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211a15047c8a8529e01adfc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 02:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211a15047c8a8529e01adfc/</guid><description>Neighbors said it sounded like an earthquake when the arches came crashing down overnight. The arches were part of the city’s multimillion-dollar City Walk Project project. They weighed 40-ton and cost $750,
Highlights Arches fell onto the pedestrian walkway and onto Main Avenue Northeast over Highway 127, near downtown Hickory. Neighbors said it sounded like an earthquake when the arches came crashing down. The arches were part of the city’s multimillion-dollar City Walk Project project, whose contract was signed in June 2019.</description></item></channel></rss>