<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>republican on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/republican/</link><description>Recent content in republican on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 23:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/republican/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former top Republican lawmaker in Colorado received leak of voting data</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282dad5a12759331f0644f9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 23:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282dad5a12759331f0644f9/</guid><description>A former Republican minority leader of the Colorado legislature is among the recipients of a trove of sensitive voting data leaked by a county official working with activists seeking to prove President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s false stolen-election claims, according to court records reviewed by Reuters.
Highlights Elbert County clerk Dallas Schroeder, a former Republican minority leader of the Colorado legislature, is among the recipients of a trove of sensitive voting data leaked by a county official.</description></item><item><title>Ohio Supreme Court rejects Republicans’ fourth set of state legislative maps</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259374134796325c03820a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 09:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6259374134796325c03820a4/</guid><description>Ohio Supreme Court rejects fourth set of state legislative maps under state constitution’s new anti-gerrymandering requirements. Decision gives Republican-controlled Ohio Redistricting Commission until May 6 to come up with new ones. Decision won
Highlights Ohio Supreme Court rejects fourth set of state legislative maps under state constitution’s new anti-gerrymandering requirements. Decision won’t affect May 3 primary election, early voting for which began last week. Decision could lead to federal takeover of state&amp;rsquo;s redistricting process.</description></item><item><title>Alabama passes bill making some transgender healthcare a felony</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62505146df7ff676b6db2ea8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62505146df7ff676b6db2ea8/</guid><description>Alabama lawmakers passed a bill on Thursday that would criminalize gender-affirming healthcare for transgender youth, with a threat of 10 years in prison for medical providers.
Highlights The bill would make it a felony punishable with up to 10 years in prison to provide medical care to minors. The bill is the latest in a flurry of measures in Republican-led states dealing with transgender youth. The American Civil Liberties Union called it the first bill of its kind to make healthcare for transgender youth a felony.</description></item></channel></rss>