<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>seized on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/seized/</link><description>Recent content in seized on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 14:09:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/seized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Highland Park seized their building; the price to get it back was 2 new police cars</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288f262efcc4a527b946a0a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 14:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288f262efcc4a527b946a0a/</guid><description>&amp;quot;It was a shakedown with a badge and a lawyer,&amp;quot; said an attorney for the building&amp;rsquo;s owners.
Highlights Highland Park, Michigan, officials seized marijuana grower&amp;rsquo;s former church. The Kozbials say they were using the building to grow medical marijuana. They say the city made an unusual offer to give them the building back for two police cars. The city says it kept prosecutors in the loop, but that&amp;rsquo;s not true, the prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s office says it didn&amp;rsquo;t even seize the building until after eight months.</description></item><item><title>France seizes luxury yacht of Russian energy boss and Putin confidant Sechin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221e651b8e17bb41496f8a4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 10:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221e651b8e17bb41496f8a4/</guid><description>The French government on Thursday said it had seized a superyacht owned by a company linked to Igor Sechin, chief executive of Russian energy giant Rosneft and close confidant of President Vladimir P…
Highlights The vessel, Amore Vero, was seized at a shipyard at La Ciotat, near Marseille, the finance ministry said. The 85.6-metre (280 ft) boat was made by Netherlands-based yacht builder Oceanco and includes a swimming pool that turns into a helipad, as well as multi-decks including one with a jacuzzi.</description></item></channel></rss>