<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>german on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/german/</link><description>Recent content in german on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 13:25:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/german/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>German intelligence reportedly intercepted Russian radio calls discussing the murder of civilians in Bucha - According to "Der Spiegel"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ee61261805c05e9cc3b5e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 13:25:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ee61261805c05e9cc3b5e/</guid><description>The German government has indications that Russia was involved in the killing of civilians in the Ukrainian town of Bucha based on satellite images, a security source said on Thursday.
Highlights Der Spiegel: German intelligence agency intercepted radio messages from Russian military sources discussing killing of civilians in Bucha. BND foreign intelligence office declined to comment on the matter. Local officials say more than 300 people were killed by Russian forces in the Ukrainian town of Bucha alone, and around 50 of them were executed.</description></item><item><title>Retired pope asks pardon for abuse, but admits no wrongdoing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202974b0e5ae64749e87cdd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 16:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202974b0e5ae64749e87cdd/</guid><description>ROME (AP) — Retired Pope Benedict XVI asked forgiveness Tuesday for any “grievous faults&amp;quot; in his handling of clergy sex abuse cases, but denied any personal or specific wrongdoing after an independent report criticized his actions in four cases while he was archbishop of Munich, Germany.
Highlights Retired Pope Benedict XVI asked forgiveness Tuesday for any “grievous faults” in his handling of clergy sex abuse cases. Independent report criticized his actions in four cases while he was archbishop of Munich, Germany.</description></item><item><title>Germany's top court orders government to protect people with disabilities and pre-existing conditions to ensure they are not discriminated against if over-streteched hospitals are forced to decide who gets care</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb7aee0e3b631155cc0c63/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb7aee0e3b631155cc0c63/</guid><description>Germany&amp;rsquo;s highest court has said officials must draw up rules to protect disabled people during pandemic triage situations. It&amp;rsquo;s an urgent issue, with Germany facing a huge new COVID wave fueled by the omicron variant.
Summary Germany&amp;rsquo;s Constitutional Court ruled on Tuesday that lawmakers must set out legally binding criteria to protect people with disabilities and preexisting conditions in pandemic-related triage situations. The court said legislators had violated the constitution by not previously setting out such rules.</description></item></channel></rss>