<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wall on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wall/</link><description>Recent content in wall on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 05:13:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chip shortage forces Ford to cut production of F-150, Bronco and other important vehicles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff58ba9fc01e3cd1cc393f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 05:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff58ba9fc01e3cd1cc393f/</guid><description>The cuts come a day after Ford significantly missed Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s earnings expectations due to supply chain issues, sending shares to tumble 9.7% on Friday.
Highlights Ford Bronco, Explorer, F-150, Ranger, Mustang Mach-E, Lincoln Aviator SUV among key products. Production downtime is due to an ongoing global shortage of semiconductor chips. The cuts come a day after Ford significantly missed Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s earnings expectations due to lower-than-expected production caused by the supply chain issues, causing shares to tumble 9.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Chief Justice says judges need 'rigorous' training on stock-trading rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d00a21f6cb7876130a4306/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d00a21f6cb7876130a4306/</guid><description>U.S. federal judges need &amp;quot;more rigorous&amp;quot; ethics training to ensure they are not hearing disputes in which they have a financial interest, U.S. Chief Justice John Roberts said in a year-end report published on Friday, citing a recent Wall Street Journal investigation.
Summary REUTERS/Jonathan Ernst/Pool/File PhotoDec 31 (Reuters) - U.S. federal judges need &amp;ldquo;more rigorous&amp;rdquo; ethics training to ensure they are not hearing disputes in which they have a financial interest, U.</description></item><item><title>Student 'Democracy Wall' disappears as Hong Kong's Chinese University removes protest posters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6894bbd90037240ba28a6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 03:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6894bbd90037240ba28a6/</guid><description>Summary A pro-democracy message board at the Chinese University of Hong Kong (CUHK) has been reduced to a blank wall after school authorities stripped off protest posters and stickers from the once-colourful display. A worker carries out maintenance work on the now-empty “Democracy Wall” at the Chinese University of Hong Kong on December 24, 2021. Stickers leftover on Chinese University’s “Democracy Wall” after the authorities’ purge. Photo: Hillary Leung/HKFPBesides the workers, there was nobody in the vicinity of the Democracy Wall.</description></item></channel></rss>