<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mass on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mass/</link><description>Recent content in mass on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 16:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mass/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde school district police chief sworn in as city council member a week after mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6297910ff357bcb272f07a50/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 16:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6297910ff357bcb272f07a50/</guid><description>Pete Arredondo, the Uvalde school district police chief who was the incident commander during the Robb Elementary school shooting, was sworn in as a city council member on Tuesday.
Highlights Pete Arredondo was the incident commander during the Robb Elementary school shooting. He was identified last week by the Texas Department of Public Safety as the person who decided not to breach the classroom where the shooter had holed up and waited for reinforcements.</description></item><item><title>Sacramento shooting leaves multiple victims, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a0017c77057f36ccce9dc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 20:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a0017c77057f36ccce9dc/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif (AP) — Six people were killed and 12 injured in a mass shooting early Sunday as bars and nightclubs were closing in downtown Sacramento and police in California’s state capital were searching for at least one suspect.
Highlights NEW: At least six people were killed and 12 injured in a mass shooting early Sunday morning in Sacramento. NEW: Police recovered “at least one firearm’s from the scene, a police statement said.</description></item></channel></rss>