<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>office on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/office/</link><description>Recent content in office on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:40:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/office/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk tells Tesla employees: Return to the office, or else</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62983f1f70239ae7600d32c0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:40:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62983f1f70239ae7600d32c0/</guid><description>Elon Musk is demanding that Tesla office workers return to in-person work or leave the company.
Highlights Tesla CEO Elon Musk is demanding that Tesla office workers return to in-person work or leave the company. The policy, disclosed in leaked emails, was first reported by electric vehicle news site Electrek.com. Musk said he would personally review any request for exemption from the policy, but that for the most part, “If you don’t show up, we will assume you have resigned” The policy is completely at odds with that of the other tech company, Twitter, which has previously announced employees can continue to work from home “forever” if they prefer.</description></item><item><title>No state charge for billionaire Sanford in child porn probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629202d97e3a77c81363f68a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 11:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629202d97e3a77c81363f68a/</guid><description>SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — The South Dakota attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office has declined to file charges against billionaire T. Denny Sanford following an investigation into possible possession of child pornography, saying it found no “prosecutable offenses” within the state&amp;rsquo;s jurisdiction, according to a court document filed Friday.
Highlights South Dakota attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office has declined to file charges against Sanford following an investigation into possible possession of child pornography, saying it found no “prosecutable offenses” within the state’s jurisdiction.</description></item><item><title>Entire Maine town forced to shut after its only clerk quits over denied vacation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628811cf1436ace65a12f8b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 22:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628811cf1436ace65a12f8b8/</guid><description>The single clerk in a small Maine town resigned after the board of selectmen had denied her vacation request.
Highlights Christen Bouchard was the town clerk in Passadumkeag, Maine, since 2020. She requested a two-week vacation about a month and a half ago. Her plea was denied by the board of selectmen. They claimed that no one was available to step in for her. The town of 356 people also lacks a code enforcement officer, an assessor, an animal control officer, and a school administration official.</description></item><item><title>Man Arrested In Dave Chappelle Attack Charged With Attempted Murder In Alleged Stabbing Of Roommate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628776c582e2c8f1fb84784f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 11:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628776c582e2c8f1fb84784f/</guid><description>Isaiah Lee has been charged with attempted murder for allegedly stabbing his roommate at a transitional housing facility last year.
Highlights Isaiah Lee has pleaded not guilty to the felony charge and is due back in court June 2. Lee, 23, is accused of rushing Chappelle while carrying a replica gun that contained a switchblade. Lee is also accused of stabbing his roommate at a transitional housing facility in December. Lee remains jailed in lieu of $30,000 bail and is ordered to remain at least 100 yards away from the Hollywood Bowl and the comedian&amp;rsquo;s home.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana State Troopers Charged in Beating of Black Man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627deec9322b8a5787b54850/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 05:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627deec9322b8a5787b54850/</guid><description>Troopers Jacob Brown, Dakota DeMoss and George “Kam” Harper were charged last week in the 2020 arrest of Antonio Harris.
Highlights State prosecutors have charged three former Louisiana State Police troopers accused of beating a Black motorist. They are accused of hoisting him to his feet by his hair braids and bragging in text messages that the “whoopin” would give him “nightmares for a long time.” The misdemeanor simple battery charges in the 2020 arrest of Antonio Harris come amid mounting scrutiny of the state’s premier law enforcement agency over allegations of excessive force.</description></item><item><title>Saturday night shootout at McDonald’s in Orange County after woman fires gun at deputies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fbcb55465308b3ca34e20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 11:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fbcb55465308b3ca34e20/</guid><description>Deputies responded to an armed robbery call at a McDonald’s on Saturday night. Deputies said the shooter, a woman in her 30s, fired a handgun inside and made threatening statements. All employees and customers were able to
Highlights Deputies responded to an armed robbery call at a McDonald’s on Saturday night. Deputies said the shooter, a woman in her 30s, fired a handgun inside and made threatening statements. All employees and customers were able to get out unharmed.</description></item><item><title>Joaquin Ciria exonerated after 32 years in prison for wrongful murder conviction</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fea7db241566258d38899/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 11:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625fea7db241566258d38899/</guid><description>Joaquin Ciria was arrested in 1990 and convicted of shooting and killing his friend, Felix Bastarrica, in San Francisco. He has now been exonerated.
Highlights Joaquin Ciria was arrested in 1990 and convicted of shooting and killing his friend Felix Bastarrica. San Francisco DA Chesa Boudin dismissed the case against Ciria after a judge overturned his conviction. Ciria&amp;rsquo;s release date is not yet known, but could be within the next few days.</description></item><item><title>A man was fatally shot by his rescuer after falling in a South Carolina lake. The shooting has been ruled self-defense</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237534082a80b97e446ef2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237534082a80b97e446ef2f/</guid><description>South Carolina prosecutors decided not to file charges in a case where a man who fell off a recreational watercraft was fatally shot by his rescuer, according to the Oconee County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.
Highlights A man and a woman fell off a boat in Oconee County, South Carolina. A sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office says the incident occurred Tuesday afternoon. The man &amp;ldquo;became agitated and began assaulting the couple on the boat,&amp;rdquo; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s statement says.</description></item><item><title>Disney employees and former judge among 108 arrested in human trafficking sting, Florida police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232c333d74c613709eebc2e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 05:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232c333d74c613709eebc2e/</guid><description>Authorities arrested 108 people, including alleged child sexual predators and those seeking prostitutes.
Highlights Authorities arrested 108 people during a six-day undercover human trafficking operation. Among those taken into custody were four Disney employees and a retired judge, police said. Detectives found prostitutes who had posted online advertisements through various websites and social media platforms to identify people who were seeking them out. They also identified adults who they thought were inappropriately communicating with children.</description></item><item><title>Former Deputy Accused Of Raping 14-Year-Old Avoids Jail Time And Sex Offender Registry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223d2017fafb61c1417dae1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223d2017fafb61c1417dae1/</guid><description>Brian Beck, 47, was accused of raping a 14-year-old girl over a 20-month period of time. The former Shelby County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputy pleaded guilty to aggravated assault. He faced 30 years in prison for each
Highlights Brian Beck, 47, was accused of raping a 14-year-old girl over a 20-month period of time. The former Shelby County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputy pleaded guilty to a lesser charge of aggravated assault. The judge suspended a four-year prison term in favor of probation.</description></item><item><title>Tina Peters arrested for allegedly recording court proceeding</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62063690260f4b0a138baf56/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62063690260f4b0a138baf56/</guid><description>Mesa County Clerk and Recorder Tina Peters was arrested in Grand Junction Tuesday, and a judge signed a search warrant to obtain a video recording from her iPad that was allegedly taken by Peters during a court hearing Monday involving her deputy clerk’s burglary and cybercrime charges.
Highlights Mesa County Clerk and Recorder Tina Peters was arrested in Grand Junction Tuesday. A judge signed a search warrant to obtain a video recording from her iPad that was allegedly taken by Peters during a court hearing Monday.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: UK will stand 'shoulder to shoulder' with Kyiv but 'extremely unlikely' to send troops, deputy PM Dominic Raab says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee40740dc840c9ca99bd5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 06:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee40740dc840c9ca99bd5c/</guid><description>Russian troops are mounting on the Ukraine border and the Foreign Office has accused Moscow of plotting to install a puppet leader in Kyiv. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to the UK has vowed to &amp;quot;fight to the death&amp;quot;.
Summary The UK will stand &amp;ldquo;shoulder to shoulder&amp;rdquo; with Ukraine but it is &amp;ldquo;extremely unlikely&amp;rdquo; British troops will be sent to the Russian border, Dominic Raab has said. The deputy prime minister said the UK and other nations will enforce economic and financial sanctions on Moscow if Russia invades Ukraine - as troops mount at the border.</description></item><item><title>Parts of Texas will go from 80 degrees and sunny to an ice storm in 36 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9a33d9129a1a98c6ae7fe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9a33d9129a1a98c6ae7fe/</guid><description>Temperatures across parts of Texas will nosedive this week, from balmy highs Wednesday in the 70s and 80s to below freezing Thursday night into Friday, with the chance of a wintry mix.
Summary A quick burst of wintry precipitation could arrive along the front, including in parts of Southern states and the Mid-Atlantic socked this week by a winter storm. &amp;ldquo;Take Corpus Christi, (Texas,) which could touch 80 degrees today but will see plummeting temperatures and possible snow and ice by Thursday evening,&amp;rdquo; he said.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan to invest $200m in Lithuania to offset Beijing’s sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6da03a14f72f1b76cbf1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6da03a14f72f1b76cbf1c/</guid><description>Taiwan is planning to invest 200 million US dollars in Lithuania, in an effort to shield the country from China&amp;rsquo;s pressu&amp;hellip;
Summary Taiwan is planning to invest 200 million US dollars in Lithuania, in an effort to shield the country from China&amp;rsquo;s pressure. The money will come from Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s National Development Fund as well as private investors. Lithuania has been a subject of undeclared economic sanctions from China after it opened the Taiwanese office.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong pro-democracy news site closes after raid, arrests | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd04ab89a30a5218870c65/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 01:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd04ab89a30a5218870c65/</guid><description>HONG KONG (AP) — A vocal pro-democracy website in Hong Kong shut down Wednesday after police raided its office and arrested seven current and former editors, board members and a journalist in a continuing crackdown on dissent in the semi-autonomous Chinese city.
Summary Editor of Stand News Patrick Lam, center, is escorted by police officers into a van after they searched evidence at his office in Hong Kong, Wednesday, Dec. 29, 2021.</description></item></channel></rss>