<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>s300 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/s300/</link><description>Recent content in s300 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 14:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/s300/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Slovakia says it has given S-300 air defence system to Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251943fe7a27e8d2bb113ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 14:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251943fe7a27e8d2bb113ba/</guid><description>Prime Minister Eduard Heger says donation does not mean the NATO member joined the war.
Highlights Slovakia has donated S-300 air defence system to Ukraine to help it defend against Russian attacks. The donation does not mean the country has joined the conflict, says the Prime Minister. The US has agreed to send weapons to Ukraine in response to Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. The United States has also pledged to send more weapons to the region, including the US Patriot missile system, to help with the Russian invasion of Crimea.</description></item><item><title>Slovakia will send Ukraine S-300 air defenses ‘immediately’ if NATO backfills its weapons</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62344d5551a1ba30b2bffcbe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62344d5551a1ba30b2bffcbe/</guid><description>The Slovakian defense minister said Thursday that his country could give its S-300 missiles to Ukraine without creating a “security gap” within NATO if the West agrees to backfill supplies or provide security guarantees.
Highlights U.S. officials were caught off-guard by the move and promptly declined. Germany’s Defense Ministry indicated in a tweet that it would deploy some of its Patriot systems to Slovakia. Poland in an unusual public announcement, declared it was willing to transfer the jets to U.</description></item></channel></rss>