<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>oldest on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oldest/</link><description>Recent content in oldest on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 16:19:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oldest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Betty Reid Soskin, America’s oldest active ranger, retires at the age of 100</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624725e72db5ecaed9d93fbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 16:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624725e72db5ecaed9d93fbd/</guid><description>She began working with the National Park Service at 84 to reveal ‘untold stories’ of Black people’s efforts during the second world war
Highlights Betty Reid Soskin worked at the Rosie the Riveter/WWII Home Front national historical park in Richmond, California. She was a file clerk in a segregated Union hall in the San Francisco Bay area during the conflict. Her efforts at the park – and her 100th birthday last fall – have captivated the public and received coverage from numerous media outlets, including a profile in the New York Times and a portrait taken by Annie Leibovitz.</description></item><item><title>World's oldest person celebrates 119th birthday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2207f869bf4c9b1a8f411/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2207f869bf4c9b1a8f411/</guid><description>Kane Tanaka at 119 has lived during the Meiji, Taisho, Showa, Heisei and current Reiwa eras
Summary Japan’s Kane Tanaka, who was born a year before the Russo-Japanese War began and is the world’s oldest person, celebrated her 119th birthday in Fukuoka Prefecture on Sunday. Notable people born in 1903 include British novelist George Orwell, film director Yasujiro Ozu and Japanese poet Misuzu Kaneko. Tanaka was recognized by Guinness World Records in March 2019 as the world’s oldest living person at 116 years old and also achieved an all-time Japanese age record when she became 117 years and 261 days old.</description></item></channel></rss>