<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cliff on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cliff/</link><description>Recent content in cliff on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 10:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cliff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4 people fall off California cliff; 1 dead and 2 badly hurt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628caef268ea097dc6f90e4b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628caef268ea097dc6f90e4b/</guid><description>Authorities say four people fell off a Southern California ocean cliff in the early morning darkness
Highlights Four people fell off a Southern California ocean cliff before dawn Monday morning. A 25-year-old man from Los Angeles died at the scene, police say. A fourth person, a man who suffered minor injuries, managed to climb back up from the beach below and alert a passing officer. Two women were airlifted from beach and each hospitalized in critical condition.</description></item><item><title>Fossil of a giant millipede reveals 'the biggest bug that ever lived'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c891a24171aed7c52c0433/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c891a24171aed7c52c0433/</guid><description>A giant millipede, nearly as long as a small car, once crawled around what is now northern England.
Summary (CNN) A fossil of a giant millipede found on a beach in northern England has revealed the &amp;ldquo;biggest bug that ever lived,&amp;rdquo; paleontologists say. The fossil was discovered in January 2018 in a chunk of sandstone that had fallen from a cliff onto the beach at Howick Bay in Northumberland. &amp;ldquo;It was an incredibly exciting find, but the fossil is so large it took four of us to carry it up the cliff face,&amp;rdquo; said Davies in a news statement.</description></item></channel></rss>