<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>twitters on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/twitters/</link><description>Recent content in twitters on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/twitters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk decides not to join Twitter board, says CEO Parag Agrawal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253ffcf02c6c04468c2468f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 10:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253ffcf02c6c04468c2468f/</guid><description>Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk abandoned his plans to join the board of Twitter after buying a 9% stake.
Highlights Tesla CEO Elon Musk has abandoned plans to join the board of Twitter. Musk proposed changes to Twitter&amp;rsquo;s subscription service, including price changes. Musk remains the largest shareholder of the social media company. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s stock briefly tumbled over 8% to less than $43 a share Monday, before recovering slightly. Musk&amp;rsquo;s appointment would have started on Saturday, &amp;ldquo;contingent on a background check and formal acceptance,&amp;rdquo; Twitter CEO says.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk to join Twitter’s board of directors, teases 'significant improvements'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c7998abdc70b658b7d0dc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 17:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c7998abdc70b658b7d0dc/</guid><description>Musk took a 9.2% passive stake in the company.
Highlights Elon Musk named to Twitter&amp;rsquo;s board. The Tesla CEO took a 9.2% passive stake in the company. Twitter CEO tweeted he would push for changes to the product. Jack Dorsey praised the move, saying Musk &amp;ldquo;cares deeply about our world and Twitter&amp;rsquo;s role in it&amp;rdquo; Musk&amp;rsquo;s term is set to expire in 2024, according to a filing with the SEC with 90 days after he was named to the board.</description></item></channel></rss>