<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>general on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/general/</link><description>Recent content in general on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maj. Gen. William Cooley guilty of sexual contact charge in first military trial of an Air Force general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264eb4f26b0ed06a2089e71/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264eb4f26b0ed06a2089e71/</guid><description>An Air Force major general in Ohio has been convicted by a military judge of one of three specifications of abusive sexual contact in the
Highlights Maj. Gen. William Cooley was convicted of one of three specifications of abusive sexual contact in the first-ever military trial of an Air Force general. Officials said the verdict marks the first court-martial trial and conviction of a general officer in the Air Force’s 75-year history.</description></item><item><title>New York Attorney General asks judge to hold Donald Trump in contempt for refusing to turn over documents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f53b199f7ef8e298cdcea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 21:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f53b199f7ef8e298cdcea/</guid><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James also asked the judge to fine Trump $10,000 per day for refusing to comply with an order to turn over documents.
Highlights New York Attorney General Letitia James wants to hold former President Donald Trump in contempt of court for refusing to comply with a judge&amp;rsquo;s order to turn over documents. James is investigating allegations that the Trump Organization manipulated the stated values of various real estate assets to get better financial terms when applying for loans and insurance, and for tax purposes.</description></item><item><title>US disrupts global ‘botnet’ controlled by Russian military intelligence, DoJ says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ef163a3c291e3a4badefb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 14:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ef163a3c291e3a4badefb/</guid><description>Attorney general also announces charges against Russian oligarch Konstantin Malofeyev for sanctions violations
Highlights US has disrupted a global “botnet’ controlled by Russia’s military intelligence agency. Attorney General Merrick Garland also announced charges against Russian oligarch Konstantin Malofeyev for sanctions violations. TV producer John Hanick, 71, a US citizen charged with violations of sanctions and false statements. The indictment is the first of a Russian oligarchs in the US since the Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US charges Russian oligarch, dismantles cybercrime operation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e9ded19710f7e5b98381f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 08:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e9ded19710f7e5b98381f/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration has charged a Russian oligarch linked to the Kremlin with violating U.S. government sanctions, and disrupted a cybercrime operation that was launched by a Russian military intelligence agency, officials said Wednesday.
Highlights The Biden administration has charged a Russian oligarch linked to the Kremlin with violating U.S. government sanctions, and disrupted a cybercrime operation that was launched by a Russian military intelligence agency, officials said Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has appointed Major General Eduard Moskaliov commander of the Joint Forces Operation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231c5cf7d6059bf0d6476c6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 11:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231c5cf7d6059bf0d6476c6/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has appointed Major General Eduard Moskaliov commander of the Joint Forces Operation. — Ukrinform.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin has announced the beginning of the invasion of Ukraine. Russia has been accused of war crimes in Ukraine. The International Criminal Court has begun documenting and investigating Russia&amp;rsquo;s war crimes. The United States, the European Union and other countries have imposed sanctions on Russia as an aggressor state whose international isolation is growing every day.</description></item></channel></rss>