<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>100 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/100/</link><description>Recent content in 100 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:09:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/100/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More than 100 confirmed or suspected cases of monkeypox have been reported in 12 countries, including the US - CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b6b39695a67b92a49b0a9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 11:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b6b39695a67b92a49b0a9/</guid><description>More cases of a rare disease have been reported worldwide, including in the United States &amp;ndash; where one health official said he expects more cases in the days ahead.
Highlights 92 confirmed cases and 28 suspected cases of monkeypox are under investigation in 12 countries, WHO says. The White House Covid-19 response coordinator says he expects &amp;ldquo;a few more&amp;rdquo; cases in the coming days. The United States had between one and five confirmed monkeypox cases as of Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Ottawa police arrest over 100 in push to end convoy blockade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210dfeca1eb61ab31d5a7cb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 12:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210dfeca1eb61ab31d5a7cb/</guid><description>Tensions in Ottawa are high as residents brace for promised police action after three weeks that have seen heated criticism of the response to the convoy blockades.
Highlights Police are in the midst of an operation to clear out the so-called “Freedom Convoy” that has been encamped for 22 days in Ottawa. Over 100 individuals have been arrested so far, with some calling for participants to retreat, and snow barricades are being built up on the streets.</description></item><item><title>Canadian police start arresting protesters in Ottawa</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62107bfda4d2d82b603bee3a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 05:11:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62107bfda4d2d82b603bee3a/</guid><description>OTTAWA, Ontario (AP) — Police arrested scores of demonstrators and towed away vehicles Friday in Canada&amp;rsquo;s besieged capital, and a stream of trucks started leaving under the pressure, raising authorities&amp;rsquo; hopes for an end to the three-week protest against the country&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 restrictions.
Highlights Police arrest scores of demonstrators and tow away vehicles in Canada’s besieged capital. At least 100 people arrested, mostly on mischief charges, and nearly two dozen vehicles had been towed.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones met with 1/6 committee and says he pleaded the Fifth ‘almost 100 times’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0b94e81066c404de9d405/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 03:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0b94e81066c404de9d405/</guid><description>Summary By Annie Grayer and Oliver Darcy, CNNRight-wing conspiracy theorist Alex Jones met virtually on Monday with the House select committee investigating the January 6 insurrection, he announced on his broadcast. “I just had a very intense experience being interrogated by the January 6 committee,” Jones said on his broadcast on Monday. Jones also relayed on Monday that the committee had asked him whether he had heard of any plans for violence on January 6.</description></item><item><title>Over 100 millionaires call for higher taxes worldwide: 'Tax us now'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9088c247558d98d634f4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9088c247558d98d634f4e/</guid><description>A group of ultrawealthy people are asking governments around the world to make them pay more in taxes in order to help close a growing wealth gap.
Summary IRS TAX-FILING SEASON TO KICK OFF ON JAN. 24&amp;quot;As millionaires, we know that the current tax system is not fair,&amp;quot; they wrote. They argued the bedrock of a strong democracy is a fair tax system that bridges the gap between everyday people and the ultrawealthy.</description></item><item><title>Climate change disasters cost the world over $100 billion this year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6f61972f9c69a999f9502/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6f61972f9c69a999f9502/</guid><description>The people affected by expensive climate disasters are often among the most vulnerable—and are asking wealthy nations to pay up.
Summary This past year saw an inundation of climate disasters worldwide. Out of the 15 climate-related disasters described in the study, ten have cost more than a billion dollars worth of damages. This will be the sixth year out of the last ten that have cost over $100 billion due to global natural catastrophes.</description></item><item><title>Paraguay now produces 100% renewable electric energy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf1b10f69443c8e0b39905/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 15:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf1b10f69443c8e0b39905/</guid><description>Itaipu board member Gerardo Blanco said that Paraguay is moving towards the achievement of a historic triple 100%.
Summary RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL - &amp;ldquo;This is an unprecedented historic event,&amp;rdquo; Abdo Benítez said during the inauguration ceremony. He also said that the inclusion of Bahía Negra into the basic service comes after &amp;ldquo;years of negligence, lack of vision and investment in the electricity system.&amp;rdquo; The head of state highlighted that with the electrification of the city of Bahía Negra, Paraguay becomes the region&amp;rsquo;s first country to have 100% renewable electricity supply.</description></item></channel></rss>