<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dog on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dog/</link><description>Recent content in dog on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Couple wakes up to find strange dog sleeping with them in their bed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ccff5863ac5dd88864ec2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 09:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ccff5863ac5dd88864ec2/</guid><description>Jimmy Johnson opened his eyes and didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize the dog sleeping in their bed in Polk County, Tennessee.
Highlights Jimmy Johnson opened his eyes and didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize the dog sleeping in their bed. After a post on Facebook went viral, someone recognized the dog named Nala. The couple thinks the back door was left open by accident and their new furry roommate just wandered in. Nala traveled almost two miles and the adventure eventually ended when the dog wanted some company.</description></item><item><title>Veterinarian in Elmsford Arrested for Six Counts of Animal Cruelty, Assault and Forgery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f77700850980790ec79cb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 06:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f77700850980790ec79cb/</guid><description>Javier Diaz, DMV, 46, the owner of Main Street Animal Hospital, was arrested. Diaz was charged with Forgery 2nd degree, Six counts of animal cruelty and assault 3rd degree. Diaz will be arraigned in Elms
Highlights Javier Diaz, DMV, 46, the owner of Main Street Animal Hospital, charged with Forgery 2nd degree, Six counts of animal cruelty and assault 3rd degree. Diaz gave a certificate of a rabies vaccination and charged a pet owner without actually administering the NYS required vaccination.</description></item><item><title>Ex-girlfriend tosses man's dog off condo balcony in Florida</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f43545540d377676df51f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 10:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f43545540d377676df51f/</guid><description>Officials say a 46-year-old woman has been arrested on animal cruelty charges after throwing a 3-year-old pug named Bucky off of a seventh-floor balcony Clearwater condominium during an argument with her ex-boyfriend
Highlights A 46-year-old woman has been arrested on animal cruelty charges after throwing a pug off of a seventh-floor balcony. Eric Adeson told Clearwater police investigators the woman, who he had dated for several months, also threw his keys and cellphone over the balcony Sunday.</description></item><item><title>Stranded dog saved from rising tide after rescuers attach sausage to drone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea13b660290325961df1f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea13b660290325961df1f7/</guid><description>Team in Hampshire ties sausage to drone as ‘last resort’ to rescue Millie the jack russell from mudflats
Summary It worked gloriously and Millie has been reunited with her grateful owner after following the dangling sausage to higher, safer ground. But they pressed ahead and after checking Civil Aviation Authority regulations, and the MTOW [maximum takeoff weight] of their machines, the rescuers calculated they could attach a single sausage to a drone.</description></item><item><title>Teen suspect accused of shooting 16-year-old 22 times free on bond, court records say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9f79c610c6ce65465d9bf/</guid><description>The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records.
Summary HOUSTON – The boyfriend accused of shooting his 16-year-old girlfriend 22 times while walking her dog in a southwest Houston neighborhood is free on bond, according to court records. Frank Deleon Jr., 17, was taken into custody Monday and charged with murder for the Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>