<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>denver on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/denver/</link><description>Recent content in denver on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 11:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/denver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jury awards $14 million to protesters injured by Denver police during 2020 demonstrations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ef4d7ccedc04c6b9d435a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 11:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ef4d7ccedc04c6b9d435a/</guid><description>Denver police officers violated protesters’ rights during the massive 2020 demonstrations against police brutality, a federal jury concluded Friday, awarding 12 protesters a total of $14 million in compensation following a three-week trial.
Highlights Jury awards 12 protesters a total of $14 million in compensation after a three-week trial. The jury found in favor of the 12 plaintiffs after about five hours of deliberation. The trial is believed to be the first in the U.</description></item><item><title>Trial Starts In Lawsuit Over Denver Cops Use Of Force In George Floyd Protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62276456b92a59b6a712d207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62276456b92a59b6a712d207/</guid><description>Trial for a lawsuit accusing Denver police of using indiscriminate force two years ago against people protesting the killing of George Floyd was set to start Monday in federal court. About a dozen lawsuits have been filed on behalf of over 60 people injured or
Highlights Trial for a lawsuit accusing Denver police of using indiscriminate force two years ago against people protesting the killing of George Floyd was set to start Monday in federal court.</description></item><item><title>Stolen box of human heads investigated by Denver police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62258703dafc5397725852a6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 04:16:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62258703dafc5397725852a6/</guid><description>Denver police are investigating the theft of a box containing human heads from a parked freight company truck, officials said Saturday.
Highlights Box was being transported for medical research purposes. Box was marked with a label that said “Exempt Human Specimen” A dolly was also stolen from the truck. No arrests had been made as of Saturday and investigators asked anyone who finds the box to call police. Someone broke into the truck while it was parked between Wednesday afternoon and Thursday morning, Denver TV station KDVR reports.</description></item></channel></rss>