<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>congress on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/congress/</link><description>Recent content in congress on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 21:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/congress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge: 'More likely than not' that Trump 'corruptly attempted' to block Congress from counting votes on January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624224b07d71fc0d9e494070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 21:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624224b07d71fc0d9e494070/</guid><description>A federal judge said Monday that former President Donald Trump and right-wing attorney John Eastman may have been planning a crime as they sought to disrupt the January 6 congressional certification of the presidential election.
Highlights Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson, President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s pick to replace retiring Justice Stephen Breyer on the U.S. Supreme Court, would become the first Black woman to serve on the Supreme Court if confirmed. Former President Donald Trump and right-wing attorney John Eastman may have been planning a crime as they sought to disrupt the January 6 congressional certification of the presidential election.</description></item><item><title>U.S. to let teens drive big rigs in test program to help ease supply chain shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e843bbe2889b93705a3bd4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e843bbe2889b93705a3bd4/</guid><description>The federal government is moving forward with a plan to let teenagers drive big rigs from state to state in a test program.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos After more than 5 million people signed an online petition, the governor of Colorado has reduced the 110-year sentence for truck driver Rogel Aguilera-Mederos to just 10 years. They say it&amp;rsquo;s unwise to let teenage drivers be responsible for rigs that can weigh 80,000 pounds and cause catastrophic damage when they hit lighter vehicles.</description></item></channel></rss>