<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>months on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/months/</link><description>Recent content in months on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 03:32:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/months/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man who stormed Capitol in caveman costume gets prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275e8464a15320a7d2c0cfc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 03:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275e8464a15320a7d2c0cfc/</guid><description>A New York City judge&amp;rsquo;s son who stormed the U.S. Capitol wearing a furry “caveman&amp;quot; costume was sentenced on Friday to eight months in prison. U.S.
Highlights Aaron Mostofsky, the son of a New York judge, was sentenced on Friday, May 6, 2022, to eight months in prison. U.S. District Judge James Boasberg said he was “literally on the front lines” of the mob’s attack on Jan. 6, 2021. He also sentenced him to one year of supervised release and ordered him to perform 200 hours of community service and pay $2,000 in restitution.</description></item><item><title>One-third of all US child Covid deaths occurred during Omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d7e0260c54b0d52289523/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 05:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d7e0260c54b0d52289523/</guid><description>Children seem to be facing increasing risks as mask mandates are abandoned and vaccination rates stall
Highlights 550 children have died from Covid-19 in the US, compared with 1,017 in the preceding 22 months. Omicron is less severe than Delta, but it is three to five times worse than previous variants, recent CDC research shows. Florida’s surgeon general recently recommended against vaccinating ‘health’ kids given the possibility of side-effects, which remain extremely rare and are outweighed by the vaccines’ protection.</description></item><item><title>Wholesale prices jumped 9.7% , setting record for 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e13bc6a4746d73025930f5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e13bc6a4746d73025930f5/</guid><description>Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.7% for all of 2021, setting an annual record and providing further evidence that inflation is still present at all levels of the U.S. economy
Summary Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.7% for all of 2021, setting an annual record and providing further evidence that inflation is still present at all levels of the U.S. economyWASHINGTON &amp;ndash; Prices at the wholesale level surged by a record 9.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutor: Ethan Crumbley tortured animals, kept severed bird head in bedroom for six months</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d93694f3d554e5f99961ca/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 07:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d93694f3d554e5f99961ca/</guid><description>Summary Friday&amp;rsquo;s bond hearing for the Crumbley parents. Beginning in March, Keast said Ethan Crumbley texted his mother multiple times that he believed there was a demon or ghost inside the house. In May, he filmed himself torturing and killing animals and kept a bird&amp;rsquo;s severed head in a jar in his room for six months. Prosecutors also presented new details about the Crumbley parents&amp;rsquo; behavior in several days following the shooting.</description></item></channel></rss>