<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>chinese on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/chinese/</link><description>Recent content in chinese on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 08:14:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/chinese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Taiwan jets scramble as China air force enters air defence zone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295ce265a3a6982c24b4f82/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 08:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295ce265a3a6982c24b4f82/</guid><description>Taiwan on Monday reported the largest incursion since January by China&amp;rsquo;s air force in its air defence zone, with the island&amp;rsquo;s defence ministry saying Taiwanese fighters scrambled to warn away 30 aircraft in the latest uptick in tensions.
Highlights Taiwan has complained for the past two years of repeated missions by China&amp;rsquo;s air force near the democratically governed island. The latest mission included 22 fighters, as well as electronic warfare, early warning and antisubmarine aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Chinese plane crash that killed 132 caused by intentional act: US officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628481b8ce5c52409be1accb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 05:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628481b8ce5c52409be1accb/</guid><description>The Eastern Airlines jet crashed into a mountain after a steep dive.
Highlights China Eastern Airlines plane crash believed to have been caused by intentional act, U.S. officials tell ABC News. Officials point to flaps not being engaged and landing gear not put down, officials say. The plane slammed into the ground with such force that it created a 66-foot deep hole in the ground. Investigators also looked into one of the pilots&amp;rsquo; personal lives and background and believe he may have been struggling through certain issues right before the crash.</description></item><item><title>Philippines summons Chinese ambassador over navy ship's 'intrusion'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fcc2fad183c6619571549/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 23:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fcc2fad183c6619571549/</guid><description>The Philippines summoned China&amp;rsquo;s ambassador on Monday to explain what it called the &amp;quot;illegal intrusion and lingering presence&amp;quot; of a Chinese navy vessel in waters between some of the archipelago nation&amp;rsquo;s largest islands.
Highlights The Philippines summoned China&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to explain what it called the &amp;ldquo;illegal intrusion and lingering presence&amp;rdquo; of a Chinese navy vessel in waters between some of the archipelago nation&amp;rsquo;s largest islands. The foreign ministry in a statement said the Chinese navy reconnaissance ship entered Philippine waters without permission and lingered from Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>