<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>committee on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/committee/</link><description>Recent content in committee on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:13:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/committee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Stop the Steal' leader cooperating with DOJ's investigation of Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62528371898ee19979fffb00/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62528371898ee19979fffb00/</guid><description>Ali Alexander, a key figure in the &amp;quot;Stop the Steal&amp;quot; movement following the 2020 presidential election, says he has received a grand jury subpoena and has agreed to cooperate with the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s investigation of the January 6, 2021, attack on the US Capitol.
Highlights Ali Alexander says he has received a grand jury subpoena and has agreed to cooperate with the Justice Department’s investigation of the January 6, 2021, attack on the US Capitol.</description></item><item><title>Russian, Belarusian athletes banned from Winter Paralympic Games as IPC reverses ruling</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62221e27ab9cc78d32106724/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 14:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62221e27ab9cc78d32106724/</guid><description>Russian and Belarusian athletes have been banned from the Winter Paralympic Games, less than 24 hours after the IPC announced it would allow Russian and Belarusian athletes to compete as neutral athletes.
Highlights The IPC reversed course and expelled athletes from Russia and Belarus. The change came less than 24 hours after the IPC announced it would allow Russians and Belarusians to compete when the Games open Friday. &amp;ldquo;We were trying to protect the Games from war,&amp;rdquo; IPC president Andrew Parsons said Thursday.</description></item><item><title>CDC to consider increasing time between vaccine doses to lower risk of heart inflammation – Boston 25 News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204e5372ded2e107ea07b72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204e5372ded2e107ea07b72/</guid><description>CDC is considering changing vaccine guidance to lengthen the time in between doses of certain vaccines. Time between the first two doses of the mRNA COVID-19 vaccines appears to reduce the risk of myocarditis, a rare type of heart
Highlights The CDC is considering changing vaccine guidance to lengthen the time in between doses of certain vaccines. The changes would apply to the Pfizer and Moderna COVID-19 vaccines, which use the mRNA technology.</description></item><item><title>Rudy Giuliani, three other Trump allies subpoenaed in January 6 riot probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</guid><description>Former New York mayor Rudy Giuliani Giuliani led efforts for Trump after the 2020 election to challenge results that showed President Joe Biden had won.
Summary Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, personal attorney to U.S. President Donald Trump, speaks in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 7, 2020. Eduardo Munoz | ReutersThe select House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot on Tuesday issued subpoenas to Rudy Giuliani, another former lawyer for ex-President Donald Trump, and two other allies.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6. The ruling Wednesday comes one day after he asked a federal judge in Florida for a temporary restraining order, and it&amp;rsquo;s the first quick response to a lawsuit from a House witness, after several went to court to try to invalidate the committee and block the House from pursuing their phone records.</description></item></channel></rss>