<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>committee on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/committee/</link><description>Recent content in committee on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/committee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rudy Giuliani, three other Trump allies subpoenaed in January 6 riot probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e79b1ad8e5249b944b714a/</guid><description>Former New York mayor Rudy Giuliani Giuliani led efforts for Trump after the 2020 election to challenge results that showed President Joe Biden had won.
Summary Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani, personal attorney to U.S. President Donald Trump, speaks in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 7, 2020. Eduardo Munoz | ReutersThe select House committee investigating the Jan. 6 Capitol riot on Tuesday issued subpoenas to Rudy Giuliani, another former lawyer for ex-President Donald Trump, and two other allies.</description></item><item><title>Michael Flynn loses his legal challenge to the House January 6 probe, one day after filing it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3bc2ebb61fe60afd004b0/</guid><description>Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.
Summary (CNN) Michael Flynn has swiftly lost his bid in court to block a possible House select committee subpoena for his phone records and to hold off demands he speak to the panel investigating January 6.</description></item></channel></rss>