<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>research on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/research/</link><description>Recent content in research on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 06:17:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arthur D. Riggs, Ph.D., the world-renowned diabetes expert who developed the technology that led to the first human synthetic insulin for the treatment of diabetes, has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624152b662dbb2c4cba21f0c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 06:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624152b662dbb2c4cba21f0c/</guid><description>Arthur D. Riggs, Ph.D., the world-renowned diabetes expert who developed the technology that led to the first human synthetic insulin for the treatment of diabetes, died March 23 after battling cancer. A biotechnology pioneer and a longtime leader at City of Hope, Riggs served as director emeritus of Beckman Research Institute of City of Hope and the Arthur Riggs Diabetes &amp;amp; Metabolism Research Institute at City of Hope.
Highlights Arthur D.</description></item><item><title>Microplastics found in human blood for first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cc2384530170bc3c6625b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cc2384530170bc3c6625b/</guid><description>Exclusive: The discovery shows the particles can travel around the body and may lodge in organs
Highlights Microplastic particles found in almost 80% of people tested in their blood. Impact on human health is as yet unknown but researchers are concerned as microplastics cause damage to human cells in the laboratory and air pollution particles are already known to enter the body and cause millions of early deaths a year. Microplastics are 10 times higher in the faeces of babies compared with adults and that babies fed with plastic bottles are swallowing millions of microplastic particle a day.</description></item><item><title>Horned helmets predate Vikings by 3,000 years, originating in the Bronze Age, researchers say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcac829fab26093b0f1d1a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcac829fab26093b0f1d1a/</guid><description>From appearing in the Asterix comic book series, to inspiring an avatar on &amp;quot;The Masked Singer,&amp;quot; Vikings have revealed themselves across pop culture sporting horned helmets to symbolize their ferocity and power.
Summary (CNN) From appearing in the Asterix comic book series, to inspiring an avatar on &amp;ldquo;The Masked Singer,&amp;rdquo; Vikings have revealed themselves across pop culture sporting horned helmets to symbolize their ferocity and power. However, two horned helmets first discovered in Viksø, Denmark have been traced back to Sardinia in the Bronze Age &amp;ndash; dispelling myths that they originated from the Viking era , according to research published in the historical journal Praehistorische Zeitschrift in December.</description></item><item><title>Global spread of autoimmune disease blamed on western diet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db3ee616931e95ee3d7f2c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db3ee616931e95ee3d7f2c/</guid><description>New DNA research by London-based scientists hopes to find cure for rapidly spreading conditions
Summary “Numbers of autoimmune cases began to increase about 40 years ago in the west,” Lee told the Observer. For example, the biggest recent increase in inflammatory bowel disease cases has been in the Middle East and east Asia. Internationally, it is now estimated that cases of autoimmune diseases are rising by between 3% and 9% a year.</description></item><item><title>Japanese university finds drug effective in treating ALS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c59a488f7422468650bf11/</guid><description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University says it has found a drug effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, also known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease.
Summary KYODO NEWS - 5 hours ago - 13:43 | All, JapanJapan&amp;rsquo;s Yamagata University said Friday it has found that a drug being developed for the treatment of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s is also effective in treating amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, more commonly known as Lou Gehrig&amp;rsquo;s disease. The drug has been found capable of curbing the abnormal agglomeration of protein that causes the progressive neurodegenerative disease, the state-run university in northeastern Japan said.</description></item></channel></rss>