<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>contact on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/contact/</link><description>Recent content in contact on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/contact/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Expert: Monkeypox likely spread by sex at 2 raves in Europe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bea51aa880e9a5f5f75a6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:11:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bea51aa880e9a5f5f75a6/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — A leading adviser to the World Health Organization described the unprecedented outbreak of monkeypox in developed countries as “a random event” that might be explained by sexual behavior at two recent raves in Europe.
Highlights Leading doctor who chairs a World Health Organization expert group described the unprecedented outbreak of monkeypox in developed countries as “a random event” that might be explained by risky sexual behavior at two recent mass events in Europe.</description></item><item><title>‘I hear shelling’: Fear grips Ukrainian villages near Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0263e0562398928f88e39/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0263e0562398928f88e39/</guid><description>Residents are losing hope in areas near the contact line between Russia-backed separatists and Ukrainian forces.
Summary As the crisis continues, residents are losing hope in areas near the contact line between Russia-backed separatists and Ukrainian forces. “I will turn 89 on January 2, but I would prefer to be dead,” she told Al Jazeera, with a traditional headscarf wrapped over her head. Military personnel allowed Al Jazeera to spend just 20 minutes reporting in the area, given the risks.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell’s little black book under FBI review, says report</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf6164c9a353d7cfdf6db2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf6164c9a353d7cfdf6db2/</guid><description>Ghislaine Maxwell’s little black book under FBI review, says report
Summary Convicted sex trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell’s “little black book” of contacts is under FBI review according to a report. A source told The Mirror : “Whereas Epstein brought the cash, Maxwell brought the contacts.”“She opened up a world to her then-lover he could only have dreamt of,” they continued. During Maxwell’s four-week trial, the 97-page contact book was not made public under an agreement reached between the defence and prosecution.</description></item></channel></rss>