<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bans on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bans/</link><description>Recent content in bans on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:15:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Greece bans LGBTQ conversion therapy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d2453b093f31e469ad654/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d2453b093f31e469ad654/</guid><description>Greece on Wednesday banned conversion therapy for minors, a practice aimed at suppressing a person&amp;rsquo;s sexual orientation or gender identity and which the lesbian, gay, bisexual and trans community worldwide, as well as health experts, have condemned as harmful.
Highlights Greece bans conversion therapy for minors, a practice aimed at suppressing a person&amp;rsquo;s sexual orientation or gender identity. Canada, New Zealand and France criminalized conversion therapy earlier this year. Health experts have condemned the practice as harmful.</description></item><item><title>Georgia high school athletic group bans transgender athletes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273541b1729976094dafbf0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6273541b1729976094dafbf0/</guid><description>Amplifying Atlanta
Highlights Georgia High School Association’s executive committee voted unanimously for the change. It will take effect for the next school year. Proponents say transgender girls have an unfair advantage because they were born as stronger males. At least 12 Republican-led states have passed laws banning transgender women or girls in sports. Other GOP states are considering similar bans in other GOP-led sports. Critics say excluding transgender children would send a harmful message to a group that&amp;rsquo;s already vulnerable to suicide or harming themselves.</description></item><item><title>Spain bans harassment of women having abortions | Spain</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f0ea9e9edcf371e8c49c1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f0ea9e9edcf371e8c49c1/</guid><description>Activists could face up to a year in prison for trying to intimidate women into not having terminations
Highlights New law criminalises people who try to stop women having abortions in Spain. It also applies to those who attempt to intimidate doctors or hospital staff. The law was introduced in 1985 to allow abortion on demand in the first 14 weeks of pregnancy. The new law will come into effect after being approved by the Spanish Senate on Wednesday.</description></item><item><title>International Ice Hockey Federation bans Russia, Belarus from its competitions 'until further notice'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e8c467cf765b04046afd3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 21:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e8c467cf765b04046afd3/</guid><description>The International Ice Hockey Federation has banned Belarus and Russia from participating in its competitions until further notice In reaction to Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights The International Ice Hockey Federation bans Russia and Belarus from participation in all competitions until further notice. The decision was made in reaction to Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The 2023 world junior hockey championship was scheduled for Dec. 2022 and Jan. 2023 with Novosibirsk and Omsk as the host cities.</description></item><item><title>TikTok bans misgendering, deadnaming trans people</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620470a7cf6175ed7d91ce69/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620470a7cf6175ed7d91ce69/</guid><description>The social media giant TikTok on Tuesday explicitly banned certain types of anti-LGBTQ content and speech on its platform.
Highlights The social media giant TikTok on Tuesday explicitly banned certain types of anti-LGBTQ content and speech on its platform. The company is also prohibiting “content that supports or promotes conversion therapy programs,” referring to a discredited practice that seeks to stop someone from being LGBTQ. The policy update follows pressure from GLAAD, an LGBTQ media advocacy nonprofit, and UltraViolet, a national gender justice advocacy group.</description></item><item><title>New York City bans natural gas in new buildings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8bbca8228dc74c63f3e5f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 19:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8bbca8228dc74c63f3e5f/</guid><description>The New York City Council voted on Wednesday to ban the use of natural gas in new buildings, following in the footsteps of dozens of smaller U.S. cities seeking to shift from fossil fuels to cleaner forms of energy.
Summary REUTERS/Eduardo Munoz/File PhotoDec 15 (Reuters) - The New York City Council voted on Wednesday to ban the use of natural gas in new buildings, following in the footsteps of dozens of smaller U.</description></item></channel></rss>