<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>japanese on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/japanese/</link><description>Recent content in japanese on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 08:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/japanese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Japan's Okinawa marks half century since U.S. handover as regional tensions grow.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628208d3d51777c04c4eb771/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 08:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628208d3d51777c04c4eb771/</guid><description>The Japanese island chain of Okinawa marked the 50th anniversary on Sunday of the end of U.S. occupation and its return to Japan with calls for more economic growth and fewer U.S. bases despite growing worries over its proximity to an increasingly assertive China.
Highlights The Japanese island chain of Okinawa marked the 50th anniversary on Sunday of the end of U.S. occupation and its return to Japan. The islands suffered massive devastation in World War Two and were finally returned to Japan in 1972.</description></item><item><title>Taliban announces a national suicide brigade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e592c6a089396f6013943c/</guid><description>The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. These “martyrdom brigades”
Summary The Taliban recently announced it will establish a battalion of suicide attackers as part of the national army of Afghanistan. Before sweeping into power in 2021, the Taliban used suicide bombers for 20 years to attack US, UK and Afghan troops. Japanese pilots used suicide tactics during the second world war, with the Japanese Kamikaze pilots crashing their aircraft into Allied naval vessels.</description></item></channel></rss>