<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kremlin on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kremlin/</link><description>Recent content in kremlin on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 03:29:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kremlin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kremlin disrespecting families as it stalls return of dead soldiers, says Zelenskiy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62427cfef063648fb8a5f1ff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 03:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62427cfef063648fb8a5f1ff/</guid><description>Ukrainian president criticises Russian authorities for not agreeing on scheme to have remains sent home
Highlights Ukrainian president accuses Russian authorities of disrespecting families of dead soldiers. Claims Kremlin was affording less respect to those killed during invasion of Ukraine than is usually given to dead pets. Russia has insisted on calling a “special military operation” in Ukraine. Nato last week estimated the Russian death toll to be between 7,000 and 15,000.</description></item><item><title>A Missouri radio station still broadcasts Kremlin programming, even as Russia invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ca94678f8a2dff05e9fb6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 17:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ca94678f8a2dff05e9fb6/</guid><description>As the Russian invasion of Ukraine continues, so do broadcasts of what critics decry as Kremlin-funded propaganda on KCXL, a radio station in Liberty, Missouri. Pressure is mounting for KCXL to end broadcasts that have kept the station in business.
Highlights Radio Sputnik is produced in Washington D.C. and funded by the Kremlin. KCXL radio station in Kansas City, Missouri, is receiving $160,000 a month from the Russian government. The National Association of Broadcasters is calling on all U.</description></item></channel></rss>