<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>american on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/american/</link><description>Recent content in american on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 07:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/american/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Senators: CIA has secret program that collects American data</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62060c1d86e7dd3778816c72/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62060c1d86e7dd3778816c72/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The CIA has a secret, undisclosed data repository that includes information collected about Americans, two Democrats on the Senate Intelligence Committee said. While neither the agency nor lawmakers would disclose specifics about the data, the senators alleged the CIA had long hidden details about the program from the public and Congress.
Highlights Two Democrats on the Senate Intelligence Committee say the CIA has a secret, undisclosed data repository that includes information collected about Americans.</description></item><item><title>American Airlines flight to London returns to Miami after passenger refuses to wear mask</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9bf5eb4864e4bbe4a08b1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 20:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9bf5eb4864e4bbe4a08b1/</guid><description>American Airlines Flight 38 was heading to London with 129 passengers on board when it had to turn back.
Summary An American Airlines flight from Miami had to turn around on Wednesday night after a disruptive passenger refused to wear a mask, the airline said. American Airlines Flight 38 was heading to London with 129 passengers on board when it had to turn back. &amp;ldquo;Everyone was shocked,&amp;rdquo; one passenger told WFOR-TV.</description></item><item><title>The great American sickout: Omicron is causing "hellacious" worker shortages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e200a16e8599152545f93e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e200a16e8599152545f93e/</guid><description>COVID-19 is tearing through the U.S. workforce, disrupting businesses from grocery stores to airlines.
Summary A record spike in COVID-19 cases due to the Omicron variant is causing a nationwide worker &amp;ldquo;sickout,&amp;rdquo; disrupting businesses ranging from grocery stores to airlines. The past few weeks have been &amp;ldquo;hellacious,&amp;rdquo; Delta Airlines CEO Ed Bastian said in a Thursday conference call with stock analysts and reporters. The latest worker shortages are compounding earlier pandemic problems, including supply-chain disruptions and shortages of some services.</description></item></channel></rss>