<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>chicago on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/chicago/</link><description>Recent content in chicago on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:15:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/chicago/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pulitzer Prizes award Washington Post for Jan. 6 coverage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a2cf6b08508efa4e49524/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a2cf6b08508efa4e49524/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The Washington Post won the Pulitzer Prize in public service journalism Monday for its coverage of the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol, an attack on democracy that was a shocking start to a tumultuous year that also saw the end of the United States’ longest war, in Afghanistan.
Highlights The Washington Post won the Pulitzer Prize in public service journalism for its coverage of the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Chicago officers won't be charged in shooting deaths of boy, 13, and adult</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231aa1fbaa627ebe226fb71/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 09:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231aa1fbaa627ebe226fb71/</guid><description>A prosecutor announced Tuesday that no charges will be issued against two police officers involved in the shooting deaths of a 13-year-old boy and 22-year-old
Highlights Cook County State’s Attorney Kim Foxx said there was insufficient evidence to charge the officers in the deaths of Adam Toledo and Anthony Alvarez. The two shootings occurred within weeks of each other. Foot pursuits preceded both shootings and both suspects appeared to have handguns prior to the shootings.</description></item><item><title>Chicago schools cancel classes for fourth day as union fight hits second week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc743e876618a0aae5455a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc743e876618a0aae5455a/</guid><description>Chicago school leaders canceled classes for the fourth day Monday as a standoff with the local teachers&amp;rsquo; union over Covid-19 protocols entered its second week.
Summary Chicago school leaders canceled classes for the fourth consecutive day on Monday as a standoff with the local teachers&amp;rsquo; union over remote learning and other Covid-19 safety protocols entered its second week. Later that day, however, Lightfoot appeared to strike a different tone, tweeting that teachers&amp;rsquo; union leaders were &amp;ldquo;not listening.</description></item><item><title>2021 ends as Chicago's deadliest year in a quarter century</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1a1fae52d831bd5ce5081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1a1fae52d831bd5ce5081/</guid><description>CHICAGO (AP) — The year of 2021 ended as one of the most violent on record in Chicago, as a rise in the number of shootings left more people dead than in any single year in a quarter century, according to statistics released by the police department on Saturday.
Summary French was killed and her partner was seriously wounded during an Aug. 7 traffic stop on the city&amp;rsquo;s South Side. The year 2021 ended as one of the deadliest on record in recent years in Chicago, according to statistics released by the city&amp;rsquo;s police department on Saturday, Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>