<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gets on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gets/</link><description>Recent content in gets on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:23:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ed Buck, wealthy political activist and donor, sentenced to 30 years in prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625971b7af00962fc2dd146e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 13:23:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625971b7af00962fc2dd146e/</guid><description>He was found guilty on charges that he injected the men with methamphetamine in exchange for sex, leading to overdoses
Highlights Ed Buck, 67, sentenced to 30 years in prison on charges that he supplied and personally injected gay men with methamphetamine in exchange for sex. He was found guilty in July on all nine counts, including having a drug house, distributing methamphetamine and enticing men to travel for prostitution. Buck, a wealthy white man active in gay causes and animal rights issues, has given more than $500,000, mostly to Democratic politicians and causes since 2000.</description></item><item><title>Los Angeles nun, 80, gets prison for $835,000 school theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 15:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62028841bbb0c70807207e84/</guid><description>A Los Angeles nun who stole more than $800,000 to pay for a gambling habit has been sentenced to a year in federal prison
Highlights Mary Margaret Kreuper, 80, admitted to stealing the money from 2008 to 2018 while she was principal at St. James Catholic School in the LA suburb of Torrance. She pleaded guilty last July to one count each of wire fraud and money laundering. Judge Otis D.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Oklahoma police officer gets 25 years for 2014 killing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9df60fca97f931fb5862a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9df60fca97f931fb5862a/</guid><description>A federal judge has sentenced a former Oklahoma police officer to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter’s boyfriend
Summary A federal judge has sentenced a former Oklahoma police officer to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter’s boyfriendTULSA, Okla. &amp;ndash; A former Oklahoma police officer was sentenced Friday to 25 years in prison for the 2014 killing of his daughter&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend after being convicted of second-degree murder the fifth time he went on trial in the case.</description></item></channel></rss>