<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plane on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plane/</link><description>Recent content in plane on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>First baby formula shipment arrives from Europe on U.S. military plane</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b33d9a5124cbf494c0190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:12:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b33d9a5124cbf494c0190/</guid><description>A military cargo plane carrying the first shipment of infant formula from Europe to help address a critical shortage in the United States landed in Indianapolis on Sunday, and the White House said a second flight had been arranged.
Highlights A military cargo plane carrying the first shipment of infant formula from Europe landed in Indianapolis on Sunday. The White House said a second flight carrying formula would leave from Ramstein Air Base in Germany in coming days.</description></item><item><title>Chinese plane crash that killed 132 caused by intentional act: US officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628481b8ce5c52409be1accb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 05:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628481b8ce5c52409be1accb/</guid><description>The Eastern Airlines jet crashed into a mountain after a steep dive.
Highlights China Eastern Airlines plane crash believed to have been caused by intentional act, U.S. officials tell ABC News. Officials point to flaps not being engaged and landing gear not put down, officials say. The plane slammed into the ground with such force that it created a 66-foot deep hole in the ground. Investigators also looked into one of the pilots&amp;rsquo; personal lives and background and believe he may have been struggling through certain issues right before the crash.</description></item><item><title>U.S. targets Abramovich plane, 99 others over Russia export violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623601c7d52d8c7bf2d0f4b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 16:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623601c7d52d8c7bf2d0f4b6/</guid><description>The U.S. Commerce Department on Friday moved to effectively ground 100 airplanes that have recently flown to Russia and are believed to violate U.S. export controls, including a plane used by Russian businessman Roman Abramovich.
Highlights The U.S. Commerce Department on Friday moved to effectively ground 100 airplanes that have recently flown to Russia. The list includes 99 Boeing airplanes operated by Russian passenger and cargo carriers including Aeroflot, AirBridge Cargo, Utair, Nordwind, Azur Air and Aviastar-TU.</description></item><item><title>Plane carrying Donald Trump made emergency landing in New Orleans after engine failure over Gulf of Mexico</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a4d59d2b8de0d0a032787/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a4d59d2b8de0d0a032787/</guid><description>A plane carrying former president Donald Trump suffered engine failure late Saturday evening over the Gulf of Mexico, forcing the pilot to make an emergency landing in New Orleans shortly after taking off from the city.
Highlights The Dassault Falcon 900 carried a retinue of Secret Service agents, other support staffers, Trump and some of his advisers. One of the plane’s engines failed, people familiar with the episode said. The plane belonged to a donor who loaned it to Trump for the evening, people said.</description></item><item><title>A large Russian cargo plane took a lengthy, unexpected, and unexplained route over central and southern Finland on Saturday night, passing over Finland's Air Force headquarters and a military intelligence unit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7003a1a2afff60d9e9272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 18:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7003a1a2afff60d9e9272/</guid><description>The incident comes as political tensions continue to rise in the Baltic region.
Summary A large Russian cargo plane took an lengthy, unexpected and unexplained route over central and southern Finland on Saturday night, passing over Finland&amp;rsquo;s Air Force headquarters and a military intelligence unit. The cargo plane took off from Moscow at about 7.26pm Finnish time on Saturday evening and flew towards the city of Murmansk in northwestern Russia. The cargo plane also passed close to the Halli military airport in Jämsä, Central Finland.</description></item></channel></rss>