<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>victory on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/victory/</link><description>Recent content in victory on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 21:13:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/victory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Spain's Queen Gifts Grenade Shipment To Ukraine, Adds Victory Message</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626da64341c21c5b918c1590/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626da64341c21c5b918c1590/</guid><description>The Queen of Spain put traditional sausages and a postcard wishing Ukraine victory over Russia in a shipment of grenades from her country. The gift was sent to Ukraine to give a boost to the fighting power of its army.
Highlights The Queen of Spain put traditional sausages and a postcard wishing Ukraine victory over Russia in a shipment of grenades from her country. The gift was sent to Ukraine to give a boost to the fighting power of its army against a numerically superior enemy.</description></item><item><title>Hungary elects Katalin Novak, first-ever female president</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c7275e23da409840726f6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 10:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c7275e23da409840726f6/</guid><description>Katalin Novak, a close ally of Prime Minister Viktor Orban, portrays her election as a victory for women.
Highlights Katalin Novak, 44, is Hungary’s first-ever female president. She is a close ally of Prime Minister Viktor Orban. Novak portrayed her election as a victory for women. She will succeed Janos Ader, a co-founder of the governing right-wing Fidesz party who has held the job since 2012. The vote comes weeks ahead of a crunch parliamentary election on April 3, where Orban faces a stiff battle to win a fourth straight term in power since 2010.</description></item></channel></rss>