<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>asks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/asks/</link><description>Recent content in asks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 09:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/asks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ERCOT Asks Texans to Conserve Power Until 8 P.M., Through the Weekend</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f72e6104fd436f0e26b0e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f72e6104fd436f0e26b0e/</guid><description>ERCOT asking all Texans to conserve energy through the weekend as we head into potentially record heat.
Highlights ERCOT asks all Texans to conserve energy through the weekend as we head into potentially record heat. Six power plants dropped off the grid Friday, resulting in a loss of about 2,900 MW of generation &amp;ndash; that&amp;rsquo;s enough electricity to power about 580,000 homes. The Electric Reliability Council of Texas said, &amp;ldquo;unseasonably hot weather&amp;rdquo; was driving record demand across Texas.</description></item><item><title>Britney Spears asks judge to deny mother's request she pay more than $600,000 in legal fees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f7032168dff5c77a9e3db/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 23:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f7032168dff5c77a9e3db/</guid><description>Britney Spears asked a judge to deny her mother&amp;rsquo;s request that the singer pay for more than $660,000 in legal fees incurred during the pop star’s former
Highlights Britney Spears asked a judge to deny her mother&amp;rsquo;s request that the singer pay for more than $660,000 in legal fees incurred during the pop star’s former conservatorship. The request from Lynne Spears, filed in November 2021, argued that she hired a legal team “to assist Britney to break the restrictions imposed by the conservator.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer asks employees who were overpaid as result of a ransomware attack to pay company back</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246c2338cb53e12bebfad19/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 09:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246c2338cb53e12bebfad19/</guid><description>Ransomware attack on Kronos resulted in Pfizer employees being over-compensated company-wide. Pfizer asked employees to pay back the company, and some underpaid.
Highlights Ransomware attack on Kronos resulted in Pfizer employees being over-compensated company-wide. Pfizer asked employees to pay back the company after the attack. Some employees were underpaid, some overpaid, Pfizer says. The company has not responded to requests for more information from the company to respond to the attack, which occurred in early December.</description></item><item><title>Texas school district asks parents to become substitute teachers amid COVID surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfce25505853304863b2e3/</guid><description>According to Hays CISD, parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation to become substitute teachers.
Summary The Hays Consolidated Independent School District (Hays CISD) in Kyle is asking parents to consider applying to become a substitute teacher as coronavirus continues to surge across Texas. According to Hays CISD, the parents would still have to apply, pass the fingerprint criminal background check, and do orientation.</description></item></channel></rss>