<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>photos on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/photos/</link><description>Recent content in photos on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 05:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/photos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shooter warning signs get lost in sea of social media posts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930139bbd2a49a95d81d25/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 05:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930139bbd2a49a95d81d25/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The warning signs were there for anyone to stumble upon, days before the 18-year-old gunman entered a Texas elementary school and slaughtered 19 children and two teachers .
Highlights Gunman who killed 19 children and two teachers in Texas left a digital trail that hinted at what was to come. The warning signs were there for anyone to stumble upon, days before the massacre. Instagram photo of a hand holding a gun magazine, a TikTok profile that warned, “Kids be scared,” and the image of two AR-style semi-automatic rifles displayed on a rug, pinned to the top of the killer’s Instagram profile.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pepper-Sprayed Man Taking Photos of His Own Children in Arlington: Police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625acec4c676a0d4b268a865/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 14:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625acec4c676a0d4b268a865/</guid><description>Police are looking for a woman who pepper-sprayed a man who was taking photos of his own children in Arlington, Virginia, police said.
Highlights Police are looking for a woman who pepper-sprayed a man who was taking photos of his own children in Arlington, Virginia. The woman reported the man to a security officer Tuesday afternoon in the 1100 block of S. Hayes Street, which is the block where Pentagon City Mall is located.</description></item><item><title>Madeleine Albright, first female US secretary of state, dies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bf0b21a2561a567ca0a40/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bf0b21a2561a567ca0a40/</guid><description>Madeleine Albright, the first female US secretary of state and who helped steer Western foreign policy in the aftermath of the Cold War, has died. She was 84 years old.
Highlights Madeleine Albright was 84 years old. The cause of her death was cancer, her family says. She was a central figure in President Bill Clinton&amp;rsquo;s administration. She championed the expansion of NATO and championed human rights and democracy across the globe.</description></item></channel></rss>