<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>red on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/red/</link><description>Recent content in red on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:27:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Full lunar eclipse to bring super blood Moon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282431a6be2bf662134deff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282431a6be2bf662134deff/</guid><description>The Moon will slowly darken and turn red as it falls into Earth&amp;rsquo;s shadow.
Highlights Western parts of Europe will get a good but short view as the Moon will set during the eclipse. The Moon will slowly darken and turn red as it falls into Earth&amp;rsquo;s shadow. Look low on the horizon between 0230 and 0430 BST and you&amp;rsquo;ll see the moon falling into shadow before glowing red. It should be visible in Africa too, with the eclipse visible in western parts of the continent.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine defence: Red lights and painted arrows fuel fear of Russian agents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240a9986fcbe1d53c6846b5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 18:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240a9986fcbe1d53c6846b5/</guid><description>Fear of Russian saboteurs operating in Ukraine has soared, but is it based on intelligence and arrests?
Highlights Fear of Russian saboteurs operating in Ukraine has soared, but is it based on intelligence and arrests? How much is fact, backed up by intelligence reports and arrests, and how much is something closer to understandable paranoia fuelled by social media rumours about mysterious lights and signs? What is the real fear that the war in Ukraine is hardening into a certainty?</description></item></channel></rss>