<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>covid19 on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/covid19/</link><description>Recent content in covid19 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/covid19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twitter permanently suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene's personal account</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</guid><description>Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep.
Summary Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene after &amp;ldquo;repeated violations&amp;rdquo; of the Covid-19 misinformation policy, the company said Sunday. &amp;ldquo;We permanently suspended the account you referenced (@mtgreenee) for repeated violations of our COVID-19 misinformation policy,&amp;rdquo; Twitter said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;We’ve been clear that, per our strike system for this policy, we will permanently suspend accounts for repeated violations of the policy.</description></item><item><title>1 in 15 people in London likely has COVID-19</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d042613328107f90ab2c19/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d042613328107f90ab2c19/</guid><description>Summary LONDON (AP) — New figures from Britain’s official statistics body estimate that about 1 in 25 people in private households in England had COVID-19 in the week before Christmas, as the highly transmissible omicron variant spread rapidly across the country. The number jumped from 1 in 45 in the previous week, the Office for National Statistics said Friday. One in 25 is the equivalent of about 2 million people with coronavirus in England, the highest number since the statistics body began estimating infection levels in May 2020.</description></item><item><title>Japan Is Working on a COVID-19 Vaccine That Offers Lifelong Immunity</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</guid><description>While pharma companies focus on developing variant-specific boosters, Japan is working on a vaccine that could offer lifelong immunity.
Summary Researchers at the Tokyo Metropolitan Institute of Medical Science are working on a COVID-19 vaccine that not only delivers lifelong immunity against the SARS-CoV-2 virus but could also be transported at room temperature to far-off corners of the world, The Japan Times reported. The vaccine that is being developed by Michinori Kohara and his team of researchers employs the most successful vaccine used in history, one against smallpox.</description></item><item><title>NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard tells the unvaccinated to ‘switch off your social media and switch on reality’</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cc69ff22ee52e41aa5aa01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cc69ff22ee52e41aa5aa01/</guid><description>NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has begged the unvaccinated population in the state to &amp;quot;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;quot;.
Summary NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has slammed those who are still unvaccinated against COVID-19 and implored them to &amp;ldquo;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;rdquo;. NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has begged the unvaccinated population in the state to &amp;ldquo;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>