<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>covid19 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/covid19/</link><description>Recent content in covid19 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 19:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/covid19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>North Korea reports 15 more suspected COVID-19 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281506ea32f14df61f9cc98/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281506ea32f14df61f9cc98/</guid><description>North Korea has confirmed 15 more deaths and high numbers of fevers as it mobilizes more than a million health and other workers to try to suppress the country&amp;rsquo;s first COVID-19 outbreak.
Highlights North Korea reports 15 more suspected COVID-19 deaths; another 296,180 people with fevers have been tallied. North Korea has said a fever has spread across the country &amp;ldquo;explosively&amp;rdquo; since late April. Experts say North Korea lacks diagnostic kits needed to test large number of suspected patients.</description></item><item><title>US supreme court rules against air force officer who refused Covid vaccine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eef9755e81ec0cd1136f1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625eef9755e81ec0cd1136f1/</guid><description>Majority of court sides with Pentagon over challenge by lieutenant colonel who cited religious grounds for refusal to get vaccine
Highlights Lt Col Jonathan Dunn cited religious grounds for his refusal to get the Covid-19 vaccine. He cited a speech given by Joe Biden that led him to conclude that “the vaccine ceased to be merely a medical invention and took on a symbolic and even sacramental quality” The court ruled in March that the US navy had the authority to determine the job assignments of 35 service members who refused to get vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Google, Apple, Twitter Reveal Return to Office Policies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62271e0549bf4e1e555464c3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 09:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62271e0549bf4e1e555464c3/</guid><description>Several major tech companies expect workers to be back in the office soon.
Highlights Apple, Google and Twitter are preparing for employees to return to in-person work. Apple CEO Tim Cook said corporate employees will return to work starting in April. Google will require most employees to come into the office three days a week as of April 4. Twitter has told its employees that when it reopens offices March 15, it will be up to workers where they work from home.</description></item><item><title>British queen still has COVID symptoms, postpones audiences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62181108f51c0323d451dd09/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 23:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62181108f51c0323d451dd09/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II postponed two virtual audiences as she continued to experience cold-like symptoms from COVID-19, Buckingham Palace said Thursday. It was the second time this week that Elizabeth, 95, had canceled virtual sessions.
Highlights Buckingham Palace said Sunday, Feb. 20, 2022 that Queen Elizabeth II tested positive for COVID-19, has mild symptoms and will continue with duties. It was the second time this week that Elizabeth, 95, had canceled virtual sessions.</description></item><item><title>A man who attacked and blamed an Asian family for Covid-19 pleaded guilty to hate crimes charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217cb5c0f3d6d9f7c376611/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217cb5c0f3d6d9f7c376611/</guid><description>A 21-year-old Texas man pleaded guilty to federal hate crime charges after he brutally attacked and blamed an Asian family whom he believed to be Chinese for the Covid-19 pandemic, prosecutors announced Wednesday.
Highlights Jose Gomez III saw a Burmese family with three young children enter a Sam’s Club in Texas. He followed them into the store and attacked the family, slashing the father and a child who was then 6 years old.</description></item><item><title>US death toll from COVID-19 hits 900,000, sped by omicron</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdeae253c56b08f40a36d8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 03:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdeae253c56b08f40a36d8/</guid><description>Propelled in part by the wildly contagious omicron variant, the U.S. death toll from COVID-19 has hit 900,000, less than two months after eclipsing 800,000
Highlights The U.S. death toll from COVID-19 has hit 900,000, less than two months after eclipsing 800,000. The two-year total is greater than the population of Indianapolis, San Francisco, or Charlotte, North Carolina. The milestone comes more than 13 months into a vaccination drive that has been beset by misinformation and political and legal strife, though the shots have proved safe and highly effective at preventing serious illness and death.</description></item><item><title>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, who has fought vaccine mandates, tests positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e932b6e160ce5e691613c2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e932b6e160ce5e691613c2/</guid><description>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton, who has fought vaccine mandates, tests positive for COVID-19
Summary AUSTIN, Texas (TEXAS TRIBUNE) - Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton has tested positive for COVID-19, his office said Wednesday. The communications staff at the attorney general’s office told The Texas Tribune in an unsigned statement that Paxton had tested positive. The attorney general’s office did not immediately say whether Paxton was vaccinated. It did not release further information on when Paxton tested positive or how he may have contracted it.</description></item><item><title>Girl under 10 is youngest person to die of COVID-19 in Houston, city health officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</guid><description>A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday.
Summary The nations COVID-19 death toll stands at around 800,000 as the anniversary of the U.S. vaccine rollout arrives. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke, File)HOUSTON – A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday. Privacy laws prevent the health department from providing any other identifiable information.</description></item><item><title>CDC forecast predicts more than 62,000 Covid-19 deaths in the US in the next four weeks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfb20ba609b542595513bc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 05:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfb20ba609b542595513bc/</guid><description>An ensemble forecast from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention published Wednesday predicts that over 62,000 more people could die from Covid-19 over the next four weeks.
Summary (Joseph Prezioso/AFP/Getty Images)An ensemble forecast from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention published Wednesday predicts that over 62,000 more people could die from Covid-19 over the next four weeks. The forecast could mean an average of 2,624 Covid-19 deaths a day, up from a current average of 1,715 per day, according to JHU data.</description></item><item><title>The highly contagious Omicron variant will 'find just about everybody,' Fauci says, but vaccinated people will still fare better</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df4f9397214fa7f9c39295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df4f9397214fa7f9c39295/</guid><description>Covid-19 hospitalizations in the United States have reached a new record high, surpassing the previous peak from January 2021, according to data from the US Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary More than 62% of the country has been fully vaccinated, but only 23% are fully vaccinated and boosted, according to data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. While fully vaccinated people are accounting for a larger share of Covid-19 hospitalizations, multiple accounts suggest that those who are fully vaccinated and boosted account for a small share.</description></item><item><title>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez tests positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</guid><description>&amp;quot;She is experiencing symptoms and recovering at home,&amp;quot; her office said in a statement on Sunday.
Summary Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has tested positive for COVID-19, her office said in a statement on Sunday. The CDC recommends that Americans who test positive for COVID-19 and develop symptoms isolate for at least five full days. COVID-19 cases continue to surge across the country, with an average of nearly 700,000 new cases reported per day, according to the CDC.</description></item><item><title>Gov. Newsom signs executive order outlawing price gouging of COVID-19 at-home test kits in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc4a1070867ba32c1e3bbe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc4a1070867ba32c1e3bbe/</guid><description>Gov. Gavin Newsom signed an executive order aimed at preventing price gouging of at-home COVID-19 test kits.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos COVID-19 testing continued at many Los Angeles Unified School District campuses on Sunday, Jan. 9, 2022, as students, teachers and staff prepared to return from winter break. SACRAMENTO, Calif. (KABC) &amp;ndash; Gov. Gavin Newsom has signed an executive order aimed at preventing price gouging of at-home COVID-19 test kits.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated People Ordered to Stay Home or Face Jail in City of 14 Million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbf5b69b3a228e67f4ade3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 09:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbf5b69b3a228e67f4ade3/</guid><description>After weeks of its lowest caseloads in the pandemic, the Philippines’ capital region is seeing a frightening rise in coronavirus infections.
Summary Under the order, unvaccinated people must stay at home except to buy essential goods or for medical purposes. Some officials criticized the council’s stay-at-home order for unvaccinated people, noting that even vaccinated people can contract and transmit the virus. “The recent exponential COVID-19 surge in Metro Manila happened even when 102 percent of the target population is already vaccinated.</description></item><item><title>Moderna donates 2.7 million vaccine doses to Mexico as COVID cases surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da96371938dd6817f5c345/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da96371938dd6817f5c345/</guid><description>Moderna donated 2.7 million COVID-19 vaccine doses to Mexico as cases surge in the country.
Summary Moderna donated 2.7 million COVID-19 vaccine doses to Mexico as cases surge in the country. The government said the doses will go to teachers as the country tries to return to fully in-person learning. The donations came after Mexico approved Cuba’s three-shot coronavirus vaccine at the end of December. Mexico has 57 percent of its population fully vaccinated and has authorized the use of 10 different vaccines.</description></item><item><title>Omicron explosion spurs nationwide breakdown of services</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da25b91336888dc9c6523b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da25b91336888dc9c6523b/</guid><description>Ambulances in Kansas speed toward hospitals then suddenly change direction because hospitals are full. Employee shortages in New York City cause delays in trash and subway services and diminish the ranks of firefighters and emergency workers.
Summary (AP Photo/Mark J. Terrill)Ambulances in Kansas speed toward hospitals then suddenly change direction because hospitals are full. Employee shortages in New York City cause delays in trash and subway services and diminish the ranks of firefighters and emergency workers.</description></item><item><title>India has “substantially greater” COVID-19 deaths than official reports suggest—close to 3 million, which is more than six times higher than the government has acknowledged and the largest number of any country. The finding could prompt scrutiny of other countries with anomalously low death rates.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d87fd897d80e29c14359ae/</guid><description>Summary India, from the earliest days of the pandemic, has reported far fewer COVID-19 deaths than expected given the toll elsewhere—an apparent death “paradox” that some believed was real and others thought would prove illusory. That’s 340 COVID-19 deaths per million—about one-seventh the per capita COVID-19 mortality tallied in the United States. “The Indian government very much is trying to suppress the numbers in the way that they coded the COVID deaths,” Jha says.</description></item><item><title>Overwhelmed by Omicron surge, U.S. hospitals delay surgeries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d871bcb893d622e77dd3ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d871bcb893d622e77dd3ed/</guid><description>Hospitals across the United States are postponing elective surgeries to free up staff and beds due to a surge in COVID-19 cases driven by the highly transmissible Omicron variant of the coronavirus.
Summary REUTERS/Shannon StapletonWASHINGTON, Jan 7 (Reuters) - Hospitals across the United States are postponing elective surgeries to free up staff and beds due to a surge in COVID-19 cases driven by the highly transmissible Omicron variant of the coronavirus.</description></item><item><title>Ontario to stop logging COVID-19 school cases, memo says; NDP calls it 'terrifying for parents'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d24aae0458d582732d8086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d24aae0458d582732d8086/</guid><description>Ontario will stop reporting COVID-19 cases in schools and child-care settings, prompting criticism from the opposition New Democratic Party, which called the move &amp;quot;terrifying for parents.&amp;quot;
Summary Ontario will stop reporting COVID-19 cases in schools and child-care settings, memos from the Ministry of Education say, prompting criticism from the opposition New Democratic Party, which called the move &amp;ldquo;terrifying for parents.&amp;rdquo; The changes come as record-breaking COVID numbers strain public health resources.</description></item><item><title>Twitter permanently suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene's personal account</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</guid><description>Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep.
Summary Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene after &amp;ldquo;repeated violations&amp;rdquo; of the Covid-19 misinformation policy, the company said Sunday. &amp;ldquo;We permanently suspended the account you referenced (@mtgreenee) for repeated violations of our COVID-19 misinformation policy,&amp;rdquo; Twitter said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;We’ve been clear that, per our strike system for this policy, we will permanently suspend accounts for repeated violations of the policy.</description></item><item><title>1 in 15 people in London likely has COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d042613328107f90ab2c19/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d042613328107f90ab2c19/</guid><description>Summary LONDON (AP) — New figures from Britain’s official statistics body estimate that about 1 in 25 people in private households in England had COVID-19 in the week before Christmas, as the highly transmissible omicron variant spread rapidly across the country. The number jumped from 1 in 45 in the previous week, the Office for National Statistics said Friday. One in 25 is the equivalent of about 2 million people with coronavirus in England, the highest number since the statistics body began estimating infection levels in May 2020.</description></item><item><title>Japan Is Working on a COVID-19 Vaccine That Offers Lifelong Immunity</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0344b8f4574009a941aa4/</guid><description>While pharma companies focus on developing variant-specific boosters, Japan is working on a vaccine that could offer lifelong immunity.
Summary Researchers at the Tokyo Metropolitan Institute of Medical Science are working on a COVID-19 vaccine that not only delivers lifelong immunity against the SARS-CoV-2 virus but could also be transported at room temperature to far-off corners of the world, The Japan Times reported. The vaccine that is being developed by Michinori Kohara and his team of researchers employs the most successful vaccine used in history, one against smallpox.</description></item><item><title>NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard tells the unvaccinated to ‘switch off your social media and switch on reality’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc69ff22ee52e41aa5aa01/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc69ff22ee52e41aa5aa01/</guid><description>NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has begged the unvaccinated population in the state to &amp;quot;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;quot;.
Summary NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has slammed those who are still unvaccinated against COVID-19 and implored them to &amp;ldquo;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;rdquo;. NSW Health Minister Brad Hazzard has begged the unvaccinated population in the state to &amp;ldquo;switch off your social media and switch on reality&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>