<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>launch on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/launch/</link><description>Recent content in launch on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 21:12:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/launch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Art Rupe, label owner who helped launch Little Richard and Sam Cooke, dies at 104 | Music</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c8294126e693559f18929/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 21:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c8294126e693559f18929/</guid><description>Rock and Roll Hall of Fame member Rupe founded Specialty Records, whose artists also included John Lee Hooker and Lloyd Price
Highlights Art Rupe was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2011. Rupe founded Specialty Records in 1946 and helped launch careers of Little Richard, Sam Cooke and others. Little Richard&amp;rsquo;s Tutti Frutti was one of rock’n’roll’s first major hits, released in September 1955. He was known for how little he paid his artists and engaged in an exploitative practice common among label owners in the early rock era: having performers sign contracts with much of the royalties and publishing rights.</description></item><item><title>Amazon internal chat app that censored talk of unions and ethics may 'never launch at all' Filter list reportedly would block 'living wage,' 'pay rises,' 'restroom,' etc</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f1c4ecc62ab9abd8ea471/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 17:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f1c4ecc62ab9abd8ea471/</guid><description>Amazon allegedly planned an internal messaging app that filtered words like &amp;quot;union,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;pay rise,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;ethics&amp;quot; alongside challenging and offensive terms. The company told The Register the software has not been approved and may never be deployed. Amazon
Highlights Amazon allegedly planned an internal messaging app that filtered words like &amp;ldquo;union,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;pay rise,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;ethics,&amp;rdquo; alongside challenging and offensive terms. The company told The Register the software has not been approved and may never be deployed.</description></item><item><title>James Webb Completely and Successfully Unfolded</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9ed82c1ac588f35200db3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 20:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9ed82c1ac588f35200db3/</guid><description>Read the latest news about NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope.
Summary Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the primary mirror of James Webb Space TelescopeWebb Space Telescope final deployment underway NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope mirror deployment webcast is underway. James Webb Space Telescope launch a success NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope is successfully in space and beginning its monthlong trek to its L2 home about 1 million miles from Earth. James Webb Space Telescope on track during ascent The Ariane 5 rocket carrying NASA&amp;rsquo;s James Webb Space Telescope continues its 2nd stage burn to carry the telescope into space.</description></item><item><title>NASA's James Webb Space Telescope launch delayed to Christmas due to bad weather</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c32f8ebb918b17a516fa61/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 14:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c32f8ebb918b17a516fa61/</guid><description>NASA&amp;rsquo;s much-awaited next-generation space telescope is finally ready to launch just as soon as the weather cooperates.
Summary The James Webb Space Telescope folded up for launch before it was encapsulated in the fairing of an Ariane 5 rocket. NASA&amp;rsquo;s much-awaited next-generation space telescope is finally ready to launch — just as soon as the weather cooperates. The James Webb Space Telescope , also known as JWST or Webb, has been in the works for decades.</description></item></channel></rss>