<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>performance on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/performance/</link><description>Recent content in performance on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:14:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/performance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US official: "We believe that Putin is being misinformed" about Russian military performance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244b9fb62c38fa98dfb97f9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 20:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244b9fb62c38fa98dfb97f9/</guid><description>The US believes that Russian President Vladimir Putin is being &amp;quot;misinformed&amp;quot; by his advisers about how badly the Russian military is performing in Ukraine and the impact of sanctions on Russia&amp;rsquo;s economy, a US official tells CNN.
Highlights Former British Prime Minister David Cameron says Russian President Vladimir Putin is “effectively a war criminal” Cameron urged the US, Britain, European countries and others not to attend the upcoming G20 summit in November in Bali, Indonesia, if Putin is invited and able to attend.</description></item><item><title>‘Nostalgic racism is racism’: Disney criticised for Texas students’ performance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623646fa4c8c83cdf77c3a5f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623646fa4c8c83cdf77c3a5f/</guid><description>Walt Disney World apologises after Texas high school drill team chants ‘Scalp ’em, Indians, scalp ’em’ during performance
Highlights Disney apologises after Texas high school drill team sings &amp;lsquo;Scalp &amp;rsquo;em, Indians, scalp &amp;rsquo;em&amp;rsquo; The performance did not reflect Disney&amp;rsquo;s core values, a spokesperson said. Native American advocates criticised Disney and Port Neches-Groves high school after video of the performance was posted to Twitter. Disney has added disclaimers to some of its older material, for instance, that the 1953 film Peter Pan shows indigenous people “in a stereotypical manner” and other films are flagged for featuring “negative depictions and/or mistreatment of people or cultures” The entertainment giant has faced backlash over its response to Florida’s controversial Parental Rights in Education act.</description></item></channel></rss>