<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>funds on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/funds/</link><description>Recent content in funds on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/funds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biden to devote $2.1 bln of new funds to strengthen US food supply chain.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298730ace6e941a02e6aa8b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298730ace6e941a02e6aa8b/</guid><description>The Biden Administration on Wednesday will announce $2.1 billion in new funding to bolster food supply chains, including initiatives to expand small- and
Highlights The Biden Administration on Wednesday will announce $2.1 billion in new funding to bolster food supply chains. The funds will also be used to finance new infrastructure such as cold storage facilities and to assist farmers shifting to organic production. Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack plans to focus on the importance of moving US food supplies away from dominance by a few highly concentrated businesses.</description></item><item><title>EU anti-fraud body accuses Marine Le Pen of embezzlement | France</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c6676bf42bde9a509ada9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 19:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c6676bf42bde9a509ada9/</guid><description>Report alleges Rassemblement National leader and others misused about €620,000 in funds while serving in European parliament
Highlights Le Pen and several party members accused of embezzling EU funds while serving in parliament. Her father, Louis Aliot, her former partner and an ex-vice-president of the RN, are also cited in the report as having misused public money. Le Pen has been under investigation since 2018 on allegations of “breach of trust” and “misuse of public funds” over the alleged use of EU money for European parliamentary assistants to finance the salaries of party staff.</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Executive To Plead Guilty To Fraudulently Claiming $1.7M In Covid Relief Funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ce2f693ae0aec349fff8c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ce2f693ae0aec349fff8c/</guid><description>Federal officials allege the Aviron Pictures founder used the money for personal expenses, including credit card payments.
Highlights William Sadleir, 67, of Beverly Hills, will enter his plea next week. Federal officials allege he fraudulently claimed $1.7 million in Paycheck Protection Program loans. Instead, they say he used the money for personal expenses, including credit card payments. He has already pleaded guilty to separate charges in New York that he misappropriated $25 million in funds invested in Aviron Pictures.</description></item><item><title>Crowd fundraising site says they will defy Canadian court order to stop disbursing funds to convoy protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</guid><description>Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters.
Highlights Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters. The Superior Court of Justice in Ontario granted a restraining order requested by the Government of Ontario against the site. Ontario Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office declined to comment on the site&amp;rsquo;s response to the court order.</description></item><item><title>Trucker convoy GoFundMe suspended after reaching $10.1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc0d892aa115f6a9ab0c9c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 17:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc0d892aa115f6a9ab0c9c/</guid><description>GoFundMe has suspended a fundraiser for the &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; of truckers and supporters who have tied up downtown Ottawa while protesting vaccine mandates.
Highlights GoFundMe suspends fundraiser for the &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; of truckers and supporters. The fundraiser has raised more than $10 million and is currently under review. It&amp;rsquo;s the second time the website has suspended access to the money. Truckers have tied up downtown Ottawa while protesting vaccine mandates. The Freedom Convoy 2022 fundraiser states in its description that money will go towards paying for the cost of the truckers’ journey to Ottawa, including fuel, food and shelter, with leftover funds being given to “a credible Veterans organization which will be chosen by the donors’s donors” The fundraiser had been declared the second largest in Canada, smaller only than the fundraiser created for the Humboldt Broncos in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Bank of America reducing overdraft fees from $35 to $10, eliminating insufficient funds fees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61defb435bcaeeef1572b72d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 16:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61defb435bcaeeef1572b72d/</guid><description>Bank of America is reducing its overdraft fees from $35 to $10 and eliminating insufficient funds fees.
Summary Bank of America, the nation&amp;rsquo;s second-largest bank, says roughly 25% of its overdraft/NSF fee revenue each year came from NSF fees. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to reduce or eliminate overdraft fees for 20 years and to give them credit, they really did listen,&amp;rdquo; said Martin Eakes, CEO of the Center for Responsible Lending. After the financial crisis, Democrats put the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau and other regulators in charge of reining in overdraft fee revenue.</description></item></channel></rss>