<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>funds on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/funds/</link><description>Recent content in funds on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/funds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Crowd fundraising site says they will defy Canadian court order to stop disbursing funds to convoy protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</guid><description>Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters.
Highlights Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters. The Superior Court of Justice in Ontario granted a restraining order requested by the Government of Ontario against the site. Ontario Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office declined to comment on the site&amp;rsquo;s response to the court order.</description></item><item><title>Trucker convoy GoFundMe suspended after reaching $10.1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc0d892aa115f6a9ab0c9c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 17:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc0d892aa115f6a9ab0c9c/</guid><description>GoFundMe has suspended a fundraiser for the &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; of truckers and supporters who have tied up downtown Ottawa while protesting vaccine mandates.
Highlights GoFundMe suspends fundraiser for the &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; of truckers and supporters. The fundraiser has raised more than $10 million and is currently under review. It&amp;rsquo;s the second time the website has suspended access to the money. Truckers have tied up downtown Ottawa while protesting vaccine mandates.</description></item><item><title>Bank of America reducing overdraft fees from $35 to $10, eliminating insufficient funds fees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61defb435bcaeeef1572b72d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 16:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61defb435bcaeeef1572b72d/</guid><description>Bank of America is reducing its overdraft fees from $35 to $10 and eliminating insufficient funds fees.
Summary Bank of America, the nation&amp;rsquo;s second-largest bank, says roughly 25% of its overdraft/NSF fee revenue each year came from NSF fees. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to reduce or eliminate overdraft fees for 20 years and to give them credit, they really did listen,&amp;rdquo; said Martin Eakes, CEO of the Center for Responsible Lending.</description></item></channel></rss>