<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jan/</link><description>Recent content in jan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:33:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. charges Proud Boys leader, four lieutenants with seditious conspiracy in widening Jan. 6 plot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e9cbcb70403840bda9944/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:33:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629e9cbcb70403840bda9944/</guid><description>This is the second group whose members face the rare charge in the Capitol insurrection.
Highlights Enrique &amp;ldquo;Enrique&amp;rdquo; Tarrio, the former longtime chairman of the Proud Boys, is indicted on a new federal charge of seditious conspiracy with four top lieutenants. The charges expand the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s allegations of organized plotting to oppose through violence the certification of President Biden’s election victory, culminating in the attack on the Capitol by a mob on Jan.</description></item><item><title>Pulitzer Prizes award Washington Post for Jan. 6 coverage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a2cf6b08508efa4e49524/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a2cf6b08508efa4e49524/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The Washington Post won the Pulitzer Prize in public service journalism Monday for its coverage of the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol, an attack on democracy that was a shocking start to a tumultuous year that also saw the end of the United States’ longest war, in Afghanistan.
Highlights The Washington Post won the Pulitzer Prize in public service journalism for its coverage of the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Jurors reject array of defenses at Capitol riot trials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267746727132310c74fd86d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 04:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267746727132310c74fd86d/</guid><description>Jurors have heard — and rejected — an array of excuses and arguments from the first rioters to be tried for storming the U.S. Capitol. The next jury to get a Capitol riot case could hear another novel defense this week at the trial of a retired New York City police officer.
Highlights Thomas Webster, a 20-year veteran of the NYPD, has claimed he was acting in self-defense when he tackled a police officer who was trying to protect the Capitol from a mob on Jan.</description></item><item><title>Former cop who stormed Capitol guilty on all six counts in second Jan. 6 jury trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254cdb066d8fa4371484ca9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254cdb066d8fa4371484ca9/</guid><description>Thomas Robertson, a former police officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia, was found guilty on all six charges on Monday.
Highlights Thomas Robertson was an officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia, when he entered the Capitol on Jan. He faced six charges, including obstruction of an official proceeding, civil disorder and entering a restricted building or grounds while carrying a deadly or dangerous weapon. Robertson was the second defendant to take his case to a jury, after Guy Reffitt was convicted on all counts last month.</description></item><item><title>Oath Keeper pleads guilty to seditious conspiracy for Jan. 6 attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622032c56c05a31a2b20e9f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622032c56c05a31a2b20e9f1/</guid><description>Joshua James, 34, of Arab, Alabama, pleaded guilty to seditious conspiracy charges on Wednesday as part of deal with prosecutors contingent on his cooperation.
Highlights Joshua James, 34, pleads guilty to seditious conspiracy charges in exchange for reduced offense level. Plea deal is the first of its kind for a Jan. 6 defendant. James admitted he and others collected firearms at hotels on the outskirts of Washington, D.C., and were ready to use them to prevent Biden from becoming president.</description></item><item><title>Memphis man arrested in Jan. 6 Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a6dd7036de9c6163e63d4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a6dd7036de9c6163e63d4/</guid><description>28-year-old Joshua Hernandez is facing multiple charges.
Highlights Joshua Hernandez, 28, is charged with multiple charges related to the breach of the U.S. Capitol. He was arrested in Memphis and made his initial appearance in the Western District of Tennessee. Court documents reveal Hernandez was among rioters who assaulted law enforcement and who entered the Capitol building. The Department of Justice says court documents reveal that Hernandez was part of a group who assaulted police and entered the building.</description></item><item><title>Legislator dies using medical suicide law he helped pass</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 21:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</guid><description>A former Vermont legislator and House majority leader has died with the help of a law he himself helped pass that allows the terminally ill to end their own lives, his wife said. Willem Jewett died Jan.
Summary The former Vermont lawmaker and House majority leader died on Wednesday, Jan. 12, 2022. Jewett, who had cancer, helped pass a Vermont&amp;rsquo;s aid-in-dying law that allows terminally ill patients to ask their doctors for a lethal dose of medication.</description></item><item><title>Iowa man arraigned on 7 charges for Jan. 6 US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</guid><description>Description An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prison
Summary An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prisonDES MOINES, Iowa &amp;ndash; An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>