<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>locks on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/locks/</link><description>Recent content in locks on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 03:17:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/locks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Idaho hospital locks down amid far-right call for protest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623156a58645432840a43212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623156a58645432840a43212/</guid><description>BOISE, Idaho (AP) — A major Boise hospital went on lockdown for about an hour Tuesday after far-right activist Ammon Bundy urged supporters to go the facility in protest of a child protection case involving one of his family friends.
Highlights St. Luke’s Health System put Boise Medical Center on lockdown Tuesday, March 15, 2022. Far-right activist Ammon Bundy urged supporters to head there to protest a child protection case involving a family friend.</description></item><item><title>OKC hospital tightens security, locks down ICU after 'online attacks' over COVID-19 patient</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e03bfabd91ca13b10da9c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 08:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e03bfabd91ca13b10da9c/</guid><description>Evangelical group the Ekklesia of Oklahoma protested outside the hospital last week as one of its members was in the hospital with COVID-19.
Highlights Mercy Hospital Oklahoma City tightens security, locks down ICU after &amp;lsquo;online attacks&amp;rsquo; over COVID-19 patient. An evangelical group, the Ekklesia of Oklahoma, protested outside the hospital last week. The patient, Robert Barth, was critically ill and being treated in the intensive care unit on a ventilator, court records say.</description></item><item><title>China locks down Yuzhou, city of 1.2 million, after recording 3 Covid-19 cases</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4edae87a2bdb3c28e3422/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4edae87a2bdb3c28e3422/</guid><description>Yuzhou, a city with a population of around 1.17 million people in Henan province, announced that from Monday night all citizens were required to stay home to control the spread of the virus. | World News
Summary More than one million people in a city in central China were being confined to their homes on Tuesday after three asymptomatic coronavirus cases were recorded in the country&amp;rsquo;s latest mass lockdown. Yuzhou, a city with a population of around 1.</description></item></channel></rss>