<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>delivery on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/delivery/</link><description>Recent content in delivery on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 05:35:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/delivery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uber charging customers new fuel fee for rides, delivery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ed40557294e5f30e6f34b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 05:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ed40557294e5f30e6f34b/</guid><description>Citing record-high prices for gasoline, Uber is charging customers a new fuel fee to help offset costs for ride-hail and delivery drivers.
Highlights Uber is charging customers a new fuel fee to help offset costs for ride-hail and delivery drivers. The temporary surcharge will be either 45 cents or 55 cents for each Uber trip and 35 cents for Uber Eats order. All the money will go directly to drivers, San Francisco-based Uber said.</description></item><item><title>USPS gets final signoff to order new delivery vehicles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62178571f1a4709d62d2c04f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 13:18:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62178571f1a4709d62d2c04f/</guid><description>The U.S. Postal Service says it has cleared the final regulatory hurdle to placing orders for next-generation mail vehicles
Highlights The U.S. Postal Service says it has cleared the final regulatory hurdle to placing orders for next-generation mail vehicles. Environmental groups have pushed back because only 10% of the vehicles would be electric-powered under the Postal Service contract with the manufacturer, Oshkosh Defense. The new vehicles boast modern amenities like climate control and safety features like air bags, backup cameras and collision avoidance — all currently lacking on the aging Grumman vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Amazon increases the price of Prime nearly 17% to $139 per year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 01:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc856e70dc4d0af0a2ac4a/</guid><description>Amazon hasn&amp;rsquo;t raised the price of its Prime membership program since 2018, when it increased from $99 to $119, the current fee.
Highlights Amazon is raising the price of its annual Prime membership to $139 from $119. Amazon also raised the monthly price of a Prime membership from $12.99 to $14.99. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s annual increase amounts to about a 17% rise in price. The company&amp;rsquo;s stock rose more than 14% at one point on Thursday in extended trading.</description></item></channel></rss>