<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>flag on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/flag/</link><description>Recent content in flag on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 22:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/flag/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Georgia students sue over blocked protest against rebel flag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62841e4fe20491d33c91ccef/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62841e4fe20491d33c91ccef/</guid><description>ATLANTA (AP) — Several Black students who were suspended for trying to protest Confederate flag displays at their school in Georgia have filed a federal lawsuit against their school district and its board members, accusing them of allowing an extensive pattern of racism including “overt bigotry and animosity by some white students and teachers against African American students.”
Highlights Lawsuit filed against school district and its board members in Georgia. Accuses them of allowing an extensive pattern of racism including “overt bigotry and animosity by some white students and teachers against African American students’ students.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court says Boston violated First Amendment rights of group seeking to raise a Christian flag outside City Hall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270660b2af196449ec319f1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 23:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270660b2af196449ec319f1/</guid><description>The Supreme Court unanimously ruled Monday that Boston violated the First Amendment rights of a group seeking to briefly raise a Christian flag atop a city flagpole outside of City Hall as a part of a city program celebrating Boston&amp;rsquo;s greater community.
Highlights The Supreme Court ruled Monday that Boston violated the First Amendment rights of a group seeking to briefly raise a Christian flag atop a city flagpole. The case was filed in 2018 after a Boston official denied the application by the group Camp Constitution to raise a flag &amp;ndash; described as &amp;ldquo;Christian&amp;rdquo; in the application &amp;ndash; on one of the three flagpoles outside Boston&amp;rsquo;s city hall.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioter draped in Confederate flag pleads guilty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620482864aaee0a133a002ef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620482864aaee0a133a002ef/</guid><description>A Maryland man who was draped in a Confederate flag when he stormed the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021, has pleaded guilty to joining the mob&amp;rsquo;s attack
Highlights Matthew Ryan Miller, 23, sprayed a fire extinguisher at law enforcement officers, prosecutors say. Video also captured Miller throwing an unidentifiable object toward officers. He is scheduled to be sentenced on May 23 in federal court. He wore a black cowboy hat, a Washington Capitals jersey and both the Maryland state flag and the Gadsden flag.</description></item></channel></rss>