<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>son on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/son/</link><description>Recent content in son on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/son/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teen arrested after mother noticed son had gun at Texas school drop-off</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d7cecd1b05fa739cedfe4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d7cecd1b05fa739cedfe4/</guid><description>A teenager was arrested after police said his own mother noticed he had a gun at a school drop-off.
Highlights A mother was dropping off her 15-year-old son at O.L. Slaton Middle School around 9 a.m. when she noticed the firearm. The teen never made it inside the building, and he ran from the school. The Lubbock Police Department responded to the area along with several other agencies in an attempt to find him.</description></item><item><title>Body found in duffel bag in Queens park; Orsolya Gaal identified, police questioning teen son</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d3a54ac3c8570c8a697be/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d3a54ac3c8570c8a697be/</guid><description>A woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a duffel bag in a New York City park Saturday. Police are now questioning her teen son.
Highlights A woman&amp;rsquo;s body was found in a duffel bag in a Queens park early Saturday morning. Police say she was not dismembered but placed in the bag and closed off. Police are now questioning her teen son. The family of four lives in the home where she was found dead in Queens park.</description></item><item><title>Mom who took her child into Capitol during riot gets prison</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d90c7b8e0e41a7ab1aeb9e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 04:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d90c7b8e0e41a7ab1aeb9e/</guid><description>A North Carolina woman who brought her 14-year-old son into the U.S. Capitol during last year&amp;rsquo;s riot was sentenced Friday to three months imprisonment. U.S. District Judge Colleen Kollar-Kotelly said she finds it “very hard to comprehend” why Virginia Marie Spencer and her husband took their child into the building during a violent insurrection.
Summary Mom who took her child into Capitol during riot gets prisonFILE - Violent protesters, loyal to President Donald Trump, storm the Capitol in Washington on Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>