<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elections on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elections/</link><description>Recent content in elections on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 17:21:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-Trump chief of staff Meadows removed from North Carolina voter roll amid probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625857e72a68bed58e210a5e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 17:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625857e72a68bed58e210a5e/</guid><description>Mark Meadows, who served as former Republican President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s chief of staff and echoed his false claims of widespread fraud in the 2020 election, has been removed from the voter roll in North Carolina as the state investigates possible irregularities in his registration.
Highlights Mark Meadows, who served as former Republican President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s chief of staff, has been removed from the voter roll in North Carolina as the state investigates possible irregularities in his registration.</description></item><item><title>Tenth person charged with Florida voter fraud investigation over jailhouse registrations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a5b557535f8507dd50c8d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 02:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a5b557535f8507dd50c8d/</guid><description>“They told us that if we weren’t already convicted of our current crime then we were able to sign up and vote.&amp;quot;
Highlights 10th former jail inmate is facing felony voter fraud charges. The 46-year-old is accused of registering to vote and casting a ballot in the 2020 presidential election. At least eight of the inmates registered during voter registration drives organized by Alachua County’s Democratic elections supervisor, Kim A. Barton, in February and July 2020.</description></item><item><title>More Miami voters report illegitimate party affiliation changes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202cec0f735cd232780bfa8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202cec0f735cd232780bfa8/</guid><description>Miami-Dade Elections Department 2021-22 records show more than 5,000 registered Democrats switched their party affiliation to Republican.
Highlights Miami-Dade Elections Department 2021-22 records show more than 5,000 registered Democrats switched their party affiliation to Republican. The increase comes just as more victims of third-party registrations are coming forward to report that their voter registration was altered without their permission. Republicans celebrated that the number of registered Republican voters in Florida surpassed Democrats in November, credited the change to an aggressive voter registration campaign.</description></item><item><title>'We're done. This is the end of the 2020 election': Maricopa County officials rebut error-plagued review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</guid><description>Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election.
Summary (CNN) Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election . Presenting the rebuttal to the Maricopa County Board of Supervisors in a four-hour meeting Wednesday, county elections officials said that 76 of the 77 claims made in the Cyber Ninjas report were false or misleading.</description></item></channel></rss>