<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hate/</link><description>Recent content in hate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 11:09:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>36-Year-Old Arrested in Dallas Salon Shooting, Possible Hate Crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62862539b75f880c3b0eacf3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 11:09:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62862539b75f880c3b0eacf3/</guid><description>Investigators believe Smith was the gunman that opened fire on the salon in Dallas&amp;rsquo; Koreatown last Wednesday.
Highlights Investigators believe Smith was the gunman that opened fire on the salon in Dallas&amp;rsquo; Koreatown. 36-year-old arrested in Dallas salon shooting, possible hate crime, police believe it was a hate crime. Smith is the suspect in the shooting, which is believed to be a hate-filled crime. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Buffalo shooting suspect planned to continue rampage down street, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282a1f5f0021dc365650e78/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282a1f5f0021dc365650e78/</guid><description>The 18-year-old suspected shooter accused of storming a Buffalo supermarket Saturday and killing 10 and injuring three others, planned to continue his bloody rampage.
Highlights Payton Gendron, 18, is accused of storming a Buffalo, New York, supermarket Saturday and killing 10 and injuring three others. Police say he planned to continue his bloody rampage down the street before he was stopped, police said. Police Commissioner Joseph Gramaglia said the supermarket attack was a hate crime as 11 of 13 people who were shot were Black.</description></item><item><title>Police search for gunman who shot three Korean women at Texas hair salon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e4fa5b9f877259b920835/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 12:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e4fa5b9f877259b920835/</guid><description>A search is underway for a suspect who opened fire at a Dallas hair salon, and injured three Korean women inside before fleeing Wednesday, police say.
Highlights Dallas police are searching for a suspect who opened fire at a Dallas hair salon, and injured three Korean women inside before fleeing. The suspect, described as a Black male dressed in all black, walked into the business and started shooting, striking the three women, police say.</description></item><item><title>Hate crimes in New York City are up 76% this year compared to the same period in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c06160027fdf4c7e549d9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 12:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c06160027fdf4c7e549d9/</guid><description>Hate crimes in New York City have increased 76% so far this year compared to the same period last year, according to data from the New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force (HCTF) released this week.
Highlights New York City has seen a rise in hate crimes compared to last year. Hate crimes have increased 76% since January 1 to April 10, data shows. The data was released as part of the New York Police Department&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat hate crimes.</description></item><item><title>A 22-year-old was attacked on the subway by a person shouting anti-gay slurs, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a1be41d95673c743932e0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 22:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a1be41d95673c743932e0/</guid><description>The New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force is investigating an incident in which an unidentified individual was captured on video shouting anti-gay slurs and attacking a 22-year-old on the subway, the NYPD announced this week.
Highlights The New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force is investigating an incident in which an unidentified individual was captured on video shouting anti-gay slurs and attacking a 22-year-old on the A-train. The individual then spit at the victim and repeatedly punched her in the face and head, police say.</description></item><item><title>Kanye West banned from Instagram after violating hate speech and bullying policies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232df75a551312a3c9ad464/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 07:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232df75a551312a3c9ad464/</guid><description>Ye, the artist formerly known as Kanye West, has been temporarily put on an Instagram time-out after apparently violating the company’s policies.
Highlights Content from his account, @kanyewest, has been deleted for violating policies on hate speech, bullying and harassment. Ye’s Instagram is also restricted from posting, commenting and sending direct messages for 24 hours. The musician reportedly posted a photo of comedian Trevor Noah and captioned it with racial slurs.</description></item><item><title>Man wanted in seven separate attacks against Asian women in one day, NYPD says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220f798ddc05b934c3116d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 17:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220f798ddc05b934c3116d3/</guid><description>The suspect who allegedly attacked seven Asian women over a two-hour period Sunday in Manhattan has been arrested and charged with hate crimes, police announced.
Highlights Steven Zajonc, 28, was arrested Wednesday, charged with seven counts each of assault as a hate crime, aggravated harassment and harassment. He was taken into custody after barricading himself in the New York Public Library. He allegedly punched or hurt seven Asian women over a two-hour period on Sunday in Manhattan.</description></item></channel></rss>