<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>higher on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/higher/</link><description>Recent content in higher on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 18:11:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/higher/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Home prices surged over 20% in March as interest rates also rose, according to S&amp;amp;P Case-Shiller</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62965a319ee805a75e2057be/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 18:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62965a319ee805a75e2057be/</guid><description>Home prices continued to increase their gains, despite slower sales and higher mortgage rates.
Highlights Case-Shiller Home Price Index rose 20.6% in March. Tampa, Phoenix and Miami continued to see the highest annual gains. Phoenix slipped from the top gainer spot for the first time in three years. March&amp;rsquo;s reading was the highest year-over-year price change in more than 35 years of data. The average mortgage rate on the 30-year fixed mortgage stood at 3.</description></item><item><title>Chevron’s profit quadruples in the first quarter as higher oil and gas prices boost operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c8b342bd3555015591521/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:05:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c8b342bd3555015591521/</guid><description>Chevron&amp;rsquo;s first-quarter results were helped by higher oil and gas prices.
Highlights Chevron&amp;rsquo;s profit more than quadrupled during the first quarter of 2022. The oil giant reported $6.3 billion in earnings during the period up from $1.37 billion during the same quarter in 2021. Chevron&amp;rsquo;s results follow a surge in commodity prices. West Texas Intermediate crude futures futures futures spiked to $130.50 in early March, a price last seen in 2008 as Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion sparked supply fears.</description></item><item><title>U.S. home sales tumble; higher prices, mortgage rates eroding affordability</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237cb804c9af8b7f4b860e4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237cb804c9af8b7f4b860e4/</guid><description>U.S. home sales fell by the most in a year in February as a perennial shortage of houses and double-digit price growth continued to squeeze first-time buyers out of the market.
Highlights Housing inventory drops 15.5% to 870,000 from year ago, down 155% from a year ago. Sales fell 7.2% to a seasonally adjusted annual rate of 6.02 million units last month. Mortgage rates are set to increase further after the Federal Reserve on Wednesday raised its policy interest rate by 25 basis points.</description></item></channel></rss>