<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>youth on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/youth/</link><description>Recent content in youth on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 18:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/youth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Attacks by Boston youth ‘terrorizing unsuspecting citizens’ continue downtown; police can’t make arrests because many suspects ‘too young’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62701ffa2bb077417f6e68b8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62701ffa2bb077417f6e68b8/</guid><description>At least five violent attacks involving juveniles &amp;quot;terrorizing unsuspecting citizens&amp;quot; that have occurred across Boston. The most recent attack happened on Wednesday night when Boston police were dispatched to Boston Common shortly after 6:30 p.m. Two women claimed
Highlights At least five violent attacks involving juveniles have occurred across Boston. The apparent ringleader of the group — a slim 5-foot-3-inch girl is “well known to Officers as she has been terrorizing unsuspecting citizens of Downtown Boston,” authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Amid increasing abuse, officials flee youth sports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62668234e844f605f90f26af/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 11:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62668234e844f605f90f26af/</guid><description>ATLANTA (AP) — When one looks at the ugly bruise encircling Kristi Moore&amp;rsquo;s left eye, it&amp;rsquo;s not surprising so many refs and umps are hanging up their stripes.
Highlights Kristi Moore was umpiring a girls’ softball game in Mississippi. A parent watching the game thought the runner was out. She began screaming profanities, according to Moore, “accused me of cheating these kids’” America is facing a crisis in prep and youth sports, where fewer and fewer people are willing to take on the thankless job of officiating.</description></item></channel></rss>