<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>threats on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threats/</link><description>Recent content in threats on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justin Moreira of Hyannis charged with threatening to commit school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294a5b27838abd7f0846e07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294a5b27838abd7f0846e07/</guid><description>A Cape Cod man was arrested after allegedly threatening to commit a school shooting.
Highlights Justin Moreira, 29, was arrested and charged with making terroristic threats. He is scheduled to be arraigned Tuesday in Barnstable District Court. Police received multiple reports about a Facebook post allegedly made by Moreira. Moreira was arrested at his Hyannis home and taken into custody without incident. Police searched Moreira&amp;rsquo;s home, but did not find any guns in his home.</description></item><item><title>Russia warns Czechia against supplying Ukraine with weapons of Soviet origin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3158957c06c6ce758141/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 21:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b3158957c06c6ce758141/</guid><description>As the Czech Republic continues to arm Ukraine, Russia has told the country that it cannot transfer Soviet-made weapons without its consent.
Highlights Russia has told the Czech Republic that it cannot transfer Soviet-made weapons without its consent. Czech Republic continues to arm Ukraine. Russia has also said it will be unable to prevent this sabotage, Czech Republic says. &amp;ldquo;We interpret this as a clear threat that Russia itself was and is preparing sabotage,&amp;rdquo; Czech minister says.</description></item><item><title>Michigan Governor Whitmer Kidnapping Plot Trial: FBI Raids Detroit Home Following Threats Against Judge, Defense Lawyers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245472bc791c2cc1e6b695e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245472bc791c2cc1e6b695e/</guid><description>NEWYou can now listen to TBEN News articles! The FBI has reportedly raided a home in suburban Detroit in connection with alleged threats against the
Highlights FBI reportedly raided home in Detroit in connection with alleged threats against judge and defense attorneys in kidnapping conspiracy trial of Michigan governor Gretchen Whitmer. Defense attorneys portrayed their clients as talkative, marijuana-smoking weekend warriors, susceptible to manipulation by FBI agents. The trial centers on the central issue of whether the FBI engaged in entrapment, the prohibited practice of cajoling or inciting individuals to commit certain criminal offenses.</description></item><item><title>FBI eyeing 6 suspects after bomb threats at Black colleges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234e7f30c7769f643588f73/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 20:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234e7f30c7769f643588f73/</guid><description>As the nation’s historically Black colleges remain on edge after receiving dozens of bomb threats in recent weeks, federal law enforcement officials said they have identified six suspects who they believe are responsible for most of the racially motivated crimes.
Highlights More than a third of America’s 101 historically Black colleges and universities have been targeted by calls or emails threatening to set off bombs on their campuses since early January.</description></item><item><title>Watchdog finds DHS identified threats prior to January 6 but did not widely share intelligence until after attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622846192ceb355fd1e97aad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 06:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622846192ceb355fd1e97aad/</guid><description>The Department of Homeland Security intelligence division had identified &amp;quot;specific&amp;quot; threats related to January 6, 2021, prior to the attack on the US Capitol, but did not widely share any intelligence it had gathered until two days after the riot, according to a new watchdog report.
Highlights DHS intelligence division had identified “specific” threats related to January 6, 2021, prior to the attack on the US Capitol, a new watchdog report says.</description></item><item><title>Covid-19: French MPs get death threats over support for vaccine pass that would bar the unvaccinated from much of public life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</guid><description>They report the threats as they consider tougher restrictions on unvaccinated people in France.
Summary In an interview with BFM TV, she said she had reported the threats to the police and would not be deterred from supporting the vaccine pass. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>