<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prosecutor on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prosecutor/</link><description>Recent content in prosecutor on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 13:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prosecutor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New evidence found in Madeleine McCann case as German prosecutor is 'sure' suspect killed British girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627672c97457334a1bf84a68/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627672c97457334a1bf84a68/</guid><description>A German prosecutor has said he is &amp;quot;sure&amp;quot; that Madeleine McCann &amp;ndash; the British girl who disappeared from a resort in Portugal in 2007 at the age of three &amp;ndash; was killed by suspect Christian Brückner.
Highlights Prosecutor says he is &amp;ldquo;sure&amp;rdquo; Madeleine McCann was killed by suspect Christian Brückner. Prosecutor says investigators have found &amp;ldquo;new evidence&amp;rdquo; that links the convicted rapist and child sex abuser to the child&amp;rsquo;s disappearance. The British girl disappeared from a holiday resort in Portugal in 2007 at the age of three.</description></item><item><title>Prosecutor: Oxford school shooting suspect asked jail: 'How do I get my fan mail?'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215c21737f3b6cafcc8235e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215c21737f3b6cafcc8235e/</guid><description>Judge will decide next week whether to keep Ethan Crumbley in an adult jail, or send him to a youth facility.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley is accused of plotting to stalk, rape, torture and kill a female classmate. Prosecutor: Oxford school shooting suspect asked jail: &amp;lsquo;How do I get my fan mail?&amp;rsquo; Defense attorney says he hasn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;altered his way of thinking&amp;rdquo; since being jailed in the Nov. 30 mass shooting. Prosecutors say he is too dangerous to be trusted around other minors.</description></item></channel></rss>