<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>survey on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/survey/</link><description>Recent content in survey on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 04:16:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/survey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>80% of Canadians support unlimited Ukrainian refugees: poll</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237fbfa74233b09769ee19c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 04:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237fbfa74233b09769ee19c/</guid><description>According to an online survey conducted by the non-profit Angus Reid Institute, Canadians have an unprecedented enthusiasm for welcoming Ukrainians fleeing war.
Highlights A new survey conducted by the non-profit Angus Reid Institute found four-in-five say they support the Liberal government&amp;rsquo;s plan to allow an unlimited number of Ukrainian refugees into the country. Canada has promised to allow entry of an “unlimited” number of fleeing Ukrainians through a new visa system under which they can be granted open-work permits and residence for two years, before they can apply for permanent residence or return home.</description></item><item><title>Court halts Shell’s offshore seismic survey along South Africa’s Wild Coast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbb3289803cb49658c7deb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbb3289803cb49658c7deb/</guid><description>The Grahamstown High Court in Makhanda on Tuesday granted an interdict against Shell’s seismic survey along the Wild Coast
Summary PRETORIA - The Grahamstown High Court in Makhanda on Tuesday granted an interdict against Shell’s seismic survey along the Wild CoastThis a second application made in the same court to stop oil multinational Shell’s seismic survey along South Africa’s Wild Coast. On Tuesday, Judge Gerald Bloem granted the applicants Amadiba, Dwesa-Cwebe, Port St Johns and Kei Mouth communities an interdict against Shell.</description></item></channel></rss>