<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>survey on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/survey/</link><description>Recent content in survey on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 07:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/survey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nearly half of families with kids can no longer afford enough food 5 months after child tax credit ended</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b052da9b95990b0708483/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 07:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b052da9b95990b0708483/</guid><description>Nearly half of parents who got expanded child tax credit checks now say they can&amp;rsquo;t afford enough food to feed their families, according to a May survey.
Highlights Child tax credit was expanded in 2021 through President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s American Rescue Plan. The legislation boosted the credit to $3,000 from $2,000, with a $600 bonus for kids under the age of 6 for the 2021 tax year. Nearly half of parents who used to get the checks now say they can&amp;rsquo;t afford enough food to feed their families, according to a May survey.</description></item><item><title>Flying insect numbers have plunged by 60% since 2004, GB survey finds | Insects</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275f272af360e6314e42a8d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 04:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275f272af360e6314e42a8d/</guid><description>Scientists behind survey of car number plates said drop was ‘terrifying’, as life on Earth depends on insects
Highlights The number of flying insects in Great Britain has plunged by almost 60% since 2004. The scientists behind the survey said the drop was ‘terrifying’, as life on Earth depends on insects. The fall was highest in England, at 65%, with Wales recording 55% fewer insects and Scotland 28% fewer. The next survey will run from June to August, Buglife said.</description></item><item><title>80% of Canadians support unlimited Ukrainian refugees: poll</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237fbfa74233b09769ee19c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 04:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237fbfa74233b09769ee19c/</guid><description>According to an online survey conducted by the non-profit Angus Reid Institute, Canadians have an unprecedented enthusiasm for welcoming Ukrainians fleeing war.
Highlights A new survey conducted by the non-profit Angus Reid Institute found four-in-five say they support the Liberal government&amp;rsquo;s plan to allow an unlimited number of Ukrainian refugees into the country. Canada has promised to allow entry of an “unlimited” number of fleeing Ukrainians through a new visa system under which they can be granted open-work permits and residence for two years, before they can apply for permanent residence or return home.</description></item><item><title>Court halts Shell’s offshore seismic survey along South Africa’s Wild Coast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbb3289803cb49658c7deb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 01:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbb3289803cb49658c7deb/</guid><description>The Grahamstown High Court in Makhanda on Tuesday granted an interdict against Shell’s seismic survey along the Wild Coast
Summary PRETORIA - The Grahamstown High Court in Makhanda on Tuesday granted an interdict against Shell’s seismic survey along the Wild CoastThis a second application made in the same court to stop oil multinational Shell’s seismic survey along South Africa’s Wild Coast. On Tuesday, Judge Gerald Bloem granted the applicants Amadiba, Dwesa-Cwebe, Port St Johns and Kei Mouth communities an interdict against Shell.</description></item></channel></rss>