<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>temperatures on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/temperatures/</link><description>Recent content in temperatures on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 10:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/temperatures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deaths of three Chicago women prompt urgent heat warnings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629497da8a4d3930f6ad202a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 10:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629497da8a4d3930f6ad202a/</guid><description>Experts say cities are failing to grapple with the deadly threat after discovery of bodies in senior housing facility
Highlights Bodies of three women found in Chicago senior housing facility found in May heatwave. Bodies were found in the James Sneider Apartments north of downtown Chicago on 14 May. Experts say cities are still learning how deadly heat can be, as global heating accelerates, disrupting norms. Chicago&amp;rsquo;s 1995 heatwave killed more than 700 people in the city on Lake Michigan.</description></item><item><title>Texans asked to turn up thermostats after sweltering heat knocks six power plants offline</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62806fd94765a9b5306d9c57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62806fd94765a9b5306d9c57/</guid><description>With an early-season heat wave searing much of Texas over the weekend, the nonprofit that manages power to more than 26 million customers wants them to turn up their thermostats.
Highlights The nonprofit that manages power to more than 26 million customers wants them to turn up their thermostats. It says soaring temperatures increased demand and caused six power generation facilities to trip offline. That resulted in the loss of about 2,900 megawatts of electricity.</description></item><item><title>Scotland hopes to save wild salmon by planting millions of trees next to rivers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbe2804c3c50c0fbe89b0f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 14:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbe2804c3c50c0fbe89b0f/</guid><description>River Dee initiative comes as rising water temperature from climate heating threatens species’ survival
Highlights Scientists found that only 35% of Scotland’s rivers have adequate tree cover. In 2018, the year Scotland recorded the lowest rod catch for salmon since records began. Temperatures in 70% of salmon rivers were too warm for at least one day that summer. A coldwater species, Atlantic salmon prefer summer temperatures above 10C; at 33C, they cannot survive.</description></item><item><title>Ground Temperatures Hit 129 Degrees as Argentina Suffers Blackouts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfdc44a8cbc3a0a3bcdd6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfdc44a8cbc3a0a3bcdd6e/</guid><description>The country is suffering through a heat wave that knocked out power in Buenos Aires and challenged all-time records.
Summary Ground temperatures climbed above 129 degrees Fahrenheit (54 degrees Celsius) in parts of Argentina this week as the country suffers through a shockingly hot start to summer. Those temperatures are different than air temperatures, which is our usual way of conveying how hot a place is. On Tuesday, temperatures rose to 106.</description></item></channel></rss>