<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>temperatures on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/temperatures/</link><description>Recent content in temperatures on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 14:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/temperatures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scotland hopes to save wild salmon by planting millions of trees next to rivers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbe2804c3c50c0fbe89b0f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 14:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbe2804c3c50c0fbe89b0f/</guid><description>River Dee initiative comes as rising water temperature from climate heating threatens species’ survival
Highlights Scientists found that only 35% of Scotland’s rivers have adequate tree cover. In 2018, the year Scotland recorded the lowest rod catch for salmon since records began. Temperatures in 70% of salmon rivers were too warm for at least one day that summer. A coldwater species, Atlantic salmon prefer summer temperatures above 10C; at 33C, they cannot survive.</description></item><item><title>Ground Temperatures Hit 129 Degrees as Argentina Suffers Blackouts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfdc44a8cbc3a0a3bcdd6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfdc44a8cbc3a0a3bcdd6e/</guid><description>The country is suffering through a heat wave that knocked out power in Buenos Aires and challenged all-time records.
Summary Ground temperatures climbed above 129 degrees Fahrenheit (54 degrees Celsius) in parts of Argentina this week as the country suffers through a shockingly hot start to summer. Those temperatures are different than air temperatures, which is our usual way of conveying how hot a place is. On Tuesday, temperatures rose to 106.</description></item></channel></rss>