<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>database on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/database/</link><description>Recent content in database on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/database/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Southern Baptist leaders covered up sex abuse, lied about secret database, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ad7ea05cc885ffd91d922/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ad7ea05cc885ffd91d922/</guid><description>Among the findings in the report was a previously unknown case of a pastor who was credibly accused of assaulting a woman a month after leaving the presidency of the Southern Baptist Convention.
Highlights The report is the first investigation of its kind in a massive Protestant denomination like the SBC. It is expected to send shock waves into a conservative Christian community that has had intense internal battles over how to handle sex abuse.</description></item><item><title>Anonymous team hacks database of Central Bank of Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c9975c0c447be38c729a4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c9975c0c447be38c729a4/</guid><description>A group of hackers Anonymous have hacked the database of the Central Bank of Russia and are going to make more than 35,000 files with secret agreements publicly available in the next 48 hours.
Highlights Anonymous team hacks database of Central Bank of Russia. More than 35,000 files will be released within 48 hours with secret agreements. Some 67% of Belarusians against shelling of Ukraine by Russian troops from territory of Belarus - study by Chatham House.</description></item><item><title>NYPD Accused Of Secretly Collecting DNA From Thousands Of New Yorkers For "Rogue" Database</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c28a63b6689afac93595a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 08:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c28a63b6689afac93595a/</guid><description>Legal Aid Society files federal lawsuit accusing NYPD of surreptitiously collecting genetic material from thousands of New Yorkers. DNA is stored indefinitely in a &amp;quot;rogue&amp;quot; DNA database, the lawsuit says. Police offer people who are being questioned
Highlights The Legal Aid Society accuses the NYPD of surreptitiously collecting genetic material from thousands of New Yorkers and storing it indefinitely in a &amp;ldquo;rogue&amp;rdquo; DNA database. The police offer people who are being questioned about a crime a beverage, a cigarette or chewing gum and then collect DNA from the items.</description></item></channel></rss>