<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>soon on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soon/</link><description>Recent content in soon on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 12:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/soon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finland and Sweden set to join NATO as soon as summer, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62541d77696e01bb58d98fc4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62541d77696e01bb58d98fc4/</guid><description>Russia has made a &amp;quot;massive strategic blunder&amp;quot; as Finland and Sweden look poised to join NATO as early as the summer, The Times reported Monday, citing unidentified officials.
Highlights Finland and Sweden look poised to join NATO as early as summer, report says. NATO membership for both Nordic countries was “a topic of conversation and multiple sessions” during talks between the alliance’s foreign ministers last week attended by Sweden and Finland.</description></item><item><title>Soon only one U.S. state will still have an indoor mask mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217f48a188df0d0eb259060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 21:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217f48a188df0d0eb259060/</guid><description>More parts of the country are dropping mask requirements, signaling a new phase in the pandemic.
Highlights Every state, with the exception of Hawaii, is either ditching or eliminating mask mandates as the Omicron surge recedes. The disease continues to kill about 2,000 Americans a day. New York and Rhode Island this month lifted indoor mask rules for businesses, but still require them in schools. In Los Angeles County, residents can soon go maskless so long as they show proof of vaccination at indoor venues.</description></item><item><title>Amazon deforestation: Record high destruction of trees in January</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a1ccc7edfcfd4606d4719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a1ccc7edfcfd4606d4719/</guid><description>An area of trees more than seven times the size of Manhattan, New York was destroyed.
Highlights Strong global demand for agricultural commodities is fuelling some of these illegal clearances. Another is the expectation that a new law will soon be passed in Brazil to legitimise and forgive land grabbing. New law is expected to be passed soon in the hope of legitimising and forgiving land grabbing in Brazil. An area of trees more than seven times the size of Manhattan, New York was destroyed in one of the worst clearances in Brazil&amp;rsquo;s history in 60 years by clearinghouses.</description></item></channel></rss>