<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plant on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plant/</link><description>Recent content in plant on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:13:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FDA comes to agreement with baby formula factory to resume production</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62838336f45acb4232acb38b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62838336f45acb4232acb38b/</guid><description>Abbott Nutrition said it would still take months to get the product back on store shelves.
Highlights Abbott Nutrition agrees to fix safety issues at a Michigan factory that has been shuttered for more than three months. The agreement represents a first step toward resolving a problem that has sent parents scrambling from store to store to find sustenance for their infants. The company has previously said that once the FDA has signed off on the fixes, it will take six to eight weeks to get the product back on shelves.</description></item><item><title>IAEA says Ukraine carried out first staff rotations at Chornobyl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62542c6cad32ae1f2639a0ab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 13:26:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62542c6cad32ae1f2639a0ab/</guid><description>Ukraine informed the International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA) on Sunday that it had carried out the first staff rotation at the Chornobyl Nuclear Power Plant in three weeks, IAEA Director General Rafael Mariano Grossi said, adding the agency would send a mission there soon to assist in returning in to normality.
Highlights Russia occupied the defunct power station north of Kyiv soon after invading Ukraine on Feb. 24 but Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s state nuclear energy company said in early April they had left the plant and were heading towards the border with Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainians shocked by 'crazy' scene at Chernobyl after Russian pullout reveals radioactive contamination</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251cd0e880d18b3a17a13ba/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251cd0e880d18b3a17a13ba/</guid><description>The sudden ear-piercing beep of a radiation meter fills the room as a Ukrainian soldier walks in. This is where Russian soldiers were living at the Chernobyl nuclear power plant, and radiation levels are now higher than normal.
Highlights CNN was given exclusive access to Chernobyl nuclear power plant for the first time since it came back into Ukrainian control. Russian soldiers held Chernobyl for a month and are thought to have been operating in contaminated areas most of the time.</description></item><item><title>Russia destroys Chernobyl radiation monitoring lab, says Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b7f910c6d79ac170ebd83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 20:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b7f910c6d79ac170ebd83/</guid><description>Russian forces have looted and destroyed a laboratory near the abandoned Chernobyl nuclear power plant that was used to monitor radioactive waste, the Ukrainian government said Wednesday.
Highlights The site of the world&amp;rsquo;s worst nuclear disaster fell into Russian hands in the first week of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion. The lab was part of a European Union-funded attempt to improve radioactive waste management. The government agency said it hoped Russia would use the samples to &amp;ldquo;harm itself, and not the civilized world&amp;rdquo; It is the latest scare at the infamous site in northern Ukraine, near the border with Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Creek near Northeast Samsung plant hit with millions more gallons of waste spilled from facility</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a7143a58c0cd8efb16739/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 15:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a7143a58c0cd8efb16739/</guid><description>Just weeks after the city reported sulfuric acid waste spilling from Austin&amp;rsquo;s Samsung plant into a nearby creek, the tech giant that is in the process of a Central Texas expansion has reported millions more gallons of spillage. More than 2 million gallons of stormwater mixed with wastewater spilled into a tributary north of the facility in January.
Highlights Samsung reported millions more gallons of spillage in January. More than 2 million gallons of stormwater mixed with wastewater spilled into a tributary north of the facility.</description></item><item><title>AP News: Thailand first in Asia to move to decriminalize marijuana</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f15405ae42be6e3e751bea/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f15405ae42be6e3e751bea/</guid><description>BANGKOK (AP) — Thailand on Tuesday became the first country in Asia to approve the de facto decriminalization of marijuana, though authorities have left a grey area around its recreational use. Health Minister Anutin Charnvirakul announced that the Narcotics Control Board had approved the dropping cannabis from the ministry&amp;rsquo;s list of controlled drugs.
Summary Thailand on Tuesday, Jan. 25, 2022, became the first country in Asia to approve the de facto decriminalization of marijuana, as its anti-narcotics agency agreed to have the Health Ministry drop cannabis from its list of controlled drugs.</description></item><item><title>One million chickens culled after H5N1 Bird Flu virus found spreading among several UK farms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79f59c1c0128349f0b525/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79f59c1c0128349f0b525/</guid><description>Lincolnshire is a bird flu hot-spot during the largest outbreak of infections England has known.
Summary Professor Ian Brown, of the Animal and Plant Health Agency, said: &amp;ldquo;There is a high density of poultry farms in Lincolnshire and the virus has found its way in because it has been able to breach the biosecurity barrier of the farms.&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>