<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>appeal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/appeal/</link><description>Recent content in appeal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/appeal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Court Orders Jussie Smollett Release From Jail During Appeal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232ee2351e025539a7b0aac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 08:16:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232ee2351e025539a7b0aac/</guid><description>Jussie Smollett was ordered released from jail Wednesday by an appeals court that agreed with his lawyers that he should be released pending the appeal of his&amp;hellip;
Highlights Jussie Smollett was ordered released from jail Wednesday by an appeals court that agreed with his lawyers that he should be released pending the appeal of his conviction. The court’s decision marks the latest chapter in a strange story that began in January 2019 when Smollet, who is Black and gay, reported to Chicago police that he was the victim of a racist and homophobic attack by two men wearing ski masks.</description></item><item><title>Facebook appeal over Cambridge Analytica data rejected by Australian court as ‘divorced from reality’ | Facebook</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200aa21c4bbaffb9be0d8e7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 05:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200aa21c4bbaffb9be0d8e7/</guid><description>Full bench of the federal court confirms earlier ruling that tech giant collects personal information in Australia
Highlights Federal court throws out Facebook&amp;rsquo;s claim that it does not carry out business in Australia. Federal court rules that social media giant collects personal information in the country. Cambridge Analytica harvested personal data of millions of Facebook users without their consent. The information was then used predominantly for political advertising, including to assist the Brexit campaign and Donald Trump.</description></item><item><title>Son of Sinéad O’Connor dies at age of 17 after going missing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9d13e3fc8393448a6f76d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 18:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9d13e3fc8393448a6f76d/</guid><description>Irish musician says Shane O’Connor, last seen on Friday morning, ‘was the very light of my life’
Summary Sinéad O’Connor’s 17-year-old son has died, two days after he was reported missing. The musician shared the news on social media, writing that he “decided to end his earthly struggle” and asked that “no one follows his example”. In the early hours of Saturday morning, O’Connor tweeted: “My beautiful son, Nevi’im Nesta Ali Shane O’Connor, the very light of my life, decided to end his earthly struggle today and is now with God.</description></item></channel></rss>