<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>train on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/train/</link><description>Recent content in train on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 18:16:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/train/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NATO warships arrive at Finnish port for training exercises</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626836f279b49ffa35e91d39/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 18:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626836f279b49ffa35e91d39/</guid><description>Three NATO warships arrived in the southwestern Finnish port of of Turku on Monday to train with Finland&amp;rsquo;s navy as Helsinki considers the possibility of joining the U.S.-led alliance amid increased tensions with Russia over Ukraine.
Highlights Three NATO warships arrived in the southwestern Finnish port of of Turku on Monday to train with Finland&amp;rsquo;s navy. Latvian minelayer LVNS Virsaitis and minehunters Estonian ENS Sakala and Dutch HNLMS Schiedam will train.</description></item><item><title>Person of Interest Named in NYC Subway Shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625644e93178b1ef1b478a7a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 03:35:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625644e93178b1ef1b478a7a/</guid><description>A gunman in a gas mask and construction vest set off smoke grenades and fired a barrage of bullets in a rush-hour subway train in Brooklyn, wounding at least 10&amp;hellip;
Highlights Police identify a person of interest as Frank R. James, 62, in relation to the attack. He has addresses in Philadelphia and Wisconsin, officials say. Five people are in critical condition but are expected to survive. A gas mask and construction vest fired a barrage of bullets in a subway train in Brooklyn, police say.</description></item><item><title>Man hit, killed by higher-speed train in Florida</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f072f43ccc917041eea60/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 09:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f072f43ccc917041eea60/</guid><description>Authorities say a Brightline train struck and killed a pedestrian, raising the death toll since the higher-speed train line resumed operations in South Florida.
Highlights Authorities say a Brightline train struck and killed a pedestrian, raising the death toll since the higher-speed train line resumed operations in South Florida. Brightline has the worst fatality rate in the nation, according to an ongoing Associated Press analysis of Federal Railroad Administration data. Its trains have fatally struck 59 people since beginning test runs in 2017, an average of about one death every 33,000 miles (about 53,000 kilometers) Central Florida’s SunRail has the second-worst rate among railroads that operate at least 100,000 mile (about 161,000 km) annually.</description></item></channel></rss>