<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hit on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hit/</link><description>Recent content in hit on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Parents of worker killed in tornado that hit Amazon facility are suing the company for wrongful death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</guid><description>The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.
Summary (CNN) The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.</description></item><item><title>Uber rider billed $600 after being stranded on I-95 during snow storm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d64d479ddf2fc971f5936d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d64d479ddf2fc971f5936d/</guid><description>A Richmond man not only got stranded on Interstate 95 in Virginia during this week’s snowstorm but was also hit with a massive Uber bill.
Summary Andrew Peters from Richmond not only got stranded on Interstate 95 during this week&amp;rsquo;s snowstorm but was also hit with a massive Uber bill. Andrew Peters, from Richmond, Virginia, not only got stranded on the highway but was also hit with a massive Uber bill.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioters hit with severe sentences and sharp reprimands from judges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c529bab46f6a641cfa9785/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 02:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c529bab46f6a641cfa9785/</guid><description>Some of the longest sentences have gone to rioters charged with ‘assaulting a police officer with a dangerous weapon’
Summary Since the riots, federal prosecutors have brought cases against 727 individuals over their involvement in the deadly riots. With hundreds facing criminal charges, Trump has come under growing scrutiny from the House select committee investigating the attacks. According to court documents, Devlyn Thompson helped move police shields up against a line of rioters in a tunnel, as well as hit police officers.</description></item></channel></rss>