<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hit on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hit/</link><description>Recent content in hit on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 09:10:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/hit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rents in the US just hit another record high</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62875aeead586c408d73c731/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 09:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62875aeead586c408d73c731/</guid><description>Rents in the US climbed to a new record high again in April, and they are expected to keep rising.
Highlights The national median rent was $1,827 a month in April, up 16.7% from a year ago. If recent trends continue, the typical rent could be more than $2,000 a month by August. The continued surge in rental prices is driven by a mismatch between rental supply and rising demand, says Realtor.</description></item><item><title>Russian ambassador to Poland hit with red paint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62793f5e21b3920489fb9c32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 16:21:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62793f5e21b3920489fb9c32/</guid><description>Protesters have thrown red paint on the Russian ambassador to Poland as he arrived at a cemetery in Warsaw to pay respects to Red Army soldiers who died during World War II
Highlights Protesters throw red paint on Russian ambassador to Poland as he arrives at a cemetery in Warsaw to pay respects to Red Army soldiers who died during World War II. Ambassador Sergey Andreev arrived at the Soviet soldiers&amp;rsquo; cemetery to lay flowers on Victory Day.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks hit with sweeping labor complaint including over 200 alleged violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62762ae4fdb9401279f7561e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 08:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62762ae4fdb9401279f7561e/</guid><description>The NLRB says Starbucks interfered with, restrained and coerced employees seeking to unionize in various ways.
Highlights National Labor Relations Board accuses Starbucks of 29 unfair labor practice charges. Accuses Starbucks of interfering with, restraining and coercing employees seeking to unionize in various ways. Starbucks does not agree that the claims have merit, but the complaint&amp;rsquo;s issuance does not constitute a finding by the NLRB. Starbucks has nearly 9,000 locations across the country and has nearly 250 stores to organize with Starbucks Workers United.</description></item><item><title>Unruly US airline passengers hit with record fines by FAA</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251b17839ead3e6dbd2c86d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251b17839ead3e6dbd2c86d/</guid><description>Aviation authority has imposed zero-tolerance policy and says incidents have soared since 6 January Capitol attack
Highlights FAA has imposed zero-tolerance policy since January 2021. Agency has proposed fines of about $7m for disruptive passengers. $81,950 fine for American Airlines passenger on July flight from Dallas to Charlotte. Another $75,000 (£57,500) fine for Delta Air Lines passenger who bit a fellow passenger after trying to hug and kiss another. Agency says incidents have soared since 6 January 2021 attack on US Capitol.</description></item><item><title>Parents of worker killed in tornado that hit Amazon facility are suing the company for wrongful death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e68e95bc25e718d7f004e9/</guid><description>The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.
Summary (CNN) The parents of Austin McEwen, one of the six victims killed after a tornado pummeled an Amazon warehouse in Edwardsville, Illinois, last month, said Monday during a press conference that they are suing Amazon over the alleged wrongful death of their son.</description></item><item><title>Uber rider billed $600 after being stranded on I-95 during snow storm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d64d479ddf2fc971f5936d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d64d479ddf2fc971f5936d/</guid><description>A Richmond man not only got stranded on Interstate 95 in Virginia during this week’s snowstorm but was also hit with a massive Uber bill.
Summary Andrew Peters from Richmond not only got stranded on Interstate 95 during this week&amp;rsquo;s snowstorm but was also hit with a massive Uber bill. Andrew Peters, from Richmond, Virginia, not only got stranded on the highway but was also hit with a massive Uber bill.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioters hit with severe sentences and sharp reprimands from judges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c529bab46f6a641cfa9785/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 02:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c529bab46f6a641cfa9785/</guid><description>Some of the longest sentences have gone to rioters charged with ‘assaulting a police officer with a dangerous weapon’
Summary Since the riots, federal prosecutors have brought cases against 727 individuals over their involvement in the deadly riots. With hundreds facing criminal charges, Trump has come under growing scrutiny from the House select committee investigating the attacks. According to court documents, Devlyn Thompson helped move police shields up against a line of rioters in a tunnel, as well as hit police officers.</description></item></channel></rss>