<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>floyd on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/floyd/</link><description>Recent content in floyd on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 17:18:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/floyd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pink Floyd to release first new music in 28 years in support of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62506e35fb4c0a21f03f49c4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 17:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62506e35fb4c0a21f03f49c4/</guid><description>Legendary rock band Pink Floyd is releasing a new single &amp;quot;Hey Hey Rise Up&amp;quot; on Friday in support of the people of Ukraine, the band said in a statement on Thursday.
Highlights The song is performed by guitarist David Gilmour and drummer Nick Mason, with bass player Guy Pratt and Nitin Sawhney on keyboard. It&amp;rsquo;s the first new music from the band since 1994, and all proceeds will go to Ukrainian humanitarian relief.</description></item><item><title>Police trainer testifies against officers in Floyd's death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202dc604d4ac3d9ae76a1d9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202dc604d4ac3d9ae76a1d9/</guid><description>ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — A Minneapolis police officer who oversaw medical training for two of the three former officers charged with violating George Floyd&amp;rsquo;s civil rights testified Tuesday that the officers were trained to give CPR as soon as they fail to find a pulse on someone.
Highlights Officer Derek Chauvin knelt on George Floyd’s neck for 9 1/2 minutes as he was handcuffed, facedown. Officer J. Alexander Kueng, Thomas Lane and Tou Thao are accused of depriving Floyd, 46, of his rights.</description></item></channel></rss>