<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>losses on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/losses/</link><description>Recent content in losses on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 20:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/losses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Melvin Capital to shut after heavy losses on meme stocks, market slump</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287f599d7a33ec083e28b52/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 20:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287f599d7a33ec083e28b52/</guid><description>Melvin Capital, once one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful hedge funds which then lost billions in the meme stock saga, will shut down after it was hit again by this year&amp;rsquo;s market slump.
Highlights Melvin Capital, once one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful hedge funds, will shut down after it was hit again by this year&amp;rsquo;s market slump. Gabe Plotkin, widely regarded as one of the industry&amp;rsquo;s best traders after posting years of double digit returns, told investors that the last 17 months have been &amp;ldquo;an incredibly trying time&amp;rdquo; Plotkin had been trying to turn around the firm after being caught out in early 2021 betting against retail favorite GameStop GME and after being wrong footed again by tumbling markets this year.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin drops below $35,000 over the weekend, extending Friday’s losses</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62788fc5f517e7963032f1a8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 03:52:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62788fc5f517e7963032f1a8/</guid><description>Bitcoin declined to $33,454.57 on Sunday, according to Coin Metrics, following a major stock sell-off in the U.S. last week.
Highlights Bitcoin declined to $33,454.57 on Sunday, according to data from Coin Metrics. The drop comes after a major stock sell-off in the U.S. last week sent the cryptocurrency market into a frenzy. Bitcoin is now down 50% from its peak price of $67,802.30 in November 2021. The Dow Jones Industrial Average lost more than 1,000 points on Thursday and the Nasdaq plunged by 5% on Friday, marking the worst single-day drops since 2020.</description></item><item><title>Russia faces heavy losses as it attacks Ukraine on all fronts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bdb60662b7d392ad85cbe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 20:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bdb60662b7d392ad85cbe/</guid><description>Russia lost 14 planes, 8 helicopters, 102 tanks, 536 BBM, 15 heavy machine guns, and 1 BUK missile since Feb. 24. Russia also lost over 3,500 soldiers, Ukraine’s Armed Forces said
Highlights Russia has lost 14 planes, 8 helicopters, 102 tanks, 536 BBM, 15 heavy machine guns, and 1 BUK missile since Feb. The Kremlin also lost over 3,500 soldiers, Ukraine’s Armed Forces said on Feb. Russia has begun redeploying reserve units in the areas bordering Ukraine and continues to carry out airstrikes on airfields, military depots, and civilians.</description></item><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg’s ‘metaverse’ business lost more than $10 billion last year, and the losses keep growing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb9c540d3d2c73f6c5d966/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 09:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb9c540d3d2c73f6c5d966/</guid><description>Those losses for 2021 are in line with what Zuckerberg said last year he expected to invest in Reality Labs.
Highlights Facebook&amp;rsquo;s parent company revealed the financials of its Reality Labs division in its fourth-quarter 2021 earnings report Wednesday. Reality Labs is tasked with building CEO Mark Zuckerberg&amp;rsquo;s vision for the metaverse. The company would have had more than $56 billion in profit for all of last year had it not been for Reality Labs.</description></item></channel></rss>