<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>virus on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/virus/</link><description>Recent content in virus on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 05:13:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/virus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man who received landmark pig heart transplant died of pig virus, surgeon says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275ffbf4227b5eef2a839fe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 05:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275ffbf4227b5eef2a839fe/</guid><description>David Bennett died two months after groundbreaking surgery in which a genetically modified pig’s heart was transplanted into him
Highlights David Bennett, 57, died in March after undergoing a pig heart transplant. Surgeon says the pig&amp;rsquo;s heart was infected with porcine cytomegalovirus, which may have contributed to Bennett’s death. Experts believe that the experiment may have been derailed as a result of an ‘unforced error’ Experts say the specific type of virus in the donor heart is not capable of infecting human cells.</description></item><item><title>Tesla CEO Elon Musk says he has Covid again</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242b1c8e17290548a4f1097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 07:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242b1c8e17290548a4f1097/</guid><description>Tesla CEO Elon Musk said he has Covid again, following an earlier bout in November 2020.
Highlights SpaceX and Tesla CEO Elon Musk tested positive for Covid-19 on Monday. He has a history of under-estimating the novel coronavirus and balking at health officials. The announcement comes after Tesla&amp;rsquo;s factory in Shanghai faced Covid restrictions that reportedly require it to suspend production for four days until around April 1. Tesla also suspended production in Shanghai for two days earlier in March after officials implemented Covid health orders.</description></item><item><title>Scientists identify antibodies that can neutralize Omicron variant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd20ce5c4519e782d43bc5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 03:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd20ce5c4519e782d43bc5/</guid><description>According to a new study, a group of international researchers have found certain antibodies can target areas of the virus spike protein that don’t undergo significant changes as the virus mutates.
Summary A team of scientists have identified antibodies they say can neutralize Omicron and other COVID-19 variants. AN UNUSUAL VARIANTThe Omicron variant is considered to be “unusual” because of a large number of mutations to two key areas of the virus’ spike protein.</description></item></channel></rss>