<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>walker on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/walker/</link><description>Recent content in walker on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/walker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anti-vaccination doctor Jonie Girouard can no longer practise in New Zealand</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbe7a8993d260601a318fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbe7a8993d260601a318fa/</guid><description>A Kaiapoi doctor caught handing out fake vaccine exemptions is no longer registered to practise medicine in New Zealand.
Summary A Kaiapoi doctor caught handing out fake vaccine exemptions is no longer registered to practise medicine in New Zealand. Medical Council chairperson Curtis Walker said Dr Girouard​ was now unable to practise medicine in New Zealand, as she was no longer registered. &amp;ldquo;The Medical Council thanks the thousands of doctors who are contributing to New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s pandemic response.</description></item><item><title>Business owner paid ex-worker with 91,000 pennies. That's retaliation, feds claim in lawsuit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</guid><description>A Georgia auto repair shop broke the law when it dumped $915 in change on a former employee&amp;rsquo;s driveway, regulator alleges.
Summary The U.S. Department of Labor has filed a lawsuit against the Peachtree, Georgia-based auto repair shop and owner Miles Walker after deciding that the stunt amounted to retaliation. According to the government&amp;rsquo;s complaint, Walker decided to pay Flaten in pennies within hours of learning that he had contacted regulators over his missing paycheck.</description></item></channel></rss>