<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>site on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/site/</link><description>Recent content in site on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police suspect arson in fire at Wyoming abortion clinic site</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291caab4cdc92f3f00e1212/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291caab4cdc92f3f00e1212/</guid><description>Police believe an overnight fire in Wyoming that damaged a building being renovated to house a new abortion clinic was deliberately set
Highlights Fire damaged building being renovated to house abortion clinic in Casper, Wyoming. Clinic was set to open in June as only the second place in the state to offer abortions. Clinic organizers had been receiving harassing emails and telephone messages. No injuries were reported; police are reviewing video footage from the area in hopes of identifying the suspect.</description></item><item><title>Russia destroys Chernobyl radiation monitoring lab, says Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b7f910c6d79ac170ebd83/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 20:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b7f910c6d79ac170ebd83/</guid><description>Russian forces have looted and destroyed a laboratory near the abandoned Chernobyl nuclear power plant that was used to monitor radioactive waste, the Ukrainian government said Wednesday.
Highlights The site of the world&amp;rsquo;s worst nuclear disaster fell into Russian hands in the first week of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion. The lab was part of a European Union-funded attempt to improve radioactive waste management. The government agency said it hoped Russia would use the samples to &amp;ldquo;harm itself, and not the civilized world&amp;rdquo; It is the latest scare at the infamous site in northern Ukraine, near the border with Belarus.</description></item><item><title>Photos show first work in years at North Korea nuke site, analysts say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622757d473e1ee594f0a31ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 13:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622757d473e1ee594f0a31ac/</guid><description>Recent photos taken from space show new buildings and other signs of work at North Korea’s Punggye-ri nuclear testing facility, analysts say.
Highlights Recent photos taken from space show new buildings and other signs of work at North Korea’s nuclear testing facility, analysts say. They call it a worrying sign that the country could be planning to resume testing atomic bombs after having claimed to have destroyed the site in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Florida breaks single-day COVID case record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d096be37ba84daa372a281/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d096be37ba84daa372a281/</guid><description>The omicron variant of the coronavirus has spiked in Florida and across the nation over the past few weeks.
Summary TAMPA, Fla. — The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Friday reported more than 75,900 new cases of COVID-19 in Florida. Friday’s report marks a single-day record for the number of new cases in Florida. It breaks the record set a day earlier when more than 58,000 cases were reported in the state.</description></item></channel></rss>