<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>number on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/number/</link><description>Recent content in number on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 04:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/number/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flying insect numbers have plunged by 60% since 2004, GB survey finds | Insects</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275f272af360e6314e42a8d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 04:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275f272af360e6314e42a8d/</guid><description>Scientists behind survey of car number plates said drop was ‘terrifying’, as life on Earth depends on insects
Highlights The number of flying insects in Great Britain has plunged by almost 60% since 2004. The scientists behind the survey said the drop was ‘terrifying’, as life on Earth depends on insects. The fall was highest in England, at 65%, with Wales recording 55% fewer insects and Scotland 28% fewer. The next survey will run from June to August, Buglife said.</description></item><item><title>‘I’ve already sold my daughters; now, my kidney’: winter in Afghanistan’s slums</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eea2f684ca39c4f33cd1ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 13:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eea2f684ca39c4f33cd1ed/</guid><description>Crushing poverty is forcing starving displaced people to make desperate choices
Summary Rahmati says she sold her daughters a few months ago for 100,000 afghani each (roughly £700), to families she doesn’t know. Delaram Rahmati, who sold a kidney to support her family. Rahmati sold her right kidney for 150,000 afghani (£1,000). The cost of a kidney transplant is 400,000 afghani, plus the price of the kidney, according to Kabir. There is more demand for kidney transplants outside Afghanistan.</description></item><item><title>U.S. reports at least 1.1 million COVID cases in a day, shattering global record</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd8d8991e65330abc578a1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd8d8991e65330abc578a1/</guid><description>The United States reported 1.35 million new coronavirus infections on Monday, according to a Reuters tally, the highest daily total for any country in the world as the spread of the highly contagious Omicron variant showed no signs of slowing.
Summary The previous record was 1.03 million cases on Jan. 3. A large number of cases are reported each Monday due to many states not reporting over the weekend. The seven-day average for new cases has tripled in two weeks to over 700,000 new infections a day.</description></item></channel></rss>