<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>feds on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/feds/</link><description>Recent content in feds on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/feds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Water is so low in the Colorado River, feds are holding some back so one dam can keep generating power</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728a1923276fefa5f6eab5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62728a1923276fefa5f6eab5/</guid><description>The decision will keep more water in Lake Powell, the reservoir located at the Glen Canyon Dam in northern Arizona.
Highlights The decision will keep more water in Lake Powell, the reservoir located at the Glen Canyon Dam in northern Arizona. Officials said the actions will help save water, protect the dam&amp;rsquo;s ability to produce hydropower and provide officials with more time to figure out how to operate the dam at lower water levels.</description></item><item><title>Feds: Forced-reset triggers are machine guns under US law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal officials are notifying gun dealers that some forced-reset triggers, which allow guns to fire rapidly with a single continuous pull of the trigger, are considered machine guns under federal law and subject to strict regulation.
Highlights The notification was being made Thursday in an open letter from the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives to federally licensed firearms dealers. It spells out how investigators have determined the triggers to be “conversion devices,” making the weapons machine guns.</description></item></channel></rss>