<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>settlement on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/settlement/</link><description>Recent content in settlement on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 21:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/settlement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. judge rejects Prince Andrew's bid to dismiss sex abuse accuser's lawsuit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df416ff7a3dc5a2429fa35/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 21:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df416ff7a3dc5a2429fa35/</guid><description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew failed to persuade a U.S. judge to dismiss Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit accusing the Duke of York of sexually abusing her when she was a teenager.
Summary Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew leaves St. Mary the Virgin church in Hillington, near royal Sandringham estate, in Norfolk, Britain January 19, 2020. REUTERS/Chris RadburnNEW YORK, Jan 12 (Reuters) - Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew failed to persuade a U.S. judge to dismiss Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit accusing the Duke of York of sexually abusing her when she was a teenager.</description></item><item><title>Israeli PM announces plan to double the amount of settlers living in Golan Heights — a multimillion dollar project meant to further consolidate Israel's hold on the territory it captured from Syria more than five decades ago</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8d7eff9cd1fcdb7a049f2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c8d7eff9cd1fcdb7a049f2/</guid><description>Israel says it plans to double the amount of settlers living in the Golan Heights and invest hundreds of millions of dollars developing the area
Summary Israel says it plans to double the amount of settlers living in the Golan Heights and invest hundreds of millions of dollars developing the areaMEVO HAMA, Golan Heights &amp;ndash; Israeli Prime Minister Naftali Bennett said Sunday the country intends to double the amount of settlers living in the Israeli-controlled Golan Heights with a multimillion-dollar plan meant to further consolidate Israel’s hold on the territory it captured from Syria more than five decades ago.</description></item></channel></rss>