<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>operations on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/operations/</link><description>Recent content in operations on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:05:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/operations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chevron’s profit quadruples in the first quarter as higher oil and gas prices boost operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c8b342bd3555015591521/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:05:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c8b342bd3555015591521/</guid><description>Chevron&amp;rsquo;s first-quarter results were helped by higher oil and gas prices.
Highlights Chevron&amp;rsquo;s profit more than quadrupled during the first quarter of 2022. The oil giant reported $6.3 billion in earnings during the period up from $1.37 billion during the same quarter in 2021. Chevron&amp;rsquo;s results follow a surge in commodity prices. West Texas Intermediate crude futures futures futures spiked to $130.50 in early March, a price last seen in 2008 as Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion sparked supply fears.</description></item><item><title>Visa, Mastercard suspend operations in Russia over Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224428465f666ec98c78328/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 05:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224428465f666ec98c78328/</guid><description>U.S. payments firms Visa Inc and Mastercard Inc on Saturday said they were suspending operations in Russia over the invasion of Ukraine, and that they would work with clients and partners to cease all transactions there.
Highlights U.S. payments firms Visa Inc (V.N) and Mastercard Inc on Saturday said they were suspending operations in Russia over the invasion of Ukraine, and that they would work with clients and partners to cease all transactions there.</description></item></channel></rss>