<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>truckers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/truckers/</link><description>Recent content in truckers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/truckers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CEO of Canada’s largest trucking company says vaccine mandate ‘not an issue at all’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202ea89b9b0093c3050a110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202ea89b9b0093c3050a110/</guid><description>National Newswatch: Canada&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive site for political news and views. Make it a daily habit.
Highlights CEO of Canada’s largest trucking company says vaccine mandate ‘not an issue at all’ CEO of TFI International Inc. says its operations are virtually untouched by the mandate. Alain Bédard says last month was looking like &amp;ldquo;the best January ever for the company&amp;rdquo; following a fourth quarter that saw profits jump by more than two-thirds and revenue leap by 91 per cent.</description></item><item><title>GoFundMe shuts down funding to 'Freedom Convoy'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fea21506ae11e36afd7b17/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 16:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fea21506ae11e36afd7b17/</guid><description>The platform said it would release the funds for a peaceful demonstration, but not for an occupation that has been linked to illegal activity.
Highlights GoFundMe pulls plug on campaign that had collected more than $10 million for &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; Convoy protest in Ottawa. Organizers say the protest by truckers and their supporters in Ottawa has become an occupation. The platform is allowing requests for donation refunds until Feb. A new fundraiser on Christian Crowdfunding site GiveSendGo had raised over $73,000 as of Friday evening.</description></item></channel></rss>