<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>truckers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/truckers/</link><description>Recent content in truckers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/truckers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Walmart says it is raising truckers’ pay and starting a training program as it grapples with driver shortage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fe0bb488d355f55ec5200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fe0bb488d355f55ec5200/</guid><description>Walmart is trying to expand the pipeline of truck drivers amid a national shortage.
Highlights Walmart says truck drivers will now make between $95,000 and $110,000 in their first year with Walmart. The retailer is ramping up recruiting efforts for truck drivers amid a tight market for trucking labor. The shortage of truck drivers in the U.S. hit an all-time high of more than 80,000 workers last year, trade group says.</description></item><item><title>Truck blockade at U.S.-Canadian border shuts auto plants</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057198cf5ec5624e0d195b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 20:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62057198cf5ec5624e0d195b/</guid><description>The truck blockade at the U.S. border by Canadians protesting the country’s COVID-19 restrictions is tightening the screws on the auto industry, forcing Ford, Toyota and General Motors to shut down plants or otherwise curtail production
Highlights The U.S. braced for the possibility of similar truck-borne protests inspired by the Canadians. The bumper-to-bumper demonstration by the self-proclaimed Freedom Convoy entered its fourth day Thursday at the Ambassador Bridge connecting Windsor, Ontario, to Detroit, disrupting the flow of auto parts and other products between the two countries.</description></item><item><title>CEO of Canada’s largest trucking company says vaccine mandate ‘not an issue at all’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202ea89b9b0093c3050a110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202ea89b9b0093c3050a110/</guid><description>National Newswatch: Canada&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive site for political news and views. Make it a daily habit.
Highlights CEO of Canada’s largest trucking company says vaccine mandate ‘not an issue at all’ CEO of TFI International Inc. says its operations are virtually untouched by the mandate. Alain Bédard says last month was looking like &amp;ldquo;the best January ever for the company&amp;rdquo; following a fourth quarter that saw profits jump by more than two-thirds and revenue leap by 91 per cent.</description></item><item><title>GoFundMe shuts down funding to 'Freedom Convoy'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fea21506ae11e36afd7b17/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 16:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fea21506ae11e36afd7b17/</guid><description>The platform said it would release the funds for a peaceful demonstration, but not for an occupation that has been linked to illegal activity.
Highlights GoFundMe pulls plug on campaign that had collected more than $10 million for &amp;lsquo;Freedom Convoy&amp;rsquo; Convoy protest in Ottawa. Organizers say the protest by truckers and their supporters in Ottawa has become an occupation. The platform is allowing requests for donation refunds until Feb. A new fundraiser on Christian Crowdfunding site GiveSendGo had raised over $73,000 as of Friday evening.</description></item></channel></rss>