<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jury on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jury/</link><description>Recent content in jury on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 11:13:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jury/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grand jury indicts man accused in Brooklyn subway mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278f74d2a1ca44d849baaaa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 11:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278f74d2a1ca44d849baaaa/</guid><description>Frank James, 62, is accused of shooting 10 people on a Manhattan-bound train on April 12. Police estimate James fired a gun 33 times while onboard an N train, police say. The day before the attack, James posted a
Highlights Frank James, 62, is charged with committing a terrorist attack or other violence against a mass transportation system. James is accused of setting off smoke grenades and firing a gun on a crowded train in Brooklyn.</description></item><item><title>NYPD veteran convicted of assaulting officer in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627057bfd2ba74e3f6bc59c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 22:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627057bfd2ba74e3f6bc59c6/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal jury on Monday convicted a New York Police Department veteran of assaulting an officer during the U.S.
Highlights Thomas Webster is the first Capitol riot defendant to be tried on an assault charge and the first to present a jury with a self-defense argument. Webster, a 20-year NYPD veteran, testified that he was trying to protect himself from a “rogue cop” who punched him in the face.</description></item><item><title>Florida woman impregnated by doctor’s sperm awarded $5.25M in damages by jury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624619594c7a0ce1ca5b8b5d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 21:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624619594c7a0ce1ca5b8b5d/</guid><description>A Florida woman who accused a Vermont doctor of impregnating her with his own sperm rather than a donor&amp;rsquo;s was awarded $5.25 million by a federal court jury Wednesday.
Highlights Cheryl Rousseau was awarded $5.25 million by a federal court jury in the case against Vermont doctor John Coates III. She and her husband, Peter Rousseau, sued Coates in 2018, accusing him of using his sperm during an artificial insemination procedure in 1977 at what was then called the Central Vermont Hospital in Berlin, Vermont.</description></item><item><title>Jury awards $14 million to protesters injured by Denver police during 2020 demonstrations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ef4d7ccedc04c6b9d435a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 11:11:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ef4d7ccedc04c6b9d435a/</guid><description>Denver police officers violated protesters’ rights during the massive 2020 demonstrations against police brutality, a federal jury concluded Friday, awarding 12 protesters a total of $14 million in compensation following a three-week trial.
Highlights Jury awards 12 protesters a total of $14 million in compensation after a three-week trial. The jury found in favor of the 12 plaintiffs after about five hours of deliberation. The trial is believed to be the first in the U.</description></item><item><title>Guy Reffitt, first January 6 defendant to stand trial, found guilty on all charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227c6867193f5fd6d197b87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 21:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227c6867193f5fd6d197b87/</guid><description>Member of the far-right militia group the Texas Three Percenters was turned in to the FBI by his teenage son, who testified against him.
Highlights Guy Reffitt, 49, found guilty on all five charges in connection with January 6, 2021, attack on U.S. Capitol. He faces a maximum of 60 years in prison; sentencing is set for June 8. He was indicted on five counts last year for transporting a rifle and a semi-automatic handgun to Washington, D.</description></item></channel></rss>