<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>breaking on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/breaking/</link><description>Recent content in breaking on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/breaking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High schooler runs sub-4 minute mile, breaking record that had stood since 1965</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285c66385f44101ea3d81fa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285c66385f44101ea3d81fa/</guid><description>Gary Martin accomplished the feat at the Pennsylvania Catholic League Championship
Highlights Gary Martin, a senior at Archbishop Wood High School Warminster, Penn., broke a record that had been set by Jim Ryun in 1965. Ryun became the first high schooler to run a mile in under four minutes in 1964, then broke his own record five times before graduating. Martin is now the 14th American high school athlete to break four minutes, and his time now ranks third all-time in outdoor runs.</description></item><item><title>04/28/2022 - US left behind $7 billion of military equipment in Afghanistan after 2021 withdrawal, Pentagon report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626aa07aaec07837eb62fa57/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 14:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626aa07aaec07837eb62fa57/</guid><description>View the latest news and breaking news today for U.S., world, weather, entertainment, politics and health at CNN.com.
Highlights The US gave a total of $18.6 billion of equipment to the Afghan National Defense and Security Forces from 2005 to 2021. Equipment worth $7.12 billion remained in Afghanistan after the US military withdrawal was completed in August. The Defense Department has no plans to return to Afghanistan to &amp;ldquo;retrieve or destroy&amp;rdquo; the equipment, a report says.</description></item></channel></rss>