<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>assistance on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/assistance/</link><description>Recent content in assistance on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 15:14:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/assistance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine begs for assistance, claiming that Russia is attempting to partition the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241d0a9f0fbde6fee1a8077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 15:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241d0a9f0fbde6fee1a8077/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky accused the West of cowardice Sunday while another top official said Russia was trying to split the nation in two, like North and South Korea.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy calls for fighter jets and tanks to be handed over to the West. Another top official says Russia is trying to split Ukraine in two, like North and South Korea. Russia quickly bans interview from being published from publication by Russian media.</description></item><item><title>Landlords finding ways to evict after getting rental aid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083067608dae9638d05bd8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 22:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083067608dae9638d05bd8/</guid><description>A day before she was due to be evicted in November from her Atlanta home, Shanelle King heard that she had been awarded about $15,000 in rental assistance. She could breathe again. But then the 43-year-old hairdresser got a letter last month from her landlord saying the company was canceling her lease in March —- seven months early — without any explanation.
Highlights $46.5 billion Emergency Rental Assistance Program has paid out tens of billions of dollars to help avert an eviction crisis.</description></item></channel></rss>