<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>loses on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/loses/</link><description>Recent content in loses on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:18:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/loses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Slovenia's populist PM loses election to environmentalist party</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62681b35dfef9f4587492756/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62681b35dfef9f4587492756/</guid><description>Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist Prime Minister, Janez Janša, lost a national election on Sunday as the environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities.
Highlights Slovenia&amp;rsquo;s populist Prime Minister, Janez Janša, lost a national election on Sunday. The environmentalist Freedom Movement party won more votes than his SDS party, according to preliminary figures from election authorities. The election had been expected to be tight but the official preliminary figures showed the Freedom Movement, a newcomer in the election, leading with 34.</description></item><item><title>Trump ally Devin Nunes loses CNN defamation appeal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625880d192352602c15715a4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 20:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625880d192352602c15715a4/</guid><description>A federal appeals court said Devin Nunes, the former California congressman and an ally of former U.S. President Donald Trump, cannot revive his defamation lawsuit against CNN over reports he was involved in efforts to uncover damaging Ukraine-related information about Joe Biden.
Highlights A federal appeals court said Devin Nunes cannot revive his defamation lawsuit against CNN. The 2nd U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Manhattan said Nunes failed to seek a correction fast enough, or show he deserved &amp;ldquo;special damages&amp;rdquo; for economic loss.</description></item><item><title>Paris replaces St. Petersburg as Champions League final host</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218f1f940cf3aa4da632563/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218f1f940cf3aa4da632563/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — Russia was stripped of hosting the Champions League final by UEFA on Friday with St. Petersburg replaced by Paris, and Formula One dropped this season&amp;rsquo;s Russian Grand Prix at Sochi, as the invasion of Ukraine drew punitive measures across the sporting world.
Highlights UEFA stripping Russia of hosting the Champions League final by UEFA on Friday. St. Petersburg replaced by Paris after Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The men&amp;rsquo;s final will still be held on May 28 but now at the 80,000-seat Stade de France.</description></item><item><title>SpaceX loses 40 satellites to geomagnetic storm a day after launch</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203d9c9b2a3e13296d24fc4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203d9c9b2a3e13296d24fc4/</guid><description>A powerful magnetic storm takes out most of a batch of Starlink satellites the day after launch.
Highlights A powerful magnetic storm takes out most of a batch of Starlink satellites the day after launch. The drag was strong enough to stop the satellites ever getting out of that &amp;ldquo;safe mode&amp;rdquo; and back into orbit they needed to reach to be stable. Instead, &amp;ldquo;up to 40&amp;rdquo; will fall back into the Earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere and burn up.</description></item></channel></rss>