<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shut on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shut/</link><description>Recent content in shut on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 20:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Melvin Capital to shut after heavy losses on meme stocks, market slump</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287f599d7a33ec083e28b52/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 20:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287f599d7a33ec083e28b52/</guid><description>Melvin Capital, once one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful hedge funds which then lost billions in the meme stock saga, will shut down after it was hit again by this year&amp;rsquo;s market slump.
Highlights Melvin Capital, once one of Wall Street&amp;rsquo;s most successful hedge funds, will shut down after it was hit again by this year&amp;rsquo;s market slump. Gabe Plotkin, widely regarded as one of the industry&amp;rsquo;s best traders after posting years of double digit returns, told investors that the last 17 months have been &amp;ldquo;an incredibly trying time&amp;rdquo; Plotkin had been trying to turn around the firm after being caught out in early 2021 betting against retail favorite GameStop GME and after being wrong footed again by tumbling markets this year.</description></item><item><title>Christian school leader who taped students’ mouths shut says kids chose punishment over suspension</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256a29fd15e3ab9c5ccb1d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 10:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256a29fd15e3ab9c5ccb1d5/</guid><description>A Louisiana Christian school headmaster, a pastor and former &amp;quot;Survivor&amp;quot; contestant who was arrested last week after he taped students’ mouths shut as a form of discipline, is defending his actions, claiming the pupils were bullying their teacher.
Highlights John Raymond, 60, was arrested Thursday on three counts of cruelty to juveniles. He was arrested last week after he taped students’ mouths shut as a form of discipline. A police investigation found Raymond used a roll of packing tape to tape the mouths of three 13-year-old students shut.</description></item></channel></rss>