<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elementary on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elementary/</link><description>Recent content in elementary on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 22:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/elementary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas school district locked down on reports of shooter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d57b739d23392644d9c5e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 22:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628d57b739d23392644d9c5e/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — An 18-year-old gunman opened fire Tuesday at a Texas elementary&amp;hellip;
Highlights An 18-year-old gunman opened fire Tuesday at a Texas elementary school, killing 14 children, one teacher and injuring others. It was the deadliest shooting at a U.S. grade school since the shocking attack in Sandy Hook, Connecticut, almost a decade ago. The gunman entered Robb Elementary School in Uvalde with a handgun and possibly a rifle, Abbott says.</description></item><item><title>The Satanic Temple sues elementary school as after-school club rejected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62678e4abae8fd0668296396/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62678e4abae8fd0668296396/</guid><description>The Satanic Temple intends to prove the Pennsylvania school&amp;rsquo;s board discriminated against the organization by barring the creation of the &amp;quot;After School Satan&amp;quot; club.
Highlights The Satanic Temple has filed a lawsuit against a Pennsylvania elementary school after the school board voted to deny the establishment of the &amp;ldquo;After School Satan&amp;rdquo; club. Northern Elementary School in York, Pa., is being sued on the grounds of constitutional violation. The temple intends to prove the board discriminated against the organization by barring the creation of the club, despite other organizations being allowed to operate their own programs.</description></item></channel></rss>