<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>twitter on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/twitter/</link><description>Recent content in twitter on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 22:11:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia Said It Has Blocked Facebook</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 22:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</guid><description>Russia’s communications regulator said it blocked Facebook because of “discrimination against Russian media and information resources.&amp;quot; Twitter was blocked shortly after.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator blocks access to Facebook and Twitter. The move comes amid President Vladimir Putin’s ongoing military invasion of Ukraine. Facebook&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Meta, says it will keep its apps, including Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp, available to Russians. Last week, Meta president Nick Clegg said Russia had restricted use of the company&amp;rsquo;s services.</description></item><item><title>Meta and YouTube block Russian state media from monetizing on its platforms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b5c60bfd32b9f3d9e6d9f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 11:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b5c60bfd32b9f3d9e6d9f/</guid><description>YouTube said Saturday that it will temporarily halt the ability of a number of Russian channels, including state-sponsored RT, to monetize their content on the platform.
Highlights YouTube said it will temporarily halt the ability of a number of Russian channels, including state-sponsored RT, to monetize their content on the platform. It will also be &amp;ldquo;significantly limiting&amp;rdquo; recommendations to those channels. The company said the channels are affiliated with recent sanctions, and that it has restricted access to RT and other channels in Ukraine in response to a request from that country&amp;rsquo;s government.</description></item><item><title>Crowd fundraising site says they will defy Canadian court order to stop disbursing funds to convoy protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</guid><description>Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters.
Highlights Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters. The Superior Court of Justice in Ontario granted a restraining order requested by the Government of Ontario against the site. Ontario Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office declined to comment on the site&amp;rsquo;s response to the court order.</description></item><item><title>Twitter 2FA text service was secretly helping governments locate people, obtain call logs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62047801b4ac7139ce498738/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62047801b4ac7139ce498738/</guid><description>The cofounder of a Twitter 2FA text service is reported to have been secretly selling access to its networks to governments, enabling &amp;hellip;
Highlights Twitter says it is cutting ties with Mitto AG, a European company that helped it send sensitive passcodes to its users via text message. Mitto was used by Twitter to send text messages on its behalf, including security codes used for two-factor authentication (2FA) Twitter says that it is “transitioning” away from the company’s services, but appears not to have completely ceased using them as yet.</description></item><item><title>Twitter permanently suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene's personal account</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</guid><description>Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep.
Summary Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene after &amp;ldquo;repeated violations&amp;rdquo; of the Covid-19 misinformation policy, the company said Sunday. &amp;ldquo;We permanently suspended the account you referenced (@mtgreenee) for repeated violations of our COVID-19 misinformation policy,&amp;rdquo; Twitter said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;We’ve been clear that, per our strike system for this policy, we will permanently suspend accounts for repeated violations of the policy.</description></item></channel></rss>