<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>twitter on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/twitter/</link><description>Recent content in twitter on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 17:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maker of Uvalde shooter’s rifle posted image of child with gun before massacre</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629258c016c4e415865b881e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629258c016c4e415865b881e/</guid><description>Gunmaker Daniel Defense posted online an advertising photo of a small child holding one of its AR-15-style rifles just days before one of its firearms was used in the elementary school shooting in Uvalde, Tex.
Highlights Gunmaker Daniel Defense posted the image to Twitter on May 16. The next week, a gunman used a Daniel Defense DDM4 Rifle to kill 19 children and two adults at a school in Texas. The gunmaker had planned to host an exhibitor’s booth at the upcoming National Rifle Association convention, set to begin Friday in Houston.</description></item><item><title>Leader of feces-eating cult arrested after 11 dead bodies discovered during raid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279e73cc3188adf0707426b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 04:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279e73cc3188adf0707426b/</guid><description>Latest Thailand English Online News Leader of feces-eating cult arrested after 11 dead bodies discovered during raid Current Affairs - Thai Enquirer %
Highlights Thai police raid the compound of a suspected cult leader in Chaiyaphum province on Sunday, discovering at least 11 bodies in coffins. The suspected leader of the group has been detained for questioning, but before the arrest many of his followers attempted to stop police from arresting the elderly man during the raid.</description></item><item><title>Twitter accepts Elon Musk's buyout deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62670ea40cfa9a6fe49c8460/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 21:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62670ea40cfa9a6fe49c8460/</guid><description>The announcement ends a weeks-long saga Musk kicked off when he offered to buy the company at $54.20 per share, his &amp;quot;best and final.&amp;quot;
Highlights Twitter&amp;rsquo;s board accepts an offer from billionaire Elon Musk to buy the social media company and take it private. The cash deal at $54.20 per share is valued at around $44 billion. Twitter&amp;rsquo;s stock closed up 5.64% for the day after it was halted for the news.</description></item><item><title>Twitter set to accept ‘best and final offer’ of Elon Musk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266acba63a9d45c947a6449/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266acba63a9d45c947a6449/</guid><description>Twitter Inc is poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, the price the chief executive of Tesla Inc has called his &amp;quot;best and final&amp;quot; offer for the social media company, people familiar with the matter said.
Highlights Twitter poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, people familiar with the matter said. Twitter may announce the $54.20-per-share deal later on Monday once its board has met to recommend the transaction to Twitter shareholders.</description></item><item><title>Twitter bans climate change propaganda ads as deniers target platforms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626569310e2d491eb6406cd7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 15:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626569310e2d491eb6406cd7/</guid><description>Twitter is banning advertisements that promote climate change denial in an effort to curb the reach of groups seeking to downplay the extent of the environmental crisis.
Highlights Twitter will be relying on reports from the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, a unit within the United Nations, to inform its decisions about which advertisements break its rules. Twitter’s Friday announcement is part of a larger trend by social media companies to address criticism from activists that they are doing too little to combat climate change disinformation campaigns.</description></item><item><title>Twitter CEO tells employees company not 'held hostage' by Musk offer -source</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62597d5e3243983fec29462b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 14:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62597d5e3243983fec29462b/</guid><description>Twitter Chief Executive Officer Parag Agrawal sought to reassure employees during an all-hands meeting on Thursday that the company was not being &amp;quot;held hostage&amp;quot; by news of Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s offer to buy the company, a source familiar with the matter told Reuters.
Highlights Twitter Chief Executive Officer Parag Agrawal sought to reassure employees during an all-hands meeting on Thursday that the company was not being &amp;ldquo;held hostage&amp;rdquo; by news of Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s offer to buy Twitter.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk offers to buy Twitter for $54.20 a share, saying it needs to be 'transformed as private company'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258495c129f5f7553cb4782/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 16:19:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258495c129f5f7553cb4782/</guid><description>Elon Musk offered to buy Twitter for $54.20 a share, saying the social media company needs to be transformed privately.
Highlights Elon Musk offers to buy Twitter for $54.20 a share in a filing published Thursday. Musk&amp;rsquo;s offer values Twitter at about $43 billion. Twitter shares were up about 4% Thursday morning after closing at $45.85 a share on Wednesday. Musk first disclosed his 9.2% stake in Twitter on April 4.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk to join Twitter’s board of directors, teases 'significant improvements'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c7998abdc70b658b7d0dc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 17:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c7998abdc70b658b7d0dc/</guid><description>Musk took a 9.2% passive stake in the company.
Highlights Elon Musk named to Twitter&amp;rsquo;s board. The Tesla CEO took a 9.2% passive stake in the company. Twitter CEO tweeted he would push for changes to the product. Jack Dorsey praised the move, saying Musk &amp;ldquo;cares deeply about our world and Twitter&amp;rsquo;s role in it&amp;rdquo; Musk&amp;rsquo;s term is set to expire in 2024, according to a filing with the SEC with 90 days after he was named to the board.</description></item><item><title>Twitter shares soar more than 25% after Elon Musk takes 9% stake in social media company</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b35f824a894ac7aff03f3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b35f824a894ac7aff03f3/</guid><description>Tesla CEO Elon Musk has taken a big stake in the social media company Twitter, a regulatory filing released Monday showed.
Highlights Tesla CEO Elon Musk purchased 73,486,938 shares of Twitter, a regulatory filing shows. The stake is worth $2.89 billion, based on the closing price of the social media company. The purchase comes less than two weeks after Musk criticized the company for what he said was its failure to uphold the tenets of free speech.</description></item><item><title>Russian warship destroyed in occupied port of Berdyansk, says Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c8abcb189988ba8184aad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 15:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c8abcb189988ba8184aad/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s navy says the Orsk, which was used to ferry Russian troops, was hit in Berdyansk.
Highlights Lucy Hockings will be hosting a Your Questions Answered on Friday at 11:30GMT. This will be on World TV and the News Channel and will cover the war in Ukraine. You can get in touch on Twitter using the hashtag BBC Your Questions - and email us at YourQuestions@bbc.co.uk. We&amp;rsquo;ll also take a look at the human consequences of the conflict in Ukraine on Friday night at 1130GMT and on Saturday morning on the News and World TV at 11.</description></item><item><title>Russia Said It Has Blocked Facebook</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 22:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62228e58e6b0535827b03611/</guid><description>Russia’s communications regulator said it blocked Facebook because of “discrimination against Russian media and information resources.&amp;quot; Twitter was blocked shortly after.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator blocks access to Facebook and Twitter. The move comes amid President Vladimir Putin’s ongoing military invasion of Ukraine. Facebook&amp;rsquo;s parent company, Meta, says it will keep its apps, including Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp, available to Russians. Last week, Meta president Nick Clegg said Russia had restricted use of the company&amp;rsquo;s services.</description></item><item><title>Meta and YouTube block Russian state media from monetizing on its platforms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b5c60bfd32b9f3d9e6d9f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 11:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b5c60bfd32b9f3d9e6d9f/</guid><description>YouTube said Saturday that it will temporarily halt the ability of a number of Russian channels, including state-sponsored RT, to monetize their content on the platform.
Highlights YouTube said it will temporarily halt the ability of a number of Russian channels, including state-sponsored RT, to monetize their content on the platform. It will also be &amp;ldquo;significantly limiting&amp;rdquo; recommendations to those channels. The company said the channels are affiliated with recent sanctions, and that it has restricted access to RT and other channels in Ukraine in response to a request from that country&amp;rsquo;s government.</description></item><item><title>Crowd fundraising site says they will defy Canadian court order to stop disbursing funds to convoy protesters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620822412337101b5b984f0d/</guid><description>Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters.
Highlights Online crowd fundraising site GiveSendGo said on Twitter it will not follow a Canadian court order mandating it stop distributing funds to convoy protesters. The Superior Court of Justice in Ontario granted a restraining order requested by the Government of Ontario against the site. Ontario Attorney General&amp;rsquo;s office declined to comment on the site&amp;rsquo;s response to the court order.</description></item><item><title>Twitter 2FA text service was secretly helping governments locate people, obtain call logs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62047801b4ac7139ce498738/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62047801b4ac7139ce498738/</guid><description>The cofounder of a Twitter 2FA text service is reported to have been secretly selling access to its networks to governments, enabling &amp;hellip;
Highlights Twitter says it is cutting ties with Mitto AG, a European company that helped it send sensitive passcodes to its users via text message. Mitto was used by Twitter to send text messages on its behalf, including security codes used for two-factor authentication (2FA) Twitter says that it is “transitioning” away from the company’s services, but appears not to have completely ceased using them as yet.</description></item><item><title>Twitter permanently suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene's personal account</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1e8436b3922c314abdee9/</guid><description>Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep.
Summary Twitter suspended a personal account for Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene after &amp;ldquo;repeated violations&amp;rdquo; of the Covid-19 misinformation policy, the company said Sunday. &amp;ldquo;We permanently suspended the account you referenced (@mtgreenee) for repeated violations of our COVID-19 misinformation policy,&amp;rdquo; Twitter said in a statement. &amp;ldquo;We’ve been clear that, per our strike system for this policy, we will permanently suspend accounts for repeated violations of the policy.</description></item></channel></rss>