<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>online on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/online/</link><description>Recent content in online on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 14:12:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/online/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>West hits Vladimir Putin’s fake news factories with wave of sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62373640f38153d35d847d20/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 14:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62373640f38153d35d847d20/</guid><description>UK and US crack down on websites peddling ‘false and misleading’ reports thought to be backed by Russian intelligence
Highlights Foreign Office has imposed sanctions on 12 key Russian-backed disinformation outlets. The Foreign Office announced last week that sanctions would be imposed on the Internet Research Agency, the notorious Russian-based troll factory. Government investigators claim Russian intelligence supports international news and analysis websites which promote the Kremlin’s view of the Ukraine invasion.</description></item><item><title>IRS will no longer use controversial facial recognition software to verify online accounts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62027a5e2f7c48903e3d523f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 14:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62027a5e2f7c48903e3d523f/</guid><description>The IRS was previously partnering with third-party software provider ID.me to verify online accounts. Amid alarm, the agency is no longer doing so.
Highlights The IRS will no longer require taxpayers to use facial recognition software to authenticate online accounts. The agency previously announced that starting this summer, taxpayers would have had to use ID.me. The move was met with alarm from privacy experts, who questioned the need for the government to partner with an outside firm to collect biometric data.</description></item><item><title>Taking a step back: US colleges returning to online classes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1073c23d967a872a377ee/</guid><description>With COVID-19 cases surging just as students are about to return from winter break, dozens of U.S. colleges are moving classes online again for at least the first week or so of the semester — and some warn it could stretch longer if the wave of infection doesn’t subside soon.
Summary The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online. The University of Chicago is delaying its new term and holding the first two weeks online.</description></item></channel></rss>