<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>21 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/21/</link><description>Recent content in 21 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:22:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/21/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Biden to devote $2.1 bln of new funds to strengthen US food supply chain.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298730ace6e941a02e6aa8b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 08:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298730ace6e941a02e6aa8b/</guid><description>The Biden Administration on Wednesday will announce $2.1 billion in new funding to bolster food supply chains, including initiatives to expand small- and
Highlights The Biden Administration on Wednesday will announce $2.1 billion in new funding to bolster food supply chains. The funds will also be used to finance new infrastructure such as cold storage facilities and to assist farmers shifting to organic production. Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack plans to focus on the importance of moving US food supplies away from dominance by a few highly concentrated businesses.</description></item><item><title>Man, 21, arrested a week after 3 killed at Georgia gun range</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bb0be25355fae30fb333c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 06:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bb0be25355fae30fb333c/</guid><description>GRANTVILLE, Ga. (AP) — A 21-year-old man has been arrested in connection with a fatal armed robbery at a Georgia gun range that left three members of a family dead last week. Jacob Christian Muse, of College Park, is charged with three counts of malice murder, the Georgia Bureau of Investigation said in a news release Friday.
Highlights Jacob Christian Muse, of College Park, is charged with three counts of malice murder.</description></item></channel></rss>