<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>museum on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/museum/</link><description>Recent content in museum on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 23:14:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/museum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How a priceless Roman bust ended up in a Texas thrift store</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276fd26a0ceff809d8647a5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 23:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276fd26a0ceff809d8647a5/</guid><description>Bought for just $35 by a sharp-eyed customer, the ancient artefact is now on display in a museum.
Highlights San Antonio Museum of Art bought for just $35 by sharp-eyed customer. Ancient artefact is now on display in a museum in San Antonio, Texas. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure how it&amp;rsquo;s possible to put a meaningful monetary value on something that has such an important history, but on the other hand could never, ever be sold,&amp;rdquo; said Lynley McAlpine from the San Antonio museum of Art.</description></item><item><title>The $1m challenge: ‘If the Turin Shroud is a forgery, show how it was done’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d477ba3cb67797f7e6416/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 11:12:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d477ba3cb67797f7e6416/</guid><description>Expert on revered relic calls on British Museum to back up the results of its disputed carbon dating tests
Highlights David Rolfe&amp;rsquo;s new film, Who Can He Be? debuts the Shroud of Turin, in which Christ&amp;rsquo;s body was wrapped when he supposedly rose from the dead. New discoveries in the past few years have again opened the question of its authenticity. The film-maker has issued a challenge worth $1m to the British Museum to prove it&amp;rsquo;s not a forgery.</description></item><item><title>New York's Museum of Modern Art evacuated after two people were stabbed inside, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e34cf13be44e4888bd493/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 18:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e34cf13be44e4888bd493/</guid><description>Patrons at New York City&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art were evacuated Saturday afternoon after two employees were stabbed inside the iconic establishment by a man who was involved in two incidents of disorderly conduct at the museum in recent days, police said.
Highlights Patrons at New York City&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art were evacuated Saturday afternoon. Two employees were stabbed in the back, collar bone and back of the neck. The NYPD is still searching for the suspect, who was identified in a news release early Sunday as 60-year-old Gary Cabana.</description></item></channel></rss>