<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>khan on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/khan/</link><description>Recent content in khan on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 02:31:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/khan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Imran Khan ousted as Pakistan's PM after key vote</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625241721c3360368c4b9007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 02:31:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625241721c3360368c4b9007/</guid><description>The former cricket star loses a no-confidence vote 13 hours after his party tried to delay it.
Highlights Mr Khan has repeatedly said that Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s opposition parties are working with foreign powers. He also claims that he is the target of a US-led conspiracy to remove him because of his refusal to stand with Washington on issues against Russia and China. The former cricket star loses a no-confidence vote 13 hours after his party tried to delay it.</description></item><item><title>Suicide bombing at Pakistan mosque kills at least 56, injures nearly 200</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62229cf23a51adcc5be8e478/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 23:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62229cf23a51adcc5be8e478/</guid><description>A suicide bomber struck inside a Shia Muslim mosque in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s northwestern city of Peshawar during Friday prayers, killing at least 56 worshippers and wounding 194 people, hospital officials said.
Highlights A suicide bomber strikes inside a Shia Muslim mosque in Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s northwestern city of Peshawar during Friday prayers, killing at least 56 worshippers and wounding 194 people. No militant group immediately claimed responsibility for the attack. Both the Islamic State group and the Pakistani Taliban — a militant group separate from the Taliban in Afghanistan — have carried out similar attacks in the past in the area.</description></item></channel></rss>