<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officer/</link><description>Recent content in officer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 02:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop for speeding and asked to see the officer's supervisor, video footage shows.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</guid><description>Video footage shows a Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who began recording his traffic stop, saying he was feeling unsafe
Highlights A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop, video footage shows. Delane Gordon began recording when the March 10 stop started to make him feel unsafe, attorney says. The man wound up facing additional charges of resisting arrest and obstruction of justice.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Virginia police officer and West Virginia lawmaker plead guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</guid><description>Jacob Fracker, who has agreed to cooperate with federal prosecutors, was fired from his job as a police officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia while Derrick Evans resigned from the West Virginia state legislature before the session started.
Highlights Jacob Fracker pleads guilty to conspiring to obstruct an official proceeding, the joint session of Congress that convened on January 6, 2021, to certify President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s electoral victory. A former West Virginia state lawmaker pleaded guilty Friday to a civil disorder charge, punishable by up to five years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas officer accused of robbing casino with department-issued gun</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d512f7eeb81165eefd88d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 02:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d512f7eeb81165eefd88d/</guid><description>An off-duty Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Officer accused of robbing a casino with his department-issued gun and suspected in two other robberies has been charged with federal crimes, officials announced Thursday.
Highlights Caleb Rogers, 33, has been charged with interference with commerce by robbery and brandishing a firearm during a crime of violence. He was arrested Feb. 27 after reportedly robbing the Rio All-Suite Hotel &amp;amp; Casino at gunpoint and attempting to abscond with $78,898.</description></item><item><title>Man was shot by police after officer mistook his gun for a Taser, police in Florida say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 03:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</guid><description>A police officer in Florida shot a man after mistaking his gun for a Taser, an initial review of the case suggests, police said in a statement.
Highlights Michael Ortiz is paralyzed and requires round-the-clock care, the complaint alleges. The Hollywood Police Department says the officer mistakenly fired a gun instead of a Taser. Ortiz was naked and handcuffed when police shot him in the back, his attorney says. Ortiz &amp;ldquo;was having a mental health crisis&amp;rdquo; on the day of the shooting after losing his dog, the lawyer says.</description></item><item><title>Protesters for Amir Locke, a Black man killed by Minneapolis police, demand police chief's resignation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 07:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</guid><description>A caravan of vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke, the 22-year old Black man who was fatally shot by Minneapolis police as officers served a no-knock search warrant.
Highlights A caravan of about 50 vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke. The caravan was organized by the Racial Justice Network and other police accountability groups. Some in the caravan then gathered in a neighborhood outside what’s believed to be the home of interim Police Chief Amelia Huffman.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: Police Officer Kills Dog in Miami-Dade After Barking Complaint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</guid><description>A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing him while responding to&amp;hellip;
Summary A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing the 8-month-old. The incident happened in unincorporated Miami-Dade near Miami Gardens on Wednesday, January 12 around 7 p.m. as a police officer was responding to a call regarding dogs barking.</description></item><item><title>Police probe clears Dayton, Ohio, officers who pulled paraplegic driver out of car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1741adfcb507831a3dba7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1741adfcb507831a3dba7/</guid><description>A Dayton, Ohio, police internal investigation of a traffic stop where officers pulled a paraplegic driver out of a car by his hair and arms cleared the officers of the most serious allegations against them.
Summary (CNN) A Dayton, Ohio, police internal investigation of a traffic stop where officers pulled a paraplegic driver out of a car by his hair and arms cleared the officers of the most serious allegations against them.</description></item></channel></rss>