<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officer on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officer/</link><description>Recent content in officer on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 13:39:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New federal lawsuits target ex-cop who killed George Floyd</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298bd524032c4cdff575c96/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 13:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298bd524032c4cdff575c96/</guid><description>Two Minnesotans have filed federal civil rights lawsuits against the city of Minneapolis and former Officer Derek Chauvin
Highlights Two Minnesotans have filed federal civil rights lawsuits against Minneapolis and former Officer Derek Chauvin. John Pope Jr. and Zoya Code are Black and Chauvin is white. They allege they were traumatized when Chauvin used his “signature move” of kneeling on their necks. Both lawsuits seek unspecified damages and name other officers involved.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde police chief who delayed officer response to shooting to join City Council</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291d9810cc9a70796c069ee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 08:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291d9810cc9a70796c069ee/</guid><description>The police chief who reportedly made the call not to immediately send officers into Robb Elementary School to confront a gunman was elected to Uvalde&amp;rsquo;s City Cou
Highlights Peter Arredondo, the chief of police for the Uvalde Consolidated Independent School District, stopped at least 19 officers from breaking into the school as the gunman opened fire for at least an hour. He believed that the shooter had barricaded himself and that the children were not under an active threat, Texas Department of Public Safety director Steven McCraw said Friday.</description></item><item><title>New York Supreme Court ruling reinstates law banning police officers from using chokeholds during arrests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628786636aa1ae9d6d363aba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628786636aa1ae9d6d363aba/</guid><description>A law banning New York law enforcement from using either a chokehold or a move that compresses someone&amp;rsquo;s diaphragm during an arrest has been reinstated after a state Supreme Court appeals court ruling on Thursday.
Highlights The law bans police from using a move that compresses someone&amp;rsquo;s diaphragm during an arrest. The law was passed by the city council in the aftermath of the death of Eric Garner. A state Supreme Court ruling reversed a June 2021 decision by the court that deemed the law &amp;ldquo;unnecessarily vague&amp;rdquo; and the ban in its entirety.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: NJ police chief was passed out, pants down, on roadway in DWI arrest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281bdf69651b43e5ed45b0b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 02:59:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281bdf69651b43e5ed45b0b/</guid><description>Body cam footage from the April encounter involving Bordentown Police Chief Brian Pesce in Hamilton Township shows that he was sleeping on the street behind his pickup truck when officers arrived.
Highlights Police Chief Brian Pesce was arrested April 22 in Hamilton Township, Mercer County. He was charged with DWI, leaving the scene of an accident involving property damage, failing to report an accident, reckless driving and careless driving. Pesce has been on restricted duty until further notice pending investigation results as he faces charges for five traffic offenses.</description></item><item><title>Former Philadelphia police officer who fatally shot 12-year-old in back charged with murder, DA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62709c1bd1fc2a1a3408a61e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62709c1bd1fc2a1a3408a61e/</guid><description>A former Philadelphia police officer who fatally shot a 12-year-old boy in the back in March has been charged with first-degree murder, District Attorney Larry Krasner announced Monday, saying the boy was unarmed and on the ground when the officer fired.
Highlights Edsaul Mendoza, 26, was one of four plainclothes officers in an unmarked car when he fatally shot a 12-year-old boy in the back in March. The boy was unarmed and on the ground when the officer fired, the DA says.</description></item><item><title>Family wants world to see footage of Grand Rapids fatal police shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253d721dbaa5507da6d5a5a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253d721dbaa5507da6d5a5a/</guid><description>A Grand Rapids police officer shot and killed Patrick Lyoya, 26, during a traffic stop earlier this week. Hundreds of people joined the Lyoya family urging police to release bodycam and dashcam footage of the shooting. The officer,
Highlights Hundreds of people join the Lyoya family urging police to release bodycam and dashcam footage. Patrick Lyoya, 26, was shot and killed by a Grand Rapids police officer during a traffic stop earlier this week.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky court dismisses $2.25M police officer misconduct verdict - Bluegrass Live</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c42e07e580b045a2f1b9e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 13:24:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c42e07e580b045a2f1b9e/</guid><description>Tiffany Washington was working in the university library when she was arrested in 2007 in a robbery. She didn&amp;rsquo;t file her malicious prosecution suit until February 2010, nearly two years after the charges against her were dropped. Washington&amp;rsquo;s case was one of
Highlights Tiffany Washington was arrested in 2007 in a robbery at the University of Louisville. She didn&amp;rsquo;t file her malicious prosecution suit until February 2010, nearly two years after the charges against her were dropped.</description></item><item><title>Police Officer 'masturbated in an open park in broad daylight'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62464e8b4e9c8a887158379a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 01:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62464e8b4e9c8a887158379a/</guid><description>A serving PCSO was filmed performing a sex act in a London park in the middle of the day. Video shows him performing the act, being confronted by an astonished onlooker. His unique &amp;lsquo;badge number&amp;rsquo; was photographed to make
Highlights A serving PCSO has been arrested on suspicion of &amp;lsquo;outraging public decency&amp;rsquo; He was recorded performing a sex act on himself in a London park in the middle of the day.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive: Widow of D.C. police officer Jeff Smith, who died by suicide, says battling rioters on Jan. 6 "changed him"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624570f41a95b3e130285bbd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 09:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624570f41a95b3e130285bbd/</guid><description>Bodycam footage obtained by CBS News shows Jeff Smith was struck in the head with a metal pole.
Highlights Jeff Smith, a 12-year veteran of the Metropolitan Police Department, died by suicide after responding to rioting on Jan. 6, 2021. His widow, Erin Smith, is pressing Congress to pass legislation recognizing the trauma suffered by law enforcement officers who take their own lives. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m fighting for everyone else who has gone through this as well as my husband,&amp;rdquo; Erin Smith said.</description></item><item><title>A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop for speeding and asked to see the officer's supervisor, video footage shows.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237e23654274f2455044f6f/</guid><description>Video footage shows a Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who began recording his traffic stop, saying he was feeling unsafe
Highlights A Tennessee police officer fired his stun gun at a food delivery man who had begun recording his traffic stop, video footage shows. Delane Gordon began recording when the March 10 stop started to make him feel unsafe, attorney says. The man wound up facing additional charges of resisting arrest and obstruction of justice.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Virginia police officer and West Virginia lawmaker plead guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</guid><description>Jacob Fracker, who has agreed to cooperate with federal prosecutors, was fired from his job as a police officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia while Derrick Evans resigned from the West Virginia state legislature before the session started.
Highlights Jacob Fracker pleads guilty to conspiring to obstruct an official proceeding, the joint session of Congress that convened on January 6, 2021, to certify President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s electoral victory. A former West Virginia state lawmaker pleaded guilty Friday to a civil disorder charge, punishable by up to five years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas officer accused of robbing casino with department-issued gun</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d512f7eeb81165eefd88d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 02:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622d512f7eeb81165eefd88d/</guid><description>An off-duty Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Officer accused of robbing a casino with his department-issued gun and suspected in two other robberies has been charged with federal crimes, officials announced Thursday.
Highlights Caleb Rogers, 33, has been charged with interference with commerce by robbery and brandishing a firearm during a crime of violence. He was arrested Feb. 27 after reportedly robbing the Rio All-Suite Hotel &amp;amp; Casino at gunpoint and attempting to abscond with $78,898.</description></item><item><title>Man was shot by police after officer mistook his gun for a Taser, police in Florida say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 03:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205d400b6969d0ac1ba5909/</guid><description>A police officer in Florida shot a man after mistaking his gun for a Taser, an initial review of the case suggests, police said in a statement.
Highlights Michael Ortiz is paralyzed and requires round-the-clock care, the complaint alleges. The Hollywood Police Department says the officer mistakenly fired a gun instead of a Taser. Ortiz was naked and handcuffed when police shot him in the back, his attorney says. Ortiz &amp;ldquo;was having a mental health crisis&amp;rdquo; on the day of the shooting after losing his dog, the lawyer says.</description></item><item><title>Protesters for Amir Locke, a Black man killed by Minneapolis police, demand police chief's resignation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 07:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</guid><description>A caravan of vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke, the 22-year old Black man who was fatally shot by Minneapolis police as officers served a no-knock search warrant.
Highlights A caravan of about 50 vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke. The caravan was organized by the Racial Justice Network and other police accountability groups. Some in the caravan then gathered in a neighborhood outside what’s believed to be the home of interim Police Chief Amelia Huffman.</description></item><item><title>VIDEO: Police Officer Kills Dog in Miami-Dade After Barking Complaint</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e44f486378b14158e5f837/</guid><description>A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing him while responding to&amp;hellip;
Summary A home surveillance camera captured a Miami-Dade police officer discharging his weapon multiple times on an American Bully dog, killing the 8-month-old. The incident happened in unincorporated Miami-Dade near Miami Gardens on Wednesday, January 12 around 7 p.m. as a police officer was responding to a call regarding dogs barking.</description></item><item><title>Police probe clears Dayton, Ohio, officers who pulled paraplegic driver out of car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1741adfcb507831a3dba7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1741adfcb507831a3dba7/</guid><description>A Dayton, Ohio, police internal investigation of a traffic stop where officers pulled a paraplegic driver out of a car by his hair and arms cleared the officers of the most serious allegations against them.
Summary (CNN) A Dayton, Ohio, police internal investigation of a traffic stop where officers pulled a paraplegic driver out of a car by his hair and arms cleared the officers of the most serious allegations against them.</description></item></channel></rss>