<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russias on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russias/</link><description>Recent content in russias on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russias/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ukraine war: Dozens feared dead after bomb hits school</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627808d1c5b3e534085a9c33/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627808d1c5b3e534085a9c33/</guid><description>A Ukrainian official says 60 people may be dead after an air strike on a village school in Luhansk.
Highlights UN has recorded at least 2,345 civilian deaths and 2,919 injured in Ukraine. Thousands of combatants are also believed to have been killed or injured on both sides. At least 60 people may be dead after an air strike on a village school in Luhansk, Ukraine, an official says. More than 2,000 people have died since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion began on 24 February, the UN said last month.</description></item><item><title>Lavrov claims Zelensky has Jewish blood 'just like Hitler'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f93924659d0fc6cf9f535/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f93924659d0fc6cf9f535/</guid><description>The Russian Foreign Minister attacked the President of Ukraine in an interview in Italy and reiterated the claims that his country has elements of Nazism.
Highlights Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov attacked Ukraine and its president Volodymyr Zelensky in an interview in Italy. Claimed that &amp;ldquo;the fact that he is a Jew does not negate the Nazi elements in his country&amp;rdquo; Lavrov also said that the upcoming anniversary of Russia&amp;rsquo;s liberation at the end of World War II will have no bearing on Moscow&amp;rsquo;s military operations in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia warned the US about weapons shipments to Ukraine. Military analyst calls it a bluff</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bbe08bd5a6a0deb6b9c3b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 07:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bbe08bd5a6a0deb6b9c3b/</guid><description>Ret. Lt. Gen. Mark Hertling discusses Russian President Putin being forced to pivot his military strategy in Ukraine due to varying terrain, and how his forces lack the adaptability to make drastic changes that may be necessary.
Highlights Ret. Gen. Mark Hertling discusses Russian President Putin being forced to pivot his military strategy in Ukraine. Hertling says Putin&amp;rsquo;s forces lack the adaptability to make drastic changes that may be necessary. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Russia warns of nuclear deployment if Sweden and Finland join NATO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62589cdc4cd9b642eb502347/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 22:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62589cdc4cd9b642eb502347/</guid><description>One of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s closest allies warned NATO on Thursday that if Sweden and Finland joined the U.S.-led military alliance then Russia would deploy nuclear weapons and hypersonic missiles in a European exclave.
Highlights Finland and Sweden are considering joining the NATO alliance. If Sweden and Finland join the U.S.-led military alliance then Russia would deploy nuclear weapons and hypersonic missiles in a European exclave. Russia has the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest arsenal of nuclear warheads and along with China and the United States is one of the global leaders in hypersonics missile technology.</description></item><item><title>China's Sinopec pauses Russia projects, Beijing wary of sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240e186a4cea0c0dd577a30/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 22:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240e186a4cea0c0dd577a30/</guid><description>China&amp;rsquo;s state-run Sinopec Group has suspended talks for a major petrochemical investment and a gas marketing venture in Russia, sources told Reuters, heeding a government call for caution as sanctions mount over the invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights China&amp;rsquo;s state-run Sinopec Group has suspended talks for a major petrochemical investment and a gas marketing venture in Russia. The move highlights the risks, even to Russia&amp;rsquo;s most important diplomatic partner, of unexpectedly heavy Western-led sanctions.</description></item><item><title>Oil 'emergency': Work from home and drive slower, IEA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623503ffe95f1f4b6f7b18e8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 22:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623503ffe95f1f4b6f7b18e8/</guid><description>Governments around the world must consider drastic steps to slash oil demand in the face of an emerging global energy crisis caused by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine, the International Energy Agency warned on Friday.
Highlights Governments around the world must consider drastic steps to slash oil demand in the face of an emerging global energy crisis caused by Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The energy watchdog detailed a 10-point emergency plan that includes reducing speed limits on highways by at least 6 miles per hour, working from home up to three days a week where possible and car-free Sundays in cities.</description></item><item><title>U.S. estimates 2,000 to 4,000 Russian troops killed in Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62289b807562b419b4dd1c48/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62289b807562b419b4dd1c48/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I think Putin&amp;rsquo;s assumptions have turned out to be profoundly flawed.&amp;quot;
Highlights Between 2,000 and 4,000 Russian troops have been killed over the course of Putin&amp;rsquo;s 12-day war in Ukraine, U.S. intelligence officials say. Putin may turn to more brutal tactics in the coming days and weeks, intelligence officials testify. CIA Director Bill Burns says Putin is likely to &amp;ldquo;double down&amp;rdquo; and may escalate his assault on heavily populated civilian areas.</description></item><item><title>CNN to stop broadcasting in Russia after new law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222e3d7db18f478c954d5c2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222e3d7db18f478c954d5c2/</guid><description>CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia, the news channel said on Friday after the introduction of a new law there that could jail anyone intentionally spreading &amp;quot;fake&amp;quot; news.
Highlights Russia has introduced a new law that could jail anyone for spreading &amp;ldquo;fake&amp;rdquo; news. The law was passed by Russian lawmakers in the wake of the Ukraine crisis. CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia while the law is in place. The U.</description></item><item><title>Turn down heating by 1C to reduce need for Russian imports, Europeans told</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221d7f8f9305282b638de50/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221d7f8f9305282b638de50/</guid><description>IEA says reducing temperature could help wean consumers off fuel that Russia is using as a weapon in Ukraine war
Highlights The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s plan would reduce Russian gas imports by about a third before next winter. Red tape should be cut to bring forward the construction of more wind and solar power stations, the IEA said. The EU relies on Russia for about 40% of its gas consumption. The UK government is also understood to be urgently examining its exposure to gas market turbulence caused by Russia’s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>The teenager that tracked Elon Musk's jet is now tracking Russian oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</guid><description>Jack Sweeney, a Florida teen who tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online has a new aviation-themed target: Russian oligarchs and billionaires.
Highlights Jack Sweeney, 19, tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online. He recently launched two new automated Twitter handles — @RUOligarchJets and @Putinjet — following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The two profiles have amassed nearly 300,000 followers combined and provide nearly live updates of the private jets&amp;rsquo; movements. Russia&amp;rsquo;s oligarchs face economic chaos at home and punishment by the West after President Vladimir Putin ordered his troops into Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>UK announces first wave of sanctions against Belarus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</guid><description>Senior military figures targeted for role in joining and facilitating Russian invasion of Ukraine
Highlights Belarusian chief of the general staff, Maj Gen Victor Gulevich, and three other deputy defence ministers will all face sanctions, along with two military enterprises. Belarus has been used as a base for Russian soldiers to pour into Ukraine. US Treasury this week designated two large state-owned banks in Belarus, Belinvestbank and Dabrabyt, as subject to sanctions.</description></item><item><title>Russia calls in Canadian envoy, complains over protests outside its embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</guid><description>Russia threatened Canada on Monday with retaliation if it failed to ensure the safety of its diplomats and complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates.
Highlights Russia says it has called in Canada&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to Moscow to lodge a formal protest. Russia has complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates. Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign ministry says it had called in the ambassador to Russia&amp;rsquo;s embassy in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>Biden says U.S. will sanction Russian financial firms, sovereign debt and individuals after Ukraine incursion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215a65fd2425c0d1f3fe962/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215a65fd2425c0d1f3fe962/</guid><description>President Joe Biden said Tuesday that Russia has begun &amp;quot;an invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine, and he announced sweeping sanctions on the Russian bank VEB.
Highlights President Joe Biden says Russia has begun &amp;ldquo;an invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine. Biden also announced sweeping sanctions on the major Russian bank VEB and its military bank, as well as on the country&amp;rsquo;s sovereign debt. Biden: &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t need blood unless you plan on starting a war&amp;rdquo; The prospect of a war involving Russia, the largest supplier of gas and oil to Europe, has rattled markets and fueled fears of higher oil prices.</description></item><item><title>Russian ships, tanks and troops on the move to Ukraine as peace talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</guid><description>With negotiations deadlocked, Moscow is continuing to build up its military forces for a possible invasion
Summary The US president, Joe Biden, last week said that Putin himself may not know what he plans to do. The Russian foreign minister, Sergei Lavrov, called talks with US secretary of state Antony Blinken “frank and substantive”. The decision to fast-track arms to Ukraine reflects an understanding that Russia could launch an attack at any moment.</description></item><item><title>Russia’s Excess Death Toll Hits 930K: "Russia recorded more than 115,000 excess deaths during November 2021 according to official statistics published Thursday — a new record high since the start of the pandemic."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf372b9501f4d9450c8d5d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf372b9501f4d9450c8d5d/</guid><description>Country recorded another record month of fatalities in November, with an 82% rise in deaths from all causes.
Summary Russia recorded more than 115,000 excess deaths during November 2021 according to official statistics published Thursday — a new record high since the start of the pandemic. The number takes Russia’s overall excess death count since the start of the pandemic to 929,000, according to The Moscow Times’ analysis. The record figure for November — equivalent to around 4,000 more fatalities a day than was recorded in the same month before the coronavirus outbreak — comes as the country faced a punishing fourth wave of the virus and nationwide vaccination rates remained low.</description></item></channel></rss>