<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>russias on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russias/</link><description>Recent content in russias on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:18:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/russias/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The teenager that tracked Elon Musk's jet is now tracking Russian oligarchs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 16:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220ea247d5f774c0bb8e24e/</guid><description>Jack Sweeney, a Florida teen who tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online has a new aviation-themed target: Russian oligarchs and billionaires.
Highlights Jack Sweeney, 19, tracks Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s private jet online. He recently launched two new automated Twitter handles — @RUOligarchJets and @Putinjet — following Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. The two profiles have amassed nearly 300,000 followers combined and provide nearly live updates of the private jets&amp;rsquo; movements. Russia&amp;rsquo;s oligarchs face economic chaos at home and punishment by the West after President Vladimir Putin ordered his troops into Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>UK announces first wave of sanctions against Belarus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</guid><description>Senior military figures targeted for role in joining and facilitating Russian invasion of Ukraine
Highlights Belarusian chief of the general staff, Maj Gen Victor Gulevich, and three other deputy defence ministers will all face sanctions, along with two military enterprises. Belarus has been used as a base for Russian soldiers to pour into Ukraine. US Treasury this week designated two large state-owned banks in Belarus, Belinvestbank and Dabrabyt, as subject to sanctions.</description></item><item><title>Russia calls in Canadian envoy, complains over protests outside its embassy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 05:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dab217da6d7300217fceb/</guid><description>Russia threatened Canada on Monday with retaliation if it failed to ensure the safety of its diplomats and complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates.
Highlights Russia says it has called in Canada&amp;rsquo;s ambassador to Moscow to lodge a formal protest. Russia has complained over what it said were hostile protests outside its embassy in Ottawa and two other consulates.</description></item><item><title>Biden says U.S. will sanction Russian financial firms, sovereign debt and individuals after Ukraine incursion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215a65fd2425c0d1f3fe962/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215a65fd2425c0d1f3fe962/</guid><description>President Joe Biden said Tuesday that Russia has begun &amp;quot;an invasion&amp;quot; of Ukraine, and he announced sweeping sanctions on the Russian bank VEB.
Highlights President Joe Biden says Russia has begun &amp;ldquo;an invasion&amp;rdquo; of Ukraine. Biden also announced sweeping sanctions on the major Russian bank VEB and its military bank, as well as on the country&amp;rsquo;s sovereign debt. Biden: &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t need blood unless you plan on starting a war&amp;rdquo; The prospect of a war involving Russia, the largest supplier of gas and oil to Europe, has rattled markets and fueled fears of higher oil prices.</description></item><item><title>Russian ships, tanks and troops on the move to Ukraine as peace talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</guid><description>With negotiations deadlocked, Moscow is continuing to build up its military forces for a possible invasion
Summary The US president, Joe Biden, last week said that Putin himself may not know what he plans to do. The Russian foreign minister, Sergei Lavrov, called talks with US secretary of state Antony Blinken “frank and substantive”. The decision to fast-track arms to Ukraine reflects an understanding that Russia could launch an attack at any moment.</description></item><item><title>Russia’s Excess Death Toll Hits 930K: "Russia recorded more than 115,000 excess deaths during November 2021 according to official statistics published Thursday — a new record high since the start of the pandemic."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf372b9501f4d9450c8d5d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf372b9501f4d9450c8d5d/</guid><description>Country recorded another record month of fatalities in November, with an 82% rise in deaths from all causes.
Summary Russia recorded more than 115,000 excess deaths during November 2021 according to official statistics published Thursday — a new record high since the start of the pandemic. The number takes Russia’s overall excess death count since the start of the pandemic to 929,000, according to The Moscow Times’ analysis. The record figure for November — equivalent to around 4,000 more fatalities a day than was recorded in the same month before the coronavirus outbreak — comes as the country faced a punishing fourth wave of the virus and nationwide vaccination rates remained low.</description></item></channel></rss>