<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mississippi on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mississippi/</link><description>Recent content in mississippi on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 15:13:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mississippi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Family of Emmett Till want woman who made false accusation to be charged with murder for 1955 lynching</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cb86b831a55fb0c7b9e7d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cb86b831a55fb0c7b9e7d/</guid><description>Family members of Emmett Till are seeking justice for his 1955 death that helped launch the civil rights movement.
Highlights Family of Emmett Till want woman who made false accusation to be charged with murder. Carolyn Bryant Donham is the only living accomplice in the murder of Till, they said. Donham&amp;rsquo;s false accusations led to the 14-year-old&amp;rsquo;s kidnapping and lynching in the Delta region. The U.S. Department of Justice opened investigations into Till&amp;rsquo;s murder in 2004 and 2018; no new charges were announced in December.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi ambulance providers fear a system collapse is near</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdf96f46869d129e1a70bc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 04:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdf96f46869d129e1a70bc/</guid><description>Mississippi’s ambulance system is falling apart, pushing more and more workers from a job that was a hard sell even before the pandemic.
Highlights Mississippi&amp;rsquo;s ambulance system is falling apart, pushing more and more workers from a job that was a hard sell even before the pandemic. Ambulance companies say they have given up on job postings because no one is applying, making it harder to quantify how large the holes are statewide.</description></item></channel></rss>