<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>protect on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/protect/</link><description>Recent content in protect on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/protect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EPA moves to give states, tribes more power to protect water</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299b37f48cdab34b624630f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299b37f48cdab34b624630f/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Thursday proposed undoing a Trump-era rule that limited the power of states and Native American tribes to block energy projects like natural gas pipelines based on their potential to pollute rivers and streams.
Highlights The Biden administration on Thursday, June 2, 2022, proposed undoing a Trump-era rule that limited the power of states and Native American tribes to block energy projects like natural gas pipelines based on their potential to pollute rivers and streams.</description></item><item><title>Pfizer says 3 COVID shots protect children under 5</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c06400c1074f3a125a309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 22:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c06400c1074f3a125a309/</guid><description>Three doses of Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine offer strong protection for children younger than 5, the company announced Monday. It&amp;rsquo;s a step toward letting the littlest kids get vaccinated.
Highlights Three doses of Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine offer strong protection for children younger than 5, the company announced Monday, May 23, 2022. Pfizer plans to give the data to U.S. regulators later this week in a step toward letting the littlest kids get the shots.</description></item><item><title>Protect the body: Ukraine volunteers craft armor, camouflage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62788406e4a8e2a72cb4dfc6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 03:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62788406e4a8e2a72cb4dfc6/</guid><description>ZAPORIZHZHIA, Ukraine (AP) — Sparks fly as a circular saw slices into metal, while welders nearby work feverishly to the sound of blaring heavy metal. Upstairs, sewing machines clatter as women mark patterns on cloth being shaped into bulletproof vests.
Highlights An old industrial complex in the southeastern Ukrainian riverside city of Zaporizhzhia has become a hive of activity for volunteers producing everything from body armor to camouflage nets. The operation relies entirely on volunteers, who now number more than 400 and come from all walks of life.</description></item><item><title>This Texas mom says she's moving her family to California to protect her transgender daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bcc9d691bb37a9156666c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 19:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621bcc9d691bb37a9156666c/</guid><description>A Texas mom is doing whatever it takes to keep her transgender child safe &amp;ndash; even if that requires picking up their lives, leaving family and friends behind and moving hundreds of miles west.
Highlights Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton declared that gender-affirming surgical procedures in children and prescribing drugs that affect puberty are to be considered &amp;ldquo;child abuse&amp;rdquo; Five Texas District Attorneys issued a joint statement on Thursday calling the directives from the governor and attorney general cruel, life-threatening and un-American.</description></item></channel></rss>