<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>world on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/world/</link><description>Recent content in world on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:15:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>China orders 51 million into lockdown as COVID surges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f5bdbc60c9c0fb7c9e78f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 15:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f5bdbc60c9c0fb7c9e78f/</guid><description>China is placing more than 51 million people into lockdown as a new COVID wave hits three provinces.
Highlights China facing its worst COVID crisis since early 2020, when the world first witnessed an entire population locked down to contain the coronavirus in Wuhan and its surrounding province. The epicenter of the omicron variant outbreak is the Northeastern Jilin province, where 895 cases were recorded, but there are also outbreaks and containment measures in place Shanghai, the financial powerhouse, and Shenzhen, the southern tech hub.</description></item><item><title>World food prices jumped toward a record last month | Food News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd0937a0f9f1b4e05eae51/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd0937a0f9f1b4e05eae51/</guid><description>The United Nations’ index of prices rose 1.1 percent in January, pushed up by more pricey vegetable oils and dairy.
Highlights The United Nations’ index of prices rose 1.1% in January. The gauge is edging closer to 2011’s all-time high. The latest leg higher in the food index could further stretch household budgets. The poorest “segments in the population will feel the pinch the most,” a UN official says. Sugar marked the only commodity that eased during the month, while costs for meat, grain, dairy and vegetable oils rose.</description></item><item><title>Over 100 millionaires call for higher taxes worldwide: 'Tax us now'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9088c247558d98d634f4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9088c247558d98d634f4e/</guid><description>A group of ultrawealthy people are asking governments around the world to make them pay more in taxes in order to help close a growing wealth gap.
Summary IRS TAX-FILING SEASON TO KICK OFF ON JAN. 24&amp;quot;As millionaires, we know that the current tax system is not fair,&amp;quot; they wrote. They argued the bedrock of a strong democracy is a fair tax system that bridges the gap between everyday people and the ultrawealthy.</description></item><item><title>Indiana state senator apologizes for saying educators need to be impartial when teaching about racism and Nazism</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de1a3f8eee9986ea4169eb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de1a3f8eee9986ea4169eb/</guid><description>An Indiana lawmaker is apologizing for saying teachers should exercise impartiality when teaching about Nazism or fascism.
Summary (CNN) An Indiana lawmaker is apologizing for saying teachers should exercise impartiality when teaching about Nazism or fascism. His remarks came after a concerned history teacher said he was teaching Nazism in his history class, and that when teaching the subject he does not remain neutral. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re learning about the rise of fascism and the rise of Nazism right now and I&amp;rsquo;m just not neutral on the political ideology of fascism.</description></item><item><title>Snow leopard dies at Illinois zoo after contracting Covid-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 03:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da4fdbafc85ad7da210234/</guid><description>A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois.
Summary (CNN) A snow leopard has died after contracting Covid-19 at Miller Park Zoo in Bloomington, Illinois. before death, according to a Rilu, an 11-year-old snow leopard, struggled with Covid-19 induced pneumoniabefore death, according to a post on the Miller Park Zoo verified Instagram account. &amp;ldquo;Rilu arrived at the Miller Park Zoo in 2011 from the Oklahoma City Zoo,&amp;rdquo; the post said.</description></item><item><title>Climate change disasters cost the world over $100 billion this year</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6f61972f9c69a999f9502/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6f61972f9c69a999f9502/</guid><description>The people affected by expensive climate disasters are often among the most vulnerable—and are asking wealthy nations to pay up.
Summary This past year saw an inundation of climate disasters worldwide. Out of the 15 climate-related disasters described in the study, ten have cost more than a billion dollars worth of damages. This will be the sixth year out of the last ten that have cost over $100 billion due to global natural catastrophes.</description></item><item><title>Teen who urinated on WW2 memorial and posted video online is jailed for four years.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7320bcf858a1578577a76/</guid><description>The 19-year-old male was found to have &amp;lsquo;desecrated&amp;rsquo; a portrait of a war veteran, and was deemed guilty under a strict new law introduced in March this year following a similar case
Summary A teenager has been sentenced to four years in prison after being seen urinating on a World War Two memorial. 19-year-old Matvey Yuferov actually recorded himself urinating on a portrait of a World War Two veteran on November 25, in the Moscow district of Izmailovo, and uploaded the footage online.</description></item></channel></rss>