<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>beats on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/beats/</link><description>Recent content in beats on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 19:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/beats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Macron beats Le Pen in French election – projections - BBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265a0e1664d9ead254b8d27/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 19:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265a0e1664d9ead254b8d27/</guid><description>The sitting president has taken about 58% of the vote to beat his far-right rival to secure a second term in office.
Highlights Eric Zemmour called for an alliance of far-right parties ahead of legislative elections in June. Said: &amp;ldquo;This is the eighth time that defeat has struck the name of Le Pen&amp;rdquo; President has taken about 58% of the vote to secure a second term in office. He said: &amp;ldquo;There is strength in unity.</description></item><item><title>Carjacker beats up 72-year-old, takes car, only to die in crash, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dd486f90be4fb13dc0aba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 21:14:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625dd486f90be4fb13dc0aba/</guid><description>A San Antonio great-grandmother is recovering after a brutal carjacking this week.
Highlights Shirlene Hernandez, 72, was on her way to a Shell gas station Tuesday morning to get a Diet Coke. On her way inside, a man grabbed her, hitting her several times in the face in a tussle to take her keys. Despite three men trying to tackle the attacker, he still got away with her car. Not long after, police found her car on the interstate, totaled – and with the suspected carjacker dead inside.</description></item></channel></rss>