<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>threatening on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threatening/</link><description>Recent content in threatening on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/threatening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justin Moreira of Hyannis charged with threatening to commit school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294a5b27838abd7f0846e07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 11:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294a5b27838abd7f0846e07/</guid><description>A Cape Cod man was arrested after allegedly threatening to commit a school shooting.
Highlights Justin Moreira, 29, was arrested and charged with making terroristic threats. He is scheduled to be arraigned Tuesday in Barnstable District Court. Police received multiple reports about a Facebook post allegedly made by Moreira. Moreira was arrested at his Hyannis home and taken into custody without incident. Police searched Moreira&amp;rsquo;s home, but did not find any guns in his home.</description></item><item><title>Teens shot trying to break into man's car were 13 and 16-years-old, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bf246ad859237b7d3b81d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 14:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626bf246ad859237b7d3b81d/</guid><description>According to investigators, the call first came in around 2 a.m. as a report of a car burglary with shots fired on Martinwood Drive.
Highlights Two teenagers were shot by a man after reportedly trying to break into his car, Orange County deputies said. The call first came in around 2 a.m. as a report of a car burglary with shots fired on Martinwood Drive in Pine Hills. The victim said the suspects made &amp;ldquo;threatening movements toward him&amp;rdquo; and so he fired several shots.</description></item><item><title>Man arrested for allegedly threatening Merriam-Webster over definition of female</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62648816f9039dbaefa37d3a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62648816f9039dbaefa37d3a/</guid><description>A California man was arrested after making online threats against the dictionary publisher over their entries that defined women, investigators said.
Highlights Jeremy David Hanson, 34, of Rossmoor, California, was charged on April 20 with one count of interstate communication of threats to commit violence. He allegedly sent the company several threatening messages through its &amp;ldquo;Contact us&amp;rdquo; section on its website and in the comments section. The threats were serious enough to force Merriam-Webster to close its Springfield and New York offices out of an abundance of caution.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota man pleads guilty to threatening to kill U.S. Rep. Ilhan Omar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262e43c40378adcdd7c2f34/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 17:22:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262e43c40378adcdd7c2f34/</guid><description>The email, in part, asked Omar if she was prepared “to die for Islam.”
Highlights David Hannon, 67, of Sarasota, entered the plea Tuesday to a charge of threatening a federal official. Hannon sent an email to Omar on July 16, 2019, after a televised news conference held by Omar and three other members of Congress. The email, in part, asked Omar if she was prepared “to die for Islam” and said Hannon was going to shoot her in the head, Justice Department says.</description></item><item><title>New grafting technique could combat the disease threatening Cavendish bananas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ceaa8d807d04b56be46cfa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ceaa8d807d04b56be46cfa/</guid><description>Grafting is the technique of joining the shoot of one plant with the root of another, so they continue to grow together as one. Until now it was thought
Summary Grafting is the technique of joining the shoot of one plant with the root of another, so they continue to grow together as one. Grafting genetically different root and shoot tissues can result in a plant with new traits – ranging from dwarf shoots, to pest and disease resistance.</description></item></channel></rss>