<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>theyre on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/theyre/</link><description>Recent content in theyre on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 10:15:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/theyre/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Detroit illegally overtaxed homeowners $600M resulting in 100,000 people losing their homes to foreclosure.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625be88e26fc10bd671f4fbc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 10:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625be88e26fc10bd671f4fbc/</guid><description>An estimated 100,000 Detoiters lost their home to foreclosures because of over-assessments
Highlights An estimated 100,000 Detroiters, most of them Black, lost their homes to foreclosure. Michigan Constitution prohibits property from being assessed at more than 50% of its market value. To this day, residents have not been compensated for losing their homes or paying more than they owed in property taxes. Coalition for Property Tax Justice surveyed more than 200 overtaxed residents to determine how they want to be compensated.</description></item><item><title>Once a retail giant, Kmart nears extinction after closure</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62548c76cae6950dffbf7046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 20:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62548c76cae6950dffbf7046/</guid><description>Kmart’s decline has been slow but steady, brought about by years of falling sales, changes in shopping habits and the looming shadow of Walmart.
Highlights The number of Kmarts in the U.S. will be down to three in the continental U.s. and a handful of stores elsewhere. Kmart cemented a place in American culture with its Blue Light Specials, a flashing blue orb affixed to a pole that would beckon shoppers to a flash sale in progress.</description></item><item><title>NASA’s new Webb space telescope opens its golden ‘eye’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db5b039b4239bd82110570/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db5b039b4239bd82110570/</guid><description>The world’s most powerful telescope unfurled its final mirror today as it sped away to its final destination one million miles from earth. NASA completed the final step of the Webb telescope’s difficult two-week initiation process Saturday, unfolding the final 21-foot piece: its ‘golden eye.’ NPR science correspondent Joe Palca joins Hari Sreenivasan to explain more about the telescope, its design, and its purpose.
Summary But if you look through an infrared telescope, oh yes, there I see a star or a galaxy.</description></item></channel></rss>