<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>parts on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/parts/</link><description>Recent content in parts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 16:16:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/parts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. targets Abramovich plane, 99 others over Russia export violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623601c7d52d8c7bf2d0f4b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 16:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623601c7d52d8c7bf2d0f4b6/</guid><description>The U.S. Commerce Department on Friday moved to effectively ground 100 airplanes that have recently flown to Russia and are believed to violate U.S. export controls, including a plane used by Russian businessman Roman Abramovich.
Highlights The U.S. Commerce Department on Friday moved to effectively ground 100 airplanes that have recently flown to Russia. The list includes 99 Boeing airplanes operated by Russian passenger and cargo carriers including Aeroflot, AirBridge Cargo, Utair, Nordwind, Azur Air and Aviastar-TU.</description></item><item><title>Idaho man charged with murder and cannibalism after body parts found in microwave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 12:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1c20825b4ec0521fec858/</guid><description>Description Summary CLARK FORK — A northern Idaho man faces serious charges after investigators say they found a dead man’s body parts in a microwave. Russell is charged with felony first-degree murder and felony cannibalism in an amended criminal complaint filed Wednesday. Deputies went to Flaget’s truck, where they found the body naked from the waist down positioned awkwardly in the passenger seat. Some of the tissue indicated heat had been applied, possibly in the microwave for one to two minutes, according to court documents.</description></item></channel></rss>