<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>exposure on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/exposure/</link><description>Recent content in exposure on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 09:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/exposure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Possible case of monkeypox reported in Broward County, FL</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b4f8204451c4136d6be53/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 09:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628b4f8204451c4136d6be53/</guid><description>A “presumptive” case of monkeypox is being investigated in South Florida, state health officials say. The case appears to be related to international travel, the Florida Department of Health in Broward County says. The person
Highlights A “presumptive” case of monkeypox is being investigated in South Florida, state health officials say. The case appears to be related to international travel, and the risk to the community is low, they say. As of Friday, there were 80 confirmed cases worldwide, including at least two in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Carcinogenic chemical benzene found in hundreds of US personal care products | US news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235d7ca3e3f12184047e5cb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 13:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235d7ca3e3f12184047e5cb/</guid><description>Independent lab found the chemical in more than a quarter of items it tested – sometimes at levels considered ‘life threatening’
Highlights Independent testing has found benzene in hand sanitizers, sunscreens, deodorant, dry shampoos, conditioners, antiperspirants, body sprays and anti-fungal treatments. Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, Bayer, CVS and Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson have issued voluntary recalls for widely distributed brands including Brut, Sure, Pantene, Herbal Essences, Old Spice, Secret, Tinactin, Lotrimin, Coppertone, Neutrogena and Aveeno.</description></item></channel></rss>