<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tesla on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tesla/</link><description>Recent content in tesla on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:40:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tesla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Elon Musk tells Tesla employees: Return to the office, or else</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62983f1f70239ae7600d32c0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:40:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62983f1f70239ae7600d32c0/</guid><description>Elon Musk is demanding that Tesla office workers return to in-person work or leave the company.
Highlights Tesla CEO Elon Musk is demanding that Tesla office workers return to in-person work or leave the company. The policy, disclosed in leaked emails, was first reported by electric vehicle news site Electrek.com. Musk said he would personally review any request for exemption from the policy, but that for the most part, “If you don’t show up, we will assume you have resigned” The policy is completely at odds with that of the other tech company, Twitter, which has previously announced employees can continue to work from home “forever” if they prefer.</description></item><item><title>Tesla recalls 130K vehicles; touch screens can go blank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b557207b4bd57ad8456e4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 06:20:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b557207b4bd57ad8456e4/</guid><description>Recall covers certain Model S sedan and Model X SUVs from 2021 and 2022, as well as Model 3 cars and Model Y SUVs. Tesla is fixing the problem with online software updates that will improve temperature management for the computer. The
Highlights Recall covers certain Model S sedan and Model X SUVs from 2021 and 2022, as well as Model 3 cars and Model Y SUVs. The company has no reports of crashes or injuries, but it received 59 related warranty claims from January to early May.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk wins shareholder lawsuit over Tesla’s $2.6 billion SolarCity acquisition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a876c85634c29d0532df5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 12:24:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a876c85634c29d0532df5/</guid><description>Tesla shareholders alleged that Tesla buying the solar installer amounted to a bailout, pushed through by Elon Musk who sat on both company boards at the time.
Highlights Delaware court rules in favor of defendant Elon Musk in a shareholder lawsuit over Tesla&amp;rsquo;s $2.6 billion acquisition of SolarCity. Tesla shareholders alleged the company&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of the solar installer amounted to a bailout, pushed through by Musk who sat on both company boards at the time.</description></item><item><title>SoCal man says car computer on his new Tesla froze, causing vehicle to be stuck at 83 mph on freeway</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625872214d15145552062de9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625872214d15145552062de9/</guid><description>The owner of a new Tesla Model 3 was left in shock after the car&amp;rsquo;s main features allegedly froze while he was driving on the freeway.
Highlights Javier Rodriguez of Irvine said it happened last Thursday while he was driving on the 10 Freeway through Cabazon. He said the car was stuck going 83 mph and the main screen was frozen. All of the buttons and switches - including turn signals and hazard lights - were not working.</description></item></channel></rss>