<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>views on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/views/</link><description>Recent content in views on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 15:11:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/views/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HSBC suspends head of responsible investing who called climate warnings ‘shrill’ | The Guardian</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ba3c7184f591a40fe0f50/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 15:11:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ba3c7184f591a40fe0f50/</guid><description>Bank investigating Stuart Kirk’s conference speech deriding flooding risks and climate warnings from UN and Bank of England
Highlights Stuart Kirk referred to climate warnings as&amp;rsquo;shrill&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;unsubstantiated&amp;rsquo; during a conference speech. Head of responsible investing has been suspended pending an internal investigation. HSBC has struggled to burnish its green credentials, despite pledges to achieve net zero emissions by 2050. Climate activists welcomed Kirk’s suspension but said HSBC had questions to answer about extent to which his views were known or supported within the bank.</description></item><item><title>Peter Thiel to step down from board of Facebook parent Meta</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201fb6834cae426c8687cb7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 05:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201fb6834cae426c8687cb7/</guid><description>Thiel, an early Facebook investor, will not stand for re-election to the board at the company&amp;rsquo;s 2022 annual stockholders&amp;rsquo; meeting.
Highlights Peter Thiel will step down from the board of Facebook owner Meta. Thiel will not stand for re-election to the board at the company&amp;rsquo;s 2022 annual stockholders&amp;rsquo; meeting. Thiel invested $500,000 in thefacebook.com in 2004, becoming the first significant outside investor in the fast-growing social networking site. Thiel has been on the Facebook board since 2005, but his tenure with the company has been fraught with controversy.</description></item></channel></rss>