<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>governor on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/governor/</link><description>Recent content in governor on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/governor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fed Governor Christopher Waller says he’s prepared to take rates past ‘neutral’ to fight inflation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295b1c23b2b93906b7d7718/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295b1c23b2b93906b7d7718/</guid><description>Fed Governor Christopher Waller said he would support hikes that pass through exceed the &amp;quot;neutral&amp;quot; level.
Highlights Fed Governor Christopher Waller says he would support hikes that exceed the &amp;ldquo;neutral&amp;rdquo; level. Waller: &amp;ldquo;I am not taking 50 basis-point hikes off the table until I see inflation coming down closer to our 2 percent target&amp;rdquo; The central bank official said he thinks the Fed can raise rates and tamp down demand without causing a severe economic downturn.</description></item><item><title>2 acquitted, jury hung on 2 more in Whitmer kidnap plot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250c185a9fdff03b9eb81db/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 23:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250c185a9fdff03b9eb81db/</guid><description>GRAND RAPIDS, Mich. (AP) — A jury on Friday acquitted two men of all charges in a plot to kidnap Michigan Gov.
Highlights Daniel Harris, 24, and Brandon Caserta, 33, were found not guilty of conspiracy. Daniel Harris was acquitted of charges related to explosives and a gun. The jury could not reach verdicts for Adam Fox, 38, and Barry Croft Jr., 46, which means the government can put them on trial again for two conspiracy charges.</description></item><item><title>Idaho governor signs abortion ban modeled on Texas law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cb55e76056edaa021b7c2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 18:16:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cb55e76056edaa021b7c2/</guid><description>BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho on Wednesday became the first state to enact a law modeled after a Texas statute banning abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy and allowing it to be enforced through lawsuits to avoid constitutional court challenges.
Highlights Idaho on Wednesday, March 23, 2022, became the first state to enact a law modeled after a Texas statute banning abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy. Republican Gov.</description></item><item><title>Florida First Lady Casey DeSantis Now Cancer-Free</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222119ef821199ff68e6360/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 13:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222119ef821199ff68e6360/</guid><description>Florida first lady Casey DeSantis is now cancer-free after battling breast cancer, she and Gov. Ron DeSantis announced Thursday.
Highlights Casey DeSantis&amp;rsquo; diagnosis was made public in October. She underwent surgery and received her final chemotherapy treatment in January. The first lady, 41, has played an active role in her husband&amp;rsquo;s administration. &amp;ldquo;There are no words to express how truly blessed, grateful and humbled I am to hear the words cancer free,&amp;rdquo; she said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Gov. Jared Polis reduces I-70 truck driver Rogel Aguilera-Mederos' sentence to 10 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ceb8a69ee3971803cb9ef5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 08:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ceb8a69ee3971803cb9ef5/</guid><description>Colorado Gov. Jared Polis on Thursday reduced the sentence for the former truck driver convicted for causing a fatal crash that killed four people from 110 years to 10 years.
Summary Polis called the sentence imposed on Rogel Aguilera-Mederos “highly atypical and unjust” in his Thursday letter announcing the commutation. A representative from the governor’s office called Aguilera-Mederos and one of his attorneys Thursday afternoon, Aguilera-Mederos’ defense attorney Jim Colgan said.</description></item></channel></rss>