<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>entire on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/entire/</link><description>Recent content in entire on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 23:10:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/entire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starbucks exits Russia, shutting 130 coffee shops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c14419acf93c60a516322/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 23:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c14419acf93c60a516322/</guid><description>The coffee chain joins McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in taking its brand out of the country. Starbucks had temporarily paused operations in March.
Highlights Starbucks says it is leaving Russia after 15 years in business. The coffee chain had temporarily shut down its stores in March over Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Starbucks joins McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in taking its brand out of the country. The company says it will continue paying its nearly 2,000 employees in Russia for six months and help them find new jobs.</description></item><item><title>BuzzFeed investors have pushed CEO Jonah Peretti to shut down entire newsroom, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b396eb62c81f8568ce93c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 15:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b396eb62c81f8568ce93c/</guid><description>BuzzFeed&amp;rsquo;s news organization has about 100 employees and loses roughly $10 million a year, according to people familiar with the matter.
Highlights The news division loses $10 million a year, people familiar with it say. The decision to shut down the division could add up to $300 million to the $2 billion loss. BuzzFeed has offered a voluntary buyout to more than 30 staff members. The company has won several awards for its work, including a Pulitzer and an award for excellence in its content, a source says.</description></item></channel></rss>