<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suspect on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspect/</link><description>Recent content in suspect on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 23:09:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Militia member believed to have shot and killed a former judge in Juneau County; sources say suspect hit list included Governor Evers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629be5eb7b17bb4c90916d83/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 23:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629be5eb7b17bb4c90916d83/</guid><description>Douglas K. Uhde, 56, is being identified as the shooter in the case. A hit list was recovered as well in the suspects vehicle which included Wisconsin Governor Tony Evers and Michigan Governor Gretchen Whitmer. The victim was
Highlights Douglas K. Uhde, 56, is being identified as the shooter in the case. He was found in the basement of the home of former Juneau County Judge John Roemer. The victim was found dead and the suspect was taken to the hospital where he remains in critical condition.</description></item><item><title>Woman with 3 kids in car charged in road-rage shooting that injured teen, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62718d26ace47f441a71142b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 20:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62718d26ace47f441a71142b/</guid><description>A woman is in custody following a road rage incident in Georgia that left a teenage victim injured, police said.
Highlights A 17-year-old was shot in the face Sunday afternoon while inside a vehicle on Interstate 20. Brittney Griffith has been charged with four counts of aggravated assault, three counts of cruelty to children and one count of possession of a firearm during commission of a felony. Griffith&amp;rsquo;s three children, ages 4 to 6, were in the car with her when she shot at the victim’s vehicle, police said.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in crash that killed Seattle pedestrian identified as Auburn police officer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267aa6a7260c8123f398933/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 08:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267aa6a7260c8123f398933/</guid><description>Michael Smith, 33, was arrested Saturday night after he struck and killed a pedestrian in Seattle’s Interbay neighborhood. Police responded to the intersection of 15th Avenue West and Gilman Drive West just before 11 p.m.
Highlights A man was arrested Saturday night after he struck and killed a pedestrian in Seattle’s Interbay neighborhood. The 33-year-old suspect was identified as off-duty Auburn police officer Michael Smith. Smith was immediately placed on administrative leave while an internal investigation is conducted.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting suspect has been arrested, law enforcement officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 01:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62577294105e87a6bb7e77cc/</guid><description>Suspected Brooklyn subway shooter Frank James was arrested by patrol officers in the East Village in New York City on Wednesday, three law enforcement officials tell CNN.
Highlights Images captured by people at the scene of the shooting show chaos and chaos. People can be heard rushing off the train after it pulled into the 36th Street subway station. The bullet hit one man in the back of his knee and came out the other side, he says.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan arrests spy ‘planning attack’ on president, other officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624aa958b580bb37ef91a1cb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 08:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624aa958b580bb37ef91a1cb/</guid><description>Kazakhstan’s security services said Sunday they have arrested a foreign spy allegedly plotting an attack against the president and other high-level
Highlights A foreign intelligence agent, a Kazakh citizen, was arrested on March 25 in Nur-Sultan by the counter-espionage services, the National Security Committee said. A foreign-made gun, drugs, and large sums of money had been found during a search of his home. The statement added the suspect had confessed after his arrest and a terrorism investigation had been opened.</description></item><item><title>Meijer theft suspect was a white man in his 30s. Police detained 60-year-old Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 00:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdc61a987bc2d3b25ae9cd/</guid><description>The incident is yet another example, a lawsuit says, of a Black person being confronted by law enforcement merely for going about his daily life.
Highlights Police were looking for a shoplifter in a West Chester Meijer in 2021. Police detained a 60-year-old Black man, Eric Lindsay, who was wearing an orange down coat and a brown-and-tan scarf. Lindsay, a business professional, was questioned for several minutes in an aisle as other shoppers looked on.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pushed to Her Death in Front of Oncoming Train at Times Square Station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</guid><description>Police have taken a person of interest into custody with a history of prior arrests.
Summary An Asian woman was pushed to her death at a subway station in Times Square on Saturday morning in what city officials are calling an &amp;ldquo;unprovoked&amp;rdquo; attack. At an afternoon press conference held a host of city officials, police said there appeared to be no connection between the victim and her attacker. #BREAKING: @NYPDTransit says a woman was killed after being shoved onto the subway tracks and into the path of a southbound R train at Times Square this morning.</description></item></channel></rss>