<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lawsuit on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawsuit/</link><description>Recent content in lawsuit on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 04:17:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lawsuit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>84-year-old man exonerated after 46 years in prison sues Cleveland for withholding evidence in wife's murder case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c1eae18519f3cc456b0b6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 04:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c1eae18519f3cc456b0b6/</guid><description>Isaiah Andrews, 84, who was exonerated of his wife&amp;rsquo;s murder last fall after spending 46 years in prison, filed a federal civil rights lawsuit against the City of Cleveland in the U.S. District Court Northern District of Ohio Monday.
Highlights Isaiah Andrews, 84, filed a federal civil rights lawsuit against the City of Cleveland Monday. Andrews was exonerated of his wife&amp;rsquo;s murder last fall after spending 46 years in prison. The lawsuit alleges police withheld critical evidence about Regina Andrews&amp;rsquo; murder on September 18, 1974.</description></item><item><title>Brad Pitt sues Angelina Jolie over sale of stake in French vineyard Chateau Miraval to Russian oligarch</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620fc64afe72d78276696274/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620fc64afe72d78276696274/</guid><description>Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt bought the Chateau Miraval estate in the village of Correns, in southeastern France, in 2008, and were married there six years later. According to court documents, both agreed never to sell their respective interests without the other&amp;rsquo;s consent.
Highlights Angelina Jolie sold stake in Chateau Miraval SA company to a Russian oligarch, lawsuit claims. Jolie and Brad Pitt bought the estate in the village of Correns, in southeastern France, in 2008.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Palin loses defamation case against New York Times</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ad3933e58e89ba58acef7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 22:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ad3933e58e89ba58acef7/</guid><description>A U.S. judge on Monday said he will throw out Sarah Palin&amp;rsquo;s defamation lawsuit against the New York Times after concluding that the newspaper did not in an editorial maliciously link the former Alaska governor and 2008 Republican U.S. vice presidential candidate to a mass murder.
Highlights Sarah Palin&amp;rsquo;s defamation lawsuit against the New York Times will be thrown out, U.S. District Judge Jed Rakoff says. The judge says Palin failed to show the Times acted with &amp;ldquo;actual malice&amp;rdquo; in a June 2017 editorial.</description></item><item><title>Star witness in Ukraine impeachment saga sues Trump allies and alleges conspiracy to intimidate him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb357790ec5ce7283f38d9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 01:53:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb357790ec5ce7283f38d9/</guid><description>Retired Army Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman, who served on the National Security Council and emerged as a star witness against then-President Donald Trump during the 2019 Ukraine impeachment, is suing Donald Trump Jr., Rudy Giuliani and former Trump White House staffers, alleging they conspired against him.
Highlights Retired Army Lt. Col. Alexander Vindman served on the National Security Council and emerged as a star witness against then-President Donald Trump during the 2019 Ukraine impeachment.</description></item><item><title>Fairfax Police Officers Protected Sex Trafficking Ring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</guid><description>A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern&amp;hellip;
Summary A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern Virginia in exchange for free sex from the trafficked women. The suit was filed on behalf of a Costa Rican woman identified in the lawsuit only as “Jane Doe.</description></item></channel></rss>