<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>priest on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/priest/</link><description>Recent content in priest on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 07:14:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/priest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Priest attacked with knife in Nice, France</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62664a2a3f7b74b7726a055a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 07:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62664a2a3f7b74b7726a055a/</guid><description>A man decribed as mentally unstable attacked a priest with a knife in a church in Nice, southern France, officials said on Sunday.
Highlights A man attacked a priest with a knife in Nice, France, officials said on Sunday. The attacker had no criminal record and was known to have purchased a knife several days earlier. The assault came as France was voting in the second round of presidential elections. The man was named as a 31-year-old man who had not been seen in the public eye since the attack.</description></item><item><title>I'm shocked by my church leaders in Moscow' - priest in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c74e28e467345088be36d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c74e28e467345088be36d/</guid><description>The Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s war stance has prompted some Ukrainian priests and parishioners to cut ties.
Highlights Russian Orthodox Church&amp;rsquo;s war stance has prompted some Ukrainian priests and parishioners to cut ties. &amp;ldquo;We were living peacefully until they came. But far from protecting us they bombed and tortured and killed. Now that has changed,&amp;rdquo; says one priest. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Alabama elementary school principal accused of ‘excessive paddling’ of student</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625620656fec5a7ab679dd8f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625620656fec5a7ab679dd8f/</guid><description>The principal of an elementary school in Lawrence County, Alabama, has been put on paid administrative lead following accusations of &amp;quot;excessive paddling&amp;quot; of a student.
Highlights Principal Dr. Datie Priest accused of paddling a third-grade student ten times in a row. Alabama law allows corporal punishment, but no more than three licks at a time is allowed. The Alabama NAACP stands by the principal, saying accusations against another principal were not in her personnel file.</description></item></channel></rss>