<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>concerns on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/concerns/</link><description>Recent content in concerns on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 12:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/concerns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recall alert: Nearly 121,000 pounds of ground beef sold nationwide recalled amid E. coli concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626935bf8a9e0f7a9fe6e1ca/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626935bf8a9e0f7a9fe6e1ca/</guid><description>Lakeside Refrigerated Services recalled 120,872 pounds of beef that may be contaminated with E. coli O103. The potential contamination was discovered during routine FSIS testing of imported products. The particular strain of E.coli
Highlights Lakeside Refrigerated Services recalled 120,872 pounds of ground beef that may be contaminated with E. coli O103. The potential contamination was discovered during routine FSIS testing of imported products. The particular strain of E.coli typically causes diarrhea and vomiting.</description></item><item><title>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edfa2e0c27330289b103f5/</guid><description>The Netherlands sends F-35s to Bulgaria due to concerns about Ukraine
Summary In response to the increasing Russian threat around Ukraine, the Netherlands is sending two F-35 fighter aircraft to Bulgaria. The two F-35s will participate in a NATO mission that has been ongoing for years to monitor the skies of Eastern Europe. The Netherlands also offers an amphibious transport ship (including landing craft and helicopters) and two ‘land-bound units’ (Ollongren does not specify which) for the NATO Response Force.</description></item></channel></rss>