<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>told on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/told/</link><description>Recent content in told on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 17:12:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/told/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Armed man arrested outside Brett Kavanaugh’s home after threatening Supreme Court justice</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0d85edc57c9edf3cca88f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 17:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0d85edc57c9edf3cca88f/</guid><description>A man with a weapon was arrested early Tuesday morning by police near the Maryland home of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh, authorities said.
Highlights Nicholas John Roske, 26, arrived in a taxi near Kavanaugh&amp;rsquo;s home in Chevy Chase, a suburb just outside of Washington, D.C. He told police he was there to kill Kavanaugh, according to authorities. Roske was apprehended a block away from the residence by members of the U.</description></item><item><title>911 dispatcher fired after allegedly hanging up on store employee during Buffalo shooting call</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a946ffd4003af0917ad8f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 23:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a946ffd4003af0917ad8f/</guid><description>The 911 dispatcher accused of hanging up on an employee calling for help during the supermarket shooting that killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, last month has been fired, officials said.
Highlights The 911 dispatcher accused of hanging up on an employee calling for help during the supermarket shooting that killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, last month has been fired, officials said. The assistant office manager at Tops Friendly Market called 911 when a white gunman, 18, stormed the store on May 14 and opened fire.</description></item><item><title>Putin treated for advanced cancer and survived assassination attempt, US intelligence reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a0be5b285cfc26cd10605/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a0be5b285cfc26cd10605/</guid><description>The Russian president has received treatment for advanced cancer and was targeted in an assassination attempt, three intelligence sources have told Newsweek
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin received treatment for advanced cancer in April, three US intelligence sources have told Newsweek. The report also confirmed an assassination plot against Mr Putin in March, the organisation said. Rumours have been swirling in the past few months that Mr Putin was suffering from cancer or was in bad health as pictures of him in a debilitated state emerged.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde gunman threatened rapes and school shootings on social media app Yubo in weeks leading up to the massacre, users say | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629221ca3d1645a02e9a7e47/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629221ca3d1645a02e9a7e47/</guid><description>Salvador Ramos told girls he would rape them, showed off a rifle he bought, and threatened to shoot up schools in livestreams on the social media app Yubo, according to several users who witnessed the threats in recent weeks.
Highlights Three users say they saw Ramos threaten to commit sexual violence or carry out school threats on Yubo. The social media app is used by tens of millions of young people around the world.</description></item><item><title>Estranged husband shot wife, 4-year-old daughter, mother-in-law before killing himself, sheriff says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287cd0be0040f439efdbe12/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287cd0be0040f439efdbe12/</guid><description>The Harris County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office is investigating a shooting with at least four people dead. Murder-suicide may be involved.
Highlights NEW: Harris County Sheriff Ed Gonzalez says the man appeared to have shot his wife and his mother-in-law before turning the gun on himself. NEW: The husband and wife were going through a divorce in recent months, and there were reports of the man being abusive to his 4-year-old daughter, the sheriff says.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo suspect's posts about attack plans could be seen online 30 minutes before mass shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628647371fc70d8a171b0473/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 13:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628647371fc70d8a171b0473/</guid><description>Thirty minutes before an 18-year-old White man allegedly carried out a racist mass shooting Saturday at a supermarket in a mostly Black enclave of Buffalo, New York, he revealed his monthslong plot to some on social media.
Highlights NEW: New York&amp;rsquo;s attorney general launches probe into social media companies used by alleged shooter. Payton S. Gendron, 18, is accused of killing 10 people and wounding three in a racist mass shooting in Buffalo, New York.</description></item><item><title>Supermarket shooter sought Black neighborhood, official says | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628143bb3b525b137fdd74d5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628143bb3b525b137fdd74d5/</guid><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The white 18-year-old who shot and killed 10 people at a Buffalo supermarket had researched the local demographics while looking for places with a high concentration of Black residents, arriving there at least a day in advance to conduct reconnaissance, law enforcement officials said Sunday.
Highlights The shooter, identified as Payton Gendron, had previously threatened a shooting at his high school last June, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Florida school yearbook on hold over student protest photos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627aac31f46ffe61e07f958b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 18:17:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627aac31f46ffe61e07f958b/</guid><description>Students at a central Florida high school were told they won’t get their yearbooks until they&amp;rsquo;re censored
Highlights Yearbooks won&amp;rsquo;t be distributed until images of students holding rainbow flags and a “love is love” sign can be covered up. District officials said they don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone thinking that the school supported the students&amp;rsquo; walkout. Florida&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rdquo; law bans classroom instruction on sexual orientation or gender identity in kindergarten through third grade.</description></item><item><title>Nine hospitalized after Texas authorities find dozens of undocumented workers in semi trailer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276e0d2c05fa0d06c16094c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 21:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6276e0d2c05fa0d06c16094c/</guid><description>Nine people were treated for dehydration and scores of others fled the scene when authorities discovered up to 100 undocumented workers in the trailer of a broken-down semi in rural Texas, officials said Friday.
Highlights The truck became disabled on a rural highway about 2 miles north of the town of Ganado. When authorities investigated just after 7 a.m. CT, they discovered a packed trailer. They apprehended 10 people while others ran from the scene.</description></item><item><title>A 13-year-old girl in India told the police she had been gang-raped. Then a police officer allegedly raped her | CTV News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627471aeb8957aec12b6d600/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:54:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627471aeb8957aec12b6d600/</guid><description>A 13-year-old girl who was allegedly gang-raped by four men in India, was allegedly raped again by a police officer after she tried to seek his help in reporting the initial attack.
Highlights A 13-year-old girl who was allegedly gang-raped by four men in India, was allegedly raped again by a police officer after she tried to seek his help in reporting the initial attack. The alleged incident has caused outrage in India with many accusing police of helping to perpetuate a systemic culture of sexual violence.</description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse says U.S. authorities will 'absolutely not' find any wrongdoing amid probe into Russian oligarch record shredding</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a6918571c2d28f8a61a99/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 10:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a6918571c2d28f8a61a99/</guid><description>CEO Thomas Gottstein told CNBC that letters received by investors had &amp;quot;nothing to do&amp;quot; with sanctions, or loans belonging to members of Putin&amp;rsquo;s inner circle.
Highlights Credit Suisse is under investigation by the House Oversight Committee over allegations it asked investors to erase documents related to a portfolio of loans backed by yachts and private jets potentially owned by sanctioned Russian oligarchs. CEO Thomas Gottstein said letters received by investors had &amp;ldquo;nothing to do&amp;rdquo; with sanctions or loans belonging to members of Putin&amp;rsquo;s inner circle.</description></item><item><title>Knife-wielding 14-year-old Massachusetts girl scares intruder out of her home and helps apprehend him, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c90f2f7478229458ed019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 22:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c90f2f7478229458ed019/</guid><description>The girl&amp;rsquo;s mother said she was armed with two steak knives when she confronted the man and scared him away.
Highlights A 14-year-old Massachusetts girl scared off a man who allegedly broke into her home Friday morning. Police said the girl, identified as Avery Cormier, was armed with two steak knives when she confronted the intruder. Joseph Ridge, 58, was charged with aggravated breaking and entering during the daytime, trespassing and disorderly conduct.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine conflict: 'Russian soldiers raped me and killed my husband'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254e6c24bc56fe75537c7f6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 02:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254e6c24bc56fe75537c7f6/</guid><description>The BBC has uncovered first-hand evidence of Russian soldiers raping and killing civilians in a village west of Kyiv.
Highlights BBC has uncovered first-hand evidence of Russian soldiers raping and killing civilians in a village west of Kyiv. About 25 girls and women aged 14 to 24 were systematically raped during the occupation in the basement of one house in Bucha. Nine of them are pregnant and nine are said to be in danger of having children with Russian soldiers.</description></item><item><title>Traveler told TSA he had 'no idea' a sword was concealed in his cane</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62539697bedcb68d1375eea2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 02:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62539697bedcb68d1375eea2/</guid><description>Someone isn&amp;rsquo;t getting through security.
Highlights A year of the world&amp;rsquo;s best beaches. Join us on a 12-month journey to see them all. A perfect beach for every week of the year is a perfect place to relax, relax and relax. For more beach news, visit CNN.com/Travel next Friday for a new look at the best beaches in the world. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Gang steal 1,600 kilos of cheese from Dutch dairy farm</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e1eb425b0e5ec82798f2e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 23:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e1eb425b0e5ec82798f2e/</guid><description>Gang steal 1,600 kilos of cheese from Dutch dairy farm
Highlights Thieves stole 1,600 kilos of cheese worth €21,000 from a dairy farm in Noord Brabant. Almost all the cheese from the farm’s storage was taken and that has set the farm back some six months in income. Cheese farmers were plagued by a string of cheese thefts a couple of years ago and this week&amp;rsquo;s heist may be a sign of things to come, dairy farmer Theo Dekker said.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine begs for assistance, claiming that Russia is attempting to partition the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241d0a9f0fbde6fee1a8077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 15:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241d0a9f0fbde6fee1a8077/</guid><description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky accused the West of cowardice Sunday while another top official said Russia was trying to split the nation in two, like North and South Korea.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy calls for fighter jets and tanks to be handed over to the West. Another top official says Russia is trying to split Ukraine in two, like North and South Korea. Russia quickly bans interview from being published from publication by Russian media.</description></item><item><title>Judge terminates conservatorship for Amanda Bynes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b2b05404dc6026d3bd23f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 14:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623b2b05404dc6026d3bd23f/</guid><description>A conservatorship for actress Amanda Bynes, which has been overseeing her personal and professional affairs for the past nine years, was officially ended by a judge on Tuesday.
Highlights A conservatorship for actress Amanda Bynes was officially ended by a judge on Tuesday. Bynes&amp;rsquo; mother, Lynne Bynes, had been acting as a conservator and did not object to the request. &amp;ldquo;The parents are happy, thrilled to get this good news,&amp;rdquo; said Tamar Arminak, a spokesman for Bynes last month.</description></item><item><title>Kidnapping suspect wanted ‘tyrant’ Gov. Whitmer tied up on table, FBI agent testifies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234791523e460b3765455aa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 12:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234791523e460b3765455aa/</guid><description>Agent Mark Schweers told the jury that he was posing as someone with like-minded views when he met Adam Fox, who made the startling admission.
Highlights Adam Fox, Barry Croft Jr., Daniel Harris and Brandon Caserta are charged with conspiracy. Prosecutors say they turned anger toward government in 2020 into a plot to kidnap Whitmer at her vacation home. The trial of four men resumed in federal court in Grand Rapids, Michigan, after a three-day delay due to someone in the courtroom testing positive for Covid-19.</description></item><item><title>Denmark opens its arms to Ukrainians, while trying to send Syrian refugees home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a9d339dbd4509149ed748/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 00:52:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a9d339dbd4509149ed748/</guid><description>When Denmark became the first liberal democracy to tell Syrian refugees to return to their war-torn home in 2019, Russian jets were still dropping missiles in Syria, in an effort to help President Bashar al-Assad&amp;rsquo;s regime regain control of the country.
Highlights Denmark is drafting legislation that will suspend asylum rules for Ukrainians. The move would allow Ukrainians to enter the EU without a visa and to choose which country to go to.</description></item><item><title>Turn down heating by 1C to reduce need for Russian imports, Europeans told</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221d7f8f9305282b638de50/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221d7f8f9305282b638de50/</guid><description>IEA says reducing temperature could help wean consumers off fuel that Russia is using as a weapon in Ukraine war
Highlights The International Energy Agency&amp;rsquo;s plan would reduce Russian gas imports by about a third before next winter. Red tape should be cut to bring forward the construction of more wind and solar power stations, the IEA said. The EU relies on Russia for about 40% of its gas consumption. The UK government is also understood to be urgently examining its exposure to gas market turbulence caused by Russia’s invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>US expelling 12 Russian diplomats from UN mission</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9df2b7fd9ca46e8e2980/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d9df2b7fd9ca46e8e2980/</guid><description>Russia’s United Nations ambassador said move ‘gross violation’ of UN agreement with US
Highlights US is expelling 12 Russian diplomats at the United Nations for engaging in activities not in accordance with their responsibilities and obligations as diplomats. Russia’s UN Ambassador Vassily Nebenzia described the move as ‘yet another hostile step undertaken by the host country’ He called the expulsions a ‘gross violation’ of the UN agreement with the US as the host of the Vienna Convention governing diplomatic relations.</description></item><item><title>Soon only one U.S. state will still have an indoor mask mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217f48a188df0d0eb259060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 21:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217f48a188df0d0eb259060/</guid><description>More parts of the country are dropping mask requirements, signaling a new phase in the pandemic.
Highlights Every state, with the exception of Hawaii, is either ditching or eliminating mask mandates as the Omicron surge recedes. The disease continues to kill about 2,000 Americans a day. New York and Rhode Island this month lifted indoor mask rules for businesses, but still require them in schools. In Los Angeles County, residents can soon go maskless so long as they show proof of vaccination at indoor venues.</description></item><item><title>Man charged with murder in fatal shooting at Oregon racial justice protest</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216bf91ec0e067ec35d31e5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216bf91ec0e067ec35d31e5/</guid><description>An Oregon man accused of killing one person and injuring five after opening fire on demonstrators in Portland was charged Tuesday with murder and other crimes, authorities said.
Highlights Benjamin Smith, 43, is charged with second-degree murder, four counts of attempted murder and multiple counts of assault. He is accused of killing one person and injuring five after opening fire on demonstrators in Portland. The shooting ended after someone returned fire, hitting Smith in the hip area, the prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s office says.</description></item><item><title>US House candidate apologizes to girls after sleepover</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215d0ed2abac965515be311/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — A U.S. House candidate in Oklahoma has apologized after reports that she became intoxicated at a Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day weekend sleepover for middle-school-aged girls, berated several of the children and vomited in a hamper.
Highlights Democrat Abby Broyles is apologizing after reports that she became intoxicated, berated several middle-school-aged girls at a sleepover and vomited in a hamper. Broyles told television station KFOR that she had an adverse reaction after drinking wine and taking medication given to her by a friend.</description></item><item><title>Zelensky: Make potential sanctions on Russia public, before a possible invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 05:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211cdb4a28882247d64a00c/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said Saturday sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s President Volodymyr Zelensky said sanctions on Russia should be made public before a possible invasion of Ukraine occurs, as tensions between western nations and Russia continue to intensify. He told CNN&amp;rsquo;s Chief International Anchor Christiane Amanpour that he disagreed with the stance that sanctions should only be listed after a potential Russian invasion takes place.</description></item><item><title>Mom decapitates 6 year old son and dog. Claims devil was speaking to her.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e4a6a443cdff855e0645a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 13:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e4a6a443cdff855e0645a/</guid><description>Police say a mother decapitated her 6-year-old child and the family dog Tuesday night in Kansas City.
Highlights Police say a mother decapitated her 6-year-old child and the family dog Tuesday night in Kansas City. Tasha Haefs, 35, has been charged with first-degree murder and armed criminal action. Police say they also found a decapitated dog in the basement of the home. Prosecutors have requested that she be held without bond.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana man is freed after new evidence uncovered in 1977 attempted rape conviction</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ba74d119ce1ce4a91404a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 13:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ba74d119ce1ce4a91404a/</guid><description>Vincent Simmons​ is a free man after decades in prison.
Highlights Vincent Simmons was convicted of attempted aggravated rape of twin sisters in 1977. He has been trying for years to get a new trial. A judge says he will not retry him, saying the time &amp;ldquo;has been overcome&amp;rdquo; by new evidence. Simmons&amp;rsquo; twin sisters, now 59, say they are the victims and that he is guilty. The girls&amp;rsquo; testimony to police initially told police they didn&amp;rsquo;t know who he was and that &amp;ldquo;all Black people look alike&amp;rdquo; and even used the N-word, defense lawyer says.</description></item><item><title>Man breaks into home, takes bath, eats shrimp leaves $200 for damages</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033135b9995d68c7af4c4e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 03:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033135b9995d68c7af4c4e/</guid><description>Teral Christesson, 34, was arrested Sunday for breaking into a home in New Mexico. He apologized, told the homeowner he just needed a warm place to sleep. Christesson told investigators he was “caught in a bl
Highlights Teral Christesson, 34, was arrested Sunday for breaking into a home in New Mexico. He apologized, told the homeowner he just needed a warm place to sleep and left the man $200 to repair the window.</description></item><item><title>Protesters block Canada-bound traffic on Ambassador Bridge in Windsor | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62023436c1695f94398e3377/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62023436c1695f94398e3377/</guid><description>Traffic entering and leaving Canada via the Ambassador Bridge linking Windsor, Ont., to Detroit was being blocked by protestors on Monday night, with the demonstration showing no signs of ending.
Highlights The Ambassador Bridge linking Windsor, Ontario, to Detroit was being blocked by protesters Monday night. Police in Essex County issued a release Monday evening saying that as of 8 p.m., the bridge was &amp;ldquo;not accessible&amp;rdquo; in either direction. Similar protests played out across Canada over the weekend as convoys of vehicles blocked city streets and highways.</description></item><item><title>Waffle House shooter who killed four people sentenced to life in prison without parole</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff6739d314bf883a7367a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 06:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff6739d314bf883a7367a9/</guid><description>Travis Reinking, who killed four people in 2018 when he opened fire with an assault-style rifle at a Waffle House in Tennessee, was sentenced Saturday to life in prison without parole.
Highlights Jurors heard from relatives of the four people who were killed in the shooting. The prosecution asked for life without parole, calling Reinking a mass murderer whose bullets were ripping apart the lives of the victims&amp;rsquo; relatives. Reinking, 33, was found guilty Friday of all 16 counts, including eight first-degree murder charges.</description></item><item><title>Mom sues social media giants for allegedly driving her 11-year-old daughter to suicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5102d956e5f086b4eb3f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5102d956e5f086b4eb3f/</guid><description>A Connecticut mother filed a lawsuit last month against Meta and Snap for allegedly causing the death of her 11-year-old daughter.
Highlights Selena Rodriguez, 11, died by suicide last July. A Connecticut mom filed a lawsuit against Meta Platforms Inc. and Snap for allegedly causing her daughter&amp;rsquo;s death. Selena suffered &amp;ldquo;severe mental harm, leading to physical injury,&amp;rdquo; according to the lawsuit. Experts have been debating the effects social media has on children and teens.</description></item><item><title>Representative Matt Gaetz's ex-girlfriend granted immunity in sex trafficking probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6abe612e3fd1225200a11/</guid><description>The woman testified in front of a federal grand jury last week hearing evidence in the Gaetz investigation.
Summary Gaetz has been under investigation to determine if he violated sex trafficking laws and obstructed justice in that probe. Gaetz has previously denied all wrongdoing, and has said he has never paid for sex nor had sex with an underage girl. One of the sources said she has information related to the investigation of both the sex trafficking and obstruction allegations.</description></item><item><title>Judge shames 72 year old cancer patient for overgrown yard</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5a0ba7ce54a6e2e588b93/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5a0ba7ce54a6e2e588b93/</guid><description>The 72-year-old&amp;rsquo;s chemo treatments leave him too weak to go out and clear overgrown plants, his son says.
Summary HAMTRAMCK, Mich. (WDIV) - A Michigan judge is being criticized after she berated a 72-year-old cancer patient for not cleaning up his lawn. “You should be ashamed of yourself.”Defendant Burhan Chowdhury, 72, is a cancer patient who is undergoing chemotherapy. His son says his treatments leave the man too weak to go out and clear overgrown plants.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco drivers can now get a text before getting towed, the first of its kind in the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2e1a82f4d83c39bf84bd3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2e1a82f4d83c39bf84bd3/</guid><description>San Francisco is the first city in America to offer this service.
Summary San Francisco officials are now offering drivers a tiny bit of relief. The San Francisco Examiner reported Thursday that locals can now receive text messages warning them if their car is about to be impounded, making San Francisco the first city in the country with such a service. The program, naturally called Text Before Tow, will send San Francisco drivers who opt in a text when their car may be towed for 72-hour parking, blocking driveways or parking in construction zones or temporary no-parking zones.</description></item><item><title>Prince Andrew stripped of military titles and charities amid sex abuse lawsuit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e084f19d768042f68c6a29/</guid><description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.
Summary London (CNN) Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew has been stripped of his military titles and charities, Buckingham Palace announced on Thursday, a day after a judge ruled a sexual abuse civil lawsuit against the Queen&amp;rsquo;s son could proceed.</description></item><item><title>Covid cases rise by 948% in Florida as Omicron drives huge wave across US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3d46cd0d60deb256140e2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3d46cd0d60deb256140e2/</guid><description>Seven-day average for hospitalizations increased by more than 40% during week between Christmas and New Year’s Eve
Summary Covid-19 cases in Florida have risen by 948% in just two weeks, as the highly transmissible Omicron variant drives a huge wave of infections and hospitalizations across the US. In Florida, local and state officials warned that residents were waiting hours in sometimes miles-long lines just to get a test. But nearly two years into the pandemic, the US was still woefully ill-equipped for such conditions and the Omicron variant, sending Americans scrambling to even find tests.</description></item><item><title>Virginia family gets keys to Habitat for Humanity's first 3D-printed home in the US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca4594ec17f800508a266c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca4594ec17f800508a266c/</guid><description>Christmas came early for one Virginia family that just received the keys to their new 3D-printed home.
Summary (CNN) One Virginia family received the keys to their new 3D-printed home in time for Christmas. The home is Habitat for Humanity&amp;rsquo;s first 3D-printed home in the nation, according to a Habitat news release. Janet V. Green, CEO of Habitat for Humanity Peninsula and Greater Williamsburg, told CNN it partnered with Alquist , a 3D printing company, earlier this year to begin the process.</description></item><item><title>North Carolina police chief placed on unpaid leave for telling officers about 'clinic' to obtain Covid-19 vaccination cards without getting the shots</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c48f0e1c2c279f3766c6ad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 15:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c48f0e1c2c279f3766c6ad/</guid><description>A North Carolina police chief has been placed on unpaid leave and probation for telling officers about a &amp;quot;clinic&amp;quot; that would issue them a Covid-19 vaccination card without actually receiving the shot, local officials said.
Summary (CNN) A North Carolina police chief has been placed on unpaid leave and probation for telling officers about a &amp;ldquo;clinic&amp;rdquo; that would issue them a Covid-19 vaccination card without actually receiving the shot, local officials said.</description></item><item><title>Intel tells unvaccinated employees they face unpaid leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</guid><description>Description Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April
Summary Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in AprilPORTLAND, Ore. &amp;ndash; Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don&amp;rsquo;t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April.</description></item><item><title>Texas QAnon cult is now drinking bleach, member’s family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c278b0c8dd262ec076e17a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c278b0c8dd262ec076e17a/</guid><description>Description ‘She was proud to tell us that she was the one mixing it up and giving it to everybody,’ says distressed family member
Summary The family of a woman who joined a fringe QAnon cult in Texas says she’s now drinking toxic chemicals with her peers – and brags that she serves them herself. Despite two occasions when the JFKs failed to show up, Mr Protzman reportedly still has dozens of followers.</description></item></channel></rss>