<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>role on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/role/</link><description>Recent content in role on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 19:08:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/role/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Very angry': Uvalde locals grapple with school chief's role</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296679932f948d7a5147fa7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 19:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296679932f948d7a5147fa7/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — The blame for an excruciating delay in killing the gunman at a Texas elementary school — even as parents outside begged police to rush in and panicked children called 911 from inside — has been placed with the school district&amp;rsquo;s homegrown police chief.
Highlights Pete Arredondo was set to be sworn in Tuesday to his new spot on the City Council after being elected earlier this month.</description></item><item><title>Proud Boys member pleads guilty for role in US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a1301f8848a840c5851bd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a1301f8848a840c5851bd/</guid><description>Plea agreement filed in federal court calls for Louis Enrique Colon to admit to a single felony charge and cooperate with prosecutors
Highlights Louis Enrique Colon pleads guilty to obstructing police officers in Washington, DC. Plea agreement calls for Colon to admit to a single felony charge and cooperate with prosecutors. Colon faces up to five years in prison and a fine of up to $250,000. One of the dozens of police officers injured during the insurrection testified on Wednesday that he didn’t punch or pick a fight with a retired New York police officer charged with attacking the officer.</description></item><item><title>No evidence of drugs or foul play in death of Bob Saget, medical examiner says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd01106491f91c0837d126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 04:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd01106491f91c0837d126/</guid><description>There is no evidence at this time that foul play or drugs played a role in the death of actor and comedian Bob Saget, authorities said Monday.
Summary There is no evidence at this time that foul play or drugs played a role in the death of actor and comedian Bob Saget, authorities said Monday. Saget was found dead in his room at the Ritz-Carlton Orlando, Grande Lakes, according to the Orange County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.</description></item></channel></rss>