<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>missouri on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missouri/</link><description>Recent content in missouri on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 10:10:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/missouri/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Suspected serial killer charged in Missouri over 7th death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62934659ffcb4a2a582780f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 10:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62934659ffcb4a2a582780f0/</guid><description>A suspected serial killer already charged in six killings in the Kansas City and St. Louis areas has been charged with first-degree murder in a seventh death
Highlights Perez Deshay Reed is already charged in six killings in Kansas City and St. Louis. The most recent charges stem from the shooting death of Stephon D. Johnson, of Kansas City, Missouri. The prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s office did not provide Johnson&amp;rsquo;s age. Reed is charged in the killings of 16-year-old Marnay Haynes, 40, Lester Robinson and Lester Robinson.</description></item><item><title>Missouri ends effort to prosecute journalist who 'viewed source' in a web browser</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623dcdb0bf024e86cc55f24e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 14:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623dcdb0bf024e86cc55f24e/</guid><description>Missouri reporter Josh Renaud faced potential hacking charges for viewing website source code in browser. Renaud found Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Department of Elementary and Secondary Education&amp;rsquo;s website exposed the Social Security details of educators. Cole County Prosecutor Locke Thompson announced no charges would
Highlights Missouri reporter Josh Renaud faced potential hacking charges for viewing website source code in his browser. Renaud found that Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Department of Elementary and Secondary Education&amp;rsquo;s website exposed the Social Security details of educators.</description></item></channel></rss>