<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pregnant on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pregnant/</link><description>Recent content in pregnant on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 21:12:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pregnant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colorado now guarantees the right to abortion in state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b5f2d7987f31f92c4ddf3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b5f2d7987f31f92c4ddf3/</guid><description>Abortion access is now guaranteed in Colorado law after Gov. Jared Polis signed a bill enshrining that right Monday.
Highlights The bill passed out of the Colorado legislature last month on a party-line vote. It would ban local and state governments from interfering in that care. It also would prevent a fertilized egg, embryo or fetus from having independent rights under state law. 15 other states and the District of Columbia have codified abortion into law with the “Reproductive Health Equity Act’s” The bill signed by Jared Polis, a Democrat of Pueblo, was passed by the House of Representatives last week.</description></item><item><title>Coronavirus can destroy the placenta and lead to stillbirths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6206611f5053c6d1f69827a9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 13:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6206611f5053c6d1f69827a9/</guid><description>New research suggests the coronavirus can invade and destroy the placenta and lead to stillbirths in infected women. It&amp;rsquo;s an uncommon outcome for any pregnancy but women with COVID-19 face an elevated risk.
Highlights Coronavirus can destroy the placenta and lead to stillbirths in infected pregnant women. Researchers in 12 countries analyzed placental and autopsy tissue from 64 stillbirth and four newborns who died shortly after birth. The cases all involved unvaccinated women who had COVID-19 during their pregnancy.</description></item></channel></rss>