<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>including on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/including/</link><description>Recent content in including on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 01:04:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/including/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York judge lifts civil contempt finding against Trump, orders him to pay $110,000 in fines</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c5d053c9b6ca92a262c04/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 01:04:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c5d053c9b6ca92a262c04/</guid><description>A New York judge on Wednesday set several conditions former President Donald Trump must meet to avoid a civil contempt finding being restored against him, including paying $110,000 in fines and explaining how his namesake company handled Post-it notes.
Highlights Judge Arthur Engoron said he wanted sworn statements describing the Trump Organization&amp;rsquo;s document retention and destruction policy. The conditions must be met by May 20, otherwise the judge said he would restore the contempt finding and apply it retroactively.</description></item><item><title>Tech giants lost more than $1 trillion in value in the last three trading days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279dac4e63481987b9b0d59/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 03:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279dac4e63481987b9b0d59/</guid><description>The biggest names of the technology industry are becoming more affordable as investors take account of the latest U.S. central bank decision.
Highlights Technology has endured more pain than other sectors of the economy. Investors are now pushing more money toward safer pockets of the market, including Campbell Soup, General Mills and J.M. Smucker. The biggest names of the technology industry are becoming more affordable as investors take account of the latest U.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks hit with sweeping labor complaint including over 200 alleged violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62762ae4fdb9401279f7561e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 08:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62762ae4fdb9401279f7561e/</guid><description>The NLRB says Starbucks interfered with, restrained and coerced employees seeking to unionize in various ways.
Highlights National Labor Relations Board accuses Starbucks of 29 unfair labor practice charges. Accuses Starbucks of interfering with, restraining and coercing employees seeking to unionize in various ways. Starbucks does not agree that the claims have merit, but the complaint&amp;rsquo;s issuance does not constitute a finding by the NLRB. Starbucks has nearly 9,000 locations across the country and has nearly 250 stores to organize with Starbucks Workers United.</description></item><item><title>France introduces free birth control for all women under 25</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d12370227d4f1c2543b386/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d12370227d4f1c2543b386/</guid><description>Free birth control for all women under 25 will be available in France from Saturday, expanding a scheme targeting under-18s to ensure young women don&amp;rsquo;t stop taking contraception because they cannot a…
Summary Contraception including the pill, IUDs, contraceptive patches and other methods will be free for women aged 25 and under in France from January 1, 2021. Free birth control for all women under 25 will be available in France from Saturday, expanding a scheme targeting under-18s to ensure young women don&amp;rsquo;t stop taking contraception because they cannot afford it.</description></item><item><title>China places outright ban on tattoos, issuing fresh calls for footballers to have existing ink removed completely</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce3a0d6dfed9f3d0689d9e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce3a0d6dfed9f3d0689d9e/</guid><description>China’s General Administration of Sport have placed an outright ban on tattoos, and instructed national team players who have been inked to have them removed.
Summary The ban will affect a number of Chinese players, including Guangzhou FC defender Zhang Linpeng (left). READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>