<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>annual on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/annual/</link><description>Recent content in annual on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 12:13:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/annual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protesters' anguished shouts fail to dampen gun enthusiasm at NRA convention in Houston</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629211e3201cff31f1c8dce6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 12:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629211e3201cff31f1c8dce6/</guid><description>Less than 72 hours after a gunman killed 19 children and two teachers in Uvalde, Texas, thousands of gun owners gathered at an NRA meeting in Houston.
Highlights Gun owners gathered in Houston to defend and celebrate the types of laws that made it possible for a teenager to purchase a pair of AR-15-style semiautomatic rifles days after his 18th birthday. Gun control activists and gun owners were separated by a four-lane road, metal barricades and horse-mounted police.</description></item><item><title>Rents in the US just hit another record high</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62875aeead586c408d73c731/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 09:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62875aeead586c408d73c731/</guid><description>Rents in the US climbed to a new record high again in April, and they are expected to keep rising.
Highlights The national median rent was $1,827 a month in April, up 16.7% from a year ago. If recent trends continue, the typical rent could be more than $2,000 a month by August. The continued surge in rental prices is driven by a mismatch between rental supply and rising demand, says Realtor.</description></item><item><title>Inflation rises 7.5% over the past year, even more than expected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620547a818dd4b36a4e08358/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 17:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620547a818dd4b36a4e08358/</guid><description>The consumer price index was expected to increase 7.2% from a year ago, according to a Dow Jones economist survey.
Highlights Consumer price index for January rose 7.5% compared with a year ago, the Labor Department says. That compared with Dow Jones estimates of 7.2%. Core inflation rose at its fastest level since August 1982. Stock market futures declined following the report, with rate-sensitive tech stocks hit especially hard. The chances of a 0.</description></item></channel></rss>