<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>amp on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/amp/</link><description>Recent content in amp on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 06:18:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/amp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two more confirmed cases of monkeypox in England - BBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62809ad553928c949b12bd64/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62809ad553928c949b12bd64/</guid><description>The individuals live together but are not linked to the case announced on 7 May, health agency says.
Highlights These settings apply to AMP pages only. You can choose not to receive personalised ads by clicking “Reject data collection and continue” below. The individuals live together but are not linked to the case announced on 7 May, health agency says. We use local storage to store your consent preferences on your device.</description></item><item><title>Russian planes face near-total airspace ban to west - BBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c05794676f2628bc963e2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 23:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c05794676f2628bc963e2/</guid><description>The ban on all Russian-registered planes is in response to the Kremlin&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights We and our partners use technologies such as cookies to give you the best online experience and to personalise the content and advertising shown to you. These settings apply to AMP pages only. You can choose not to receive personalised ads by clicking “Reject data collection and continue” in the footer of the page. You may be asked to set these preferences again when you visit non-AMP pages.</description></item></channel></rss>