<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>military on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/military/</link><description>Recent content in military on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:17:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/military/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Air Force cadets who refused Covid vaccine won’t be commissioned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bc15f2c70ed12b11701dd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 17:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bc15f2c70ed12b11701dd/</guid><description>Three cadets at the U.S. Air Force Academy who have refused the Covid-19 vaccine will not be commissioned as military officers, the academy said Saturday.
Highlights The Air Force is the only military academy, so far, where cadets are not being commissioned due to vaccine refusal. The Naval Academy in Annapolis, Maryland, said Saturday that none of the Navy or Marine Corps seniors there are being prevented from commissioning. A fourth cadet who had refused the vaccine until about a week ago, decided to be vaccinated and will graduate and become an Air Force officer.</description></item><item><title>AP News: Independent probe points to Israeli fire in journalist death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281c6e961192b99ec3c8a89/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 03:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281c6e961192b99ec3c8a89/</guid><description>JERUSALEM (AP) — As Israel and the Palestinians wrangle over the investigation into the killing of Al Jazeera journalist Shireen Abu Akleh, several independent groups have launched their own probes.
Highlights Shireen Abu Akleh was shot and killed while covering an Israeli raid in the occupied West Bank. She was a household name across the Arab world, known for documenting the hardship of Palestinian life under Israeli rule. Israel and Palestinians are locked in a war of narratives that already has put Israel on the defensive.</description></item><item><title>Maj. Gen. William Cooley guilty of sexual contact charge in first military trial of an Air Force general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264eb4f26b0ed06a2089e71/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264eb4f26b0ed06a2089e71/</guid><description>An Air Force major general in Ohio has been convicted by a military judge of one of three specifications of abusive sexual contact in the
Highlights Maj. Gen. William Cooley was convicted of one of three specifications of abusive sexual contact in the first-ever military trial of an Air Force general. Officials said the verdict marks the first court-martial trial and conviction of a general officer in the Air Force’s 75-year history.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine rejects deadline to surrender in Mariupol as Russia threatens to eliminate resistance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c597b9b07feed7b6ad22c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c597b9b07feed7b6ad22c/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces besieged in Mariupol have rejected Russia&amp;rsquo;s demands to surrender and are still resisting an unrelenting assault on the southeastern port city, top Ukrainian officials said on Sunday.
Highlights NEW: Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s prime minister says &amp;ldquo;not one big city in Ukraine has fallen&amp;rdquo; NEW: He says more than 900 cities, towns and villages have been freed from Russian occupation since Moscow took control. Russia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Defense called on the Ukrainian soldiers still in Mariupol to surrender by 1 p.</description></item><item><title>US military confirms an interstellar meteor collided with Earth in 2014</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258651e2ba2db304919bd9d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258651e2ba2db304919bd9d/</guid><description>A meteor crashed into the Pacific Ocean in 2014, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t until Harvard scientists researched its velocity and trajectory five years later that they learned it came from outside our solar system.
Highlights Researchers discovered the first known interstellar meteor to hit Earth. Amir Siraj identified the object as an interstellar meteor in a study co-authored by Harvard University. The meteor was moving at a high speed of about 28 miles per second (45 kilometers per second) relative to the sun.</description></item><item><title>Israeli forces shoot 3 Palestinians, kill at least 2</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254378a6af04a52c420a862/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 14:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254378a6af04a52c420a862/</guid><description>TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israeli forces shot and killed two Palestinians, including an unarmed woman, in confrontations across Israel and the occupied West Bank on Sunday, Israeli and Palestinian officials said.
Highlights Israeli forces shoot and kill two Palestinians, including an unarmed woman, in confrontations across Israel and the occupied West Bank. The shootings came as Israeli troops combed the northern West Bank city of Jenin and the surrounding area, home to two of the Palestinians who staged deadly attacks against Israelis in recent weeks.</description></item><item><title>US official: Russia appoints new Ukraine war commander</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253f14366b76509ed863537/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253f14366b76509ed863537/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Russia has tapped a new Ukraine war commander to take centralized control of the next phase of battle after its costly failures in the opening campaign and carnage for Ukrainian civilians.
Highlights Russia has appointed Gen. Alexander Dvornikov as commander of an armed campaign that Russian authorities still refer to as a “special military operation&amp;quot; U.S. officials don’t see one man making a difference in Moscow’s prospects. The White House national security adviser, Jake Sullivan, said “no appointment of any general can erase the fact that Russia has already faced a strategic failure in Ukraine” The decision to establish new battlefield leadership comes as Russia gears up for what is expected to be a large and more focused push to expand Russian control in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s east and south, including the Donbas, and follows a failed opening bid in the north.</description></item><item><title>NATO plans permanent military presence at border, says Stoltenberg</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625302e36261093bf9f50c39/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625302e36261093bf9f50c39/</guid><description>NATO is working on plans for a permanent military presence on its border in an effort to battle future Russian aggression, The Telegraph reported, citing NATO Secretary-General Jens Stoltenberg.
Highlights NATO is working on plans for a permanent military presence on its border in an effort to battle future Russian aggression, The Telegraph reports. NATO Secretary-General Jens Stoltenberg said NATO was &amp;ldquo;in the midst of a very fundamental transformation&amp;rdquo; that will reflect &amp;ldquo;the long-term consequences&amp;rdquo; of Russian President Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s actions.</description></item><item><title>US disrupts global ‘botnet’ controlled by Russian military intelligence, DoJ says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ef163a3c291e3a4badefb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 14:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ef163a3c291e3a4badefb/</guid><description>Attorney general also announces charges against Russian oligarch Konstantin Malofeyev for sanctions violations
Highlights US has disrupted a global “botnet’ controlled by Russia’s military intelligence agency. Attorney General Merrick Garland also announced charges against Russian oligarch Konstantin Malofeyev for sanctions violations. TV producer John Hanick, 71, a US citizen charged with violations of sanctions and false statements. The indictment is the first of a Russian oligarchs in the US since the Russian invasion of Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops have accidentally shot down own aircraft and refused to carry out orders, UK spy chief to reveal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62453855b76e69931714b0bb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62453855b76e69931714b0bb/</guid><description>Sir Jeremy Fleming, the head of GCHQ, used the rare public speech to say it increasingly looks like Russia&amp;rsquo;s President Vladimir Putin &amp;quot;has massively misjudged the situation&amp;quot; in Ukraine.
Highlights He said: &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve seen that we have seen that he looks to be taking it up a gear,&amp;rdquo; he said. He also added: &amp;ldquo;They are looking at the nature of the human body&amp;rdquo; as well as the physical condition of the body.</description></item><item><title>Russia starts military drill on disputed islands off Japan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ebd12f9028d36c83a5bb2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 07:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ebd12f9028d36c83a5bb2/</guid><description>The Russian military starts a military exercise involving more than 3,000 troops on a chain of islands including those disputed with Japan, Russian news agency Interfax reports.
Highlights It is the first drill on the disputed islands off Japan&amp;rsquo;s northernmost main island of Hokkaido since Russia&amp;rsquo;s Foreign Ministry announced earlier this week it will suspend territorial talks with Japan. Some hundreds of military vehicles are participating in the drill under a scenario of launching a counterattack against enemy forces attempting to land.</description></item><item><title>Mounting Russian casualties in Ukraine lead to more questions about its military readiness</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623468cec5edbbb8f2a9a9f4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 11:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623468cec5edbbb8f2a9a9f4/</guid><description>Thousands of Russian troops have been killed in Ukraine since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion began nearly one month ago, US and NATO officials told CNN this week, and Russia is now struggling to resupply those forces as it faces sagging troop morale and fierce Ukrainian resistance.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s offensive to capture Kyiv has largely stalled, NATO officials say. Russia is now struggling to resupply its troops as it faces sagging troop morale and fierce Ukrainian resistance.</description></item><item><title>UN court orders Russia to cease hostilities in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62326ef287617621e7642c05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 23:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62326ef287617621e7642c05/</guid><description>THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The United Nations’ highest court on Wednesday ordered Russia to stop hostilities in Ukraine, granting measures requested by Kyiv although many are skeptical that Russia will comply.
Highlights The International Court of Justice ordered Russia to stop hostilities in Ukraine, granting measures requested by Kyiv. Russia snubbed a hearing last week, when lawyers for Ukraine told the court that Russia had started an “unprovoked aggression” The court also told Moscow to ensure military units “take no steps” to further the conflict, which Russia refers to as a “special military operation’s.</description></item><item><title>Russia has requested military and economic assistance from China, US officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fe2fcb78c52ee299bcc3f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fe2fcb78c52ee299bcc3f/</guid><description>Russia has asked China for military support, including drones, as well as economic assistance for its unprovoked invasion of Ukraine, according to conversations CNN had with two US officials.
Highlights NEW: China says it was not asked by Russia for military equipment or other assistance. NEW: Chinese and Russian governments deny that the request happened. Russia expanded its offensive to western Ukraine on Sunday, firing missiles near Lviv and hitting a large military base.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine still has 'significant majority' of its military aircraft -U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223455e5b1741458a5adda2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223455e5b1741458a5adda2/</guid><description>Ukraine still has a &amp;quot;significant majority&amp;quot; of its military aircraft available nine days after Russian forces started their invasion of the country, a U.S. defense official said on Friday.
Highlights Ukraine still has a “significant majority” of its military aircraft available nine days after Russian forces started their invasion of the country, a U.S. defense official said on Friday. The Pentagon has established a new hotline with Russia’s ministry of defense to prevent “miscalculation, military incidents and escalation” in the region.</description></item><item><title>UK announces first wave of sanctions against Belarus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:12:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f50e6776385d6ea2fdd25/</guid><description>Senior military figures targeted for role in joining and facilitating Russian invasion of Ukraine
Highlights Belarusian chief of the general staff, Maj Gen Victor Gulevich, and three other deputy defence ministers will all face sanctions, along with two military enterprises. Belarus has been used as a base for Russian soldiers to pour into Ukraine. US Treasury this week designated two large state-owned banks in Belarus, Belinvestbank and Dabrabyt, as subject to sanctions.</description></item><item><title>UK to impose sanctions on Russia over ‘attack on Ukraine’s sovereignty’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214ef4f2af705c3e3ca77ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214ef4f2af705c3e3ca77ac/</guid><description>Boris Johnson announces plans after Vladimir Putin backs independence for breakaway states and sends troops into Ukrainian territory
Highlights UK to sign off a package of sanctions against Russia on Tuesday morning. Initial signs were that the package would target ‘those complicit in the violation of Ukraine’s territorial integrity’ Russia has massed about 190,000 troops – with separatists accounting for another 30,000. The UK has been in close discussions with the EU and the US about launching coordinated sanctions.</description></item><item><title>RAF in second 'unidentified aircraft' alert</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd25f5dbedc148cea47e43/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 13:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd25f5dbedc148cea47e43/</guid><description>RAF fighters tracked two aircraft a day after intercepting four Russian planes north of Scotland.
Highlights RAF fighters tracked two Russian aircraft a day after intercepting four Russian planes north of Scotland. RAF jets shadowed the Russian aircraft as they travelled through international airspace &amp;ldquo;within the UK&amp;rsquo;s area of interest&amp;rdquo; The Russian planes did not enter UK airspace, but did not into UK airspace. RAF fighter jets tracked two aircraft in a day and intercepted four planes north-east of Scotland on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Biden admin warns that serious Russian combat forces have gathered near Ukraine in last 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f35c6774ec6a42b43d18ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f35c6774ec6a42b43d18ae/</guid><description>Asked about a timeline, Kirby said: &amp;lsquo;We have always said and said for quite some time, another incursion by Russia could be imminent &amp;ndash; and imminent means imminent.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights AdvertisementPresident Joe Biden reportedly told Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Thursday to brace his country for a certain Russian invasion. &amp;lsquo;President Biden reaffirmed the readiness of the United States along with its allies and partners to respond decisively if Russia further invades Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan detects 39 Chinese warplanes, scrambles jets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee86c9e9f7489b0e0ad76d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee86c9e9f7489b0e0ad76d/</guid><description>Dozens of Chinese jets entered Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s air defense zone, the island&amp;rsquo;s officials said. Taiwan responded by scrambling its own fighter jets and activating missile defense systems.
Summary Taiwan reported on Sunday that 39 Chinese warplanes, including a bomber, were detected in the south-western Air Defense Identification Zone (ADIZ). The island&amp;rsquo;s ministry of defense said 34 fighter aircraft and an H-6 bomber were among the aircraft involved in the incursion. According to flight paths the ministry officials posted online, Chinese aircraft flew to the northeast of the Taiwan-controlled Pratas Island.</description></item><item><title>UK sends 30 elite troops and 2,000 anti-tank weapons to Ukraine amid fears of Russian invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 04:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</guid><description>British surveillance aircraft have also been spotted as part of a quiet but notable build-up of support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s military by the UK.
Summary A group of around 30 elite British troops has arrived in Ukraine to help train the Ukrainian armed forces on new anti-tank weapons gifted by the UK amid fears of an imminent, new Russian invasion, Sky News understands. Open source flight-tracking software has plotted Royal Air Force C-17 transport aircraft flying back and forth between the UK and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Canada's military launches formal proceedings against more than 900 unvaccinated troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2b796d16322b65e0197f3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2b796d16322b65e0197f3/</guid><description>Summary OTTAWA — The Department of National Defence says proceedings have been launched against more than 900 Canadian Armed Forces members for refusing to get vaccinated, though none have yet been forced to hang up their uniforms. While most Armed Forces members complied with the order, with the Defence Department reporting a 98.3 per cent vaccination rate among Canadian troops, hundreds of others did not. According to the Defence Department’s latest statistics, by the end of December, more than 830 Armed Forces members had received formal warnings, orders to attend counselling and probation for refusing to get jabbed.</description></item><item><title>Veterans ask Queen to strip Prince Andrew of honorary military titles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</guid><description>Duke will no longer use HRH title in any official capacity, and will fight US sexual assault lawsuit as private citizen
Summary In a devastating blow to Prince Andrew, who was born His Royal Highness, Buckingham Palace also said he would no longer use the HRH royal style in any official capacity. Buckingham Palace said in a statement on Thursday: “With the Queen’s approval and agreement, the Duke of York’s military affiliations and royal patronages have been returned to the Queen.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: NATO prepares for possible Russian invasion as diplomats fear talks will fail | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</guid><description>There are fears Vladimir Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war - with a Ukrainian source saying they expect any Russian attack would be intense but limited.
Summary That was the warning from Jens Stoltenberg, the head of the NATO alliance, which is braced for the possibility of a further Russian invasion of the vast eastern European state. A fear among western diplomats is that President Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war, eight years on from his annexation of Crimea and the backing of an insurgency in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia withdraws portion of troops from border with Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c794791b59df1531ba3f00/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 22:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c794791b59df1531ba3f00/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Military District is returning 10,000 troops to their permanent bases after a month of
Summary Russia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Military District is returning 10,000 troops to their permanent bases after a month of &amp;ldquo;field training.&amp;rdquo; The military are returning after exercises at the Astrakhan, Volgograd and Rostov regions, the Stavropol and Krasnodar regions, the North Caucasus, and Russia&amp;rsquo;s military bases in Armenia, occupied Crimea, Abkhazia and South Ossetia, the report said.</description></item></channel></rss>