<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>military on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/military/</link><description>Recent content in military on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 12:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/military/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canada's military launches formal proceedings against more than 900 unvaccinated troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2b796d16322b65e0197f3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2b796d16322b65e0197f3/</guid><description>Summary OTTAWA — The Department of National Defence says proceedings have been launched against more than 900 Canadian Armed Forces members for refusing to get vaccinated, though none have yet been forced to hang up their uniforms. While most Armed Forces members complied with the order, with the Defence Department reporting a 98.3 per cent vaccination rate among Canadian troops, hundreds of others did not. According to the Defence Department’s latest statistics, by the end of December, more than 830 Armed Forces members had received formal warnings, orders to attend counselling and probation for refusing to get jabbed.</description></item><item><title>Veterans ask Queen to strip Prince Andrew of honorary military titles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</guid><description>Duke will no longer use HRH title in any official capacity, and will fight US sexual assault lawsuit as private citizen
Summary In a devastating blow to Prince Andrew, who was born His Royal Highness, Buckingham Palace also said he would no longer use the HRH royal style in any official capacity. Buckingham Palace said in a statement on Thursday: “With the Queen’s approval and agreement, the Duke of York’s military affiliations and royal patronages have been returned to the Queen.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: NATO prepares for possible Russian invasion as diplomats fear talks will fail | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</guid><description>There are fears Vladimir Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war - with a Ukrainian source saying they expect any Russian attack would be intense but limited.
Summary That was the warning from Jens Stoltenberg, the head of the NATO alliance, which is braced for the possibility of a further Russian invasion of the vast eastern European state. A fear among western diplomats is that President Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war, eight years on from his annexation of Crimea and the backing of an insurgency in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia withdraws portion of troops from border with Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c794791b59df1531ba3f00/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 22:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c794791b59df1531ba3f00/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Military District is returning 10,000 troops to their permanent bases after a month of
Summary Russia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Military District is returning 10,000 troops to their permanent bases after a month of &amp;ldquo;field training.&amp;rdquo; The military are returning after exercises at the Astrakhan, Volgograd and Rostov regions, the Stavropol and Krasnodar regions, the North Caucasus, and Russia&amp;rsquo;s military bases in Armenia, occupied Crimea, Abkhazia and South Ossetia, the report said.</description></item></channel></rss>