<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>military on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/military/</link><description>Recent content in military on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 13:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/military/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RAF in second 'unidentified aircraft' alert</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd25f5dbedc148cea47e43/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 13:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd25f5dbedc148cea47e43/</guid><description>RAF fighters tracked two aircraft a day after intercepting four Russian planes north of Scotland.
Highlights RAF fighters tracked two Russian aircraft a day after intercepting four Russian planes north of Scotland. RAF jets shadowed the Russian aircraft as they travelled through international airspace &amp;ldquo;within the UK&amp;rsquo;s area of interest&amp;rdquo; The Russian planes did not enter UK airspace, but did not into UK airspace. RAF fighter jets tracked two aircraft in a day and intercepted four planes north-east of Scotland on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Biden admin warns that serious Russian combat forces have gathered near Ukraine in last 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f35c6774ec6a42b43d18ae/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f35c6774ec6a42b43d18ae/</guid><description>Asked about a timeline, Kirby said: &amp;lsquo;We have always said and said for quite some time, another incursion by Russia could be imminent &amp;ndash; and imminent means imminent.&amp;rsquo;
Highlights AdvertisementPresident Joe Biden reportedly told Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Thursday to brace his country for a certain Russian invasion. &amp;lsquo;President Biden reaffirmed the readiness of the United States along with its allies and partners to respond decisively if Russia further invades Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan detects 39 Chinese warplanes, scrambles jets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee86c9e9f7489b0e0ad76d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee86c9e9f7489b0e0ad76d/</guid><description>Dozens of Chinese jets entered Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s air defense zone, the island&amp;rsquo;s officials said. Taiwan responded by scrambling its own fighter jets and activating missile defense systems.
Summary Taiwan reported on Sunday that 39 Chinese warplanes, including a bomber, were detected in the south-western Air Defense Identification Zone (ADIZ). The island&amp;rsquo;s ministry of defense said 34 fighter aircraft and an H-6 bomber were among the aircraft involved in the incursion. According to flight paths the ministry officials posted online, Chinese aircraft flew to the northeast of the Taiwan-controlled Pratas Island.</description></item><item><title>UK sends 30 elite troops and 2,000 anti-tank weapons to Ukraine amid fears of Russian invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 04:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</guid><description>British surveillance aircraft have also been spotted as part of a quiet but notable build-up of support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s military by the UK.
Summary A group of around 30 elite British troops has arrived in Ukraine to help train the Ukrainian armed forces on new anti-tank weapons gifted by the UK amid fears of an imminent, new Russian invasion, Sky News understands. Open source flight-tracking software has plotted Royal Air Force C-17 transport aircraft flying back and forth between the UK and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Canada's military launches formal proceedings against more than 900 unvaccinated troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2b796d16322b65e0197f3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2b796d16322b65e0197f3/</guid><description>Summary OTTAWA — The Department of National Defence says proceedings have been launched against more than 900 Canadian Armed Forces members for refusing to get vaccinated, though none have yet been forced to hang up their uniforms. While most Armed Forces members complied with the order, with the Defence Department reporting a 98.3 per cent vaccination rate among Canadian troops, hundreds of others did not. According to the Defence Department’s latest statistics, by the end of December, more than 830 Armed Forces members had received formal warnings, orders to attend counselling and probation for refusing to get jabbed.</description></item><item><title>Veterans ask Queen to strip Prince Andrew of honorary military titles</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e092fdfdb6e94cc6539518/</guid><description>Duke will no longer use HRH title in any official capacity, and will fight US sexual assault lawsuit as private citizen
Summary In a devastating blow to Prince Andrew, who was born His Royal Highness, Buckingham Palace also said he would no longer use the HRH royal style in any official capacity. Buckingham Palace said in a statement on Thursday: “With the Queen’s approval and agreement, the Duke of York’s military affiliations and royal patronages have been returned to the Queen.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: NATO prepares for possible Russian invasion as diplomats fear talks will fail | World News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc03c89bf259ab8b2bccb3/</guid><description>There are fears Vladimir Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war - with a Ukrainian source saying they expect any Russian attack would be intense but limited.
Summary That was the warning from Jens Stoltenberg, the head of the NATO alliance, which is braced for the possibility of a further Russian invasion of the vast eastern European state. A fear among western diplomats is that President Putin intends for the talks to fail to create a pretext for war, eight years on from his annexation of Crimea and the backing of an insurgency in eastern Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Russia withdraws portion of troops from border with Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c794791b59df1531ba3f00/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 22:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c794791b59df1531ba3f00/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Military District is returning 10,000 troops to their permanent bases after a month of
Summary Russia&amp;rsquo;s Southern Military District is returning 10,000 troops to their permanent bases after a month of &amp;ldquo;field training.&amp;rdquo; The military are returning after exercises at the Astrakhan, Volgograd and Rostov regions, the Stavropol and Krasnodar regions, the North Caucasus, and Russia&amp;rsquo;s military bases in Armenia, occupied Crimea, Abkhazia and South Ossetia, the report said.</description></item></channel></rss>