<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>market on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/market/</link><description>Recent content in market on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:58:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>40% of bitcoin investors are now underwater, new data shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279b885339a1ae9fbeac6d0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279b885339a1ae9fbeac6d0/</guid><description>Bitcoin is off nearly 55% from its November peak, and 40% of holders are now underwater on their investments, according to new data from Glassnode.
Highlights Bitcoin is off nearly 55% from its November peak, and 40% of holders are now underwater on their investments. In the last month alone, 15.5% of all bitcoin wallets fell into an unrealized loss. More than $3.15 billion in value moved into or out of exchanges, the largest amount since market hit its all-time high in November 2021.</description></item><item><title>Citigroup causes a "flash crash" in European stock markets; one index loses nearly 8% in minutes.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627227940c76dff91dac4205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627227940c76dff91dac4205/</guid><description>Inputting mistake led to suspension of trading on several markets after sudden steep falls
Highlights Trading was briefly suspended in several European markets after sudden steep declines. Europe Stoxx 600 index of leading shares lost as much as 3% before closing down 1.5%. One of the hardest hit was Sweden’s benchmark OMX 30 index, which fell by nearly 8%, but recouped most of the losses and ended the day 1.9% lower.</description></item><item><title>S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones to remove all Russian stocks from indices and strip country of emerging market status</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622337aae23d82a79a5d393f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 10:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622337aae23d82a79a5d393f/</guid><description>Further isolation from global economy effective from before market opens on Wednesday
Highlights S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones announces it will remove all stocks listed or domiciled in Russia from its benchmark indices. The move is just the latest measure put in place to punish Russia economically for its invasion of Ukraine. Russia will be further isolated from the global economy by its declassification as an emerging market, effective from Wednesday. After that it will be categorised as a standalone group after the 2023 review.</description></item></channel></rss>