<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ron on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ron/</link><description>Recent content in ron on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 01:02:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ron/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ban on protests in front of homes signed by Gov. DeSantis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282f3f312e8507aa5dab823/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 01:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282f3f312e8507aa5dab823/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Anyone who protests in front of a private residence in Florida can face jail time and fines under a bill Republican Gov. Ron DeSantis signed Monday. The legislation makes it a second-degree misdemeanor to protest in a manner that is aimed at intentionally harassing or disturbing someone in their home.
Highlights Ban on protests in front of homes signed by Gov. DeSantis. Florida governor said the new law will prevent protests in Florida like those waged by abortion rights protesters.</description></item><item><title>‘Don’t Say Gay’ bill signed by Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624217413a25172f5258a9ff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624217413a25172f5258a9ff/</guid><description>TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed a bill on Monday that forbids instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade, a policy that has drawn intense national scrutiny from critics who argue it marginalizes LGBTQ people.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signs a bill that forbids instruction on sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade. Critics say the bill marginalizes LGBTQ people, marginalizes them.</description></item></channel></rss>