<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>20 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/20/</link><description>Recent content in 20 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:13:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/20/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Official Age of Adulthood in Japan Lowered to 18</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</guid><description>The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. This makes it possible for 18- or 19-year-olds to sign a smartphone contract or take out a loan without parental consent, but also means that they need to take responsibility for such decisions.
Highlights The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. It means that 18- or 19-year-olds will be able to sign a contract for a smartphone or credit card, lease an apartment, or enter an expensive loan contract for an automobile or English conversation school, without parental consent.</description></item><item><title>Former youth pastor sentenced to 20 years in prison for molesting boys</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d801c856f92725587ce788/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d801c856f92725587ce788/</guid><description>A former Indiana youth pastor was sentenced to 20 years in prison Wednesday for molesting boys between the ages of 11 and 13 for years, court officials said.
Summary A former Indiana youth pastor was sentenced to 20 years in prison for molesting 11- to 13-year-old boys for years, court officials said. Former youth pastor Scott Christner. Christner molested several boys ages 11 to 13 beginning in May 2012, NBC affiliate WNDU of South Bend reported.</description></item></channel></rss>