<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>20 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/20/</link><description>Recent content in 20 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 22:09:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/20/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emmett grandmother gets up to 20 years after granddaughter found dead in trash bag</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628962ff1e2fe405912b6987/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 22:09:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628962ff1e2fe405912b6987/</guid><description>An Emmett woman accused of failing to notify authorities of her granddaughter&amp;rsquo;s death last year has been sentenced to up to 20 years. Earlier this year, Connie Ann Smith pleaded guilty to felony injury to a child and failure to notify of a death. She is the grandmother of 8-year-old Taryn Summers&amp;rsquo; (aka Quinton), whose remains were found on Smith&amp;rsquo;s property inside a trash bag on April 14. She&amp;rsquo;ll have to serve a minimum of five years before she&amp;rsquo;ll be eligible for parole, court records state.</description></item><item><title>Apple has discontinued the iPod, 20 years after it was released</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ac7f66a0d4aee160bf3a0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ac7f66a0d4aee160bf3a0/</guid><description>The iPod, the first MP3 player that could hold 1,000 songs and had a 10-hour battery life, transformed how we listen to music.The US tech giant said its iconic music player had now been made redundant by phones that could also play music.
Highlights Apple has discontinued the iPod, 20 years after it was released. US tech giant said its iconic music player has been replaced by other devices. iPod was the first MP3 player that could hold 1,000 songs and had a 10-hour battery life.</description></item><item><title>Official Age of Adulthood in Japan Lowered to 18</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246de4732f846f7a67b48b7/</guid><description>The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. This makes it possible for 18- or 19-year-olds to sign a smartphone contract or take out a loan without parental consent, but also means that they need to take responsibility for such decisions.
Highlights The age of adulthood in Japan was lowered from 20 to 18 on April 1, 2022. It means that 18- or 19-year-olds will be able to sign a contract for a smartphone or credit card, lease an apartment, or enter an expensive loan contract for an automobile or English conversation school, without parental consent.</description></item><item><title>Former youth pastor sentenced to 20 years in prison for molesting boys</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d801c856f92725587ce788/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d801c856f92725587ce788/</guid><description>A former Indiana youth pastor was sentenced to 20 years in prison Wednesday for molesting boys between the ages of 11 and 13 for years, court officials said.
Summary A former Indiana youth pastor was sentenced to 20 years in prison for molesting 11- to 13-year-old boys for years, court officials said. Former youth pastor Scott Christner. Christner molested several boys ages 11 to 13 beginning in May 2012, NBC affiliate WNDU of South Bend reported.</description></item></channel></rss>