<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>black on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/black/</link><description>Recent content in black on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 05:26:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/black/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pride, Black History Month book displays among those no longer allowed at Lafayette public libraries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629849de68a5e656995eed65/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 05:26:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629849de68a5e656995eed65/</guid><description>Book displays highlighting controversial topics or specific segments of the population such as Pride Month, Black History Month, Women&amp;rsquo;s History Month, Native American history and Cajun heritage are no longer
Highlights Book displays highlighting controversial topics or specific segments of the population no longer exist. Pride Month, Black History Month, Women&amp;rsquo;s History Month and Native American history and Cajun heritage are no longer. Book displays no longer feature controversial topics such as Native American heritage and.</description></item><item><title>Supermarket shooter sought Black neighborhood, official says | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628143bb3b525b137fdd74d5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628143bb3b525b137fdd74d5/</guid><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The white 18-year-old who shot and killed 10 people at a Buffalo supermarket had researched the local demographics while looking for places with a high concentration of Black residents, arriving there at least a day in advance to conduct reconnaissance, law enforcement officials said Sunday.
Highlights The shooter, identified as Payton Gendron, had previously threatened a shooting at his high school last June, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Louisiana State Troopers Charged in Beating of Black Man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627deec9322b8a5787b54850/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 05:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627deec9322b8a5787b54850/</guid><description>Troopers Jacob Brown, Dakota DeMoss and George “Kam” Harper were charged last week in the 2020 arrest of Antonio Harris.
Highlights State prosecutors have charged three former Louisiana State Police troopers accused of beating a Black motorist. They are accused of hoisting him to his feet by his hair braids and bragging in text messages that the “whoopin” would give him “nightmares for a long time.” The misdemeanor simple battery charges in the 2020 arrest of Antonio Harris come amid mounting scrutiny of the state’s premier law enforcement agency over allegations of excessive force.</description></item><item><title>Turkey defuses mine after Russia warns of strays from Ukraine ports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f8fc509f15f9d5ca3e169/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 22:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f8fc509f15f9d5ca3e169/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s military deactivated a mine on Saturday that had drifted in from the Black Sea, setting off a loud explosion north of Istanbul, days after Russia warned several of them had washed away from Ukrainian ports.
Highlights Turkey&amp;rsquo;s military deactivated a mine that had drifted in from the Black Sea, setting off a loud explosion north of Istanbul. The mine was first discovered by fishermen in the upper Bosphorus strait. Russia warned several of them had washed away from Ukrainian ports earlier this month.</description></item><item><title>Black man grabbing tea from car shot by New Jersey police and paralyzed, lawsuit says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62354a47f05cf05715d21fc8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62354a47f05cf05715d21fc8/</guid><description>Jajuan R. Henderson, 29, was unarmed and grabbing an iced tea before he was paralyzed by Trenton police on Feb. 12, a lawsuit alleges.
Highlights Jajuan R. Henderson, 29, was getting the drink from a Saturn Ion parked outside of his home shortly after midnight on Feb. 12 in Trenton, New Jersey. A group of men in dark clothing and masks driving an unidentified vehicle boxed in the Saturn, which was parallel parked, according to the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Black man's death in Indiana ruled a lynching nearly 100 years later</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ff695d86a10484277cc20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ff695d86a10484277cc20/</guid><description>The death of a young Black man who was found hanging from a tree in Indiana nearly 100 years ago has finally been ruled a lynching, officials said.
Highlights George Tompkins&amp;rsquo; hands had been bound behind his back, but his death was ruled a suicide in 1922. Marion County Deputy Chief Coroner Alfie McGinty: &amp;ldquo;We will bring justice to something that was unconscionable to me&amp;rdquo; The U.S. Senate only last week gave final passage to a bill to make lynching a federal crime.</description></item><item><title>‘Plain old racist’: teen in New Jersey mall fight condemns arrest of Black youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 12:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</guid><description>Youth, 15, was shoved to couch but not restrained while 14-year-old was handcuffed in incident that went viral
Highlights Video of incident involving Black 14-year-old went viral last week. Teen says police treated him differently than the other boy in the altercation. Incident prompted calls for police to be disciplined for racially disparate treatment. Family and friends of the teen held a protest in front of police headquarters on Saturday. Governor of New Jersey said the incident was &amp;lsquo;deeply disturbing&amp;rsquo; and showed &amp;lsquo;progress we&amp;rsquo;ve made on relationships between law enforcement and community they serve&amp;rsquo; The incident prompted an internal affairs investigation and calls for disciplining the officers involved.</description></item><item><title>Rapper Kodak Black, three others shot in West Hollywood</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62094a2b3cccc834ee4c0043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 18:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62094a2b3cccc834ee4c0043/</guid><description>Kodak Black was among four people shot early Saturday outside a restaurant in West Hollywood, California. Justin Bieber was hosting an after party inside the restaurant on the night of the shooting.
Highlights The 24-year-old Florida rapper and three others were shot; two were taken by ambulance and two self-transported to a hospital. Police are searching for a black male suspect who fled south from the location. It is not immediately clear what sparked the fight outside the club in the 400 block of N.</description></item><item><title>A Tennessee woman allegedly chopped her dad with an ax and punched her grandpa in the face before they disarmed and subdued her, according to authorities.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eeb0faae75e339813113e9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 14:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eeb0faae75e339813113e9/</guid><description>A Tennessee woman allegedly chopped her dad with an ax and punched her grandpa in the face before they disarmed and subdued her, according to authorities.
Summary Nevada Fortson, a 25-year-old Elizabethton resident, faces charges of aggravated assault, aggravated burglary, violating an order of protection and resisting arrest in Carter County. (Carter County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office)FLORIDA WOMAN PLEADS GUILTY TO BITCOIN MURDER-FOR-HIRE PLOT&amp;quot;Look what you got us into now,&amp;quot; he told the passenger.</description></item></channel></rss>