<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>black on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/black/</link><description>Recent content in black on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:15:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/black/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black man's death in Indiana ruled a lynching nearly 100 years later</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ff695d86a10484277cc20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ff695d86a10484277cc20/</guid><description>The death of a young Black man who was found hanging from a tree in Indiana nearly 100 years ago has finally been ruled a lynching, officials said.
Highlights George Tompkins&amp;rsquo; hands had been bound behind his back, but his death was ruled a suicide in 1922. Marion County Deputy Chief Coroner Alfie McGinty: &amp;ldquo;We will bring justice to something that was unconscionable to me&amp;rdquo; The U.S. Senate only last week gave final passage to a bill to make lynching a federal crime.</description></item><item><title>‘Plain old racist’: teen in New Jersey mall fight condemns arrest of Black youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 12:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</guid><description>Youth, 15, was shoved to couch but not restrained while 14-year-old was handcuffed in incident that went viral
Highlights Video of incident involving Black 14-year-old went viral last week. Teen says police treated him differently than the other boy in the altercation. Incident prompted calls for police to be disciplined for racially disparate treatment. Family and friends of the teen held a protest in front of police headquarters on Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Rapper Kodak Black, three others shot in West Hollywood</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62094a2b3cccc834ee4c0043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 18:13:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62094a2b3cccc834ee4c0043/</guid><description>Kodak Black was among four people shot early Saturday outside a restaurant in West Hollywood, California. Justin Bieber was hosting an after party inside the restaurant on the night of the shooting.
Highlights The 24-year-old Florida rapper and three others were shot; two were taken by ambulance and two self-transported to a hospital. Police are searching for a black male suspect who fled south from the location. It is not immediately clear what sparked the fight outside the club in the 400 block of N.</description></item><item><title>A Tennessee woman allegedly chopped her dad with an ax and punched her grandpa in the face before they disarmed and subdued her, according to authorities.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eeb0faae75e339813113e9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 14:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eeb0faae75e339813113e9/</guid><description>A Tennessee woman allegedly chopped her dad with an ax and punched her grandpa in the face before they disarmed and subdued her, according to authorities.
Summary Nevada Fortson, a 25-year-old Elizabethton resident, faces charges of aggravated assault, aggravated burglary, violating an order of protection and resisting arrest in Carter County. (Carter County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office)FLORIDA WOMAN PLEADS GUILTY TO BITCOIN MURDER-FOR-HIRE PLOT&amp;quot;Look what you got us into now,&amp;quot; he told the passenger.</description></item></channel></rss>