<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>early on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/early/</link><description>Recent content in early on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 22:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/early/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An Indiana teacher granted early retirement after hitting a student in the face is charged with battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223e0464af0841f6b89842e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223e0464af0841f6b89842e/</guid><description>A now-retired Indiana high school teacher who was arrested after video showed him hitting a student during a confrontation over wearing a hooded sweatshirt on school grounds was charged Friday with battery, according to court documents.
Highlights Michael Hosinski, 61, was arrested after video showed him hitting a student during a confrontation over wearing a hooded sweatshirt on school grounds. The incident occurred February 25 at Jimtown High School in Elkhart, Indiana.</description></item><item><title>President Bolsonaro admitted to São Paulo hospital</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d39c3079c839bfce5cb49e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d39c3079c839bfce5cb49e/</guid><description>Bolsonaro left the Santa Catarina coast by helicopter bound for Joinville, plane with his wife Michelle Bolsonaro
Summary The President&amp;rsquo;s doctor says he was hospitalized early this morning with suspected intestinal obstruction. RIO DE JANEIRO, BRAZIL - Bolsonaro left the Santa Catarina coast by helicopter bound for Joinville, where he boarded the presidential plane with his wife Michelle Bolsonaro and daughter Laura. According to reports, Bolsonaro is in the Vila Nova Star Hospital in São Paulo.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee Planned Parenthood destroyed in early morning fire | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cffc0c5f05cd0807de044f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 07:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cffc0c5f05cd0807de044f/</guid><description>KNOXVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee Planned Parenthood building was destroyed by an early morning fire on Friday, Planned Parenthood officials said. Knoxville Fire Department crews were called about 6:40 a.m.
Summary Firefighters spray water to put out a fire at the Planned Parenthood building in Knoxville, Tenn., on Friday, Dec. 31, 2021. The fire comes as the U.S. Supreme Court considers a case that could severely curtail abortion rights that have stood for half a century.</description></item></channel></rss>