<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>money on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/money/</link><description>Recent content in money on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man mistakenly sent 46.3 mil. yen in COVID funds gambles it all away</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283cb2bdc47f448629ccd87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 16:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283cb2bdc47f448629ccd87/</guid><description>A 24-year-old man mistakenly sent 46.3 million yen ($360,000) in COVID-19 relief money by the western Japan town he resides in, says he gambled it all away on overseas casino sites, sources close to the matter say.
Highlights A 24-year-old man mistakenly sent 46.3 million yen ($360,000) in COVID-19 relief money by the western Japan town he resides in, says he gambled it all away on overseas casino sites. The man is unlikely to be able to return the money transferred to him in error by the town of Abu, Yamaguchi Prefecture, according to his lawyer.</description></item><item><title>Two plead guilty to pocketing funds raised for ‘We Build the Wall’ project</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62633699e17ff196aeea0c33/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 23:14:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62633699e17ff196aeea0c33/</guid><description>Co-founder of project to raise money for US-Mexico wall pleads guilty in case that once included Trump’s adviser Steve Bannon
Highlights Brian Kolfage admitted to pocketing hundreds of thousands of dollars while promising all donations would pay for the wall. Co-founder of the “We Build The Wall’s Wall” group raised more than $25m from thousands of donors as they repeatedly pledged that every dollar would be used for the project. Andrew Badolato, 57, pleaded guilty to wire fraud conspiracy and tax charges brought originally in Florida.</description></item><item><title>California cities spent huge share of federal Covid relief funds on police | US policing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625028e6189cd888fbe69a79/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 12:22:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625028e6189cd888fbe69a79/</guid><description>Records reveal that some cities gave more stimulus money to law enforcement than to health, housing and food initiatives
Highlights San Francisco allocated 49% ($153m) of federal funds on police, 13% ($41m) to the sheriff’s department, and the remainder to the fire department. Long Beach allocated the majority of its $135.8 million Arpa funds to police. Fresno allocated $36.6m of its Cares funds on the police, making up 67% of Cares spending on city salaries.</description></item><item><title>Teen is arrested after posting on social media with drugs, money, guns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62497366e3b2cc0b8df68d95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 10:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62497366e3b2cc0b8df68d95/</guid><description>SAN ANTONIO (WOAI) — Deputies arrested a teen after he posted images on social media with drugs, money and guns. Teen is arrested after posting on social media with drugs, money, and guns (Photo Courtesy of Bexar County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office) The incident happened Tuesday, March 29, when David Anakin Guerra, 17 posted on social media that he had THC cartridges, weapons and cash.
Highlights Deputies arrested a teen after he posted images on social media with drugs, money and guns.</description></item><item><title>Man used COVID loan to buy Pokémon card, sentenced to prison.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622739c4be3299fe68de2766/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 11:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622739c4be3299fe68de2766/</guid><description>A Georgia man has been sentenced to three years in prison after he used a COVID-19 relief loan to buy a rare Pokémon card, according to the Department of Justice.
Highlights Vinath Oudomsine, 31, was awarded an Economic Injury Disaster Loan (EIDL) for $85,000 after claiming to own a small business that supported 10 employees. He used $57,789 of the loan to buy a first-edition, shadowless and holographic Charizard card with a 9.</description></item><item><title>Auditor: Iowa Gov. Reynolds must return $450K in COVID funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f89779c041f9df5b3b171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 15:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f89779c041f9df5b3b171/</guid><description>Iowa’s state auditor again called for Gov. Kim Reynolds to return nearly $450,000 in federal coronavirus relief funds that were used to pay for 21 governor’s office staff members for three months in 2020
Highlights Iowa’s state auditor again called for Gov. Kim Reynolds to return nearly $450,000 in federal coronavirus relief funds. Reynolds paid salaries for 21 staff members — including her spokesman, a lawyer and her chief of staff — from March 15 to June 30, 2020, out of federal funds.</description></item><item><title>J&amp;amp;J, distributors finalize $26B landmark opioid settlement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621938516df82d6dfbff4e0f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 20:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621938516df82d6dfbff4e0f/</guid><description>CAMDEN, N.J. (AP) — Drugmaker Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson and three major distributors finalized nationwide settlements over their role in the opioid addiction crisis Friday, an announcement that clears the way for $26 billion to flow to nearly every state and local government in the U.S.
Highlights Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, AmerisourceBergen, Cardinal Health and McKesson announced the settlement plan last year. The deal was contingent on getting participation from a critical mass of state and local governments.</description></item><item><title>Major banks pledging net zero are pouring money into the dirtiest fossil fuel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c093fdcaa3b7dcf5cbd24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c093fdcaa3b7dcf5cbd24/</guid><description>Financial institutions channeled more than $1.5 trillion into the coal industry in loans and underwriting from January 2019 to November 2021, even though many have made net-zero pledges, a report by a group of 28 non-government organizations showed.
Highlights Financial institutions channeled more than $1.5 trillion into the coal industry in loans and underwriting from January 2019 to November 2021. Reducing coal use is a key part of global efforts to slash climate-warming greenhouse gases.</description></item><item><title>Detroit Police commissioner removed from towing committee after downplaying bribery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c75c3c77346718417030b3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c75c3c77346718417030b3/</guid><description>Detroit police commissioner has been unappointed from a committee overseeing the towing industry after controversial comments during a 7 Action News interview where she downplayed the gravity of bribery.
Summary DETROIT (WXYZ) — A Detroit police commissioner has been unappointed from a committee overseeing the towing industry after making controversial comments where she downplayed the seriousness of bribery. Jim Holley—the chair of the Board of Police Commissioners—removed Bernard from the board’s towing committee.</description></item></channel></rss>