<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>money on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/money/</link><description>Recent content in money on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Major banks pledging net zero are pouring money into the dirtiest fossil fuel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c093fdcaa3b7dcf5cbd24/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 20:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c093fdcaa3b7dcf5cbd24/</guid><description>Financial institutions channeled more than $1.5 trillion into the coal industry in loans and underwriting from January 2019 to November 2021, even though many have made net-zero pledges, a report by a group of 28 non-government organizations showed.
Highlights Financial institutions channeled more than $1.5 trillion into the coal industry in loans and underwriting from January 2019 to November 2021. Reducing coal use is a key part of global efforts to slash climate-warming greenhouse gases.</description></item><item><title>Detroit Police commissioner removed from towing committee after downplaying bribery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c75c3c77346718417030b3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c75c3c77346718417030b3/</guid><description>Detroit police commissioner has been unappointed from a committee overseeing the towing industry after controversial comments during a 7 Action News interview where she downplayed the gravity of bribery.
Summary DETROIT (WXYZ) — A Detroit police commissioner has been unappointed from a committee overseeing the towing industry after making controversial comments where she downplayed the seriousness of bribery. Jim Holley—the chair of the Board of Police Commissioners—removed Bernard from the board’s towing committee.</description></item></channel></rss>