<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>representatives on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/representatives/</link><description>Recent content in representatives on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 18:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/representatives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FBI: Gubernatorial candidate Ryan Kelley arrested, home searched</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a237981b0a2cc2be3c0654/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 18:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a237981b0a2cc2be3c0654/</guid><description>The FBI said that Kelley was arrested on charges relating to the Jan. 6 riot.
Highlights Ryan Kelley was arrested and a search was executed at his home Thursday morning. Kelley, 40, was among the Republican candidates looking to run in the 2022 August gubernatorial primary. He was seen at the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol, though he has said he didn&amp;rsquo;t go inside the building. An anonymous tipster pointed them toward pictures of Kelley in the crowd.</description></item><item><title>Northern Ireland election results: Sinn Féin wins most seats in historic election</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627789c4e1afacbeb0c28fbe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 09:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627789c4e1afacbeb0c28fbe/</guid><description>The party has won 27 seats in the Stormont assembly election, while the DUP returned with 25.
Highlights The party has won 27 seats in the Stormont assembly election. The DUP won the election with 25 seats, while the DUP won 25 seats. The party won 27 of the 27 seats, with the DUP winning 25, in the poll. It is now incumbent on all political parties and elected representatives to deliver on their mandate.</description></item></channel></rss>