<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>posted on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/posted/</link><description>Recent content in posted on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 17:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/posted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maker of Uvalde shooter’s rifle posted image of child with gun before massacre</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629258c016c4e415865b881e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629258c016c4e415865b881e/</guid><description>Gunmaker Daniel Defense posted online an advertising photo of a small child holding one of its AR-15-style rifles just days before one of its firearms was used in the elementary school shooting in Uvalde, Tex.
Highlights Gunmaker Daniel Defense posted the image to Twitter on May 16. The next week, a gunman used a Daniel Defense DDM4 Rifle to kill 19 children and two adults at a school in Texas. The gunmaker had planned to host an exhibitor’s booth at the upcoming National Rifle Association convention, set to begin Friday in Houston.</description></item><item><title>Teen charged in 151-mph crash that killed 6 posted Instagram videos of himself racing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626365b9b86a764fe0678c3d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 02:35:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626365b9b86a764fe0678c3d/</guid><description>A Florida teenager has been charged in the deaths of six people in a violent 151-mph crash in January, and new court documents reveal he posted himself racing at 182 mph in his luxury BWM on social media just two weeks prior.
Highlights Noah Galle, 18, was formally charged Monday with six counts of vehicular homicide in the Jan. 27 crash that killed six farm employees leaving work in Delray Beach, Florida.</description></item><item><title>US hunter fined after trophy photo proves he shot sheep in Canada | Canada</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235e4d90e454bb5cd8fbf05/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 14:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235e4d90e454bb5cd8fbf05/</guid><description>Donald Lee claimed he killed a Fannin bighorn sheep in Alaska but an online sleuth and Yukon conservation officers proved he didn’t
Highlights Donald Lee claimed he killed a bighorn sheep in Alaska but it was in Canada, not the U.S. He was fined C$8,500 and banned from hunting in Canada for five years. He posted pictures of the scene in the Yukon on social media, but officers found the sheep had been killed in Canada.</description></item></channel></rss>