<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>largest on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/largest/</link><description>Recent content in largest on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:58:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/largest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>40% of bitcoin investors are now underwater, new data shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279b885339a1ae9fbeac6d0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279b885339a1ae9fbeac6d0/</guid><description>Bitcoin is off nearly 55% from its November peak, and 40% of holders are now underwater on their investments, according to new data from Glassnode.
Highlights Bitcoin is off nearly 55% from its November peak, and 40% of holders are now underwater on their investments. In the last month alone, 15.5% of all bitcoin wallets fell into an unrealized loss. More than $3.15 billion in value moved into or out of exchanges, the largest amount since market hit its all-time high in November 2021.</description></item><item><title>Germany shuts down world's largest darknet market with US help</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d7595bdbedd604c179363/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 11:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d7595bdbedd604c179363/</guid><description>German authorities seize the server infrastructure and $25 million in bitcoin. Hydra Market was a Russian-language marketplace that had operated via the Tor network since at least 2015. Authorities said the market was being used for criminal transactions, money laundering and
Highlights German authorities say they seized Hydra&amp;rsquo;s server infrastructure and about $25 million in bitcoin. Hydra Market was a Russian-language marketplace that had operated via the Tor network since at least 2015.</description></item><item><title>Florida Mandates Personal Finance Education in High Schools</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623db8bcfa014a1a30e85ae4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623db8bcfa014a1a30e85ae4/</guid><description>On Tuesday, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed bill SB 1054, which mandates personal finance education for high school graduation.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed bill SB 1054 into law on Tuesday. The legislation was unanimously passed by both the state House of Representatives and Senate in March. Florida is the latest in a growing trend of states adopting legislation that includes personal finance education for students. Currently, there are 54 bills pending in 26 states, according to Next Gen Personal Finance&amp;rsquo;s bill tracker.</description></item><item><title>CEO of Canada’s largest trucking company says vaccine mandate ‘not an issue at all’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202ea89b9b0093c3050a110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202ea89b9b0093c3050a110/</guid><description>National Newswatch: Canada&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive site for political news and views. Make it a daily habit.
Highlights CEO of Canada’s largest trucking company says vaccine mandate ‘not an issue at all’ CEO of TFI International Inc. says its operations are virtually untouched by the mandate. Alain Bédard says last month was looking like &amp;ldquo;the best January ever for the company&amp;rdquo; following a fourth quarter that saw profits jump by more than two-thirds and revenue leap by 91 per cent.</description></item></channel></rss>