<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>woman on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/woman/</link><description>Recent content in woman on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/woman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Woman tied to Jan. 6 Capitol riot involved in fatal crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</guid><description>UNION, Mo. (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.
Summary (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Pakistan to get its first woman Supreme Court judge - Justice Ayesha Malik</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d81de63093acba16efac77/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d81de63093acba16efac77/</guid><description>The Judicial Commission of Pakistan has paved the way for Justice Ayesha Malik of the Lahore High Court to be elevated as the country&amp;rsquo;s first woman Supreme Court judge.
Summary Pakistan is set to get its first woman Supreme Court judge - Justice Ayesha Malik of the Lahore High Court. In most cases, this committee concurs with the JCP&amp;rsquo;s recommendation, which means that Justice Ayesha Malik is now one step closer to becoming Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s first woman Supreme Court judge.</description></item><item><title>Fairfax Police Officers Protected Sex Trafficking Ring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</guid><description>A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern&amp;hellip;
Summary A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern Virginia in exchange for free sex from the trafficked women. The suit was filed on behalf of a Costa Rican woman identified in the lawsuit only as “Jane Doe.</description></item></channel></rss>