<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>woman on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/woman/</link><description>Recent content in woman on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/woman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justice Stephen Breyer to retire from Supreme Court, paving way for Biden appointment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1c5a34d8b390b6379f22e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1c5a34d8b390b6379f22e/</guid><description>Justice Stephen Breyer will step down from the Supreme Court, allowing President Joe Biden to appoint a liberal successor.
Summary WASHINGTON — Justice Stephen Breyer will step down from the Supreme Court at the end of the current term, according to people familiar with his thinking. Supreme Court Justice Stephen Breyer in Washington in 2021. It’s time for a Black woman Supreme Court justice.&amp;quot; Circuit Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson of the Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia, a former Breyer law clerk; and Leondra Kruger, a justice on California’s Supreme Court.</description></item><item><title>Italian nurse accused of giving fake Covid jabs to anti-vaxxers arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4bfcca593d61b03a5648b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 01:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4bfcca593d61b03a5648b/</guid><description>Police say people were fraudulently obtaining Covid passes by having fake vaccinations in Palermo
Summary It is not the first time a nurse has been arrested in Italy for pretending to inject Covid vaccines. Last Wednesday, an Italian nurse in Ancona in the Marche region was arrested for allegedly giving fake Covid vaccines to at least 45 people. The nurse arrested on Friday in Palermo is the second health worker from the same hospital in the city to end up in prison.</description></item><item><title>Woman with semi-automatic rifle, other guns in vehicle arrested outside U.S. Capitol Police headquarters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0d942a82850dcb118deda/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 02:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0d942a82850dcb118deda/</guid><description>The arrest came less than a week after officials marked​ the first anniversary of the January 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol​.
Summary A woman was arrested Wednesday outside the headquarters for the U.S. Capitol Police after police saw a gun case and the butt of a long gun in her vehicle, the police said. The woman, identified as Kery Lynn McAttee, is facing multiple weapons charges, the police said in a statement to CBS News.</description></item><item><title>Woman tied to Jan. 6 Capitol riot involved in fatal crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</guid><description>UNION, Mo. (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.
Summary (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Pakistan to get its first woman Supreme Court judge - Justice Ayesha Malik</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d81de63093acba16efac77/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d81de63093acba16efac77/</guid><description>The Judicial Commission of Pakistan has paved the way for Justice Ayesha Malik of the Lahore High Court to be elevated as the country&amp;rsquo;s first woman Supreme Court judge.
Summary Pakistan is set to get its first woman Supreme Court judge - Justice Ayesha Malik of the Lahore High Court. In most cases, this committee concurs with the JCP&amp;rsquo;s recommendation, which means that Justice Ayesha Malik is now one step closer to becoming Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s first woman Supreme Court judge.</description></item><item><title>Fairfax Police Officers Protected Sex Trafficking Ring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</guid><description>A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern&amp;hellip;
Summary A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern Virginia in exchange for free sex from the trafficked women. The suit was filed on behalf of a Costa Rican woman identified in the lawsuit only as “Jane Doe.</description></item></channel></rss>