<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>woman on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/woman/</link><description>Recent content in woman on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 16:11:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/woman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Woman gets 15 months in prison for punching flight attendant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62924984d5f7053850373fa9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 16:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62924984d5f7053850373fa9/</guid><description>SAN DIEGO (AP) — A California woman who punched a Southwest Airlines flight attendant in the face during a flight, breaking her teeth, has been sentenced to 15 months in federal prison. Vyvianna Quinonez was also ordered Tuesday by the federal judge in San Diego to pay nearly $26,000 in restitution and a $7,500 fine for the assault on a May 23, 2021, Southwest flight between Sacramento and San Diego.</description></item><item><title>US Woman Shocked After Being Charged $40 "For Crying" During Doctor's Visit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62884b487bd9a49f5329298a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62884b487bd9a49f5329298a/</guid><description>A US woman recently shared that her sister was charged $40 (early Rs 3,100) &amp;quot;for crying&amp;quot; at a doctor&amp;rsquo;s appointment. The photo of the medical bill has gone viral with more than 486,000 likes and thousands of comments.
Highlights Camille Johnson shared a picture of her sister&amp;rsquo;s medical bill on Twitter. She highlighted a segment of the bill that docked her sibling for a “brief emotional/behavioural assessment” The photo has gone viral with more than 486,000 likes and thousands of comments.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Supreme Court rules in favor of woman who expected to pay $1,337 for surgery but was charged $303,709</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285929f6952b13c044ee069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285929f6952b13c044ee069/</guid><description>A woman who expected to pay $1,337 for surgery at a Westminster hospital but was billed $303,709 may be off the hook for the massive bill after the Colorado Supreme Court ruled in her favor Monday.
Highlights Lisa French was billed $303,709 for a pair of back surgeries in 2014 at St. Anthony North Health Campus. The Colorado Supreme Court ruled Monday that the contracts she signed with the hospital do not obligate her to pay the hospital’s secretive “chargemaster” price rates.</description></item><item><title>Patient claims a Christian rehab facility kicked her out for kissing another woman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62711f81c97c1ee2c8a84ae6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62711f81c97c1ee2c8a84ae6/</guid><description>A Florida woman claims she was forced to go to jail after being kicked out of a court-ordered, Christian-based drug rehab center for kissing another woman.
Highlights Kaylia Hevia, 29, was sentenced to 120 days in jail for violating probation at Teen Challenge, a &amp;ldquo;Christ-centered&amp;rdquo; drug and addiction program she attended as part of a plea for her February 2021 arrest. The program has a &amp;ldquo;no touching&amp;rdquo; rule&amp;quot; contained within the program agreement, prosecutors say.</description></item><item><title>Body of Florida woman, 93, found in freezer in her garage, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270f24bc7c64dce5d706e47/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 09:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270f24bc7c64dce5d706e47/</guid><description>Police in Florida are investigating what happened to Marie Hoskins, 93, whose body was found in a freezer in her garage.
Highlights Marie Hoskins was discovered inside the freezer in her home’s garage Thursday. A neighbor called police that day to conduct a welfare check on Hoskins, police say. A 64-year-old resident inside the home told police she hadn’t seen her mother in some time. Detectives are working with the medical examiner and the state attorney in the case, police said in a statement posted Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Alabama woman killed by pack of dogs; owner charged with manslaughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f140b41f5665ecd718a0b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 23:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f140b41f5665ecd718a0b/</guid><description>An employee of the Alabama Department of Public Health was killed by a pack of dogs in the northwestern part of the state last week as she was responding to a
Highlights Jacqueline Summer Beard was pronounced dead Friday by the Franklin County coroner after local residents called the police to report a suspicious vehicle. Officers found the car with Beard&amp;rsquo;s body inside it in a rural area outside Red Bay, near the Mississippi line.</description></item><item><title>World's oldest person, Japan's Kane Tanaka, dies at 119</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266a253edc98b81aeaa4024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 13:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266a253edc98b81aeaa4024/</guid><description>Kane Tanaka was born on Jan. 2, 1903 in the old village of Wajiro, Japan. She was recognized by the Gerontology Research Group and the Guinness World Record as the oldest woman and the oldest person in the world
Highlights The oldest person in the world has died at 119 years and 108 days. She was born in 1903 in the city of Wojakama, Japan. She is also the oldest living person in Japan, according to the oldest person on record.</description></item><item><title>Amid increasing abuse, officials flee youth sports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62668234e844f605f90f26af/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 11:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62668234e844f605f90f26af/</guid><description>ATLANTA (AP) — When one looks at the ugly bruise encircling Kristi Moore&amp;rsquo;s left eye, it&amp;rsquo;s not surprising so many refs and umps are hanging up their stripes.
Highlights Kristi Moore was umpiring a girls’ softball game in Mississippi. A parent watching the game thought the runner was out. She began screaming profanities, according to Moore, “accused me of cheating these kids’” America is facing a crisis in prep and youth sports, where fewer and fewer people are willing to take on the thankless job of officiating.</description></item><item><title>Woman arrested in Starr County on murder for ‘illegal abortion’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250fbe7bc6d7171551680c0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 03:22:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250fbe7bc6d7171551680c0/</guid><description>Law enforcement authorities in Starr County confirmed that a woman was arrested on a charge of murder over what they called an &amp;quot;illegal abortion.&amp;quot;
Highlights Lizelle Herrera, 26, was arrested and served with an indictment “on the charge of Murder’s Murder after Herrera did then and there intentionally and knowingly cause the death of an individual by self-induced abortion” Her arrest comes as Texas enacted one of the strictest abortion laws in the country last year in SB 8 which encourages private citizens to sue individuals or organizations that help people get an abortion after six weeks of gestation.</description></item><item><title>Police officer 'shared sensitive images of sexual assault case'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241df9a9a3cfd15a9230ab8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 16:18:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241df9a9a3cfd15a9230ab8/</guid><description>DC Joseph Gilligan met a vulnerable victim of domestic abuse through his investigation into her case. He abused his power by misusing police computer systems to gather information on the woman and her partner. He also accessed her mobile phone to read her
Highlights DC Joseph Gilligan met the victim of domestic abuse through his investigation into her case. He also abused his power by misusing police computer systems to gather information on the woman and her partner.</description></item><item><title>A man was fatally shot by his rescuer after falling in a South Carolina lake. The shooting has been ruled self-defense</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237534082a80b97e446ef2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6237534082a80b97e446ef2f/</guid><description>South Carolina prosecutors decided not to file charges in a case where a man who fell off a recreational watercraft was fatally shot by his rescuer, according to the Oconee County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.
Highlights A man and a woman fell off a boat in Oconee County, South Carolina. A sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office says the incident occurred Tuesday afternoon. The man &amp;ldquo;became agitated and began assaulting the couple on the boat,&amp;rdquo; the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s statement says.</description></item><item><title>Asian woman punched 125 times in New York attack; suspect charged with attempted murder as hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623013532bd52389fdf73657/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 04:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623013532bd52389fdf73657/</guid><description>A man was charged with attempted murder in what police have described as a &amp;quot;brutal hate crime&amp;quot; against an Asian woman in New York state last week, with video
Highlights Tammel Esco, 42, was arrested and accused of calling a 67-year-old woman an &amp;ldquo;Asian b&amp;mdash;-,&amp;rdquo; following her into a building and severely beating her Friday in Yonkers, New York state. The woman, who was not publicly identified, is stable and recovering in a hospital, police said.</description></item><item><title>William Hurt Dies: Oscar-Winning Actor For ‘Kiss Of The Spider Woman’ Was 71</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ec29d3d5bbcfface0c9ee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ec29d3d5bbcfface0c9ee/</guid><description>William Hurt Dies: Oscar-Winning Actor for &amp;lsquo;Kiss of the Spider-Woman&amp;rsquo; Was 71
Highlights William Hurt died a week before his 72nd birthday. The actor had terminal prostate cancer that had spread to the bone. He had three consecutive Best Actor Academy Award nominations in the mid-1980s for Kiss of the Spider Woman. He also won Best Actor Oscar for Children of a Lesser God (1986) and Broadcast News (1987) In 2014, Hurt was on the scene of one of the worst on-set accidents in movie history when a train smashed into the set on a trestle in rural Georgia, killing a camera assistant and injuring several others.</description></item><item><title>Tacoma woman sentenced for burning 5 police cars during 2020 Seattle protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221f3b8bac6367231fee1d1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 11:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221f3b8bac6367231fee1d1/</guid><description>Margaret Aislinn Channon was arrested on June 11, 2020, after an investigation by the FBI, ATF and the Seattle Police Department. Channon admitted to smashing windows at a Verizon store, entering a sandwich shop and destroying a
Highlights Margaret Aislinn Channon was arrested on June 11, 2020, after an investigation by the FBI, ATF and the Seattle Police Department. Channon is shown using fire and aerosol cans as a blowtorch to light five Seattle police cars on fire.</description></item><item><title>Man wanted in seven separate attacks against Asian women in one day, NYPD says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220f798ddc05b934c3116d3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 17:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6220f798ddc05b934c3116d3/</guid><description>The suspect who allegedly attacked seven Asian women over a two-hour period Sunday in Manhattan has been arrested and charged with hate crimes, police announced.
Highlights Steven Zajonc, 28, was arrested Wednesday, charged with seven counts each of assault as a hate crime, aggravated harassment and harassment. He was taken into custody after barricading himself in the New York Public Library. He allegedly punched or hurt seven Asian women over a two-hour period on Sunday in Manhattan.</description></item><item><title>Toronto Police Arrest Man And Woman On Hundreds Of Sexual Abuse Crimes Spanning 15 Years, 41 Victims Identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 17:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</guid><description>Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. Police have a number of unidentified victims and are seeking the public&amp;rsquo;s assistance in identifying them.
Highlights Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. It is alleged that a man and a woman committed multiple sexual and physical assaults against men, women and children. Martin “Mark” Wettlaufer, 37, and Kathleen Wardlaw, 42, of Toronto, have been arrested and charged with hundreds of offences relating to the allegations listed above.</description></item><item><title>Woman says doctor secretly fathered her and then violated her as OB-GYN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216162fbfaaf66b93f8b1f6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 11:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216162fbfaaf66b93f8b1f6/</guid><description>A growing suspicion led a Rochester woman to get genetic testing. What she found was horrifying.
Highlights Morgan Hellquist is suing Dr. Morris Wortman, a fertility specialist and her previous OB-GYN. Her mother and her husband were told when she was 8 years old that she was donor-conceived. Wortsman was a well-known fertility specialist in the Rochester area. Hellquist married in 2008 and had two children, born in 2009 and 2011, before and after the births, she decided in 2012 to turn to the man whom her mother worshipped.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco DA drops charges against woman whose rape kit DNA linked her to a property crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eba52c21a59f1063e6f8d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 21:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620eba52c21a59f1063e6f8d/</guid><description>District attorney Chesa Boudin said the charges violated constitutional protections against unreasonable searches and seizures
Highlights District attorney Chesa Boudin drops charges against a woman whose DNA collected from a rape kit was used to link her to a property crime. Officials said the practice violated the defendants’ fourth amendment protections against unreasonable searches and seizures by the government, and runs afoul of California’s Victims’ Bill of Rights. The district attorney also expressed concerns the practice would deter victims of sexual assault, which is widely underreported in the US, from coming forward.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco Police reportedly link woman to crime using DNA taken from her rape kit San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 15:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bc27dd7705eca834ba103/</guid><description>San Francisco district attorney says it was possibly a rights violation and could deter sexual assault victims from speaking out
Highlights San Francisco police used DNA collected from rape exam to link a woman to a crime, district attorney says. District attorney Chesa Boudin says use of victims’ DNA could violate the state&amp;rsquo;s Victims’ Bill of Rights as well as constitutional laws related to unreasonable searches and seizures. State senator Scott Wiener, who represents the city, says lawmakers are seeking to determine whether a change in state law was needed to prevent the practice.</description></item><item><title>Woman, 58, falls to death from mast of historic ship in Galveston, Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62025f5ddb358fc7e201c6df/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62025f5ddb358fc7e201c6df/</guid><description>A woman fell to her death from a mast on a historic ship that’s featured at a Texas museum after her safety harness somehow came unclipped, police said.
Highlights 58-year-old woman died Saturday after falling from a mast on the tall ship Elissa. The Elissa is berthed at Galveston’s seaport museum. Training classes are held each year on the Elissa and they include lessons in sail rigging. Ship was built in 1877, from a scrapyard in Greece in 1978, according to the historical foundation.</description></item><item><title>Woman takes legal action after Met officer who called her ‘hot’ keeps job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 04:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62009cf7125cfcbda21cac7b/</guid><description>Kristina O’Connor says detective who was investigating after men tried to steal her phone asked her out
Highlights Kristina O&amp;rsquo;Connor said she was sent inappropriate messages by DCI James Mason. The officer asked her out to dinner while taking her statement about an attempted robbery. A panel at a police misconduct hearing last year found him guilty of gross misconduct. The Met has confirmed he remains a serving officer. O’Connor is seeking a judicial review of how the investigation was handled by the force.</description></item><item><title>Justice Stephen Breyer to retire from Supreme Court, paving way for Biden appointment</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1c5a34d8b390b6379f22e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1c5a34d8b390b6379f22e/</guid><description>Justice Stephen Breyer will step down from the Supreme Court, allowing President Joe Biden to appoint a liberal successor.
Summary WASHINGTON — Justice Stephen Breyer will step down from the Supreme Court at the end of the current term, according to people familiar with his thinking. Supreme Court Justice Stephen Breyer in Washington in 2021. It’s time for a Black woman Supreme Court justice.&amp;quot; Circuit Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson of the Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia, a former Breyer law clerk; and Leondra Kruger, a justice on California’s Supreme Court.</description></item><item><title>Italian nurse accused of giving fake Covid jabs to anti-vaxxers arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4bfcca593d61b03a5648b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 01:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4bfcca593d61b03a5648b/</guid><description>Police say people were fraudulently obtaining Covid passes by having fake vaccinations in Palermo
Summary It is not the first time a nurse has been arrested in Italy for pretending to inject Covid vaccines. Last Wednesday, an Italian nurse in Ancona in the Marche region was arrested for allegedly giving fake Covid vaccines to at least 45 people. The nurse arrested on Friday in Palermo is the second health worker from the same hospital in the city to end up in prison.</description></item><item><title>Woman with semi-automatic rifle, other guns in vehicle arrested outside U.S. Capitol Police headquarters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0d942a82850dcb118deda/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 02:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0d942a82850dcb118deda/</guid><description>The arrest came less than a week after officials marked​ the first anniversary of the January 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol​.
Summary A woman was arrested Wednesday outside the headquarters for the U.S. Capitol Police after police saw a gun case and the butt of a long gun in her vehicle, the police said. The woman, identified as Kery Lynn McAttee, is facing multiple weapons charges, the police said in a statement to CBS News.</description></item><item><title>Woman tied to Jan. 6 Capitol riot involved in fatal crash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d855aaa3788813dbbf3ec6/</guid><description>UNION, Mo. (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.
Summary (AP) — A Missouri woman charged with participating in the riot at U.S. Capitol last year has been arrested after she allegedly caused a fatal crash while driving drunk and the wrong way on an interstate, authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Pakistan to get its first woman Supreme Court judge - Justice Ayesha Malik</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d81de63093acba16efac77/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d81de63093acba16efac77/</guid><description>The Judicial Commission of Pakistan has paved the way for Justice Ayesha Malik of the Lahore High Court to be elevated as the country&amp;rsquo;s first woman Supreme Court judge.
Summary Pakistan is set to get its first woman Supreme Court judge - Justice Ayesha Malik of the Lahore High Court. In most cases, this committee concurs with the JCP&amp;rsquo;s recommendation, which means that Justice Ayesha Malik is now one step closer to becoming Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s first woman Supreme Court judge.</description></item><item><title>Fairfax Police Officers Protected Sex Trafficking Ring</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca7de2dc5ef9f7d676b031/</guid><description>A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern&amp;hellip;
Summary A federal lawsuit filed by a prominent civil rights attorney alleges that police officers in Fairfax County protected a sex trafficking ring in Northern Virginia in exchange for free sex from the trafficked women. The suit was filed on behalf of a Costa Rican woman identified in the lawsuit only as “Jane Doe.</description></item></channel></rss>