<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>history on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/history/</link><description>Recent content in history on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 13:34:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vatican documents show secret back channel between Pope Pius XII and Adolph Hitler</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0a52dcd8f076f1419bb39/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 13:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a0a52dcd8f076f1419bb39/</guid><description>A series of recently opened Vatican archives are shedding new light on the relationship between Pope Pius XII and Adolph Hitler as he led Nazi Germany during World War II. A new book takes a deeper look at these revelations. Historian David Kertzer, author of “The Pope At War: The Secret History of Pope Pius XII, Mussolini, and Hitler,” joins Amna Nawaz to discuss.
Highlights A series of recently opened Vatican archives shed new light on the relationship between Pope Pius XII and Adolph Hitler as he led Nazi Germany during World War II.</description></item><item><title>Sri Lanka defaults on debt for first time in its history</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62873e92f297e89f49f3d3ba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 07:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62873e92f297e89f49f3d3ba/</guid><description>The governor of the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank and two major credit rating agencies said it has defaulted.
Highlights Central bank governor P Nandalal Weerasinghe said: &amp;ldquo;Our position is very clear, we said that until they come to the restructure [of our debts], we will not be able to pay&amp;rdquo; Two major credit rating agencies said it has defaulted. The governor of the country&amp;rsquo;s central bank said the country was pre-emptively defaulted on Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Euromillions: this winner of the 2nd biggest jackpot in history donates the money to a foundation for the planet</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dca96eede0e94da32e5ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 17:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dca96eede0e94da32e5ee/</guid><description>SFR offers Netflix and a package of channels to all its new fiber subscribers for six months. Scientists have already counted about 50 subspecies of the omicron strain of coronavirus. Maddison donated 100 thousand rubles for the
Highlights SFR offers Netflix and a package of channels to all its new fiber subscribers for six months. Scientists have already counted about 50 subspecies of the omicron strain of coronavirus. Maddison donated 100 thousand rubles for the passage of Max Payne using the steering wheel.</description></item></channel></rss>