<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>boy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/boy/</link><description>Recent content in boy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:13:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/boy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1-year-old child shot, killed in downtown Pittsburgh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62947c7723b214aba81cd7e8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62947c7723b214aba81cd7e8/</guid><description>The boy has been identified as DeAery Thomas. The shooting happened at around 2:44 p.m. on Saturday afternoon. The child was not the intended target, but a passenger in the car was. Officials said that residents
Highlights A 1-year-old boy was shot and killed in downtown Pittsburgh on Saturday afternoon. The boy has been identified as DeAery Thomas. The shooting happened at around 2:44 p.m. and a bullet went right through the window of a Jeep, hitting the child.</description></item><item><title>Ex-officer charged with murder in shooting of 12-year-old</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270c8d4671d67dea435713a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 06:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270c8d4671d67dea435713a/</guid><description>A fired Philadelphia police officer has been charged with murder in the shooting of a fleeing 12-year-old boy
Highlights Thomas &amp;ldquo;T.J.&amp;rdquo; Siderio, 12, was shot in the back of the neck after he fired at an unmarked police car, prosecutors say. A grand jury presentment unsealed Monday shows video contradicts the officer&amp;rsquo;s version of events. The boy&amp;rsquo;s great-grandmother: &amp;ldquo;I’m so heartbroken, none of us can’t sleep’s horrible” The officer is also charged with voluntary manslaughter and other charges.</description></item><item><title>In milestone deal, Proud Boy pleads guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</guid><description>A New York man pleaded guilty Wednesday to storming the U.S. Capitol with fellow members of the far-right Proud Boys, a milestone in the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s prosecution of extremists who joined the Jan.
Summary At least four others linked to the Oath Keepers also have pleaded guilty to riot-related charges. Proud Boys members describe themselves as a politically incorrect men’s club for “Western chauvinists.” Its members frequently have engaged in street fights with antifascist activists at rallies and protests.</description></item></channel></rss>