<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>500 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/500/</link><description>Recent content in 500 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/500/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla removed from S&amp;amp;P 500 ESG Index, prompting Musk fury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628617a4ddfd2c410d9c0440/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628617a4ddfd2c410d9c0440/</guid><description>An S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones Indices executive said it had removed Tesla from the S&amp;amp;P 500 ESG Index because of issues including claims of racial discrimination and crashes linked to its autopilot vehicles.
Highlights S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones Indices says it has removed electric carmaker Tesla from the widely followed index. Tesla CEO Elon Musk responded with harsh tweets including that &amp;ldquo;ESG is a scam&amp;rdquo; The back-and-forth over the index changes reflects a wider debate about the metrics used to judge corporate performance on environmental, social and governance (ESG) issues.</description></item><item><title>AP News: US finds 500 Native American boarding school deaths so far</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c8bcb2b988446f8bb453d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 04:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c8bcb2b988446f8bb453d/</guid><description>FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. (AP) — A first-of-its-kind federal study of Native American boarding schools that for over a century sought to assimilate Indigenous children into white society has identified more than 500 student deaths at the institutions, but officials expect that figure to grow exponentially as research continues.
Highlights First-of-its-kind federal study of Native American boarding schools has identified more than 500 student deaths at the institutions. Officials expect that figure to grow exponentially as research continues.</description></item><item><title>Son of animal hoarder drops off nearly 500 parakeets at animal shelter before Christmas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c83d3c02decfb2bacb2db4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 10:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c83d3c02decfb2bacb2db4/</guid><description>The parakeets were said to be crammed together in just seven cages and barely able to move.
Summary Son of animal hoarder drops off nearly 500 parakeets at animal shelter before ChristmasThe son of an animal hoarder dropped off nearly 500 parakeets to a southeast Michigan rescue shelter shortly before Christmas, and plans to return later with at least 50 more birds. But when the son arrived at the shelter late Thursday night, he actually had 497 parakeets in his pickup.</description></item></channel></rss>