<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>released on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/released/</link><description>Recent content in released on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:16:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/released/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple has discontinued the iPod, 20 years after it was released</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ac7f66a0d4aee160bf3a0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:16:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ac7f66a0d4aee160bf3a0/</guid><description>The iPod, the first MP3 player that could hold 1,000 songs and had a 10-hour battery life, transformed how we listen to music.The US tech giant said its iconic music player had now been made redundant by phones that could also play music.
Highlights Apple has discontinued the iPod, 20 years after it was released. US tech giant said its iconic music player has been replaced by other devices. iPod was the first MP3 player that could hold 1,000 songs and had a 10-hour battery life.</description></item><item><title>Nick Cave announces death of son, Jethro, aged 30</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a3b38ce2df85259691f22/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 10:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a3b38ce2df85259691f22/</guid><description>The musician issued a brief statement asking for privacy after his son, a model and actor, dies.
Highlights The musician issued a brief statement asking for privacy after his son, a model and actor, dies. He had only been released on bail from Melbourne Remand Centre last Thursday, 5 May. A magistrate had instructed that he must undergo substance abuse treatment and avoid contact with his mother for the next two years.</description></item><item><title>Newly released video shows 9/11 hijackers with alleged Saudi intelligence operative</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c1e0401f90a45ecc0c75a/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 17:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c1e0401f90a45ecc0c75a/</guid><description>Less than two weeks after 9/11, boxes of evidence, including personal notes and video, were seized by British police from a home in Birmingham, England.
Highlights Families of 9/11 victims say they had to go through the British courts to get records and videos seized two decades ago from an alleged Saudi government operative. Boxes of evidence, including personal notes and video, were seized by British police from a home in Birmingham, England.</description></item><item><title>17 LA gangs have sent out crews to follow and rob city's wealthiest, LAPD says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256e8a879f4c951d21d114e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 15:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256e8a879f4c951d21d114e/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES — More than a dozen Los Angeles gangs are targeting some of the city&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
Highlights LAPD task force is trying to identify the cause of a sudden surge in &amp;ldquo;follow-home&amp;rdquo; robberies. Police say at least 17 gangs, most based out of South L.A. and operating independently, are involved. The gangs are sending crews in multiple cars to find, follow and rob people driving high-end vehicles or wearing expensive jewelry, police say.</description></item><item><title>7 Hospitalized after fentanyl released through vents at juvenile detention center in Williams Co. Ohio</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238c0d24b49beab59d1fee4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 18:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6238c0d24b49beab59d1fee4/</guid><description>Three corrections officers and four juveniles who were detained in the facility were taken to the hospital, authorities said.
Highlights Fentanyl was released through the air vents at the Northwest Ohio Juvenile Detention Training and Rehabilitation Center. Three corrections officers and four juveniles who were detained in the facility were taken to the hospital. The other detainees were moved to the Corrections Center of Northwest Ohio next door. Multiple fire departments, ambulances and emergency personnel were at the facility in Stryker Sunday night, including those from neighboring counties.</description></item><item><title>New York's Museum of Modern Art evacuated after two people were stabbed inside, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e34cf13be44e4888bd493/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 18:16:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e34cf13be44e4888bd493/</guid><description>Patrons at New York City&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art were evacuated Saturday afternoon after two employees were stabbed inside the iconic establishment by a man who was involved in two incidents of disorderly conduct at the museum in recent days, police said.
Highlights Patrons at New York City&amp;rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art were evacuated Saturday afternoon. Two employees were stabbed in the back, collar bone and back of the neck. The NYPD is still searching for the suspect, who was identified in a news release early Sunday as 60-year-old Gary Cabana.</description></item><item><title>Man used ‘ghost gun’ to kill 3 daughters in church</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226f480aa1c3a79c001494d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 06:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6226f480aa1c3a79c001494d/</guid><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The gunman who killed his three daughters, a chaperone who&amp;hellip;
Highlights Gunman killed three daughters, chaperone and himself in Northern California church this week. David Mora, 39, was armed with a homemade semiautomatic rifle-style weapon. He had an illegal 30-round ammunition magazine and 17 bullets were fired. Authorities do not know how or when he obtained the weapon, a sheriff’s spokesman says. He was released from an involuntary mental health hold in April 2021 after threatening to harm himself and his estranged girlfriend.</description></item><item><title>Bob Saget's cause of death released</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204912394ceedfddf397029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 04:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6204912394ceedfddf397029/</guid><description>Bob Saget, who was found dead in his Orlando, Florida hotel room last month, died from the result of a head trauma, according to a statement from his family.
Highlights Bob Saget was found dead in his Orlando, Florida hotel room last month. The &amp;ldquo;Fuller House&amp;rdquo; star, 65, died from a head trauma, his family said. &amp;ldquo;We ask everyone to remember the love and laughter that Bob brought to this world,&amp;rdquo; the statement said.</description></item></channel></rss>