<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>theory on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/theory/</link><description>Recent content in theory on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 13:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/theory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laws restricting lessons on racism make it hard for teachers to discuss the massacre in Buffalo</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288e730b5b9dd23d19a5a5c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 13:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6288e730b5b9dd23d19a5a5c/</guid><description>After a gunman killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, teachers are grappling with anti-critical race theory laws that limit what they can discuss with students.
Highlights Teachers fear for their jobs because of state laws limiting how they can discuss racism. Educators took to social media and wrote essays debating how to talk about the Buffalo shooting. Experts describe social studies and history courses as a potential antidote to extremist ideologies that appear to have motivated the suspect in Buffalo, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky governor vetoes bill incorporating 'anti-critical race theory,' calling it a step backward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250386506c7ee4c76d2b351/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 13:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250386506c7ee4c76d2b351/</guid><description>Democratic Gov. Andy Beshear has vetoed a bill that contains elements of an &amp;quot;anti-critical race theory&amp;quot; bill that he says &amp;quot;tries to police classroom discussions on topics such as race.&amp;quot;
Highlights Democratic Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear has vetoed a bill that contains elements of an &amp;ldquo;anti-critical race theory&amp;rdquo; bill. SB1 states in part that public schools shall provide instructions that align with certain concepts including: &amp;ldquo;An individual, by virtue of the individual&amp;rsquo;s race or sex, does not bear responsibility for actions committed by other members of the same race&amp;rdquo; The bill received final passage from the state Senate last month, according to the Kentucky General Assembly page on SB 1.</description></item></channel></rss>