<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>detroit on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/detroit/</link><description>Recent content in detroit on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 05:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/detroit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Weird Al’ Yankovic catches COVID, postpones two Michigan concerts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285d283103d1d1c8cfa015a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 05:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285d283103d1d1c8cfa015a/</guid><description>“Weird Al” Yankovic says he caught the virus and won’t be coming to Saginaw and Detroit. “I’m vaxxed and double-boosted and the symptoms
Highlights “Weird Al” Yankovic says he caught the virus and won’t be coming to Saginaw and Detroit. Weird Al is currently on his “The Unfortunate Return of the Ridiculously Self-Indulgent, Ill-Advised Vanity Tour’s next tour stops are scheduled for Nashville, Springfield, IL and Milwaukee. The concerts are comprised mostly of his original (non-parody) songs and in smaller theatres.</description></item><item><title>Man walking to Detroit Tigers game on footbridge fell through when concrete collapsed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62845fd230f265d7e047a6ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 02:54:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62845fd230f265d7e047a6ee/</guid><description>Ely Hydes was walking to a Detroit Tigers game at Comerica Park when he claimed the concrete on the Spruce Street pedestrian bridge gave way and he fell about 15 feet. Hydes said he landed near oncoming freeway traffic.
Highlights Ely Hydes was walking to a Detroit Tigers game at Comerica Park when he claimed the concrete on the Spruce Street pedestrian bridge gave way and he fell about 15 feet.</description></item><item><title>US Navy intends to decommission some of its newest warships</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253b8f8de0042473a08c00c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 05:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253b8f8de0042473a08c00c/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — The Navy that once wanted smaller, speedy warships to chase down pirates has made a speedy pivot to Russia and China — and many of those recently built ships could be retired.
Highlights The Navy wants to decommission nine ships in the Freedom-class, warships that cost about $4.5 billion to build. The move would free up $50 million per ship annually for other priorities. But it would also reduce the size of the fleet that’s already surpassed by China in sheer numbers, something that could cause members of Congress to balk.</description></item><item><title>Mother shoots her 4-year-old child twice while attempting to clean gun, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</guid><description>A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said.
Summary A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said. The mother initially told officers someone opened fire outside an apartment after unsuccessfully trying to snatch her purse, hitting the child twice.</description></item></channel></rss>