<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>instagram on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/instagram/</link><description>Recent content in instagram on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 05:15:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/instagram/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shooter warning signs get lost in sea of social media posts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930139bbd2a49a95d81d25/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 05:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930139bbd2a49a95d81d25/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The warning signs were there for anyone to stumble upon, days before the 18-year-old gunman entered a Texas elementary school and slaughtered 19 children and two teachers .
Highlights Gunman who killed 19 children and two teachers in Texas left a digital trail that hinted at what was to come. The warning signs were there for anyone to stumble upon, days before the massacre. Instagram photo of a hand holding a gun magazine, a TikTok profile that warned, “Kids be scared,” and the image of two AR-style semi-automatic rifles displayed on a rug, pinned to the top of the killer’s Instagram profile.</description></item><item><title>Teen charged in 151-mph crash that killed 6 posted Instagram videos of himself racing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626365b9b86a764fe0678c3d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 02:35:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626365b9b86a764fe0678c3d/</guid><description>A Florida teenager has been charged in the deaths of six people in a violent 151-mph crash in January, and new court documents reveal he posted himself racing at 182 mph in his luxury BWM on social media just two weeks prior.
Highlights Noah Galle, 18, was formally charged Monday with six counts of vehicular homicide in the Jan. 27 crash that killed six farm employees leaving work in Delray Beach, Florida.</description></item><item><title>Two cousins, 12 and 14, killed while playing with gun on Instagram Live, family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242a44733c2f2f0a74a6761/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242a44733c2f2f0a74a6761/</guid><description>Two young cousins from Missouri were livestreaming when one fatally shot the other before killing herself, police and a relative of the victims said.
Highlights Paris Harvey, 12, and her cousin Kuaron Harvey, 14, were livestreaming when one fatally shot the other before she killed herself, police say. Police classified the incident as a murder-suicide, but family members say it was a tragic accident. Paris’ mother, Shinise Harvey, says she let her daughter go to the apartment for a family party celebrating March birthdays.</description></item></channel></rss>