<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ms on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ms/</link><description>Recent content in ms on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 22:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prince Andrew and Virginia Giuffre settle out of court over civil sex assault claim | UK News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c2544b5d1c99ee0fa655c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 22:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c2544b5d1c99ee0fa655c/</guid><description>Representatives for the duke say he will not be expanding beyond the statement filed in court and Ms Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s lawyer says: &amp;quot;I believe this event speaks for itself.&amp;quot;
Highlights Prince Andrew and Virginia Giuffre have settled out of court in her civil sex assault claim against him. Court documents show the parties had &amp;ldquo;reached a settlement in principle&amp;rdquo; Duke of York will make a &amp;ldquo;substantial donation&amp;rdquo; to Ms Giufre&amp;rsquo;s charity in support of victims' rights.</description></item><item><title>No documents in Prince Andrew's possession to prove inability to sweat claim</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0a4cec0f091a4ed19ac47/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0a4cec0f091a4ed19ac47/</guid><description>The Duke of York has revealed there are no witnesses or documents to support his claim.
Summary He also said he had no documents in his possession regarding the &amp;ldquo;peculiar medical condition&amp;rdquo; he said prevented him from sweating. The claims were made in court documents filed on Thursday night in response to discovery requests made by his alleged victim, Virginia Roberts Giuffre. Ms Giuffre has lodged a civil claim for unspecified damages, alleging that the Duke assaulted or raped her on three separate occasions in 2001 when she was 17.</description></item></channel></rss>