<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>job on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/job/</link><description>Recent content in job on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 07:13:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tech exec prioritizes job opening to people of color, critics argue civil rights violation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280a811446b80ae2de81f87/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 07:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280a811446b80ae2de81f87/</guid><description>Dropbox’s Senior Director of Product Design Jasmin Friedl indicated in a post on Twitter that she was “prioritizing” people of color in her hiring practices at the company. First up, I care deeply about building teams that represent the communities we work in and the people we serve,” Friedl said in atweet explaining details about a new job opening. “I also deeply care about equity in hiring. Therefore, I choose to prioritize folks in our BIPOC and URM communities.</description></item><item><title>Arkansas doctor sued for allegedly giving inmates ivermectin without their consent recognized by local leaders for "job well done"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202a521237a41fc9d175b2f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202a521237a41fc9d175b2f/</guid><description>The doctor has also been sued dozens of times for allegedly providing inadequate medical care to detainees, including for mistreating broken bones.
Highlights Dr. Robert Karas has been accused of treating COVID-positive detainees with anti-parasitic drug ivermectin. The ACLU has sued Karas on behalf of four inmates for the alleged treatment. Local officials agreed to commend Karas for a &amp;ldquo;job well done&amp;rdquo; in his handling of the coronavirus pandemic. The local doctor has not shied away from touting the use of the drug to treat COVID, despite the CDC and other agencies advising against doing so.</description></item></channel></rss>