<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>recovery on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/recovery/</link><description>Recent content in recovery on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:22:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/recovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Work begins to turn 99,000 hectares in England into ‘nature recovery’ projects | Conservation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62937378a79cb528aa2c223a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62937378a79cb528aa2c223a/</guid><description>Five projects to receive funding from Defra and Natural England to tackle wildlife loss and improve access to nature
Highlights Five landscape-scale projects in the West Midlands, Cambridgeshire, the Peak District, Norfolk and Somerset. Aim to help tackle wildlife loss and the climate crisis, and improve public access to nature. Will share an initial £2.4m pot from the Department for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs and Natural England. Work in the projects will range from converting farmland into chalk grassland to restoring ‘dewponds’ and managing wetlands sustainably.</description></item><item><title>Queen tests positive for coronavirus, Buckingham Palace says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62124c1774b6d62330957ee3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62124c1774b6d62330957ee3/</guid><description>The monarch, 95, is experiencing mild cold-like symptoms and expects to continue light duties at Windsor this week, the palace says.
Highlights The Queen, 95, is experiencing mild cold-like symptoms and expects to continue light duties at Windsor this week. She is understood to be triple vaccinated and is &amp;lsquo;immensely practical&amp;rsquo; Her Majesty&amp;rsquo;s doctors will be on hand to take care of and monitor her health. Announcement made just weeks after Queen reached her historic Platinum Jubilee of 70 years on the throne.</description></item><item><title>US Navy Wants To Get Crashed Stealth Fighter Back From South China Sea, Before China Can</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1e0adc906535dea756a32/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1e0adc906535dea756a32/</guid><description>The United States Navy is trying to retrieve its most advanced fighter jet from the depths of the South China Sea, an extremely complex operation that analysts say will be closely monitored by Beijing.
Summary The F-35C, a single-engine stealth fighter and the newest jet in the US Navy fleet, crash-landed on the aircraft carrier USS Carl Vinson during routine operations on Monday, the Navy said. Chinese naval and coast guard vessels maintain a constant presence in South China Sea waters.</description></item></channel></rss>