<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>marathon on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/marathon/</link><description>Recent content in marathon on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:33:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/marathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Family of 6-year-old who ran marathon visited by child protective services, parents speak out</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b3c812d118f06e767e883/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 04:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b3c812d118f06e767e883/</guid><description>The parents of a 6-year-old marathoner are speaking out after they say child protective services paid their family an unannounced visit.
Highlights Parents of 6-year-old marathoner say child protective services visited their home. Ben and Kami Crawford shared a photo of one of their children being interviewed by CPS. The Crawfords made headlines last week after they let their children, including their son Rainier, run the Flying Pig Marathon in Cincinnati.</description></item><item><title>Ukrainian refugee wins Jerusalem Marathon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240564881b565fb6d819218/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240564881b565fb6d819218/</guid><description>Veretska competed in the race after fleeing Ukraine in late February with her 11-year-old daughter
Highlights Valentyna Veretska, 31, of Mykolaiv, Ukraine, was the first woman across the finish line in 2:45:54. She was invited to the race after her third-place finish at the Riyadh Half Marathon in Saudi Arabia in early March. Her husband stayed behind in Ukraine, since men of fighting age (18-60) are not allowed to leave. Ageze Guadie, 33, from Israel, finished first in the men’s category, with a time of 2:37:17.</description></item></channel></rss>