<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>911 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/911/</link><description>Recent content in 911 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 10:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/911/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'She created a McMess': Polk County woman arrested for calling 911 over McDonald's order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a0bf429f664b833325895/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a0bf429f664b833325895/</guid><description>The Polk County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office arrested a woman they say called 911 and assaulted restaurant workers because her McDonald&amp;rsquo;s order was wrong.
Highlights Polk County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office arrested a woman they say called 911 and assaulted restaurant workers because her McDonald&amp;rsquo;s order was wrong. Tianis Jones, 22, was arrested Friday evening. She was arrested on burglary with assault, criminal mischief, disorderly conduct and misuse of 911 charges. Surveillance video shows Jones becoming increasingly displeased with the service, despite workers offering to fix the issues as well as return her money.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo 911 dispatcher who allegedly hung up on shooting call put on leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62868a20852b80382efd95fe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 18:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62868a20852b80382efd95fe/</guid><description>A 911 dispatcher is on leave and may lose her job after allegedly hanging up on an supermarket employee hiding during this weekend&amp;rsquo;s shooting rampage in Buffalo, New York.
Highlights A 911 dispatcher has been placed on leave and may lose her job after allegedly hanging up on an supermarket employee hiding during this weekend’s shooting rampage in Buffalo, New York. The store employee alleges the dispatcher shouted at her, asked why she was whispering — then hung up.</description></item><item><title>Florida man calls 911 to have meth tested for authenticity, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622dd135c6d79e5d88eaeb87/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 11:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622dd135c6d79e5d88eaeb87/</guid><description>A Spring Hill man is accused of calling 911 to have the methamphetamine he recently purchased from a man he met at an area bar tested because he believed it was really bath salts.
Highlights Thomas Eugene Colucci made the emergency call around 7 p.m. on Thursday. Colucci told deputies he wanted his methamphetamine tested because he did not want other people to purchase &amp;ldquo;fake&amp;rdquo; methamphetamine from the person who sold it to him.</description></item></channel></rss>