<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>service on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/service/</link><description>Recent content in service on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:13:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sky News: Kevin Spacey charged with four counts of sexual assault against three men, CPS says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fc3241bd5f202b4ef3752/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 18:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fc3241bd5f202b4ef3752/</guid><description>The alleged incidents took place in London between March 2005 and August 2008, and in Gloucestershire in April 2013.
Highlights Oscar-winning actor Kevin Spacey charged with four counts of sexual assault against three men. The 62-year-old has also been charged with causing a person to engage in penetrative sexual activity without consent. The alleged incidents took place in London between March 2005 and August 2008, and in Gloucestershire in April 2013.</description></item><item><title>Robberies of mail carriers rise dramatically in U.S. with no signs of abating</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62645e36bfba38a4d925ad94/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62645e36bfba38a4d925ad94/</guid><description>Criminals across the country are increasingly targeting mail carriers.
Highlights Criminals across the country are increasingly targeting mail carriers. Between 2018 and 2021, robberies of mail carriers more than tripled. Robberies involving a gun more than quadrupled, according to U.S. Postal Inspection Service data. USPS says surge in letter carrier robberies fueled by economic impact of Covid crisis, growth in USPS parcel volume amid the rise of e-commerce, e-mailing of government checks related to pandemic aid programs.</description></item><item><title>Feds say towing company illegally sold service members’ cars</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c9f23992f913350bb012e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c9f23992f913350bb012e/</guid><description>Federal prosecutors have filed a lawsuit accusing a Virginia company of illegally taking and selling service members’ vehicles.
Highlights Federal prosecutors file lawsuit accusing Virginia company of illegally taking and selling service members’ vehicles. Lawsuit seeks damages for affected service members, a civil penalty, and a court order barring the company from auctioning off vehicles without court orders. Federal prosecutors say the move violates the law requiring towing companies to get court orders before taking off service members&amp;rsquo; vehicles.</description></item><item><title>White House Secret Service personnel ‘compromised’ by men impersonating DHS agents, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250d91e4c5c73ccffae3c12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250d91e4c5c73ccffae3c12/</guid><description>A Secret Service agent assigned to protect first lady Jill Biden is a witness in the case of two men accused of impersonating Homeland Security agents.
Highlights Two men charged with impersonating DHS agents &amp;ldquo;compromised&amp;rdquo; Secret Service personnel assigned to protect first lady Jill Biden and the White House, prosecutors say. Federal prosecutors ask a judge to hold the duo without bail. Magistrate Judge G. Michael Harvey: &amp;ldquo;This is not just two people dressing up for Halloween, your honor.</description></item><item><title>Spotify says it will suspend service in Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e7863fec466ed1fa751f4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 02:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e7863fec466ed1fa751f4/</guid><description>Spotify Technology SA said on Friday it will suspend its streaming service in Russia in response to the country&amp;rsquo;s new media law.
Highlights Spotify Technology SA said on Friday it will suspend its streaming service in Russia in response to the country&amp;rsquo;s new media law. The audio streaming platform closed its office in Russia indefinitely earlier this month, citing what it described as Moscow&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;unprovoked attack on Ukraine&amp;rdquo; Russia&amp;rsquo;s new legislation makes it illegal to report any event that could discredit the Russian military.</description></item><item><title>‘Long-overdue’: all-Black, female WWII battalion to receive Congressional Gold Medal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234a1b51f10fb9d0216a94f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 15:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234a1b51f10fb9d0216a94f/</guid><description>Known as the ‘six triple eight’, the battalion was the only group of African American women to serve overseas during second world war
Highlights The 6888th central post directory battalion, also known as the ‘six triple eight’, was the only group of African American women to serve overseas during second world war. Created in 1944, it included 824 enlisted Black women and 31 officers from the women’s army corps, the army service forces and the army air forces.</description></item><item><title>Worker lost arm from injury at U.S. mail facility in North Carolina, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623092ac3e2f303de2035120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 13:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623092ac3e2f303de2035120/</guid><description>The arm of a mechanic working at a U.S. mail facility in North Carolina was amputated last year after coming into contact with a machine that had a safety guard removed, the U.S. Labor Department has found.
Highlights Inspection identified ‘repeat and serious safety violations’ at facility in Greensboro, North Carolina. Facility failed to train staff on working near conveyors or proper methods for safely operating equipment, agency says. Facility allowed workers without adequate training and protective equipment to perform tests on live electrical equipment.</description></item><item><title>Dunkin’ worker sentenced to house arrest after fatally punching irate customer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62280d160c25dd8eb6d8926e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 02:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62280d160c25dd8eb6d8926e/</guid><description>Corey Pujols, 27, is ordered to complete 200 hours of community service and attend anger management course. He pleaded guilty to felony battery and was sentenced to two years of house arrest. He was initially charged with manslaughter. Puj
Highlights Corey Pujols, 27, is ordered to complete 200 hours of community service and attend anger management course. He pleaded guilty to felony battery and was sentenced to two years of house arrest.</description></item><item><title>Toronto Police Arrest Man And Woman On Hundreds Of Sexual Abuse Crimes Spanning 15 Years, 41 Victims Identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 17:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</guid><description>Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. Police have a number of unidentified victims and are seeking the public&amp;rsquo;s assistance in identifying them.
Highlights Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. It is alleged that a man and a woman committed multiple sexual and physical assaults against men, women and children. Martin “Mark” Wettlaufer, 37, and Kathleen Wardlaw, 42, of Toronto, have been arrested and charged with hundreds of offences relating to the allegations listed above.</description></item><item><title>Officials: Defenders of Ukrainian island may still be alive and now POWs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b406b5688d1ccead3a1c7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 09:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621b406b5688d1ccead3a1c7/</guid><description>The defenders of the small Ukrainian island of Zmiinyi in the Black Sea may still be alive, according to a statement released on Saturday by the State Border Guard Service of Ukraine (SBGSU).
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine is encountering &amp;ldquo;stiffer than expected&amp;rdquo; resistance from the Ukrainian military and unexpected difficulties supplying its forces. Russia is suffering heavier losses in personnel, armor and aircraft than expected, US officials say. Russia has yet to establish air supremacy over Ukraine, a senior defense official says.</description></item><item><title>Army to immediately start discharging vaccine refusers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb0fcd2956e6f3d6edda78/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 23:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb0fcd2956e6f3d6edda78/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Army said Wednesday it will immediately begin discharging soldiers who have refused to get the mandatory COVID-19 vaccine , putting more than 3,300 service members at risk of being thrown out soon.
Highlights The Army says it will immediately begin discharging soldiers who have refused to get the mandatory COVID-19 vaccine. The Marine Corps, Air Force and Navy have already discharged active-duty troops or entry-level personnel at boot camps for refusing the shots.</description></item><item><title>Swiss army bans WhatsApp, Telegram and Signal due to privacy concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db22c6d3ae192757fa6692/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db22c6d3ae192757fa6692/</guid><description>Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s army has banned the use of WhatsApp whilst on duty, a spokesman confirmed Thursday, in favour of a Swiss messaging service deemed more secure in terms of data protection.
Summary The ban also applies to using other messaging apps like Signal and Telegram on soldiers’ private phones during service operations. READ MORE: Swiss army launches fitness app for future recruitsThe recommendation applies “to everyone”, including conscripts doing their military service and those returning for refresher courses, army spokesman Daniel Reist told AFP.</description></item><item><title>Lynx hunting in Latvia to be prohibited</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82120b10e7fd924c93805/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c82120b10e7fd924c93805/</guid><description>Summary The reason is because there are plans to add the Eurasian lynx (Lynx lynx) to the list of especially protected species. Hunting rules state lynx are limited game species and VMD needs to calculate the permissible hunting amount every season. It is also planned to add amendments to the Cabinet of Ministers rules on the list of especially protected species and limited use of especially protected speciesThe goal is to add the Eurasian lynx (Lynx lynx) to the list of especially protected animal species.</description></item><item><title>Troops find religious exemption for vaccines unattainable</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 09:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c197a82662877606bd8072/</guid><description>Description WASHINGTON (AP) — More than 12,000 military service members refusing the COVID-19 vaccine are seeking religious exemptions, and so far they are having zero success. That total lack of approvals is creating new tensions within the military, even as the vast majority of the armed forces have gotten vaccinated.
Summary The services, urgently trying to keep the coronavirus pandemic in check by getting troops vaccinated, are now besieged with exemption requests they are unlikely to approve.</description></item></channel></rss>