<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>asked on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/asked/</link><description>Recent content in asked on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 16:15:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/asked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>During the Uvalde shooting, an off-duty federal agent's wife texted him for help. "I asked my barber if he had a gun," he said.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298e1fd2d68b56efe55fe1b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 16:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298e1fd2d68b56efe55fe1b/</guid><description>Jacob Albarado was in his barber&amp;rsquo;s chair when both men got text messages about the shooting unfolding at Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas.
Highlights Jacob Albarado was in his barber&amp;rsquo;s chair when both men got text messages about the shooting unfolding at Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, last week. He had attended an awards ceremony at the school earlier that morning and was off duty, with his weapon at home.</description></item><item><title>Texans asked to turn up thermostats after sweltering heat knocks six power plants offline</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62806fd94765a9b5306d9c57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62806fd94765a9b5306d9c57/</guid><description>With an early-season heat wave searing much of Texas over the weekend, the nonprofit that manages power to more than 26 million customers wants them to turn up their thermostats.
Highlights The nonprofit that manages power to more than 26 million customers wants them to turn up their thermostats. It says soaring temperatures increased demand and caused six power generation facilities to trip offline. That resulted in the loss of about 2,900 megawatts of electricity.</description></item><item><title>Texts show Marjorie Taylor Greene asked Meadows about martial law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267fdcfd39fdcaa74f67c27/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 14:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267fdcfd39fdcaa74f67c27/</guid><description>The Georgia congresswoman has testified she doesn&amp;rsquo;t recall whether she encouraged Trump to impose martial law.
Highlights Georgia Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene texted then-White House chief of staff Mark Meadows to tell him some GOP members of Congress had privately suggested former President Trump should declare martial law. She testified last week she doesn&amp;rsquo;t recall whether she encouraged the president to impose martial law as a way to remain in power.</description></item></channel></rss>