<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>california on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/california/</link><description>Recent content in california on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:12:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/california/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>School apologizes after teacher leads California preschoolers in anti-Biden chant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bfdb18d179c860cc88f3a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bfdb18d179c860cc88f3a/</guid><description>A Southern California private school apologized to parents after a teacher shared a video last month of her leading preschool students in a chant denouncing President Joe Biden.
Highlights The video shows the unnamed teacher asking the 4- and 5-year-olds, &amp;ldquo;Who’s our president?” The teacher then asks, “What do we want to do with him?&amp;rdquo; The students shout back, &amp;ldquo;We want him out!” It&amp;rsquo;s unclear what, if any, disciplinary action was taken against the teacher.</description></item><item><title>Police helicopter goes down in California's Newport Bay, 2 pilots hospitalized</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621269317d8d5afb54b6fced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621269317d8d5afb54b6fced/</guid><description>One officer has died and another was critically injured when the police department helicopter they were in crashed into shallow water in Southern California&amp;rsquo;s N
Highlights Nicholas Vella, 44, a died of his injuries from the crash, Huntington Beach Police Chief Eric Parra said Saturday night. The helicopter was responding to a report of a fight in Newport Beach when it crash-landed around 6:30 p.m. The second officer, whose identity has not been released, was hospitalized in critical but stable condition.</description></item><item><title>Employer must face worker's lawsuit over husband's COVID death -California court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</guid><description>Description HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CALIFORNIA-WORKERS:Employer must face worker&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit over husband&amp;rsquo;s COVID death -California court
Summary The California Court of Appeal, Second Appellate District, rejected South San Francisco-based See&amp;rsquo;s Candies&amp;rsquo; argument that the employee, Matilde Ek, must file for workers&amp;rsquo; compensation rather than seek damages in court because her husband&amp;rsquo;s death was &amp;ldquo;derivative&amp;rdquo; of her own workplace injury. Ek and her three daughters sued See&amp;rsquo;s last year, saying she contracted COVID-19 because the company failed to ensure safety in the workplace.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item></channel></rss>