<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>california on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/california/</link><description>Recent content in california on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/california/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Employer must face worker's lawsuit over husband's COVID death -California court</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c3137734d8d5a62c057f85/</guid><description>Description HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CALIFORNIA-WORKERS:Employer must face worker&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit over husband&amp;rsquo;s COVID death -California court
Summary The California Court of Appeal, Second Appellate District, rejected South San Francisco-based See&amp;rsquo;s Candies' argument that the employee, Matilde Ek, must file for workers' compensation rather than seek damages in court because her husband&amp;rsquo;s death was &amp;ldquo;derivative&amp;rdquo; of her own workplace injury. Ek and her three daughters sued See&amp;rsquo;s last year, saying she contracted COVID-19 because the company failed to ensure safety in the workplace.</description></item><item><title>Walmart illegally dumps 1m toxic items in landfills yearly, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61c1899a9f34298293cb4092/</guid><description>Description California attorney general accuses retail giant of failing to properly dispose of items including batteries, cleaning supplies and electronic waste
Summary Walmart illegally dumps more than 1 million batteries, aerosol cans of insect killer and other products, toxic cleaning supplies, electronic waste, latex paints and other hazardous waste into California landfills each year, state prosecutors have alleged. In a lawsuit announced on Monday, the California attorney general, Rob Bonta, accused the retail giant of failing to properly dispose of discarded or returned goods.</description></item></channel></rss>