<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fine/</link><description>Recent content in fine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trump pays contempt fine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889eb5ac15ad9924e1b9e3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62889eb5ac15ad9924e1b9e3/</guid><description>His legal team is expected to file additional documents today related to a sprawling civil financial fraud probe by New York.
Highlights Trump has paid the $110,000 fine levied after he was held in contempt by a New York judge. An attorney for Trump also filed more than a dozen affidavits due Friday in an effort to purge the contempt finding. Trump was fined $10,000 per day through May 6, the date of his most recent attempt to satisfy Judge Arthur Engoron&amp;rsquo;s demands.</description></item><item><title>New York judge lifts civil contempt finding against Trump, orders him to pay $110,000 in fines</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c5d053c9b6ca92a262c04/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 01:04:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c5d053c9b6ca92a262c04/</guid><description>A New York judge on Wednesday set several conditions former President Donald Trump must meet to avoid a civil contempt finding being restored against him, including paying $110,000 in fines and explaining how his namesake company handled Post-it notes.
Highlights Judge Arthur Engoron said he wanted sworn statements describing the Trump Organization&amp;rsquo;s document retention and destruction policy. The conditions must be met by May 20, otherwise the judge said he would restore the contempt finding and apply it retroactively.</description></item><item><title>California Targets Loud Exhaust With Sound Activated Camera Enforcement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627898015275b456ec920daf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 04:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627898015275b456ec920daf/</guid><description>Six California cities may take part in the automated enforcement pilot program aimed at curbing noise pollution.
Highlights California is set to implement camera-automated exhaust noise enforcement. The pilot program will span from January 2023 to December 2027 and will be tested in six different cities across the state. Camera-enforced fines will be issued only after subsequent violations of the 95- and 80-decibel ceiling for cars and motorcycles, respectively. It is not immediately clear how these cameras will pinpoint vehicles in traffic, or how they will differentiate between cars and bikes.</description></item><item><title>Unruly US airline passengers hit with record fines by FAA</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251b17839ead3e6dbd2c86d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251b17839ead3e6dbd2c86d/</guid><description>Aviation authority has imposed zero-tolerance policy and says incidents have soared since 6 January Capitol attack
Highlights FAA has imposed zero-tolerance policy since January 2021. Agency has proposed fines of about $7m for disruptive passengers. $81,950 fine for American Airlines passenger on July flight from Dallas to Charlotte. Another $75,000 (£57,500) fine for Delta Air Lines passenger who bit a fellow passenger after trying to hug and kiss another. Agency says incidents have soared since 6 January 2021 attack on US Capitol.</description></item><item><title>Keurig to pay $3 million fine for false, misleading claims on recycling of its K-CUPs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8f03ebaf20f8281fa907d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8f03ebaf20f8281fa907d/</guid><description>OTTAWA - The Competition Bureau says Keurig Canada will pay a $3 million penalty for making false or misleadin&amp;hellip;
Summary But the Bureau said the K-Cups aren’t widely accepted for recycling in any province except Quebec and British Columbia and those instructions don’t go far enough for many cities that might accept them in a recycling program. In addition to the financial penalties, Keurig Canada has to change its packaging, publish notices about the changes on its websites, social media and in local and national media outlets, as well as include the information in packaging for new Keurig brewing machines and send an email to subscribers.</description></item></channel></rss>