<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fine on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fine/</link><description>Recent content in fine on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 16:17:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Unruly US airline passengers hit with record fines by FAA</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251b17839ead3e6dbd2c86d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 16:17:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251b17839ead3e6dbd2c86d/</guid><description>Aviation authority has imposed zero-tolerance policy and says incidents have soared since 6 January Capitol attack
Highlights FAA has imposed zero-tolerance policy since January 2021. Agency has proposed fines of about $7m for disruptive passengers. $81,950 fine for American Airlines passenger on July flight from Dallas to Charlotte. Another $75,000 (£57,500) fine for Delta Air Lines passenger who bit a fellow passenger after trying to hug and kiss another. Agency says incidents have soared since 6 January 2021 attack on US Capitol.</description></item><item><title>Keurig to pay $3 million fine for false, misleading claims on recycling of its K-CUPs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8f03ebaf20f8281fa907d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8f03ebaf20f8281fa907d/</guid><description>OTTAWA - The Competition Bureau says Keurig Canada will pay a $3 million penalty for making false or misleadin&amp;hellip;
Summary But the Bureau said the K-Cups aren’t widely accepted for recycling in any province except Quebec and British Columbia and those instructions don’t go far enough for many cities that might accept them in a recycling program. In addition to the financial penalties, Keurig Canada has to change its packaging, publish notices about the changes on its websites, social media and in local and national media outlets, as well as include the information in packaging for new Keurig brewing machines and send an email to subscribers.</description></item></channel></rss>