<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>omicron on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/omicron/</link><description>Recent content in omicron on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:13:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/omicron/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NJ to Lift School Masking Mandate in March</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:13:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024229adabf0e2cded87fd/</guid><description>New Jersey will lift its school mask mandate in the second week of March, Gov. Phil Murphy told the New York Times.
Highlights New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy announced Monday that the state will end its school mask mandate on March 7. Murphy said school districts can continue their own mandates if they want. Connecticut Gov. Ned Lamont announced that his state mask mandate will end on Feb. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>The Omicron surge hasn't peaked nationwide, and 'the next few weeks will be tough,' US surgeon general says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e70e5161c2ef7bf0c114e4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 19:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e70e5161c2ef7bf0c114e4/</guid><description>Areas that were among the first to get hit hard by the Omicron variant are starting to see their Covid-19 numbers level off or even improve. But that&amp;rsquo;s not the case for much of the country, US Surgeon General Dr. Vivek Murthy said.
Summary But that&amp;rsquo;s not the case for much of the country, US Surgeon General Dr. Vivek Murthy said. Chicago Public Schools resumed in-person teaching last week after pledging to increase Covid-19 testing as well as provide higher-quality KN95 masks.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated to be banned from restaurants and other venues in France under new Covid law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5aecda93cd027ca6e0c48/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 09:52:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5aecda93cd027ca6e0c48/</guid><description>The new law requires full vaccination for such venues, including tourist sites, many trains and all domestic flights, and applies to everyone aged 16 and over
Summary The National Assembly adopted the law by a vote of 215-58. The new law requires full vaccination for such venues, including tourist sites, many trains and all domestic flights, and applies to everyone aged 16 and over. The law also imposes tougher fines for fake passes and allows ID checks to avoid fraud.</description></item><item><title>Biden says his administration will make free high-quality face masks available to all Americans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0f57088a5c3d6cee53246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0f57088a5c3d6cee53246/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Thursday announced his administration would make &amp;quot;high-quality masks&amp;quot; available to Americans for free, as the US struggles to contain the new surge of the Omicron variant and hospitalizations from Covid-19 reach new highs.
Summary Washington (CNN) President Joe Biden on Thursday announced his administration would make &amp;ldquo;high-quality masks&amp;rdquo; available to Americans for free, as the US struggles to contain the new surge of the Omicron variant and hospitalizations from Covid-19 reach new highs.</description></item><item><title>The highly contagious Omicron variant will 'find just about everybody,' Fauci says, but vaccinated people will still fare better</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df4f9397214fa7f9c39295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df4f9397214fa7f9c39295/</guid><description>Covid-19 hospitalizations in the United States have reached a new record high, surpassing the previous peak from January 2021, according to data from the US Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary More than 62% of the country has been fully vaccinated, but only 23% are fully vaccinated and boosted, according to data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. While fully vaccinated people are accounting for a larger share of Covid-19 hospitalizations, multiple accounts suggest that those who are fully vaccinated and boosted account for a small share.</description></item><item><title>US hospitals struggle to match Walmart pay as staff flees omicron</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da881a85181d78d62d09f0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da881a85181d78d62d09f0/</guid><description>Breaking news and updates from around the world.
Summary Some relief arrived in uniform in December: The state sent a couple of medics and other support staff from the National Guard. They mostly work in the emergency department, where every morning patients wait for hospital beds to open. Troy Bruntz runs Community Hospital, a 25-bed critical access facility in McCook, Nebraska. “That’s the only way we get people to come to work.</description></item><item><title>U.S. reports over 1 million new daily Covid cases as omicron surges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d47d2fef87438ece772a0d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d47d2fef87438ece772a0d/</guid><description>The U.S. also has the highest seven-day average of daily new cases in any country tracked by Johns Hopkins.
Summary Jeff Kowalsky | AFP | Getty ImagesThe U.S. has reported a record single-day number of daily Covid cases, with more than 1 million new infections. The new daily tally brings the total number of cases confirmed in the U.S. since the start of the pandemic to 56,189,547. Nonetheless, as of Jan.</description></item><item><title>Hundreds in Australia mistakenly told coronavirus test result was negative when they were positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca53a553ad5f95139afabc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca53a553ad5f95139afabc/</guid><description>The Sydney lab responsible blamed human error after hundreds with coronavirus were told they were negative amid record case numbers.
Summary A major laboratory in Australia incorrectly told 400 people their coronavirus test result was negative on Christmas Day, when they had actually tested positive for the virus. The lab responsible, based at St. Vincent&amp;rsquo;s Hospital in Sydney, sent incorrect text messages on the evening of Christmas Day telling people they did not have the virus.</description></item><item><title>First confirmed US death related to Omicron variant was unvaccinated and had been infected before</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 17:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c20832352ed51c0e863237/</guid><description>Description A Texas man, whose death was the first confirmed Omicron-related in the US, was unvaccinated and had previously been infected with the coronavirus, according to a press release from Harris County Public Health.
Summary A large crowd of people is seen wearing face masks as a preventive measure against the spread of coronavirus as they walk through a zebra crossing in Hong Kong, China, on 12 December 2021. (Miguel Candela/SOPA Images/LightRocket/Getty Images)Hong Kong will mandate all government employees to be fully vaccinated against Covid-19, or get tested for the virus every three days, authorities announced on Tuesday.</description></item></channel></rss>