<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>virginia on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/virginia/</link><description>Recent content in virginia on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 22:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/virginia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prince Andrew and Virginia Giuffre settle out of court over civil sex assault claim | UK News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c2544b5d1c99ee0fa655c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 22:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c2544b5d1c99ee0fa655c/</guid><description>Representatives for the duke say he will not be expanding beyond the statement filed in court and Ms Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s lawyer says: &amp;quot;I believe this event speaks for itself.&amp;quot;
Highlights Prince Andrew and Virginia Giuffre have settled out of court in her civil sex assault claim against him. Court documents show the parties had &amp;ldquo;reached a settlement in principle&amp;rdquo; Duke of York will make a &amp;ldquo;substantial donation&amp;rdquo; to Ms Giufre&amp;rsquo;s charity in support of victims' rights.</description></item><item><title>Deputy Virginia AG resigns after posts surface of her applauding Jan. 6 rioters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205cad80c6d2d1894afda44/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 02:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205cad80c6d2d1894afda44/</guid><description>A Republican deputy attorney general in Virginia resigned from her position Thursday after Facebook posts surfaced showing she had applauded Jan. 6 rioters and
Highlights Monique Miles resigned from her position Thursday after Facebook posts surfaced showing she had applauded Jan. 6 rioters and falsely claimed that Donald Trump won the 2020 presidential election. The Virginia attorney general&amp;rsquo;s office became aware of these posts by Miles Thursday when The Washington Post shared screenshots it obtained of her previous comments.</description></item><item><title>Virginia AG sues town where police threatened Black Army lieutenant during stop</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 03:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfc3cd26b5b35abba6ad52/</guid><description>Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.
Summary Virginia’s attorney general sued the town where a police officer appeared to threaten the execution of a Black Army lieutenant during a traffic stop, alleging Thursday that the city&amp;rsquo;s police department engages in a broader pattern of discriminatory policing.</description></item></channel></rss>