<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>share on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/share/</link><description>Recent content in share on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 06:17:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/share/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Watchdog finds DHS identified threats prior to January 6 but did not widely share intelligence until after attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622846192ceb355fd1e97aad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 06:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622846192ceb355fd1e97aad/</guid><description>The Department of Homeland Security intelligence division had identified &amp;quot;specific&amp;quot; threats related to January 6, 2021, prior to the attack on the US Capitol, but did not widely share any intelligence it had gathered until two days after the riot, according to a new watchdog report.
Highlights DHS intelligence division had identified “specific” threats related to January 6, 2021, prior to the attack on the US Capitol, a new watchdog report says.</description></item><item><title>SEC probes Elon Musk, brother Kimbal over Tesla share sales - WSJ</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621857d1bd80f98f747a9ba4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 04:15:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621857d1bd80f98f747a9ba4/</guid><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is investigating whether recent stock sales by Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk and his brother Kimbal Musk &amp;quot;violated insider trading rules&amp;quot;, the Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday, citing people familiar with the matter.
Highlights The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is investigating whether recent stock sales by Tesla CEO Elon Musk &amp;ldquo;violated insider trading rules&amp;rdquo; The Wall Street Journal reported on Thursday that the decision was made after Musk sent a tweet asking for information about his plans to sell his stock.</description></item></channel></rss>