<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wildlife on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wildlife/</link><description>Recent content in wildlife on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wildlife/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>9-year-old girl survives rare cougar attack in Washington</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62963e6987821c594dfb490f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62963e6987821c594dfb490f/</guid><description>The girl fought back while her friends ran for their lives.
Highlights Witnesses say a 9-year-old girl survived a cougar attack after wandering up a trail with two friends. The girl fought back while her friends ran for their lives. Adults rushed to help and found the girl covered in blood. She was soon airlifted to a hospital, where she’s recovering after surgery for multiple wounds to her head and upper body.</description></item><item><title>Wildlife activists make 11th hour plea to save koalas before Victorian blue gums logged</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281192c1851a76d9355fa57/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281192c1851a76d9355fa57/</guid><description>Wildlife campaigners have made a last ditch plea to the Victorian government to save koalas in a blue gum plantation due to be logged on Friday.
Highlights Victorian government approved clear-felling of the Gordon plantation by owner Midway Pty Ltd without relocating the koalas. The 16-hectare plantation is situated next to the Western Freeway, a major highway west of Melbourne. A report commissioned last month by landowner Central Highlands Water recommended the koala be relocated to an area 5km from the site.</description></item><item><title>Hunters kill 20 Yellowstone wolves that roamed out of park</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d84793dfc5d19c55c40337/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d84793dfc5d19c55c40337/</guid><description>Twenty of Yellowstone National Park’s renowned gray wolves roamed from the park and were shot by hunters in neighboring states in recent months
Summary Twenty of Yellowstone National Park’s renowned gray wolves roamed from the park and were shot by hunters in neighboring states in recent monthsBILLINGS, Mont. Park Superintendent Cam Sholly first raised concerns last September about wolves dying near the park border. “Allowances for trapping and especially baiting are a major concern, especially if these tactics lure wolves out of the park,” Yellowstone spokesperson Morgan Warthin said.</description></item></channel></rss>