<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>interest on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/interest/</link><description>Recent content in interest on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 12:15:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/interest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Multiple people shot in Tennessee, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629363abfe557847be52d29e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 12:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629363abfe557847be52d29e/</guid><description>Multiple people were shot on Saturday night during an exchange of gunfire in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, police said.
Highlights At least six people were injured in an exchange of gunfire in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, police said. Police officers were patrolling downtown at about 10:48 p.m. local time when they &amp;ldquo;observed multiple parties exchanging gunfire and numerous people fleeing the area&amp;rdquo; Most of the victims were in their teens or early 20s.</description></item><item><title>Brooklyn subway shooting: Suspect Frank James posted racist rants to YouTube for years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6257134ca769d476db4dc20e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 18:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6257134ca769d476db4dc20e/</guid><description>Frank James, now considered a suspect in connection with the Brooklyn subway shooting, posted a string of antagonistic video rants to a YouTube channel for years.
Highlights Frank James posted hour-long, profanity-laced rants on YouTube channel for years. Police have identified James as a person of interest in the Brooklyn subway shooting. James posted rants about race, politics and current events. At times, he sharply criticized Black Europeans and Americans using strings of slurs and racism, as well as women and the homeless.</description></item><item><title>Pennsylvania high school on lockdown after shooting, district says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c945614e63c644e1d6e44/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 19:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c945614e63c644e1d6e44/</guid><description>A student at Erie High School in Pennsylvania was injured during a shooting Monday morning, and a person of interest fled, according to officials.
Highlights Multiple shots were fired at Erie High School shortly after 9:20 a.m., Erie’s Public Schools said in a statement. One student was injured but stable, the district said in the afternoon. Police are searching for a person of interest who fled the campus. The school will be closed leading up to spring break, which begins next week, according to district.</description></item><item><title>Outlets hurt by dwindling public interest in news in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca61aa085cc54e084f7f8a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 01:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca61aa085cc54e084f7f8a/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. To a large degree, 2021 represented the inevitable hangover.
Summary (AP Photo)NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. The Trump era saw explosive subscriber growth for some digital news sites like The New York Times and Washington Post.</description></item></channel></rss>