<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>texas on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/texas/</link><description>Recent content in texas on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 09:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/texas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas school shooting victims take action against gunmaker</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b214e7cfe123158370b5d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 09:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b214e7cfe123158370b5d/</guid><description>The father of a 10-year-old girl slain in the Uvalde, Texas, school shooting and a school employee have taken initial steps that could lead to lawsuits against Daniel Defense, the maker of the semiautomatic rifle used in last week&amp;rsquo;s massacre that killed 21 people.
Highlights Father of slain girl and school employee have taken initial steps that could lead to lawsuits against Daniel Defense, maker of the semiautomatic rifle used in last week&amp;rsquo;s massacre that killed 21 people.</description></item><item><title>Police: Man in Texas smashes ancient museum artifacts worth millions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299a62a58af4cc2164fc159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299a62a58af4cc2164fc159/</guid><description>According to police, the man used a metal chair to break into the museum.
Highlights Brian Hernandez, 21, is charged with criminal mischief of more than or equal to $300,000. He was booked Thursday into the Dallas County jail with bond set at $100,000. Jail records list no attorney for Hernandez. Police say he used a metal chair to break into the museum, smashed three ancient Greek artifacts before he was arrested.</description></item><item><title>'Very angry': Uvalde locals grapple with school chief's role</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296679932f948d7a5147fa7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 19:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296679932f948d7a5147fa7/</guid><description>UVALDE, Texas (AP) — The blame for an excruciating delay in killing the gunman at a Texas elementary school — even as parents outside begged police to rush in and panicked children called 911 from inside — has been placed with the school district&amp;rsquo;s homegrown police chief.
Highlights Pete Arredondo was set to be sworn in Tuesday to his new spot on the City Council after being elected earlier this month.</description></item><item><title>Anonymous donor pays all funeral expenses for Uvalde shooting victims</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62939b025f9797e23073b791/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62939b025f9797e23073b791/</guid><description>Anonymous donor pays all funeral expenses for Uvalde shooting victims. Cost of all of the funeral expenses totaled about $175,000. Texas Gov. Greg Abbott briefed the public on the mental health services that will be available to those affected
Highlights Anonymous donor pays all funeral expenses for Uvalde shooting victims. Cost of all of the funeral expenses totaled about $175,000. Texas Gov. Greg Abbott briefed the public on the mental health services that will be available to those affected by the murders.</description></item><item><title>Police face questions over response to Uvalde school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628feca253e1a461385da575/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 21:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628feca253e1a461385da575/</guid><description>A Texas law enforcement official now says the 18-year-old gunman who slaughtered 21 people, including 19 children, at an elementary school entered the building &amp;quot;unobstructed&amp;quot; through a door that was apparently unlocked.
Highlights The gunman entered the school &amp;ldquo;unobstructed,&amp;rdquo; a law enforcement official says. The gunman was apparently inside the building for at least three-quarters of an hour before U.S. Border Patrol agents stormed a classroom and killed him. The motive for the Texas school shooting is still under investigation.</description></item><item><title>Victims' families urged armed police officers to charge into Uvalde school while massacre carried on for upwards of 40 minutes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f5fb153bb8489e43ce645/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f5fb153bb8489e43ce645/</guid><description>A mass shooting at a Texas elementary school left 19 children and two adults dead, adding to a gruesome series of mass killings in America.
Highlights Gunman killed at least 19 fourth-graders and two teachers in Uvalde, Texas. Salvador Ramos, 18, crashed his truck into a ditch outside the school, grabbed his AR-15-style semi-automatic rifle and shot at two people outside a nearby funeral home who ran away uninjured. Ramos then fired on two arriving police officers who were outside the building, a Texas Department of Public Safety spokesperson said.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families’ defamation damages trial against Alex Jones to move forward in CT</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628daebfb0b099bc309dc2b2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:21:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628daebfb0b099bc309dc2b2/</guid><description>Representatives for Alex Jones and the Sandy Hook families reached an agreement in&amp;hellip;
Highlights A federal judge clears the way for Sandy Hook families to have the defamation lawsuit they won against Alex Jones released from bankruptcy protection. The families&amp;rsquo; target will be Jones himself and his parent company Free Speech Systems. A trial to determine the damages Jones must pay for calling the worst crime in Connecticut history “staged,’ “synthetic,” “manufactured,“ and “a giant hoax” A federal bankruptcy judge in Texas released Jones from Chapter 11 protection and sent his defamation cases back to state court in Texas.</description></item><item><title>36-Year-Old Arrested in Dallas Salon Shooting, Possible Hate Crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62862539b75f880c3b0eacf3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 11:09:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62862539b75f880c3b0eacf3/</guid><description>Investigators believe Smith was the gunman that opened fire on the salon in Dallas&amp;rsquo; Koreatown last Wednesday.
Highlights Investigators believe Smith was the gunman that opened fire on the salon in Dallas&amp;rsquo; Koreatown. 36-year-old arrested in Dallas salon shooting, possible hate crime, police believe it was a hate crime. Smith is the suspect in the shooting, which is believed to be a hate-filled crime. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>ERCOT Asks Texans to Conserve Power Until 8 P.M., Through the Weekend</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f72e6104fd436f0e26b0e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f72e6104fd436f0e26b0e/</guid><description>ERCOT asking all Texans to conserve energy through the weekend as we head into potentially record heat.
Highlights ERCOT asks all Texans to conserve energy through the weekend as we head into potentially record heat. Six power plants dropped off the grid Friday, resulting in a loss of about 2,900 MW of generation &amp;ndash; that&amp;rsquo;s enough electricity to power about 580,000 homes. The Electric Reliability Council of Texas said, &amp;ldquo;unseasonably hot weather&amp;rdquo; was driving record demand across Texas.</description></item><item><title>Rewards offered after dolphin 'harassed to death' on Texas beach, another impaled in Florida</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627653f562aab06a76a83955/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 11:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627653f562aab06a76a83955/</guid><description>Rewards are being offered in two recent deadly incidents involving dolphins — one that was “harassed to death” on a Texas beach and a second in Florida that
Highlights A $20,000 reward is being offered in a March 24 case, in which a dolphin was found dead from impalement with a spear-like object on a Fort Myers Beach, Florida. That dolphin died after washing ashore at Quintana Beach, southwest of Galveston, on April 10.</description></item><item><title>Over Sandy Hook families’ objections, federal judge gives Alex Jones time to defend bankruptcy plans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d523564eac54187309fcf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 15:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d523564eac54187309fcf/</guid><description>A federal judge gave Sandy Hook families awaiting defamation damages trials in&amp;hellip;
Highlights A federal judge agreed to hear motions to dismiss Alex Jones’ bankruptcies as “bad faith’s” filings. The judge also gave Jones attorneys enough breathing room to prepare an unhurried defense of their plan to pay the Sandy Hook families defamation damages Jones owes without putting Infowars out of business. Jones has suffered financially since he called the worst crime in Connecticut history “staged” and “manufactured” “a giant hoax,” his representatives said in court.</description></item><item><title>Texas attorney general says school district’s Pride week ‘breaks state law’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e2273328c947f122d03a5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 20:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e2273328c947f122d03a5/</guid><description>Ken Paxton called district’s Pride week ‘sex education’ and claimed without parental consent it is against law
Highlights Texas attorney general Ken Paxton sent a letter to the Austin school district calling Pride week ‘sex education’ and notifying the school that without parental consent, the celebration is “breaking state law” The district has held Pride week for the past eight years as a chance to celebrate LGBTQ+ students, staff and families in the district.</description></item><item><title>‘Nostalgic racism is racism’: Disney criticised for Texas students’ performance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623646fa4c8c83cdf77c3a5f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623646fa4c8c83cdf77c3a5f/</guid><description>Walt Disney World apologises after Texas high school drill team chants ‘Scalp ’em, Indians, scalp ’em’ during performance
Highlights Disney apologises after Texas high school drill team sings &amp;lsquo;Scalp &amp;rsquo;em, Indians, scalp &amp;rsquo;em&amp;rsquo; The performance did not reflect Disney&amp;rsquo;s core values, a spokesperson said. Native American advocates criticised Disney and Port Neches-Groves high school after video of the performance was posted to Twitter. Disney has added disclaimers to some of its older material, for instance, that the 1953 film Peter Pan shows indigenous people “in a stereotypical manner” and other films are flagged for featuring “negative depictions and/or mistreatment of people or cultures” The entertainment giant has faced backlash over its response to Florida’s controversial Parental Rights in Education act.</description></item><item><title>Texas judge blocks investigations into parents of trans children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c63f24578b3189de8a9c7/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 09:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622c63f24578b3189de8a9c7/</guid><description>A Texas judge on Friday blocked the state from investigating as child abuse gender-confirming care for transgender youth.
Highlights District Judge Amy Clark Meachum issued a temporary injunction preventing the state from enforcing Republican Gov. Greg Abbott’s directive to compel the Department of Family and Protective Services to investigate gender-confirming care for transgender youth. The ACLU and Lambda Legal sued on behalf of the parents of a family with a trans child.</description></item><item><title>Texas loses appeal over investigation of transgender teen’s family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a77fa0142694bc51b6806/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a77fa0142694bc51b6806/</guid><description>The Texas 3rd Court of Appeals dismissed Republican Attorney General Ken Paxton’s appeal of the temporary order a judge issued last week halting the investigation by the Department of Family and Protective Services into the parents of the 16-year-old girl.
Highlights Court of Appeals rules ruling against ruling on gender-confirming parents&amp;rsquo; rights. Court also throws out order to stop state of Texas law requiring parents to report child sex abuse. The order was issued last week in response to the judge’s decision to halt the order.</description></item><item><title>Texas abortion seekers flooded out-of-state clinics after six-week ban went into effect, Planned Parenthood records show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62188148d44286e41ebf1da1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 07:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62188148d44286e41ebf1da1/</guid><description>Planned Parenthood clinics in the five states neighboring Texas saw a nearly 800% increase in abortion patients from the Lone&amp;hellip; (25 Feb 2022, 12:24 am)
Highlights Texas abortion seekers flooded out-of-state clinics after six-week ban went into effect, Planned Parenthood records show. Colorado and Oklahoma clinics saw some of the biggest surges. Planned Parenthood clinics in the five states neighboring Texas saw a nearly 800% increase in abortion patients from the Lone Star State after the ban went in effect in September, the organization said Thursday.</description></item></channel></rss>