<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>capitol on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/capitol/</link><description>Recent content in capitol on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/capitol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez tests positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</guid><description>&amp;quot;She is experiencing symptoms and recovering at home,&amp;quot; her office said in a statement on Sunday.
Summary Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has tested positive for COVID-19, her office said in a statement on Sunday. The CDC recommends that Americans who test positive for COVID-19 and develop symptoms isolate for at least five full days. COVID-19 cases continue to surge across the country, with an average of nearly 700,000 new cases reported per day, according to the CDC.</description></item><item><title>Capitol Police intelligence official says she sounded alarm about potential violence days before January 6 riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</guid><description>&amp;quot;We knew there were going to be thousands of protesters. And we knew there were gonna be extremists there,&amp;quot; the official said.
Summary Three days before the January 6 riot, a top Capitol Police intelligence official sounded the alarm about potential violence at the U.S. Capitol. Julie Farnam, now the acting director of intelligence for the Capitol Police, had been with the department for 72 days when violent protestors attacked the Capitol on January 6th.</description></item><item><title>More police officers sue Trump over January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</guid><description>Police officers are suing the former president for alleged wrongful conduct and inciting a riot.
Summary Three more law enforcement officers are suing former President Trump in two separate lawsuits over his words and actions leading up to the January 6, 2021, assault on the Capitol. &amp;ldquo;When Officer Tabron finally did get home around midnight, he removed his chemical-soaked clothes, showered, and tried to sleep. &amp;ldquo;The weight on Officer Moore has been heavy and inescapable.</description></item></channel></rss>