<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>capitol on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/capitol/</link><description>Recent content in capitol on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 12:16:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/capitol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EXPLAINER: Hundreds charged with crimes in Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f415f0320a96268ad331a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 12:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f415f0320a96268ad331a/</guid><description>More than 800 people across the U.S. have been charged in the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol, which left officers bloodied and sent lawmakers into hiding, and federal authorities continue to make new arrests practically every week.
Highlights More than 800 people across the U.S. have been charged in the Jan. 6 riot at the Capitol that left officers bloodied and sent lawmakers running in fear, and federal authorities continue to make new arrests practically every week.</description></item><item><title>Jury finds alleged Nazi sympathizer guilty of 5 charges ranging from obstruction to disorderly conduct in Jan. 6 case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62922d16bf98057cb63f4582/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 14:10:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62922d16bf98057cb63f4582/</guid><description>Thomas Hale-Cusanelli, an alleged Nazi sympathizer and Army reservist, was charged with obstructing an official proceeding.
Highlights Thomas Hale-Cusanelli, an alleged Nazi sympathizer and Army reservist, was charged with obstructing an official proceeding. He was found guilty on five charges ranging from obstruction to disorderly conduct in the Capitol riot case. The jury was shown video, audio and social media images, as well as text messages involving his actions on and before the Jan.</description></item><item><title>NYPD veteran convicted of assaulting officer in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627057bfd2ba74e3f6bc59c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 22:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627057bfd2ba74e3f6bc59c6/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal jury on Monday convicted a New York Police Department veteran of assaulting an officer during the U.S.
Highlights Thomas Webster is the first Capitol riot defendant to be tried on an assault charge and the first to present a jury with a self-defense argument. Webster, a 20-year NYPD veteran, testified that he was trying to protect himself from a “rogue cop” who punched him in the face.</description></item><item><title>D.C. board rules that officer who committed suicide after Jan. 6 died in line of duty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ab0bdc8074f88ac32ee88/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 02:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ab0bdc8074f88ac32ee88/</guid><description>A District of Columbia retirement board has ruled that a police officer died in the line of duty when he took his own life due to injuries he suffered during the Jan. 6, 2021, riot at the U.S. Capitol, the Washington Post reported.
Highlights Washington&amp;rsquo;s Police and Firefighters&amp;rsquo; Retirement and Relief Board said in a letter on Monday that Jan. 6 was the &amp;ldquo;sole and direct cause&amp;rdquo; of Jeffrey Smith&amp;rsquo;s suicide.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioter from Idaho gets 4 years for attacking police with pipe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62240471aa5e446be35bc120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62240471aa5e446be35bc120/</guid><description>An Idaho man who hit a police officer with a pipe as part of the mob that stormed the U.S.
Highlights Idaho man sentenced to more than four years in federal prison. Duke Edward Wilson, 68, hit a police officer with a pipe as part of the mob that stormed the U.S. Capitol. Prosecutors said he attacked at least three officers in a tunnel in the Capitol Building on Jan. 6, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioter ordered back to jail after DWI arrest, AR-15 rifle discovered in car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8d048cb6990eaabe4cbcc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 03:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8d048cb6990eaabe4cbcc/</guid><description>An accused Capitol rioter has been ordered to be returned to federal custody after he tried to flee an arrest for suspected drunk driving last month and police discovered an AR-15 rifle in his car.
Summary James Tate Grant, who is accused of attacking a Capitol Police officer in the Jan. 6, 2021, riot. As he was being arrested, Grant tried to flee, the filing said. In Grant’s car, police recovered an AR-15 assault rifle, 60 rounds of ammunition, weapon accessories and combat fatigues, court documents said.</description></item><item><title>Woman with semi-automatic rifle, other guns in vehicle arrested outside U.S. Capitol Police headquarters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0d942a82850dcb118deda/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 02:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0d942a82850dcb118deda/</guid><description>The arrest came less than a week after officials marked​ the first anniversary of the January 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol​.
Summary A woman was arrested Wednesday outside the headquarters for the U.S. Capitol Police after police saw a gun case and the butt of a long gun in her vehicle, the police said. The woman, identified as Kery Lynn McAttee, is facing multiple weapons charges, the police said in a statement to CBS News.</description></item><item><title>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez tests positive for COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc58433907501fb4c758cd/</guid><description>&amp;quot;She is experiencing symptoms and recovering at home,&amp;quot; her office said in a statement on Sunday.
Summary Representative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has tested positive for COVID-19, her office said in a statement on Sunday. The CDC recommends that Americans who test positive for COVID-19 and develop symptoms isolate for at least five full days. COVID-19 cases continue to surge across the country, with an average of nearly 700,000 new cases reported per day, according to the CDC.</description></item><item><title>Capitol Police intelligence official says she sounded alarm about potential violence days before January 6 riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d6777bfee84c366eefc894/</guid><description>&amp;quot;We knew there were going to be thousands of protesters. And we knew there were gonna be extremists there,&amp;quot; the official said.
Summary Three days before the January 6 riot, a top Capitol Police intelligence official sounded the alarm about potential violence at the U.S. Capitol. Julie Farnam, now the acting director of intelligence for the Capitol Police, had been with the department for 72 days when violent protestors attacked the Capitol on January 6th.</description></item><item><title>More police officers sue Trump over January 6</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5f8f79f91de6c8c161726/</guid><description>Police officers are suing the former president for alleged wrongful conduct and inciting a riot.
Summary Three more law enforcement officers are suing former President Trump in two separate lawsuits over his words and actions leading up to the January 6, 2021, assault on the Capitol. &amp;ldquo;When Officer Tabron finally did get home around midnight, he removed his chemical-soaked clothes, showered, and tried to sleep. &amp;ldquo;The weight on Officer Moore has been heavy and inescapable.</description></item></channel></rss>