<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>county on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/county/</link><description>Recent content in county on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:45:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/county/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One dead, seven wounded after shootout at Memorial Day festival in Muskogee County</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629413749e0d44e1b8e0f110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:45:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629413749e0d44e1b8e0f110/</guid><description>Skyler Buckner, 26, surrendered to the Muskogee County Sheriff’s Office and the Oklahoma State Bureau of Investigation Sunday afternoon. The shooting took place at a Memorial Day festival in Taft just after midnight. One of
Highlights Skyler Buckner surrendered to authorities Sunday, wanted in connection with a shooting in Taft, Oklahoma. The shooting took place at a Memorial Day festival just after midnight. The deceased is a 39-year-old Black female; the other seven injured range in age from 9 to 56.</description></item><item><title>Andy Dick Arrested On Suspicion Of Sexual Battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d4296538f1b17bd656504/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 17:24:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d4296538f1b17bd656504/</guid><description>Comedian Andy Dick was arrested Wednesday at a campground in Orange County, California, on suspicion of sexual battery, authorities said.
Highlights Comedian Andy Dick was arrested Wednesday at a campground in Orange County, California, on suspicion of sexual battery. The Orange County Sheriff’s Department responded to O’Neill Regional Park around 9 a.m. after the adult male victim called authorities about a possible sexual assault. It was not immediately clear whether Dick had an attorney who could speak on his behalf in the incident.</description></item><item><title>Stolen pizza, Pokémon cards lead to deadly deputy shooting in Osceola County, records show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e25d0f923710d95bca9c5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 06:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e25d0f923710d95bca9c5/</guid><description>Two men stealing a pizza and several packs of Pokémon cards from a Target lead to a deadly deputy shooting Wednesday night, records released Thursday revealed.
Highlights Two men were seen stealing a pizza and packs of Pokémon cards from a Target. Two deputies opened fire, killing one man, according to Osceola County Sheriff Marcos Lopez. In addition to the man who was killed, another person was hit in the hand by bullet shrapnel.</description></item><item><title>Ohio doctor accused of overprescribing fentanyl to the dying found not guilty of murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626041d367cc9212831ee792/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 17:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626041d367cc9212831ee792/</guid><description>The Ohio doctor accused of overprescribing fentanyl to his critically ill patients and hastening their deaths was found not guilty of 14 counts of murder on Wednesday.
Highlights William Husel was accused of overprescribing fentanyl to dying patients in the intensive care unit from 2015 to 2018. He was indicted on 25 counts of murder, though 11 of those counts were dismissed pretrial. Husel&amp;rsquo;s former colleagues testified that he was a wonderful doctor who was hardworking, fought to save people&amp;rsquo;s lives.</description></item><item><title>Suspect in South Carolina mall shooting on house arrest after judge sets $25,000 bond</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625ce702a7547db4a33b8d5c/</guid><description>The suspect in a South Carolina mall shooting in which nine people were wounded has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor after
Highlights Nine people were injured in a shooting in South Carolina early Sunday morning. The victims are ages 15 to 73. The suspect has been released under house arrest and ordered to wear an ankle monitor. Police say no deaths have been reported in the shooting in Hampton County, South Carolina.</description></item><item><title>Man, 21, arrested a week after 3 killed at Georgia gun range</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bb0be25355fae30fb333c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 06:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625bb0be25355fae30fb333c/</guid><description>GRANTVILLE, Ga. (AP) — A 21-year-old man has been arrested in connection with a fatal armed robbery at a Georgia gun range that left three members of a family dead last week. Jacob Christian Muse, of College Park, is charged with three counts of malice murder, the Georgia Bureau of Investigation said in a news release Friday.
Highlights Jacob Christian Muse, of College Park, is charged with three counts of malice murder.</description></item><item><title>Woman arrested in Starr County on murder for ‘illegal abortion’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250fbe7bc6d7171551680c0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 03:22:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250fbe7bc6d7171551680c0/</guid><description>Law enforcement authorities in Starr County confirmed that a woman was arrested on a charge of murder over what they called an &amp;quot;illegal abortion.&amp;quot;
Highlights Lizelle Herrera, 26, was arrested and served with an indictment “on the charge of Murder’s Murder after Herrera did then and there intentionally and knowingly cause the death of an individual by self-induced abortion” Her arrest comes as Texas enacted one of the strictest abortion laws in the country last year in SB 8 which encourages private citizens to sue individuals or organizations that help people get an abortion after six weeks of gestation.</description></item><item><title>Judge sides with 12 disabled kids seeking masks in schools</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e8607b8a7151655a1fece/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 03:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e8607b8a7151655a1fece/</guid><description>RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A federal judge has ruled that an executive order and new Virginia law allowing parents to opt their children out of classroom COVID-19 mask mandates cannot prevent 12 vulnerable students from seeking a “reasonable modification” that could include a requirement that their classmates wear masks.
Highlights A federal judge has ruled that an executive order and new Virginia law allowing parents to opt their children out of classroom COVID-19 mask mandates cannot prevent 12 vulnerable students from seeking a “reasonable modification” that could include a requirement that their classmates wear masks.</description></item><item><title>Maryland’s last public Confederate monument removed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623004e7a92592caa2f2de9b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623004e7a92592caa2f2de9b/</guid><description>A statue that was thought to be the last Confederate monument on a courthouse lawn in Maryland has been removed.
Highlights The “Talbot Boys Statue’ was relocated Monday. The statue stood on the Talbot County courthouse lawn in Easton for more than a century. A coalition raised more than $80,000 to relocate it to a historic battlefield in Virginia. The sculpture features a boy holding a Confederate flag and names the men from the Eastern Shore county who joined the Confederacy and died in the war.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after colleague in bulldozer accidentally runs over port-a-potty he was using, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 05:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</guid><description>A Florida landfill worker died Friday after a colleague in a bulldozer accidentally ran over the port-a-potty he was using, authorities said.
Highlights Aaron Henderson, 40, worked for CertiTemp, a company contracted by Polk County, Florida. He was pronounced dead on the scene. Investigators determined that a fellow bulldozer employee was putting the bulldozer away for the day when he drove up an embankment, with the front blade of his bulldozer “elevated 3-4 feet off the ground,” according to the sheriff’s office.</description></item><item><title>8-year-old girl killed in drive-by shooting in South Florida, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024fb5098e79d70a221f20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:11:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024fb5098e79d70a221f20/</guid><description>An 8-year-old girl was shot and killed in a drive-by shooting in South Florida, according to the Palm Beach County Sheriff’s Office.
Highlights An 8-year-old girl was shot and killed in a drive-by shooting in South Florida. Deputies responded to the 500 block of SE 1st Street in Belle Glade where they found the girl shot multiple times. Family members said the child was critically hurt and she died after being rushed to the hospital.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey plow driver who sprayed Orthodox Jews with snow during storm facing criminal probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</guid><description>The snow plow driver in Lakewood, New Jersey, who cast a wave of snow and ice from his plow onto two Orthodox Jewish men walking along a roadway has been suspended from his job and could face criminal charges, pending the outcome of a police investigation. Video of the act, which appears to have been intentional, was posted on social media. A passenger recorded the video with his phone as the driver approached the two men walking along County Line Road near the Jackson Township border.</description></item><item><title>Uyghur woman sentenced for 14 years for teaching Islam, hiding Qurans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbbd6e8cd39bc4dc4118c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbbd6e8cd39bc4dc4118c6/</guid><description>Hasiyet Ehmet has not been heard from since her abduction four years ago.
Summary A Manas county court official confirmed that Hasiyet Ehmet had been sentenced to 14 years. “It was because of teaching kids the Quran and hiding two copies of Quran when authorities were confiscating them, and later getting caught,” the official said. Hasiyet had stopped teaching children two years before her arrest because of health problems. Authorities did not try Hasiyet on the charges in court, but instead sent a court verdict letter to her family, the person said.</description></item></channel></rss>