<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>county on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/county/</link><description>Recent content in county on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 03:19:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/county/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Judge sides with 12 disabled kids seeking masks in schools</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e8607b8a7151655a1fece/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 03:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e8607b8a7151655a1fece/</guid><description>RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A federal judge has ruled that an executive order and new Virginia law allowing parents to opt their children out of classroom COVID-19 mask mandates cannot prevent 12 vulnerable students from seeking a “reasonable modification” that could include a requirement that their classmates wear masks.
Highlights A federal judge has ruled that an executive order and new Virginia law allowing parents to opt their children out of classroom COVID-19 mask mandates cannot prevent 12 vulnerable students from seeking a “reasonable modification” that could include a requirement that their classmates wear masks.</description></item><item><title>Maryland’s last public Confederate monument removed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623004e7a92592caa2f2de9b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623004e7a92592caa2f2de9b/</guid><description>A statue that was thought to be the last Confederate monument on a courthouse lawn in Maryland has been removed.
Highlights The “Talbot Boys Statue’ was relocated Monday. The statue stood on the Talbot County courthouse lawn in Easton for more than a century. A coalition raised more than $80,000 to relocate it to a historic battlefield in Virginia. The sculpture features a boy holding a Confederate flag and names the men from the Eastern Shore county who joined the Confederacy and died in the war.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after colleague in bulldozer accidentally runs over port-a-potty he was using, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 05:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</guid><description>A Florida landfill worker died Friday after a colleague in a bulldozer accidentally ran over the port-a-potty he was using, authorities said.
Highlights Aaron Henderson, 40, worked for CertiTemp, a company contracted by Polk County, Florida. He was pronounced dead on the scene. Investigators determined that a fellow bulldozer employee was putting the bulldozer away for the day when he drove up an embankment, with the front blade of his bulldozer “elevated 3-4 feet off the ground,” according to the sheriff’s office.</description></item><item><title>8-year-old girl killed in drive-by shooting in South Florida, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024fb5098e79d70a221f20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:11:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62024fb5098e79d70a221f20/</guid><description>An 8-year-old girl was shot and killed in a drive-by shooting in South Florida, according to the Palm Beach County Sheriff’s Office.
Highlights An 8-year-old girl was shot and killed in a drive-by shooting in South Florida. Deputies responded to the 500 block of SE 1st Street in Belle Glade where they found the girl shot multiple times. Family members said the child was critically hurt and she died after being rushed to the hospital.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey plow driver who sprayed Orthodox Jews with snow during storm facing criminal probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb56e03356d4c43700fa4e/</guid><description>The snow plow driver in Lakewood, New Jersey, who cast a wave of snow and ice from his plow onto two Orthodox Jewish men walking along a roadway has been suspended from his job and could face criminal charges, pending the outcome of a police investigation. Video of the act, which appears to have been intentional, was posted on social media. A passenger recorded the video with his phone as the driver approached the two men walking along County Line Road near the Jackson Township border.</description></item><item><title>Uyghur woman sentenced for 14 years for teaching Islam, hiding Qurans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbbd6e8cd39bc4dc4118c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbbd6e8cd39bc4dc4118c6/</guid><description>Hasiyet Ehmet has not been heard from since her abduction four years ago.
Summary A Manas county court official confirmed that Hasiyet Ehmet had been sentenced to 14 years. “It was because of teaching kids the Quran and hiding two copies of Quran when authorities were confiscating them, and later getting caught,” the official said. Hasiyet had stopped teaching children two years before her arrest because of health problems. Authorities did not try Hasiyet on the charges in court, but instead sent a court verdict letter to her family, the person said.</description></item></channel></rss>