<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>buffalo on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/buffalo/</link><description>Recent content in buffalo on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 23:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/buffalo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>911 dispatcher fired after allegedly hanging up on store employee during Buffalo shooting call</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a946ffd4003af0917ad8f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 23:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a946ffd4003af0917ad8f/</guid><description>The 911 dispatcher accused of hanging up on an employee calling for help during the supermarket shooting that killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, last month has been fired, officials said.
Highlights The 911 dispatcher accused of hanging up on an employee calling for help during the supermarket shooting that killed 10 Black people in Buffalo, New York, last month has been fired, officials said. The assistant office manager at Tops Friendly Market called 911 when a white gunman, 18, stormed the store on May 14 and opened fire.</description></item><item><title>Amazon’s Twitch, Discord, 4chan face New York AG probe after Buffalo shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285ed4fa471f2a8fba31693/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285ed4fa471f2a8fba31693/</guid><description>Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Twitch, Discord, 4chan and 8chan will be among the platforms her office will probe.
Highlights New York&amp;rsquo;s Attorney General Letitia James will investigate social media companies in connection to the shooting. The shooter initially livestreamed his actions to Twitch during the massacre at Tops grocery store on Saturday. James&amp;rsquo; office will also focus on 4chan, 8chan and Discord, but is not limited to those platforms. Investigators will look at online resources the gunman &amp;ldquo;used to discuss and amplify his intentions and acts to carry out this attack,&amp;rdquo; the AG said in a statement.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo shooter's prior threat, hospital stay face scrutiny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628287d793848ae566447b38/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 17:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628287d793848ae566447b38/</guid><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The white gunman accused of a racist rampage at a Buffalo supermarket planned to keep killing if he had escaped the scene, the police commissioner said Monday, as authorities investigated the massacre of 10 Black people as a potential hate crime or act of domestic terrorism.
Highlights Police: Buffalo gunman aimed to keep killing if he got away. Payton Gendron, 18, had threatened to carry out a shooting at Susquehanna Valley High School in Conklin around graduation, a law enforcement official says.</description></item></channel></rss>