<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cadets on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cadets/</link><description>Recent content in cadets on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 17:13:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cadets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man, 21, accused of selling fentanyl-laced cocaine to West Point spring breakers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e2616c01f0f9f41bf39f4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 17:13:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622e2616c01f0f9f41bf39f4/</guid><description>Prosecutors accused a 21-year-old man of selling the fentanyl-laced cocaine that had spring breakers dependent on intensive care ventilators at a Broward County hospital.
Highlights Axel Giovany Casseus, 21, is accused of selling the fentany-laced cocaine that caused 7 overdoses. The tragedy on Thursday at a rental home in Wilton Manors included four cadets from the U.S. Military Academy at West Point. Four of the seven hospitalized voluntarily ingested the cocaine; the other three came into contact with it when they performed cardiopulmonary resuscitation.</description></item><item><title>6 West Point cadets overdose on fentanyl during spring break, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cd4746dfe881370939d71/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 17:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622cd4746dfe881370939d71/</guid><description>Six West Point cadets on spring break in Fort Lauderdale were hospitalized after overdosing on a powder substance laced with the drug fentanyl, police said Friday.
Highlights Six West Point cadets on spring break in Fort Lauderdale were hospitalized after overdosing on a powder substance laced with the drug fentanyl. Authorities in Broward County, Florida, have made an arrest in connection to the overdoses. The names of the students have not been released, though police said the college students are from New York.</description></item></channel></rss>