<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prisoners on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prisoners/</link><description>Recent content in prisoners on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:18:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prisoners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In Mariupol, the occupiers plan a war crime, a “parade of prisoners”. The Ukrainian serviceman remembers a similar “parade” in 2014 in Donetsk, and human rights activists explain how Russia will be punished for it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278b20bbde588aecb3df8d0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278b20bbde588aecb3df8d0/</guid><description>In Mariupol, the occupiers are planning to hold &amp;quot;parade of prisoners&amp;quot; on May 9. A similar one was held on August 24, 2014 in Donetsk. Vasyl Stasiev is planning the parad. Lawyers explain why it is a war crime.
Highlights Vasyl Stasiev was in captivity from August 13 to December 26, 2014. The only thing I remember from that &amp;ldquo;parade&amp;rdquo; is the beastly crowd. The feeling was that they were ready just to attack us and tear us apart.</description></item><item><title>Guantanamo Bay detainee allowed to return to Saudi Arabia after 20 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62279d227c071d2575c88541/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 18:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62279d227c071d2575c88541/</guid><description>Mohammad Ahmad al-Qahtani was accused of attempting to enter the US to hijack planes in the September 11 attack
Highlights Mohammad Ahmad al-Qahtani has been flown back to Saudi Arabia for mental health treatment. The 46-year-old prisoner has suffered from mental illness, including schizophrenia, since childhood. He was accused of attempting to join hijackers in carrying out the September 11 attacks. The US dropped plans to try him after a Bush administration legal official concluded he had been tortured at Guantánamo.</description></item></channel></rss>