<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>entered on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/entered/</link><description>Recent content in entered on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 04:13:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/entered/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Federal agents entered Uvalde school to kill gunman despite local police initially asking them to wait</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291a14b959660ffebec7e82/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 04:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291a14b959660ffebec7e82/</guid><description>Federal agents who went to Robb Elementary in Uvalde, Tex., on Tuesday to confront a gunman were told by local police to wait, but chose to enter the school.
Highlights Federal agents who went to Robb Elementary School in Uvalde, Texas, on Tuesday to confront a gunman were told by local police to wait and not enter the school. After about half an hour, the federal agents opted of their own volition to lead the “stack” of officers inside the school and take down the shooter, two senior federal law enforcement officials say.</description></item><item><title>Police face questions over response to Uvalde school shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628feca253e1a461385da575/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 21:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628feca253e1a461385da575/</guid><description>A Texas law enforcement official now says the 18-year-old gunman who slaughtered 21 people, including 19 children, at an elementary school entered the building &amp;quot;unobstructed&amp;quot; through a door that was apparently unlocked.
Highlights The gunman entered the school &amp;ldquo;unobstructed,&amp;rdquo; a law enforcement official says. The gunman was apparently inside the building for at least three-quarters of an hour before U.S. Border Patrol agents stormed a classroom and killed him. The motive for the Texas school shooting is still under investigation.</description></item></channel></rss>