<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fight on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fight/</link><description>Recent content in fight on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 13:16:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Over 66,200 Ukrainian men have returned from abroad to fight, says defence minister</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223626f69d933810172928a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223626f69d933810172928a/</guid><description>Ukrainian Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Saturday that 66,224 Ukrainian men had returned from abroad to join the fight against Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion.
Highlights Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Saturday that 66,224 Ukrainian men had returned from abroad to join the fight against Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion. Reznikov: &amp;ldquo;These are 12 more combat and motivated brigades! Ukrainians, we are invincible,&amp;rdquo; he said in an online post. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Minister said in a post: &amp;ldquo;Ukrainians are invincible.</description></item><item><title>‘Plain old racist’: teen in New Jersey mall fight condemns arrest of Black youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 12:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</guid><description>Youth, 15, was shoved to couch but not restrained while 14-year-old was handcuffed in incident that went viral
Highlights Video of incident involving Black 14-year-old went viral last week. Teen says police treated him differently than the other boy in the altercation. Incident prompted calls for police to be disciplined for racially disparate treatment. Family and friends of the teen held a protest in front of police headquarters on Saturday.</description></item></channel></rss>