<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fight on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fight/</link><description>Recent content in fight on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida man strangles parents, kisses underage stepsister, and attacks deputy. All on his birthday.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246a614bb3e080633937696/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6246a614bb3e080633937696/</guid><description>A 22-year-old Deltona man is facing eight felony charges after tackling a deputy during a violent fight, according to the Volusia County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office.
Highlights The alleged fight started when the suspect’s girlfriend said she saw him forcibly kiss his 16-year-old stepsister. The incident happened on March 29, which also happened to be the birthday of the suspect, Russell Slimon. Russell is facing 10 charges including eight felonies including battery, child abuse and resisting arrest.</description></item><item><title>Off-duty officer put his knee on a 12-year-old's neck for more than 20 seconds while breaking up school fight, video shows</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236b7d9c7f1413873ed895a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 05:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236b7d9c7f1413873ed895a/</guid><description>Surveillance video released by the Kenosha Unified School District Friday shows an off-duty Kenosha police officer put his knee on the neck of a 12-year-old girl to restrain her for more than 20 seconds while attempting to break up a fight in the cafeteria of Lincoln Middle School.
Highlights Surveillance video released by the Kenosha Unified School District shows an off-duty officer put his knee on the neck of a 12-year-old girl to restrain her for more than 20 seconds.</description></item><item><title>Coca-Cola suspends business in Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227f9b555a9f4bdc7272911/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6227f9b555a9f4bdc7272911/</guid><description>Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president addresses the House of Commons as the UK and US announce bans on Russian oil imports.
Highlights Oil prices jumped more than 7% at one point on Tuesday, as the US and UK announced plans to ban Russian oil imports. The price of Brent crude, an international benchmark, is now hovering at around $130 (£99) a barrel. In the US, Americans are now paying an average of $4.17 per gallon – the highest on record.</description></item><item><title>Over 66,200 Ukrainian men have returned from abroad to fight, says defence minister</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223626f69d933810172928a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 13:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223626f69d933810172928a/</guid><description>Ukrainian Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Saturday that 66,224 Ukrainian men had returned from abroad to join the fight against Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion.
Highlights Defence Minister Oleksii Reznikov said on Saturday that 66,224 Ukrainian men had returned from abroad to join the fight against Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion. Reznikov: &amp;ldquo;These are 12 more combat and motivated brigades! Ukrainians, we are invincible,&amp;rdquo; he said in an online post. Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s Defence Minister said in a post: &amp;ldquo;Ukrainians are invincible.</description></item><item><title>‘Plain old racist’: teen in New Jersey mall fight condemns arrest of Black youth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 12:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6213836bf02fa5cbb2d0e147/</guid><description>Youth, 15, was shoved to couch but not restrained while 14-year-old was handcuffed in incident that went viral
Highlights Video of incident involving Black 14-year-old went viral last week. Teen says police treated him differently than the other boy in the altercation. Incident prompted calls for police to be disciplined for racially disparate treatment. Family and friends of the teen held a protest in front of police headquarters on Saturday. Governor of New Jersey said the incident was &amp;lsquo;deeply disturbing&amp;rsquo; and showed &amp;lsquo;progress we&amp;rsquo;ve made on relationships between law enforcement and community they serve&amp;rsquo; The incident prompted an internal affairs investigation and calls for disciplining the officers involved.</description></item></channel></rss>