<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kelly on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kelly/</link><description>Recent content in kelly on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 10:14:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/kelly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Construction crew finds mummified body in wall at old Oakland convention center</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b20f8a58b16540ef2ad44/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 10:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622b20f8a58b16540ef2ad44/</guid><description>A construction crew discovered what authorities described Wednesday as a mummified body in the wall of a historic building undergoing a remodel in Oakland.
Highlights A worker noticed what appeared to be a human body in a wall that was being deconstructed. Authorities plan on obtaining fingerprints to determine who the person is, how they got there and how long they&amp;rsquo;ve been there. The Henry J. Kaiser Convention Center opened in 1914 and was shuttered nearly a century later.</description></item><item><title>OC Deputy DA, vocal critic of vaccine mandates, dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d55e2fe9b4c05c90c6e4cb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d55e2fe9b4c05c90c6e4cb/</guid><description>Orange County Deputy District Attorney Kelly Ernby has died of COVID-19. Ernby was an outspoken critic of COVID vaccine mandates on a number of occasions.
Summary Orange County Deputy District Attorney Kelly Ernby has died of COVID-19, according to Ben Chapman, Chairman of the Greater Costa Mesa Republicans. Ernby was an outspoken critic of COVID-19 vaccine mandates on a number of occasions. &amp;ldquo;The Orange County District Attorney’s Office is utterly heartbroken by the sudden and unexpected passing of Deputy District Attorney Kelly Ernby,&amp;rdquo; District Attorney Todd Spitzer said in a statement Monday.</description></item><item><title>Iowa man arraigned on 7 charges for Jan. 6 US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</guid><description>Description An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prison
Summary An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prisonDES MOINES, Iowa &amp;ndash; An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>