<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trial on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trial/</link><description>Recent content in trial on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 22:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former Idaho lawmaker found guilty of raping intern</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c633c63a968bc26359e9f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 22:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c633c63a968bc26359e9f/</guid><description>BOISE, Idaho (AP) — A former Idaho lawmaker was convicted Friday of raping a 19-year-old legislative intern after a dramatic trial in which the young woman fled the witness stand during testimony, saying “I can’t do this.”
Highlights Former Idaho state Rep. Aaron von Ehlinger convicted Friday of raping a 19-year-old legislative intern after a dramatic trial in which the young woman fled the witness stand during testimony, saying “I can’t do this.</description></item><item><title>Derek Chauvin appeals his murder conviction in the death of George Floyd</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694f87ecd648ae1b44f5dc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62694f87ecd648ae1b44f5dc/</guid><description>Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has asked the state Court of Appeals to overturn his conviction for the 2020 murder of George Floyd, according to an appeal filed Monday.
Highlights Former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin has asked the state Court of Appeals to overturn his conviction for the 2020 murder of George Floyd. The 82-page filing lists more than a dozen aspects of the case and trial that Chauvin&amp;rsquo;s attorney argues tainted the proceedings.</description></item><item><title>Jurors reject array of defenses at Capitol riot trials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267746727132310c74fd86d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 04:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6267746727132310c74fd86d/</guid><description>Jurors have heard — and rejected — an array of excuses and arguments from the first rioters to be tried for storming the U.S. Capitol. The next jury to get a Capitol riot case could hear another novel defense this week at the trial of a retired New York City police officer.
Highlights Thomas Webster, a 20-year veteran of the NYPD, has claimed he was acting in self-defense when he tackled a police officer who was trying to protect the Capitol from a mob on Jan.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones' Infowars files for bankruptcy in wake of defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook massacre was a hoax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:23:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d58144bdfe3b0c55ec8ac/</guid><description>Jones was found liable in at least two defamation suits over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.
Highlights Infowars and two other companies owned by radio host Alex Jones have filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in light of several defamation lawsuits. The filings were made in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas. A judge has ruled that Jones get back $75,000 in fines he paid to a Connecticut court for failing to appear at a deposition last month in a lawsuit over his assertions that the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.</description></item><item><title>Cardi B wins order forcing YouTuber to remove defamatory videos</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ccd42136da741d067a3eb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 23:14:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ccd42136da741d067a3eb/</guid><description>A judge has ordered Latasha Kebe, known as Tasha K, to to delete and never repost defamatory videos.
Highlights Latasha Kebe, known as Tasha K, has been ordered to delete and never repost defamatory videos. Lawyers for the singer said Kebe had waged &amp;ldquo;a campaign to damage and destroy [Cardi B&amp;rsquo;s] reputation among her fans and the consuming public&amp;rdquo; The judge has ordered Kebe to delete the videos and never re-post them again.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell's sex trafficking conviction upheld as US judge refuses retrial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62479e2f599992f1cc89e369/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62479e2f599992f1cc89e369/</guid><description>Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s sex trafficking conviction has been upheld, despite a juror&amp;rsquo;s acknowledgment that he had falsely stated before the trial that he had not been sexually abused.
Highlights Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s sex trafficking conviction has been upheld by a US judge. The 60-year-old Briton was convicted in December of helping Jeffrey Epstein to sexually abuse teenage girls. Maxwell requested a retrial after it emerged that one of the jurors had been sexually abused but had falsely stated before the trial that he had not been.</description></item><item><title>Disgraced producer Harvey Weinstein caught smuggling Milk Duds in jail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622426e5d3d778470e6112e1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622426e5d3d778470e6112e1/</guid><description>Harvey Weinstein was caught with contraband Milk Duds in November, prompting a reprimand from L.A. County jail guards, according to records viewed by Variety.
Highlights Harvey Weinstein was caught with contraband Milk Duds in November, prompting a reprimand from L.A. County jail guards. The Milk Duds were found during a search on Nov. 10, after Weinstein had a face-to-face meeting with one of his attorneys. Prison guards warned that they would have to search his attorneys’ legal binders and laptop bags on future visits.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell juror to be questioned under oath by judge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621873e47f623c24f4c5c3f8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621873e47f623c24f4c5c3f8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A Ghislaine Maxwell trial juror who said on a written questionnaire that he&amp;rsquo;d never been a sexual abuse victim will be questioned by the trial judge
Highlights A juror who said he&amp;rsquo;d never been a sexual abuse victim will be questioned by the trial judge. The juror said during jury selection for Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s criminal trial only to reveal after the trial that he was a child sex abuse victim.</description></item><item><title>Far-right Oath Keepers leader to stay in jail until Capitol attack trial, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210d04a29cf3c7dddf34048/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 11:11:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210d04a29cf3c7dddf34048/</guid><description>Stewart Rhodes ‘presents a clear and convincing danger’ after spending thousands on weapons before riot, judge says
Highlights Stewart Rhodes &amp;lsquo;presents a clear and convincing danger&amp;rsquo; after spending thousands on weapons before riot, judge says. US district judge Amit Mehta said Rhodes spent thousands of dollars on weapons and equipment. Rhodes is accused of spearheading a conspiracy to block the certification of the presidential election by recruiting others and even stationing armed ‘quick reaction force’ units outside of Washington to be ready to stop the peaceful transfer of power.</description></item><item><title>After 8 years, a retired Florida police captain will stand trial for killing a man in an argument about texting in a movie theater</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8038a60eb127de16e169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 16:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8038a60eb127de16e169/</guid><description>A 79-year-old man is finally expected to stand trial this week, eight years after he fatally shot a man who was texting in a Florida movie theater.
Highlights Curtis Reeves, 79, fatally shot Chad Oulson in January 2014, eight years after he got into an argument over texting. The case garnered widespread attention in part due to the defendants&amp;rsquo; self defense claim under Florida&amp;rsquo;s controversial &amp;ldquo;stand your ground&amp;rdquo; law. A judge denied that the law did not apply in this case, forcing it to trial.</description></item><item><title>Iran vows revenge for Soleimani killing if Trump not put on trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3aa3c52f0d8ce973f182e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d3aa3c52f0d8ce973f182e/</guid><description>Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi, speaking on the second anniversary of the assassination of General Qassem Soleimani by the United States, said that former U.S. President Donald Trump must face trial for the killing or Tehran would take revenge.
Summary DUBAI, Jan 3 (Reuters) - Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi, speaking on the second anniversary of the assassination of General Qassem Soleimani by the United States, said that former U.S. President Donald Trump must face trial for the killing or Tehran would take revenge.</description></item><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell found guilty in sex-trafficking trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccf6a147608853a91b4235/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccf6a147608853a91b4235/</guid><description>Maxwell, 60, convicted on five of the six charges she faced as US prosecutors hail verdict and say ‘justice has been done’
Summary The British former socialite Ghislaine Maxwell was found guilty of sex trafficking in her Manhattan federal court trial on Wednesday afternoon. Maxwell, 60, was arrested in July 2020, charged with involvement in ex-boyfriend Jeffrey Epstein’s sexual abuse of teenage girls, some as young as 14. Following the guilty verdict, Damian Williams, the Manhattan US attorney, said in a statement: “A unanimous jury has found Ghislaine Maxwell guilty of one of the worst crimes imaginable: facilitating and participating in the sexual abuse of children.</description></item></channel></rss>