<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rates on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rates/</link><description>Recent content in rates on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 20:09:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mortgage demand falls to the lowest level in 22 years, amid rising rates and slowing home sales</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a101e77dec06735097b1d1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 20:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a101e77dec06735097b1d1/</guid><description>Mortgage demand continues to fall as interest rates rise further and affordability in the housing market weakens.
Highlights Mortgage demand continues to fall as interest rates rise further and affordability in housing market weakens. Average contract interest rate for 30-year fixed-rate mortgages with conforming loan balances $647,200 or less increased to 5.40% from 5.33%. Mortgage Bankers Association: Total mortgage application volume fell 6.5% last week. Refinance demand, which is most sensitive to weekly rate moves, fell another 6% for the week and was 75% lower than the same week one year ago.</description></item><item><title>Home prices jumped nearly 20% in February</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268d3e6df9012faa2d861fa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 05:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6268d3e6df9012faa2d861fa/</guid><description>Home prices continued to surge higher in February, but rising mortgage rates may make that kind of growth unsustainable in the months ahead.
Highlights Home prices increased 19.8% in February year over year, according to S&amp;amp;P CoreLogic Case-Shiller index. Sun Belt cities continued to see the highest gains, with Phoenix, Tampa, Florida, and Miami seeing highest gains. Minneapolis, New York and Washington, D.C., saw the smallest price gains, although they were still in the double digits.</description></item><item><title>US home prices surge 18.4% in October</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb88fa9aeb5cec935932e2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 22:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb88fa9aeb5cec935932e2/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. home prices surged again in October as the housing market continues to boom in the wake of last year&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus recession. The S&amp;amp;P CoreLogic Case-Shiller 20-city home price index, out Tuesday, climbed 18.4% in October from a year earlier.
Summary U.S. home prices rose briskly in September, another sign that the housing market is booming in the aftermath of last year&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus recession. U.S. home prices rose briskly in September, another sign that the housing market is booming in the aftermath of last year&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus recession.</description></item></channel></rss>