<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>providing on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/providing/</link><description>Recent content in providing on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/providing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Health Ministry formally bans LGBTQ+ conversion therapy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b1a1794b30a60a7c155f8/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620b1a1794b30a60a7c155f8/</guid><description>While the Health Ministry has recommended against conversion therapy for years, this is the first formal ban.
Highlights Health Ministry issues circular banning medical professionals in Israel from providing conversion therapy. Licensed professionals who do so will face sanctions, including severe disciplinary proceedings and the revocation of their licenses. The circular stresses the risks to mental health posed by conversion therapy and prohibits all professionals from the offering, publicizing, or providing such &amp;ldquo;therapies&amp;rdquo; The circular defines conversion therapy as any therapy given in consultation or consultation which has the goal of changing the identity or sexual identity of a person.</description></item><item><title>Chinese officials admitted Wednesday they have faced challenges getting enough supplies to residents in locked-down Xi'an, after the city's inhabitants took to social media to complain they didn't have enough food and call for help</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdbb7b0bffccb9c59fac81/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 14:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cdbb7b0bffccb9c59fac81/</guid><description>Chinese officials admitted Wednesday they have faced challenges getting enough supplies to residents in locked-down Xi&amp;rsquo;an, after the city&amp;rsquo;s inhabitants took to social media to complain they didn&amp;rsquo;t ha…
Summary Beijing has followed a strict &amp;ldquo;zero Covid&amp;rdquo; strategy involving tight border restrictions and targeted lockdowns since the virus first surfaced in a central city in late 2019. Xi&amp;rsquo;an official Chen Jianfeng told reporters that the local government has mobilised enterprises to step up community distribution, with cadres supervising wholesale markets and supermarkets.</description></item></channel></rss>