<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gov on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gov/</link><description>Recent content in gov on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:18:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/gov/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oklahoma's Gov. Stitt signs bill restricting school bathrooms to birth sex, effective immediately</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fb63a1fd93b426ab09105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:18:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628fb63a1fd93b426ab09105/</guid><description>The Oklahoma bill requires districts to restrict bathroom access by students&amp;rsquo; sex. If schools don&amp;rsquo;t comply, they face a 5% deduction in state funding.
Highlights Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt signs bill restricting school bathrooms to birth sex, effective immediately. School districts and charter schools that don&amp;rsquo;t comply face a 5% deduction in their state funding. The legislation follows months of debate over whether students should be allowed to use the restroom that matches their gender identity, not strictly their sex at birth.</description></item><item><title>Florida Gov. DeSantis signs bill revoking Disney's special district status</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62634efcec7856751f735831/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:58:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62634efcec7856751f735831/</guid><description>Sunsetting the Reedy Creek Improvement District means that local counties will likely be left to foot the bill for potholes and emergency services at Disney World.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law a bill revoking the Walt Disney Company&amp;rsquo;s special district status in the state, just days after the legislation was first introduced. The bill, which would see the Reedy Creek Improvement District dissolved, passed the state Senate on Wednesday and the state&amp;rsquo;s House of Representatives on Thursday by a vote of 70-38.</description></item><item><title>British Columbia becomes first jurisdiction to tie minimum wage increases to inflation. On June 1 minimum wage will go up to $15.65, up 45 cents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62304b3a7260a47421e79df4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 08:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62304b3a7260a47421e79df4/</guid><description>On June 1, 2022, B.C.&amp;rsquo;s lowest-paid workers will get a pay boost, with the general minimum wage increasing from $15.20 to $15.65 an hour.
Highlights B.C. &amp;rsquo;s minimum wage will increase from $11.35 to $15.65 an hour on June 1, 2022. Increase of 2.8% will also apply to the live-in camp leader and live in home support worker minimum daily wages. Minimum wage increases tied to inflation are part of government&amp;rsquo;s plan to build an economy that works for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Montana Gov. Gianforte hunts, kills National Park Service-tracked mountain lion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fdd391aa9b11f610f0c4c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fdd391aa9b11f610f0c4c/</guid><description>Montana Gov.
Highlights Montana Gov. Greg Gianforte shot and killed a mountain lion that was being tracked by the National Park Service. Federal law prohibits hunting and discharging of firearms in Yellowstone National Park. The hunt was legal, Montana Fish, Wildlife &amp;amp; Parks spokesperson Greg Lemon says. In 2021, he said he &amp;ldquo;made a mistake&amp;rdquo; after he killed a Montana black wolf that was also tagged in Yellowstone before he completed the required state certification.</description></item><item><title>Auditor: Iowa Gov. Reynolds must return $450K in COVID funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f89779c041f9df5b3b171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 15:13:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f89779c041f9df5b3b171/</guid><description>Iowa’s state auditor again called for Gov. Kim Reynolds to return nearly $450,000 in federal coronavirus relief funds that were used to pay for 21 governor’s office staff members for three months in 2020
Highlights Iowa’s state auditor again called for Gov. Kim Reynolds to return nearly $450,000 in federal coronavirus relief funds. Reynolds paid salaries for 21 staff members — including her spokesman, a lawyer and her chief of staff — from March 15 to June 30, 2020, out of federal funds.</description></item></channel></rss>