<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>federal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/federal/</link><description>Recent content in federal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:16:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/federal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Michigan Governor Whitmer Kidnapping Plot Trial: FBI Raids Detroit Home Following Threats Against Judge, Defense Lawyers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245472bc791c2cc1e6b695e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245472bc791c2cc1e6b695e/</guid><description>NEWYou can now listen to TBEN News articles! The FBI has reportedly raided a home in suburban Detroit in connection with alleged threats against the
Highlights FBI reportedly raided home in Detroit in connection with alleged threats against judge and defense attorneys in kidnapping conspiracy trial of Michigan governor Gretchen Whitmer. Defense attorneys portrayed their clients as talkative, marijuana-smoking weekend warriors, susceptible to manipulation by FBI agents. The trial centers on the central issue of whether the FBI engaged in entrapment, the prohibited practice of cajoling or inciting individuals to commit certain criminal offenses.</description></item><item><title>Biden signs bill making lynching a federal hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Presidents typically say a few words before they turn legislation into law. But Joe Biden flipped the script Tuesday when it came time to put his signature on the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act.
Highlights Biden signs the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act in the White House Rose Garden. Biden said it&amp;rsquo;s “a little unusual to do the bill signing, not say anything and then speak” Biden: “Racial hate isn’t an old problem — it’s a persistent problem.</description></item><item><title>Feds: Forced-reset triggers are machine guns under US law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal officials are notifying gun dealers that some forced-reset triggers, which allow guns to fire rapidly with a single continuous pull of the trigger, are considered machine guns under federal law and subject to strict regulation.
Highlights The notification was being made Thursday in an open letter from the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives to federally licensed firearms dealers. It spells out how investigators have determined the triggers to be “conversion devices,” making the weapons machine guns.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Congressman Fortenberry found guilty of lying to FBI about funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623df8e25df3ce3b3788be8f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623df8e25df3ce3b3788be8f/</guid><description>A U.S. jury on Thursday convicted U.S. Congressman Jeff Fortenberry, a Republican from Nebraska, of lying to FBI investigators about illegal contributions to his 2016 re-election campaign.
Highlights U.S. Congressman Jeff Fortenberry, a Republican from Nebraska, found guilty of scheming to falsify and conceal material facts. Federal law prohibits foreign nationals from donating to federal election campaigns. Federal prosecutors alleged that he lied about $30,000 in campaign contributions he received in 2016 from Nigerian billionaire Gilbert Chagoury.</description></item><item><title>Judge orders Walmart to rehire worker with Down syndrome, provide more than $50,000 in back pay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a8602f4138df8c5744981/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 23:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a8602f4138df8c5744981/</guid><description>The judge, however, denied a request by a federal agency for the retailer to be under tighter government scrutiny for five years.
Highlights Marlo Spaeth prevailed in a disability discrimination lawsuit related to her firing from a Wisconsin store. The judge denied a request to force Walmart to take other actions for the next five years in light of how it treated the woman. Walmart told CNBC on Wednesday that it would comply with the order to give Spaeth her job back.</description></item><item><title>Judge restores protections for gray wolves across much of US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207b24a2c31ece6ab67e917/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207b24a2c31ece6ab67e917/</guid><description>A judge has restored federal protections for gray wolves across much of the U.S. after they were removed in the waning days of the Trump administration
Highlights A judge has restored federal protections for gray wolves across much of the U.S. after they were removed in the waning days of the Trump administration. The ruling does not directly impact wolves in the northern Rocky Mountains of Idaho, Montana and Wyoming and portions of several adjacent states.</description></item><item><title>Lawmakers asking for a federal investigation into travel nurse salaries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62036942cae09c5eb4c35920/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62036942cae09c5eb4c35920/</guid><description>A bipartisan letter signed by lawmakers across the nation has asked the COVID-19 response team to investigate potential price gouging by some nursing staff agencies. Some local healthcare workers say this growing scrutiny could lead to state-level restrictions. “It wasn&amp;rsquo;t even COVID that was rough, it was more of a staffing issue, and not being treated how I felt like I deserve to be treated as a nurse, and not getting breaks, not even urinating in a 12 hour shift.</description></item><item><title>Iowa man arraigned on 7 charges for Jan. 6 US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</guid><description>Description An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prison
Summary An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prisonDES MOINES, Iowa &amp;ndash; An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>