<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>federal on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/federal/</link><description>Recent content in federal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 17:22:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/federal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rising US traffic deaths put focus on one Philadelphia road</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62964ebaec01a9c912db65d7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 17:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62964ebaec01a9c912db65d7/</guid><description>PHILADELPHIA (AP) — Just one more step and the stroller would have been on the curb. The thought haunts Latanya Byrd years after a driver racing down Roosevelt Boulevard in Philadelphia struck and killed her 27-year-old niece, Samara Banks, and three of Banks’ young sons as they crossed the 12-lane road.
Highlights Roosevelt Boulevard is an almost 14-mile maze of chaotic traffic patterns that passes through some of the city&amp;rsquo;s most diverse neighborhoods and Census tracts with the highest poverty rates.</description></item><item><title>Red Power Ranger Actor Among 19 Accused in North Texas PPP Scheme – NBC 5 Dallas-Fort Worth</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a199b8b0f2359b2dfebb3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 11:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a199b8b0f2359b2dfebb3/</guid><description>Nineteen people, including the actor who played the Red Power Ranger on television, are facing federal charges after being accused of conspiracy to commit wire&amp;hellip;
Highlights Austin St. John, whose real name is Jason Lawrence Geiger, was named in an indictment returned by a federal grand jury on May 12. The actor was best known for his role in the 1990s children&amp;rsquo;s children&amp;rsquo;s superhero show “Mighty Morphin’s Gold Ranger in the “Power Rangers Zeo” St John played the Red Power Ranger in 1996 in the TV show and recently, in 2020, wore the red ranger&amp;rsquo;s red suit again.</description></item><item><title>Feds: National Guard members on state duty can join unions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870142d921a0dada4896c9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870142d921a0dada4896c9/</guid><description>HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — The Department of Justice has given the green light to National&amp;hellip;
Highlights A 1978 federal law makes it a criminal felony for members of the armed forces, including the National Guard, to join or attempt to form a labor organization. The department on Tuesday settled a federal lawsuit filed in Connecticut by labor unions. Some Texas National Guard members already have moved ahead with their plans, joining the Texas State Employees Union starting in February.</description></item><item><title>A federal judge accepts Derek Chauvin's plea deal and will sentence him to 20 to 25 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272fa9140e442542d31f23e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 22:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272fa9140e442542d31f23e/</guid><description>The federal judge presiding over the cases of the four Minneapolis police officers implicated in the killing of George Floyd has accepted Derek Chauvin&amp;rsquo;s plea deal and will sentence him to 20 to 25 years in prison.
Highlights Derek Chauvin was sentenced last June after he was convicted of murder in the 2020 death of George Floyd. Chauvin would be expected to serve between 17 and a little over 21 years, &amp;ldquo;assuming all good-time credit&amp;rdquo; Chauvin pleaded guilty in December 2021 to violating Floyd&amp;rsquo;s civil rights.</description></item><item><title>U.S. agrees to return $1.1 million to company busted for hauling legal weed money in Kansas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258dfe4e9fd675218415867/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 03:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258dfe4e9fd675218415867/</guid><description>Last year, a sheriff’s deputy in Dickinson County, Kansas, stopped one of Empyreal Logistics&amp;rsquo; vehicles on Interstate 70 and seized nearly $166,000 in cash it was transporting from legal medical marijuana dispensaries in Kansas City, Missouri, to a credit union in Colorado.
Highlights Denver-based Empyreal Logistics was transporting cash from state-licensed cannabis businesses in California. A sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputy in Kansas seized nearly $166,000 in cash last year. The U.S. Attorney’s Office in Kansas subsequently filed a civil forfeiture action against the armored car company.</description></item><item><title>White House Secret Service personnel ‘compromised’ by men impersonating DHS agents, prosecutors say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250d91e4c5c73ccffae3c12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 00:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6250d91e4c5c73ccffae3c12/</guid><description>A Secret Service agent assigned to protect first lady Jill Biden is a witness in the case of two men accused of impersonating Homeland Security agents.
Highlights Two men charged with impersonating DHS agents &amp;ldquo;compromised&amp;rdquo; Secret Service personnel assigned to protect first lady Jill Biden and the White House, prosecutors say. Federal prosecutors ask a judge to hold the duo without bail. Magistrate Judge G. Michael Harvey: &amp;ldquo;This is not just two people dressing up for Halloween, your honor.</description></item><item><title>Two men allegedly impersonated federal agents to get access to Secret Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f882e0a796d814d38aa67/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:56:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f882e0a796d814d38aa67/</guid><description>The two allegedly used fake credentials to get closer to members of federal law enforcement agencies, including Secret Service agents assigned to the first lady.
Highlights Arian Taherzadeh, 40, and Haider Ali, 35, have been arrested for allegedly impersonating federal agents. The two allegedly obtained paraphernalia, handguns and assault rifles used by federal law enforcement agencies. Four Secret Service agents have been placed on administrative leave amid the investigation. The men were discovered on March 14, when the U.</description></item><item><title>N.Y. Supreme Court judge whose home was raided by investigators found dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e81b08ccaa2fef14c8a82/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 06:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624e81b08ccaa2fef14c8a82/</guid><description>John Michalski, an acting justice on the Erie County Supreme Court, died of an apparent suicide, according to attorney Terry Connors. Michalski was 61.
Highlights John Michalski, an acting justice on the Erie County Supreme Court, died of an apparent suicide. His property was raided by federal agents two weeks ago, his lawyer says. He had returned to his duties in January after going on medical leave in the wake of his apparent suicide attempt in February 2021.</description></item><item><title>Michigan Governor Whitmer Kidnapping Plot Trial: FBI Raids Detroit Home Following Threats Against Judge, Defense Lawyers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245472bc791c2cc1e6b695e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 06:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245472bc791c2cc1e6b695e/</guid><description>NEWYou can now listen to TBEN News articles! The FBI has reportedly raided a home in suburban Detroit in connection with alleged threats against the
Highlights FBI reportedly raided home in Detroit in connection with alleged threats against judge and defense attorneys in kidnapping conspiracy trial of Michigan governor Gretchen Whitmer. Defense attorneys portrayed their clients as talkative, marijuana-smoking weekend warriors, susceptible to manipulation by FBI agents. The trial centers on the central issue of whether the FBI engaged in entrapment, the prohibited practice of cajoling or inciting individuals to commit certain criminal offenses.</description></item><item><title>Biden signs bill making lynching a federal hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Presidents typically say a few words before they turn legislation into law. But Joe Biden flipped the script Tuesday when it came time to put his signature on the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act.
Highlights Biden signs the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act in the White House Rose Garden. Biden said it&amp;rsquo;s “a little unusual to do the bill signing, not say anything and then speak” Biden: “Racial hate isn’t an old problem — it’s a persistent problem.</description></item><item><title>Feds: Forced-reset triggers are machine guns under US law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f1269dcddc47c2bcd27f9/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Federal officials are notifying gun dealers that some forced-reset triggers, which allow guns to fire rapidly with a single continuous pull of the trigger, are considered machine guns under federal law and subject to strict regulation.
Highlights The notification was being made Thursday in an open letter from the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives to federally licensed firearms dealers. It spells out how investigators have determined the triggers to be “conversion devices,” making the weapons machine guns.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Congressman Fortenberry found guilty of lying to FBI about funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623df8e25df3ce3b3788be8f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 17:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623df8e25df3ce3b3788be8f/</guid><description>A U.S. jury on Thursday convicted U.S. Congressman Jeff Fortenberry, a Republican from Nebraska, of lying to FBI investigators about illegal contributions to his 2016 re-election campaign.
Highlights U.S. Congressman Jeff Fortenberry, a Republican from Nebraska, found guilty of scheming to falsify and conceal material facts. Federal law prohibits foreign nationals from donating to federal election campaigns. Federal prosecutors alleged that he lied about $30,000 in campaign contributions he received in 2016 from Nigerian billionaire Gilbert Chagoury.</description></item><item><title>Judge orders Walmart to rehire worker with Down syndrome, provide more than $50,000 in back pay</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a8602f4138df8c5744981/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 23:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622a8602f4138df8c5744981/</guid><description>The judge, however, denied a request by a federal agency for the retailer to be under tighter government scrutiny for five years.
Highlights Marlo Spaeth prevailed in a disability discrimination lawsuit related to her firing from a Wisconsin store. The judge denied a request to force Walmart to take other actions for the next five years in light of how it treated the woman. Walmart told CNBC on Wednesday that it would comply with the order to give Spaeth her job back.</description></item><item><title>Judge restores protections for gray wolves across much of US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207b24a2c31ece6ab67e917/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207b24a2c31ece6ab67e917/</guid><description>A judge has restored federal protections for gray wolves across much of the U.S. after they were removed in the waning days of the Trump administration
Highlights A judge has restored federal protections for gray wolves across much of the U.S. after they were removed in the waning days of the Trump administration. The ruling does not directly impact wolves in the northern Rocky Mountains of Idaho, Montana and Wyoming and portions of several adjacent states.</description></item><item><title>Lawmakers asking for a federal investigation into travel nurse salaries</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62036942cae09c5eb4c35920/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 07:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62036942cae09c5eb4c35920/</guid><description>A bipartisan letter signed by lawmakers across the nation has asked the COVID-19 response team to investigate potential price gouging by some nursing staff agencies. Some local healthcare workers say this growing scrutiny could lead to state-level restrictions. “It wasn&amp;rsquo;t even COVID that was rough, it was more of a staffing issue, and not being treated how I felt like I deserve to be treated as a nurse, and not getting breaks, not even urinating in a 12 hour shift.</description></item><item><title>Iowa man arraigned on 7 charges for Jan. 6 US Capitol attack</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3055783c930e246b8b272/</guid><description>Description An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prison
Summary An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol was arraigned on a new federal indictment that includes a felony count that could carry up to 20 years in prisonDES MOINES, Iowa &amp;ndash; An Iowa man charged earlier for his participation in the Jan.</description></item></channel></rss>