<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lgbtq on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lgbtq/</link><description>Recent content in lgbtq on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:15:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lgbtq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Greece bans LGBTQ conversion therapy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d2453b093f31e469ad654/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d2453b093f31e469ad654/</guid><description>Greece on Wednesday banned conversion therapy for minors, a practice aimed at suppressing a person&amp;rsquo;s sexual orientation or gender identity and which the lesbian, gay, bisexual and trans community worldwide, as well as health experts, have condemned as harmful.
Highlights Greece bans conversion therapy for minors, a practice aimed at suppressing a person&amp;rsquo;s sexual orientation or gender identity. Canada, New Zealand and France criminalized conversion therapy earlier this year. Health experts have condemned the practice as harmful.</description></item><item><title>L.A. bans official travel to Florida and Texas over parents' rights bill, LGBTQ+ policies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fd3388a2df1d47de220b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 06:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fd3388a2df1d47de220b6/</guid><description>TheLos Angeles County Board of Supervisors voted unanimously on Tuesday to suspend all official travel to both Florida and Texas. The travel ban was proposed and passed in response to legislationenacted in Florida and Texas. Critics, including the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors, claim those bills target LGBTQ+ youth and families. The board reportedly voted in support of the ban in order to support &amp;quot;affirming care and inclusion for LGBTQ+ youth and their families.</description></item></channel></rss>