<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>civilians on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/civilians/</link><description>Recent content in civilians on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 05:13:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/civilians/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>All women, children and elderly evacuated from Azovstal, Ukraine's deputy PM says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277516bd757db1afafcebc9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 05:13:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277516bd757db1afafcebc9/</guid><description>All women, children and elderly people have been evacuated from the besieged Azovstal steel plant in the southern port of Mariupol, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s deputy prime minister said on Saturday.
Highlights All women, children and elderly people have been evacuated from the besieged Azovstal steel plant in the southern port of Mariupol, Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s deputy prime minister says. Earlier, Russian-backed separatists in Donetsk region said that 50 civilians had been evacuated on Saturday. Ukraine announced on Friday an evacuation plan from the steel plant and other parts of the city for Saturday.</description></item><item><title>Russia offers ceasefire for civilians to leave Azovstal plant in Mariupol, says defense ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266e5e84fc5fab4d47612b1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 18:18:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266e5e84fc5fab4d47612b1/</guid><description>Russia’s Ministry of Defense has offered to cease all hostilities around the Azovstal steel plant in besieged Mariupol to allow civilians to leave “in any direction they choose.”
Highlights Russian government says it will allow civilians to leave in any direction they choose. Government says it has set up a round-the-clock humanitarian corridor for civilians. U.S. officials have said Russia has repeatedly broken its pledge to allow civilian access to the Azovstal factory in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>‘They were all shot’: Russia accused of war crimes as Bucha reveals horror of invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a41bb1257dd0c87b4746b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a41bb1257dd0c87b4746b/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces liberating the town of Bucha near Kyiv find streets littered with corpses of civilians and burned-out Russian tanks
Highlights At least 20 bodies, all in civilian clothing, found strewn across a single street in Bucha, a town north-west of the capital. At least 280 other bodies have been buried in mass graves in the town, local residents say. British foreign secretary Liz Truss said she was ‘appalled’ by atrocities in town of Bucha.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s amateur army: Thousands of young civilians are drafted into the military and trained for war in desperate bid to fend off Putin’s 100,000 well-trained troops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0028ac60312e303adc8f7/</guid><description>Young Ukrainian men and women, some as young as 21, have been taking part in Kyiv Territorial Defence unit training over the weekend, as they prepare for a possible conflict with Moscow.
Summary In the event of a potential invasion by Russia, these youngsters will be part of the country&amp;rsquo;s civil resistance that will carry on the fight against Russian soldiers if the Ukrainian military is overwhelmed. Tatiana, who is enrolled in a military reserve program, joined hundreds of other young Ukrainians in a Kyiv Territorial Defence Unit training exercise on Saturday in a snow-covered forest in Kyiv.</description></item></channel></rss>