<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>plot on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plot/</link><description>Recent content in plot on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 05:14:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/plot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NYC woman lured man on Instagram and tortured him in $100K kidnapping plot, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623171f9522888f02cc4a9fb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 05:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623171f9522888f02cc4a9fb/</guid><description>A New York City woman is accused of kidnapping and torturing a man she met on Instagram for more than 12 hours while demanding a $100,000 ransom from his
Highlights A New York woman is accused of kidnapping and torturing a man she met on Instagram for more than 12 hours while demanding a $100,000 ransom from his brother. The victim, 24, was taken to the hospital in stable condition, police said.</description></item><item><title>Neo-Nazi leader sentenced to 7 years for plot to intimidate Jews, journalists</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 11:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61deb4ce3cfc7a9866e0f94a/</guid><description>A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison.
Summary A Neo-Nazi leader convicted in a plot to intimidate Jews and journalists has been sentenced to seven years in prison. The man, Kaleb Cole, 25, the former leader of the Neo-Nazi group Atomwaffen Division, was convicted in September of conspiracy, mailing threatening communications and interfering with a federally protected activity, the Justice Department said in a statement Tuesday.</description></item></channel></rss>