<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>casualties on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/casualties/</link><description>Recent content in casualties on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 10:11:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/casualties/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More than 30 people, including children, killed in stampede at church event in Nigeria</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295e99707e815f4036a39c5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 10:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295e99707e815f4036a39c5/</guid><description>More than 30 people were killed and others injured when a stampede broke out at a church event in the southeastern Nigerian city of Port Harcourt on Saturday, according to police and security officials.
Highlights The incident took place at a local polo club, where the nearby Kings Assembly Church had organized a gift donation drive. Most of the casualties were children, police say. The drive had not yet started when the stampede took place, a spokeswoman for the state police says.</description></item><item><title>Mounting Russian casualties in Ukraine lead to more questions about its military readiness</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623468cec5edbbb8f2a9a9f4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 11:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623468cec5edbbb8f2a9a9f4/</guid><description>Thousands of Russian troops have been killed in Ukraine since Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion began nearly one month ago, US and NATO officials told CNN this week, and Russia is now struggling to resupply those forces as it faces sagging troop morale and fierce Ukrainian resistance.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s offensive to capture Kyiv has largely stalled, NATO officials say. Russia is now struggling to resupply its troops as it faces sagging troop morale and fierce Ukrainian resistance.</description></item></channel></rss>