<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>village on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/village/</link><description>Recent content in village on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 23:14:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/village/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia pushed back from Kharkiv - report from front line</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628037ba7847e109e53f69eb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 23:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628037ba7847e109e53f69eb/</guid><description>Correspondent Quentin Sommerville and cameraman Darren Conway are with Ukrainian troops as they advance.
Highlights Half a dozen locals detained in the basement of one building suspected of aiding the enemy. Their eyes are covered with balaclavas taped over their heads, their hands tied. At least one woman is among them. They are left alone in a room, then taken away to the security services for questioning. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Fire season drives demand for July 4 drone shows to replace fireworks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279677c714e6cdb05bab85d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279677c714e6cdb05bab85d/</guid><description>When the Caldor Fire raced toward the southern shore of Lake Tahoe last year, its 100-foot (30-meter) flames spread across the tree canopy. Miles away, towns on the north shore took notice.
Highlights Three communities on the California-Nevada border are switching from the traditional fireworks show for the U.S. Independence Day holiday this July 4 to a drone light show. With Western states enduring a historic drought, some towns are rejecting fireworks as a wildfire risk.</description></item><item><title>Elephants dying from eating plastic waste in Sri Lankan dump</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e22ad057afdde5be3037eb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e22ad057afdde5be3037eb/</guid><description>PALLAKKADU, Sri Lanka (AP) — Conservationists and veterinarians are warning that plastic waste in an open landfill in eastern Sri Lanka is killing elephants in the region, after two more were found dead over the weekend.
Summary Elephants dying from eating plastic waste in Sri Lankan dumpPALLAKKADU, Sri Lanka (AP) — Conservationists and veterinarians are warning that plastic waste in an open landfill in eastern Sri Lanka is killing elephants in the region, after two more were found dead over the weekend.</description></item><item><title>‘Bloodthirsty’ squirrel attacks 18 people in Welsh village in two-day Christmas rampage</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccb04f8c4b2de752610c49/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 19:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ccb04f8c4b2de752610c49/</guid><description>‘Those teeth could bite right through a child’s tiny finger’, said the woman who put an end to the attacks
Summary A squirrel’s reign of terror over a sleepy Welsh village has been brought to an end after it bit 18 residents leaving some too scared to leave their homes. The attacks were ended when Ms Reynolds set out a cage in her garden leaving a handful of peanuts, Stripe’s favourite snack, as bait.</description></item></channel></rss>