<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cars on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cars/</link><description>Recent content in cars on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$29,000 for an average used car? Would-be buyers are aghast</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d428cbb6e44c411c70a890/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d428cbb6e44c411c70a890/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A couple of months ago, a woman paid a visit to Jeff Schrier&amp;rsquo;s used car lot in Omaha, Nebraska. She was on a tight budget, she said, and was desperate for a vehicle to commute to work.
Summary A dealership sign is seen outside of Honda certified used car dealership in Schaumburg, Ill., Thursday, Dec. 16, 2021. (AP Photo/Nam Y. Huh)A dealership sign is seen outside of Honda certified used car dealership in Schaumburg, Ill.</description></item><item><title>All 21 people who were trapped in New Mexico tramway overnight have been rescued</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2046b619783975541b952/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2046b619783975541b952/</guid><description>Officials have rescued 21 people who were trapped on the Sandia Peak Tramway in Albuquerque, New Mexico for more than 12 hours during icy conditions Friday night.
Summary (CNN) Officials have rescued 21 people who were trapped on the Sandia Peak Tramway in Albuquerque, New Mexico for more than 12 hours during icy conditions Friday night. &amp;ldquo;We are happy to report that at this time all people needing rescue from the Tram cars have been rescued and are safely at base,&amp;rdquo; the Bernalillo County Fire Department said on Twitter.</description></item></channel></rss>