<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bar on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bar/</link><description>Recent content in bar on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 02:52:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Multiple victims' shot, critically hurt near downtown Chattanooga bar, say police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629d6ba34d44427d20a6f759/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 02:52:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629d6ba34d44427d20a6f759/</guid><description>2:30 PM UPDATE:Chattanooga Police Department is beginning to re-open portions of McCallie Avenue. We have a crew at the scene:1 PM UPDATE:Chattanooga Mayor Tim Kelly and Chief Murphy held a press conference following the shooting this morning. Mayor Kelly is asking for Congress to take action to address the issue of gun violence in the country. &amp;quot;Our city will put a stop to this,” says Mayor Kelly.
Highlights Police Department is beginning to re-open portions of McCallie Avenue.</description></item><item><title>Argument leads to fatal shooting in checkout line of grocery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200f0870c2638ac3acadb69/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 10:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200f0870c2638ac3acadb69/</guid><description>An argument in the checkout line of a South Florida grocery store escalated into a fatal shooting
Highlights Argument started in checkout line of Publix in upscale neighborhood of Coral Gables. Four people were shot Saturday night at Player’s Sports Bar and Grill in North Lauderdale. In Orlando, police are searching for a suspect in a fatal shooting at a banquet hall early Sunday. One victim has injuries that are believed to be life-threatening, sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said in a news release.</description></item></channel></rss>