<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attempts on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attempts/</link><description>Recent content in attempts on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 02:31:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/attempts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Florida education officials reject 54 math textbooks for ‘attempts to indoctrinate students’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b7bd835918c1480a7c20e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 02:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b7bd835918c1480a7c20e/</guid><description>Dozens of math textbooks were rejected by the Florida Department of Education after officials said the publishers were attempting to indoctrinate students.
Highlights 54 textbooks submitted for the state of Florida&amp;rsquo;s approved list have been rejected by the Florida Department of Education. 41% of the submitted textbooks included references to critical race theory, common core and social emotional learning. Governor Ron DeSantis said in a statement, “It seems that some publishers attempted to slap a coat of paint on an old house built on the foundation of Common Core, and indoctrinate concepts like race essentialism, bizarrely for elementary students.</description></item><item><title>Meta says Russians targeting Ukrainians with misinformation and hacking attempts on Facebook</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e627ab0c0a1d692baa9e3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 18:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e627ab0c0a1d692baa9e3/</guid><description>Meta on Sunday said it took down a Russian misinformation campaign along with a hacking group targeting accounts in Ukraine.
Highlights Facebook parent company Meta says it has taken down a coordinated Russian influence operation targeting Ukrainians across Facebook and Instagram. The misinformation campaign has ties to another Russian network in the Donbas region that was previously banned from Facebook in April 2020. The operation also ran a handful of websites, Meta said, which would publish claims about the West betraying Ukraine and Ukraine being a failed state.</description></item></channel></rss>