<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>system on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/system/</link><description>Recent content in system on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 14:10:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kazakhstan to hold constitutional referendum that strips Nazarbayev's immunity and restricts power of president in the government</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ce73282833d835f2a2e57/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 14:10:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628ce73282833d835f2a2e57/</guid><description>On June 5, Kazakhs will vote on a package of reforms intended to transform the country from a super-presidential system to a “presidential system with a strong parliament.”
Highlights Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s president Kassym-Jomart Tokayev called protesters terrorists and requested support from the Russian-backed Collective Security Treaty Organization to quell mass unrest. The vote will take place on June 5, just one month after the proposed reforms were released. The reform package addresses 33 separate articles – about one third of the total constitutional articles – and was developed by a working group.</description></item><item><title>Oregon sued over failure to provide public defenders | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283249f24a5fcb01d44172e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 04:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283249f24a5fcb01d44172e/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Criminal defendants in Oregon who have gone without legal representation for long periods of time amid a critical shortage of public defense attorneys filed a lawsuit Monday that alleges the state violated their constitutional right to legal counsel and a speedy trial.
Highlights Criminal defendants in Oregon who have gone without legal representation for long periods of time amid a critical shortage of public defense attorneys filed a lawsuit Monday.</description></item><item><title>EU wants to remove Russia's largest bank from SWIFT system and ban state-owned broadcasters</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272ec88341644d39f769c5f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 21:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272ec88341644d39f769c5f/</guid><description>In addition to proposing a ban on Russian oil, the European Union is taking several other measures against Moscow over its war in Ukraine, EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said Wednesday.
Highlights EU Commission President Ursula von der Leyen called on the 27-nation bloc to ban oil imports from Russia in a sixth package of sanctions targeting Moscow for its war in Ukraine. In addition to proposing a ban on Russian oil, the EU is taking several other measures against Moscow over its war.</description></item><item><title>Over 40 million people are under severe storm threat this weekend .</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d989b2f32cf19522e1655/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 20:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d989b2f32cf19522e1655/</guid><description>Two separate weather systems will bring severe storms to more than a dozen states this weekend, some of the same ones that were hit Friday night.
Highlights Two separate weather systems will bring severe storms to more than a dozen states this weekend. The system that brought over 150 severe storm reports to the central Plains on Friday will now push east on Saturday. All severe weather hazards will be possible including damaging winds, hail, and tornadoes.</description></item><item><title>Alaska Supreme Court upholds ranked choice voting and top-four primary</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea4c03f24e7810db62532d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea4c03f24e7810db62532d/</guid><description>Summary Bethel citizens vote at the Yupiit Piciryarait Cultural Center in Bethel, Alaska on Nov. 3, 2020. (Katie Basile/KYUK)The Alaska Supreme Court on Wednesday upheld as valid a voter-approved election system that would end party primaries in the state and institute ranked choice voting in general elections. The new system, narrowly approved by voters in 2020, is unique among states and set to be used for this year’s elections. Under the open primary, the top four vote-getters in a race, regardless of party affiliation, would advance to the general election, where ranked choice voting would be used.</description></item><item><title>The Navy Illegally Flushed Tainted Water Into Storm Drains As Red Hill Crisis Took Hold</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c56207756fc4983d3891cc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 06:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c56207756fc4983d3891cc/</guid><description>DOH says it is focusing on mitigating the crisis rather than sanctioning the Navy.
Summary “The DOH typically has the authority to take enforcement actions when there is a discharge of a pollutant to a storm drain system,” she said. Halsey Terrace resident Laura Warfold said she first saw men in uniform flushing water from fire hydrants into the grass in her backyard on Nov. 29. She noticed puddles with an oily sheen near a storm drain by her home.</description></item></channel></rss>