<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>exchange on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/exchange/</link><description>Recent content in exchange on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/exchange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moscow Exchange won't resume stock trading on Wednesday - cenbank</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fb43e61b0b7aaa278d207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621fb43e61b0b7aaa278d207/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank kept stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange suspended for a third day in a row on Wednesday, but said it would allow a limited range of operations for the first time this week.
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s central bank kept stock market trading on the Moscow Exchange suspended for a third day in a row on Wednesday. The central bank said it would allow a limited range of operations for the first time this week.</description></item><item><title>‘Let’s Go Brandon’ merchandise at Alaska exchange crossed AAFES’ line on vulgarity</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5a47e017f3feafb2c7e8e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d5a47e017f3feafb2c7e8e/</guid><description>The Army and Air Force Exchange Service is emphasizing a ban on the sale of lewd or profane products in its stores after a vendor in Alaska sold figurines carrying a crude catch phrase aimed at the commander in chief.
Summary Buy Photo “Let’s Go Brandon” serves as code for some who oppose Joe Biden’s presidency. Pro-Trump crowds routinely chant the phrase during rallies, and it now adorns T-shirts, hats, coffee mugs and a host of other merchandise popular with conservatives.</description></item></channel></rss>