<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prevent on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prevent/</link><description>Recent content in prevent on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 20:14:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prevent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California once prohibited Native American fire practices. Now, it's asking tribes to use them to help prevent wildfires.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b519b650c8789a7f70b38/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 20:14:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b519b650c8789a7f70b38/</guid><description>California is calling upon Native American tribes to bring back the once-prohibited practice of lighting controlled burns to help prevent devastating wildfires that have wreaked havoc on the state.
Highlights Gov. Gavin Newsom’s Wildfire and Forest Resilience Task Force has launched a new plan – “Strategic Plan for Expanding the Use of Beneficial Fire” Native American tradition of prescribed, cultural burns will be revived, Newsom says. These burns are purposefully set, low-intensity fires to rid the land of wildfire fuel like debris, scrub, undergrowth and certain grasses.</description></item><item><title>U.S. has intel that Russian commanders have orders to proceed with Ukraine invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212a0c2303ee227e10eae2f/</guid><description>The intelligence indicates that commanders on the ground making specific plans for how they would maneuver in their sector of the battlefield.
Highlights U.S. intelligence indicates Russian commanders have received orders to proceed with an invasion of Ukraine. Defense minister of Belarus announced Russia will be extending military drills near Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s northern borders. Russia has massed roughly 150,000 troops, warplanes and equipment on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s three sides, escalating tensions with neighboring country.</description></item><item><title>Ivermectin does not prevent severe COVID-19, study finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621117d3166debb3aa5e613b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 16:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621117d3166debb3aa5e613b/</guid><description>Treatment with the dewormer drug ivermectin failed to prevent patients with mild to moderate COVID-19 from progressing to serious illness, a study published Friday by JAMA Internal Medicine found.
Highlights Treatment with dewormer drug ivermectin failed to prevent patients with mild to moderate COVID-19 progressing to serious illness. 43 of 249 patients, or 17%, who received &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; treatment progressed to severe illness, researchers say. Study compared the safety and effectiveness of the drug to standard care in 480 Malaysian patients.</description></item><item><title>Tennis: Novak Djokovic granted injunction to prevent deportation from Australia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2d38dc3f54a99fb96403f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2d38dc3f54a99fb96403f/</guid><description>The tennis superstar has been detained by border officials ahead of a final court hearing.
Summary After admitting this week that he knew he had Covid-19 when he made public appearances, Novak Djokovic has had his Australian visa cancelled. Video / BBCAfter admitting this week that he knew he had Covid-19 when he made public appearances, Novak Djokovic has had his Australian visa cancelled. Interesting to see the gov wants single judge to hear Djokovic case tomorrow, while tennis star’s team advocates for full federal court.</description></item><item><title>Japan bans facial recognition tech exports due to China's human rights abuses: Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 23:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d380140bb7f13f88693409/</guid><description>Tokyo signals intention to work with US and other allies on future export restrictions | 2022-01-03 16:53:00
Summary A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. A Chinese national flag and security camera at the Urumqi No. 3 Detention Center in China&amp;rsquo;s Xinjiang. Tokyo has deemed the new measures necessary to prevent technologies from being used in this way. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>