<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fatally on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fatally/</link><description>Recent content in fatally on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:09:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fatally/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mother charged after Florida toddler fatally shoots father</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f23d4a496fbce80d7a5bd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f23d4a496fbce80d7a5bd/</guid><description>ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — A 2-year old boy fatally shot his father in an accident after finding a gun, and the boy&amp;rsquo;s mother is now facing criminal charges, authorities in Florida said Monday. Reggie Mabry, 26, was fatally shot late last month while he was playing a video game.
Highlights Reggie Mabry, 26, was fatally shot late last month while he was playing a video game. The gun was fired by his 2-year-old son in the home he shared with his wife and their three children.</description></item><item><title>Mom: Daughter mistaken for intruder by father, fatally shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce724e6aaed51be37d241e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce724e6aaed51be37d241e/</guid><description>Police say a man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family’s Ohio home after he mistook her for an intruder
Summary Police say a man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family’s Ohio home after he mistook her for an intruderCOLUMBUS, Ohio &amp;ndash; A man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family&amp;rsquo;s Columbus home after he mistook her for an intruder, according to what the girl&amp;rsquo;s mother told police.</description></item><item><title>Teen in dressing room fatally shot by LA police firing at assault suspect, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c58c36091d61f6ed40dbe6/</guid><description>A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday,
Summary LOS ANGELES — A teenage girl in a dressing room was fatally shot by police who were firing on an assault suspect at a store full of last-minute holiday shoppers Thursday, authorities said. The 14-year-old girl was found dead behind the dressing room wall, which was penetrated by gunfire, Los Angeles police officials said.</description></item></channel></rss>