<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>arrive on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arrive/</link><description>Recent content in arrive on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:45:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/arrive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trucks are gone from Ambassador Bridge, but more protesters arrive on foot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208547dc4a16ec8da59b553/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208547dc4a16ec8da59b553/</guid><description>About 50 police officers have gathered near protesters who have been blocking the Ambassador Bridge for six days.
Highlights About 50 police officers have gathered near protesters who have been blocking the Ambassador Bridge for six days. Truckers have been ordered to clear the bridge or face arrest. Crews use earth-moving equipment to position concrete barricades on Huron Church Road. Trucks are gone from Ambassador Bridge, but more protesters arrive on foot, growing their ranks to several hundred.</description></item><item><title>Russian troops arrive in Kazakhstan, as dozens of protesters killed, thousands arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8397e0ce0a7e083e6efbd/</guid><description>Russia sent paratroopers to Kazakhstan to help its government end mass protests there.
Summary Small numbers of Russian paratrooper units landed at an airbase in Kazakhstan, with Russian state media showing the soldiers disembarking from transport planes and off-loading armored vehicles. The number of Russian troops was unclear, but it was estimated from several hundred to a few thousand, alongside several hundred from Belarus, Tajikistan and Armenia that were also due to arrive.</description></item><item><title>California twins, born 15 minutes apart, arrive in different years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d48b3dd97f23d2c8457317/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d48b3dd97f23d2c8457317/</guid><description>Alfredo Antonio Trujillo was born at 11:45 p.m. on Dec. 31, 2021. He was followed by his twin sister, Aylin Yolanda Trujillo, who arrived at 12 a.m. on Jan. 1, 2022, making her the first baby to be born this year at Natividad Medical Center and in Monterey County, according to a statement from the hospital.
Summary Twins in California might have been born just 15 minutes apart, but they were born in different years.</description></item></channel></rss>