<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>statement on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/statement/</link><description>Recent content in statement on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 13:34:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/statement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>7 wounded in Vegas biker gangs freeway shooting, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62961940cce8589daff9d9bf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62961940cce8589daff9d9bf/</guid><description>Police say rival motorcycle gangs were involved in a metro Las Vegas freeway shooting that injured seven people over the weekend
Highlights Police say rival motorcycle gangs were involved in a metro Las Vegas freeway shooting. Police say the shooting involved people associated with the Hells Angels and the Vagos gangs. Seven people were injured in the shooting over the weekend, police say. Three men were arrested on suspicion on charges of attempted murder with a deadly weapon and other crimes, police said.</description></item><item><title>Birmingham teacher arrested after allegedly sexually assaulting four girls</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628100479268b0a3a61d21fd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628100479268b0a3a61d21fd/</guid><description>28-year-old man held by West Midlands police also accused of sending indecent images of himself
Highlights The 28-year-old suspect, who works at a school in Birmingham, is also accused of sending indecent images of himself. West Midlands police said the man was originally arrested on 9 May but was rearrested on Saturday morning at his home in the city. He has been suspended by the school and remains in police custody, police said.</description></item><item><title>As many as 8 dead in mass shooting at upstate New York supermarket: Law enforcement source - ABC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628029c58f94ee832d1c0140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 22:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628029c58f94ee832d1c0140/</guid><description>Reported mass shooting in upstate New York TOPS Friendly Markets
Highlights At least 10 people are dead and another 3 wounded after a mass shooting at a supermarket in Buffalo, New York, police say. The 18-year-old male suspect entered the supermarket shortly after 2:30 p.m. and fired a rifle, law enforcement officials say. One of the victims was a retired Buffalo police officer working security at the store, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Pink Floyd to release first new music in 28 years in support of Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62506e35fb4c0a21f03f49c4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 17:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62506e35fb4c0a21f03f49c4/</guid><description>Legendary rock band Pink Floyd is releasing a new single &amp;quot;Hey Hey Rise Up&amp;quot; on Friday in support of the people of Ukraine, the band said in a statement on Thursday.
Highlights The song is performed by guitarist David Gilmour and drummer Nick Mason, with bass player Guy Pratt and Nitin Sawhney on keyboard. It&amp;rsquo;s the first new music from the band since 1994, and all proceeds will go to Ukrainian humanitarian relief.</description></item><item><title>Norway has decided to additionally transfer anti-tank weapons to Ukraine, according to the website of the Norwegian Defense Ministry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245c55b8759cc5201539b88/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245c55b8759cc5201539b88/</guid><description>“Norway handed over another 2,000 anti-tank weapons (M72) to Ukraine. The weapons were donated,” the statement said.
Highlights Norway handed over another 2,000 anti-tank weapons to Ukraine. The weapons were donated to Ukraine by Norway, Norway said in a statement. Norway also handed over more than 3,000 other weapons to the country, the statement said. Ukraine has been fighting a growing insurgency in Ukraine since Ukraine began in 2010. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Russia accuses Azerbaijan of violating ceasefire in Karabakh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62401d07e59d956276d58332/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 08:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62401d07e59d956276d58332/</guid><description>Moscow on Saturday accused Azerbaijan of violating a ceasefire agreement by entering the Russian peacekeeping mission&amp;rsquo;s zone in the breakaway region of Nagorno-Karabakh, the first time Russia publicl…
Highlights Moscow accuses Azerbaijan of violating ceasefire agreement by entering Russian peacekeeping mission&amp;rsquo;s zone in breakaway region of Nagorno-Karabakh. Russian defence ministry also accuses Azerbaijani troops of using Turkish-made drones to strike Karabakh troops. Russian foreign ministry in Moscow expresses &amp;ldquo;extreme concern&amp;rdquo; over spiralling tensions in the region.</description></item><item><title>School apologizes after teacher leads California preschoolers in anti-Biden chant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bfdb18d179c860cc88f3a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 05:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623bfdb18d179c860cc88f3a/</guid><description>A Southern California private school apologized to parents after a teacher shared a video last month of her leading preschool students in a chant denouncing President Joe Biden.
Highlights The video shows the unnamed teacher asking the 4- and 5-year-olds, &amp;ldquo;Who’s our president?” The teacher then asks, “What do we want to do with him?&amp;rdquo; The students shout back, &amp;ldquo;We want him out!” It&amp;rsquo;s unclear what, if any, disciplinary action was taken against the teacher.</description></item><item><title>N.Y. college student burned in suspected acid attack criticizes police investigation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236e260bdac757620e615d7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 08:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236e260bdac757620e615d7/</guid><description>A Hofstra University student who was badly burned in a suspected acid attack last year detailed the pain she still endures and questioned whether Long Island police are taking the investigation seriously.
Highlights Hofstra University student Nafiah Ikram, 22, was walking into her Elmont home last March around 8:30 p.m. when a person ran up to her and threw a liquid in her face. Ikram has spent the past year in and out of the hospital undergoing surgeries.</description></item><item><title>Ethiopia pledges action after video shows uniformed men burning civilians alive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230204702378569c7d47731/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 05:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230204702378569c7d47731/</guid><description>Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s government said on Saturday it would act against the perpetrators after a video appeared on social media showing armed men, some in military uniforms, burning civilians to death in the country&amp;rsquo;s west.
Highlights Ethiopia&amp;rsquo;s government says it will act against perpetrators after a video appeared on social media showing armed men, some in military uniforms, burning civilians to death in the country&amp;rsquo;s west. The incident occurred in the Ayisid Kebele of Metekel Zone in the Benishangul-Gumuz region, a site of frequent ethnic violence for more than a year in which hundreds of civilians have died.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after colleague in bulldozer accidentally runs over port-a-potty he was using, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 05:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</guid><description>A Florida landfill worker died Friday after a colleague in a bulldozer accidentally ran over the port-a-potty he was using, authorities said.
Highlights Aaron Henderson, 40, worked for CertiTemp, a company contracted by Polk County, Florida. He was pronounced dead on the scene. Investigators determined that a fellow bulldozer employee was putting the bulldozer away for the day when he drove up an embankment, with the front blade of his bulldozer “elevated 3-4 feet off the ground,” according to the sheriff’s office.</description></item><item><title>Visa, Mastercard block Russian banks from network</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e7e61917dc355ca3fa331/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 20:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e7e61917dc355ca3fa331/</guid><description>Payments News
Highlights Visa and Mastercard have cut Russian financial institutions off from their payments networks. The move was sought by Ukraine National Bank Governor Kyrylo Shevchenko to increase pressure on Vladimir Putin and his regime. The card giants each pledged to donate $2 million for humanitarian assistance to help Ukrainians displaced by the war. The U.N. expects to swell to as many as 5 million people displaced by war, the UN expects to reach 5 million by the end of the year, according to the U.</description></item><item><title>Lukashenko promises to send "whole contingent of Belarusian army" to the border with Ukraine claiming that "the Ukrainians have started dragging troops there”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01eb5e0e2347fcede0d28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01eb5e0e2347fcede0d28/</guid><description>Summary Lukashenko explained this by the fact that &amp;ldquo;the Ukrainians have allegedly started dragging troops there”Alexander Lukashenko at &amp;ldquo;Big Conversation with the President&amp;rdquo; BeltaSelf-proclaimed President of Belarus Alexander Lukashenko said that he would take &amp;ldquo;a whole contingent of the Belarusian army&amp;rdquo; to the border with Ukraine. Lukashenko made this statement during a meeting with the chairman of the State Border Committee of Belarus. We just want to protect our southern border.</description></item><item><title>Business owner paid ex-worker with 91,000 pennies. That's retaliation, feds claim in lawsuit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</guid><description>A Georgia auto repair shop broke the law when it dumped $915 in change on a former employee&amp;rsquo;s driveway, regulator alleges.
Summary The U.S. Department of Labor has filed a lawsuit against the Peachtree, Georgia-based auto repair shop and owner Miles Walker after deciding that the stunt amounted to retaliation. According to the government&amp;rsquo;s complaint, Walker decided to pay Flaten in pennies within hours of learning that he had contacted regulators over his missing paycheck.</description></item></channel></rss>