<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>statement on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/statement/</link><description>Recent content in statement on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/statement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lukashenko promises to send "whole contingent of Belarusian army" to the border with Ukraine claiming that "the Ukrainians have started dragging troops there”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01eb5e0e2347fcede0d28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 16:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f01eb5e0e2347fcede0d28/</guid><description>Summary Lukashenko explained this by the fact that &amp;ldquo;the Ukrainians have allegedly started dragging troops there”Alexander Lukashenko at &amp;ldquo;Big Conversation with the President&amp;rdquo; BeltaSelf-proclaimed President of Belarus Alexander Lukashenko said that he would take &amp;ldquo;a whole contingent of the Belarusian army&amp;rdquo; to the border with Ukraine. Lukashenko made this statement during a meeting with the chairman of the State Border Committee of Belarus. We just want to protect our southern border.</description></item><item><title>Business owner paid ex-worker with 91,000 pennies. That's retaliation, feds claim in lawsuit.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d97ce8dd367d43d5d18548/</guid><description>A Georgia auto repair shop broke the law when it dumped $915 in change on a former employee&amp;rsquo;s driveway, regulator alleges.
Summary The U.S. Department of Labor has filed a lawsuit against the Peachtree, Georgia-based auto repair shop and owner Miles Walker after deciding that the stunt amounted to retaliation. According to the government&amp;rsquo;s complaint, Walker decided to pay Flaten in pennies within hours of learning that he had contacted regulators over his missing paycheck.</description></item></channel></rss>