<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>oxford on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oxford/</link><description>Recent content in oxford on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/oxford/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Victims, parents of Oxford school shooting victims sue school employees</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628de4e0c5f62b4bdd93e509/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628de4e0c5f62b4bdd93e509/</guid><description>The lawsuit against Oxford Community School District and administrators
Highlights Plaintiffs and families of victims of November shooting in Michigan file lawsuit against school district, school administrators. Lawsuit accuses administrators of failing to notify law enforcement of the actions of the accused shooter leading up to the shooting. Justin Shilling and Tate Myre, who were killed in the shooting, and representatives for four minors who were injured in shooting. The lawsuit claims other students saw Ethan Crumbley with shell casings and live ammunition rounds one day before shooting.</description></item><item><title>Ferdinand Marcos Jr urged to stop pretending he has an Oxford degree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628310a576d1b4d894c00a06/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628310a576d1b4d894c00a06/</guid><description>University has said Philippines leader was awarded ‘special diploma in social studies’ in 1978, not a BA
Highlights Ferdinand Marcos Jr is facing calls to stop misrepresenting the circumstances of his studies at Oxford University. The university has confirmed that he did not complete his BA in Philosophy, Politics and Economics after enrolling in 1975. Marcos Jr has claimed in interviews that Oxford issued him with a bachelor’s degree, while his official spokesperson has said that the politician and his team “stand by the degree confirmation which was issued by the University of Oxford” Marcos failed two of his three preliminary exams at Oxford in the summer of 1976, later doing only enough to pass one of two resits – failing politics for a second time.</description></item></channel></rss>