<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>consumption on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/consumption/</link><description>Recent content in consumption on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 12:23:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/consumption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cannabis Retail Sales Become Legal in New Mexico April 1</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242fa127c086984614d9b27/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242fa127c086984614d9b27/</guid><description>New Mexico will allow adult-use sales of cannabis and “cannabis-infused” products to individuals 21 years of age and older in New Mexico on April 1. The Cannabis Regulation Act requires retailers to reserve 20 percent
Highlights New Mexico will allow adult-use sales of cannabis and “cannabis-infused” products to individuals 21 years of age and older in New Mexico on April 1. Cannabis Control Division of the New Mexico Regulation and Licensing Department is tasked with overseeing the new industry.</description></item><item><title>Scotland missed 100% clean electricity consumption in 2020 by only 1.4%</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfdfedede570939739675d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfdfedede570939739675d/</guid><description>In 2011, Scotland set a target of reaching 100% gross clean electricity consumption in 2020, and it almost made it by reaching 98.6%.
Summary In 2011, Scotland set a target of reaching 100% clean electricity consumption in 2020. And last year, the country almost reached its target – 98.6% of gross electricity consumption came from renewable sources, according to the Scottish government’s December energy statement. The BBC notes:In 2019, Scotland met 90.</description></item></channel></rss>