<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cdc on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cdc/</link><description>Recent content in cdc on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 22:15:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cdc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>At least 9 states investigating cases of liver disease in kids, as CDC finds no Covid link</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626db4cb5ca0af3e80a4bfb3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 22:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626db4cb5ca0af3e80a4bfb3/</guid><description>How many cases of liver disease in kids in the US? At least 9 states are investigating mysterious hepatitis illness as CDC finds no Covid link in Alabama.
Highlights A new report appears to rule out Covid as a factor in the mysterious cases of severe hepatitis in children, at least in nine confirmed cases in Alabama. More than a dozen other cases are now being investigated in eight other states.</description></item><item><title>Covid-19 was third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, CDC reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6263734f7a7e5d2e375dd940/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 03:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6263734f7a7e5d2e375dd940/</guid><description>Covid-19 was the third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, following heart disease and cancer, for the second year in a row, according to provisional data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Highlights Covid-19 was the third leading cause of death in the United States in 2021, following heart disease and cancer. The data was published Friday in the CDC&amp;rsquo;s Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report.</description></item><item><title>U.S. extends airplane mask mandate through April 18</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ae92477be6e27e210f239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 06:16:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ae92477be6e27e210f239/</guid><description>The U.S. is extending a requirement that masks are worn on planes, trains and other forms of transportation until the middle of next month.
Highlights The CDC says it will work with government agencies over the next month to &amp;ldquo;help inform a revised policy framework&amp;rdquo; Travel industry groups urge Biden administration to lift Covid testing requirements for inbound international travelers. The new rules will be based on Covid cases, new variant risk &amp;ldquo;and the latest science,&amp;rdquo; CDC says.</description></item><item><title>CDC to significantly ease pandemic mask guidelines Friday | WTOP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218b92ed831908d2b2228a7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 11:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218b92ed831908d2b2228a7/</guid><description>The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday, according to two people familiar with the matter, meaning most Americans will no longer be advised to wear masks in indoor public settings.
Highlights The Biden administration will significantly loosen federal mask-wearing guidelines to protect against COVID-19 transmission on Friday. The change comes as the Biden administration moves to shift its focus to preventing serious illness and death from the virus, rather than all instances of infection.</description></item><item><title>US has suffered more than 1m excess deaths during pandemic, CDC finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ec83d73f565cb456f3193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 22:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ec83d73f565cb456f3193/</guid><description>The latest statistic hints at the breadth of Covid-19’s impact on health in the United States
Highlights There have been more than 1m excess deaths in the US during the pandemic. The deaths are mainly attributable to Covid-19, as well as conditions that may have resulted from delayed medical care and overwhelmed health systems. At least 923,000 Americans have died from confirmed Covid cases, according to the CDC. Other causes of death above the normally expected number have included heart disease, hypertension and Alzheimer’s disease.</description></item><item><title>CDC's suggestion to cancel football, band in nearly every US school called 'unrealistic'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e69dcd61f0da782771a1fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e69dcd61f0da782771a1fd/</guid><description>If the scientists at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had their way, to curb the spread of Covid-19 right now, nearly every US school would cancel football, wrestling, band and loads of other mainstay school activities.
Summary (CNN) If the scientists at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had their way, to curb the spread of Covid-19 right now, nearly every US school would cancel football, wrestling, band and loads of other mainstay school activities.</description></item><item><title>U.S. hits record high with nearly 500,000 COVID-19 cases in a single day</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf0cfd470861cb7f09e997/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 14:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf0cfd470861cb7f09e997/</guid><description>The staggering number comes as the Omicron variant continues to spread across the nation.
Summary The U.S. reported nearly half a million new COVID infections in a single day, marking the largest daily total of any country during the pandemic. More than 486,000 new cases were reported in a 24-hour period, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said Thursday. Puerto Rico and Washington, D.C., are also averaging more daily cases than ever.</description></item><item><title>CDC shortens recommended Covid-19 isolation and quarantine time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</guid><description>The CDC shortened the recommended times that people should isolate when they&amp;rsquo;ve tested positive for Covid-19 from 10 days to five days if they don&amp;rsquo;t have symptoms &amp;ndash; and if they wear a mask around others for at least five more days.
Summary The CDC also shortened the recommended time for people to quarantine if they are exposed to the virus to a similar five days if they are vaccinated. People who are fully vaccinated and boosted may not need to quarantine at all, the CDC said.</description></item></channel></rss>