<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>houston on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/houston/</link><description>Recent content in houston on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 03:19:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/houston/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man with cane shot, killed after being harassed by group of teens in north Houston: HPD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b2b1cc7c9cda9ebc0b466/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 03:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b2b1cc7c9cda9ebc0b466/</guid><description>A man is dead after police said he was shot following harassment from teens in north Houston Monday.
Highlights A 49-year-old man was shot in the chest in north Houston Monday night. Police say he was approached and harassed by a group of teenagers. Four teenage girls ages 14-16 and two teenage boys that are believed to be 16-18 years old. Police said they aren’t sure if the teens got away on foot or in a vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Southwest, United cut thousands of flights over gas prices and staffing issues</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231e3d204ac6b5afbdaee75/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 13:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231e3d204ac6b5afbdaee75/</guid><description>Airlines reported a range of economic reasons for reducing flight capacity, despite&amp;hellip;
Highlights Southwest Airlines drops 65,000 flights from its spring schedule due to staffing issues. United Airlines cites &amp;ldquo;macroeconomic&amp;rdquo; factors, including high gas prices, supply chain issues. The news comes amid a host of frustrations for Houston travelers. Houston airports expect 1.76 million people to travel through William P. Hobby Airport and George Bush International over the course of Spring Break 2022, according to a recent KHOU report.</description></item></channel></rss>