<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>suspects on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspects/</link><description>Recent content in suspects on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/suspects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Just before Buffalo shooting, 15 users signed into suspect’s chatroom, says person familiar with review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62874d7bbc147e10b44fabc8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62874d7bbc147e10b44fabc8/</guid><description>The users were able to scroll through months of voluminous writings and racist screeds.
Highlights Alleged gunman Payton Gendron&amp;rsquo;s online chatroom invitation was accepted by 15 users, according to a person with knowledge of the messaging platform Discord’s investigation into the matter. When the 15 accepted the invite to that server, they were able to scroll back through months of his voluminous writings and racist screeds. The invitation, headed “Happening: This is not a drill,” also included a separate link to an account on the video streaming service Twitch, where he allegedly broadcast video of his attack from a camera mounted on his military-style helmet.</description></item><item><title>Teens charged with hate crime in Islamophobic attack near Lynnwood</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240708fdb37aea887e9db2d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 14:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6240708fdb37aea887e9db2d/</guid><description>They’re the first local juveniles charged with hate crime since the start of 2020. The alleged assault lasted an hour.
Highlights Two teens charged with hate crimes in November assault on 13-year-old boy. It&amp;rsquo;s the first such charges for Snohomish County minors since state Legislature renamed allegation from malicious harassment to hate crime offense. The two teens had a history of harassing the victim, his father told police. One reportedly called the boy a “Muslim terrorist” and “(expletive) Arab” for months.</description></item><item><title>NYC woman lured man on Instagram and tortured him in $100K kidnapping plot, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623171f9522888f02cc4a9fb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 05:14:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623171f9522888f02cc4a9fb/</guid><description>A New York City woman is accused of kidnapping and torturing a man she met on Instagram for more than 12 hours while demanding a $100,000 ransom from his
Highlights A New York woman is accused of kidnapping and torturing a man she met on Instagram for more than 12 hours while demanding a $100,000 ransom from his brother. The victim, 24, was taken to the hospital in stable condition, police said.</description></item><item><title>Missing Utah college student Madelyn Allen found alive, 'covered in coal' in suspect's basement</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 02:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c286b5cf7217ffa7649eac/</guid><description>Description Utah college student Madelyn &amp;ldquo;Maddie&amp;rdquo; Allen vanished last week and was found alive, covered in coal, in the basement of 39-year-old suspect Brent Brown.
Summary A Utah college student who vanished last week was found alive and covered in coal in the basement of a 39-year-old suspect&amp;rsquo;s home, according to authorities. The student, Madelyn Allen, 19, was reported missing after she was seen leaving her dorm at Snow College in Ephraim around 9:22 p.</description></item></channel></rss>