<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>unprecedented on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unprecedented/</link><description>Recent content in unprecedented on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 09:15:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unprecedented/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lake Powell officials take unprecedented, emergency steps to delay water releases as level plummets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272440efa0fbce065f9788c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272440efa0fbce065f9788c/</guid><description>The federal government announced Tuesday it is taking unprecedented, emergency steps to help boost water levels at Lake Powell.
Highlights The US Bureau of Reclamation expects the dual actions will boost Lake Powell by nearly 1 million acre-feet of water. The measures are intended to buy the surrounding communities more time to plan for the very real possibility the reservoir will soon run out of water and the ability to produce hydropower amid the West&amp;rsquo;s climate change-driven megadrought.</description></item><item><title>New government maps show nearly all of the West is in drought and it's not even summer yet: "This is unprecedented"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e9558a2248a51edafc57f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 14:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e9558a2248a51edafc57f/</guid><description>The latest government maps show 95% of California is suffering severe or extreme drought.
Highlights Southern California officials ask residents to limit outdoor watering to once a week. Nearly all of the West is in drought, and 95% of California is suffering severe or extreme drought. Lake Mead, the largest reservoir in the nation formed by the Hoover Dam on the Colorado River, needs a new pump to ensure water can flow to Las Vegas.</description></item></channel></rss>