<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>letter on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/letter/</link><description>Recent content in letter on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:18:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/letter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Musk threatens to walk away from Twitter deal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ed188f0b9e51e26078786/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629ed188f0b9e51e26078786/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — Elon Musk is threatening to walk away from his $44 billion bid to buy Twitter, accusing the company of refusing to give him information about its spam bot and fake accounts .
Highlights Elon Musk is threatening to end his $44 billion agreement to buy Twitter. Lawyers for the Tesla and SpaceX CEO made the threat in a letter to Twitter dated Monday, June 6, 2022 that the social platform included in a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission.</description></item><item><title>Russian diplomat to UN in Geneva resigns over war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c55af747c55fa3aa765b7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 03:49:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c55af747c55fa3aa765b7/</guid><description>DAVOS, Switzerland (AP) — A veteran Russian diplomat to the U.N. Office at Geneva says he handed in his resignation before sending out a scathing letter to foreign colleagues inveighing against the “aggressive war unleashed” by Russian President Vladimir Putin in Ukraine.
Highlights Boris Bondarev, 41, confirmed his resignation in a letter delivered Monday morning at the Russian diplomatic mission in Geneva. The resignation amounts to a rare — if not unprecedented — public admission of disgruntlement about Russia’s war in Ukraine among Russian diplomatic corps.</description></item><item><title>Robberies of mail carriers rise dramatically in U.S. with no signs of abating</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62645e36bfba38a4d925ad94/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62645e36bfba38a4d925ad94/</guid><description>Criminals across the country are increasingly targeting mail carriers.
Highlights Criminals across the country are increasingly targeting mail carriers. Between 2018 and 2021, robberies of mail carriers more than tripled. Robberies involving a gun more than quadrupled, according to U.S. Postal Inspection Service data. USPS says surge in letter carrier robberies fueled by economic impact of Covid crisis, growth in USPS parcel volume amid the rise of e-commerce, e-mailing of government checks related to pandemic aid programs.</description></item><item><title>Diplomats spar over 'edited' Russian letter: Russia has accused Canada of "kindergarten-level" diplomacy in a Twitter tiff over a social media post by Canada's United Nations mission.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62361d81660fb0073e45f1e6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 18:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62361d81660fb0073e45f1e6/</guid><description>Russia accuses Canada of &amp;lsquo;kindergarten&amp;rsquo; diplomacy in spat over a Russian letter sent to UN members.
Highlights Russia accuses Canada of &amp;lsquo;kindergarten&amp;rsquo; diplomacy in spat over a Russian letter sent to UN members. Russia: &amp;ldquo;Your diplomatic skills and good manners are at lowest ebb&amp;rdquo; Russia says it failed to secure enough support to win a non-permanent seat on the powerful UN Security Council. Russia&amp;rsquo;s first deputy permanent representative of Russia to the U.</description></item><item><title>Senators: CIA has secret program that collects American data</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62060c1d86e7dd3778816c72/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62060c1d86e7dd3778816c72/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The CIA has a secret, undisclosed data repository that includes information collected about Americans, two Democrats on the Senate Intelligence Committee said. While neither the agency nor lawmakers would disclose specifics about the data, the senators alleged the CIA had long hidden details about the program from the public and Congress.
Highlights Two Democrats on the Senate Intelligence Committee say the CIA has a secret, undisclosed data repository that includes information collected about Americans.</description></item><item><title>Delta CEO repeats call for a 'no-fly' list for unruly passengers in letter to US attorney general</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff2d6cdd06d48a7de1254e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:08:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff2d6cdd06d48a7de1254e/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian sent a letter to US Attorney General Merrick Garland on Friday reiterating his call for the Justice Department to prosecute unruly passengers and place them on a &amp;quot;no-fly&amp;quot; list.
Highlights Delta Air Lines CEO Ed Bastian reiterates his call for the Justice Department to prosecute unruly passengers and place them on a &amp;ldquo;no-fly&amp;rdquo; list. Last year was the worst on record for unruly airplane passenger behavior in the United States, according to FAA data.</description></item><item><title>Lafayette judge linked to video featuring racist remarks resigns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfb5bda5c073d142302582/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 02:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cfb5bda5c073d142302582/</guid><description>Lafayette judge Michelle Odinet, tied to a video that features racist language, is resigning as Lafayette City Court Judge.
Summary Lafayette judge resigns amid controversy over racist videoLAFAYETTE — Lafayette judge Michelle Odinet, who was recently tied to a video that features racist language, is resigning as Lafayette City Court Judge. After much reflection and prayer, and in order to facilitate healing within the community, I hereby resign as judge of the Lafayette City Court effective immediately.</description></item></channel></rss>