<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tax on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tax/</link><description>Recent content in tax on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 05:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tax/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. posts $119 billion budget surplus in January; first in over 2 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205efe8c48bcc3ae418156c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 05:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6205efe8c48bcc3ae418156c/</guid><description>The U.S. government posted a $119 billion budget surplus in January, the first in more than two years, amid strong growth in tax receipts and a sharp drop in pandemic-related outlays, the Treasury Department said on Thursday.
Highlights The U.S. government posted a $119 billion budget surplus in January, the first in more than two years. The January surplus compared to a January 2021 deficit of $163 billion, a record for the month.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated Quebecers will have to pay a health tax</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de6e90a2a0ddcc83b36c5a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 06:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de6e90a2a0ddcc83b36c5a/</guid><description>Quebec Premier François Legault said Tuesday the province would be demanding a significant &amp;quot;health contribution&amp;quot; from Quebecers who refuse to get their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine in the coming weeks.
Summary Quebec Premier François Legault said Tuesday the province would be imposing a health tax on Quebecers who refuse to get their first dose of a COVID-19 vaccine in the coming weeks. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a health contribution for adults who refuse to be vaccinated for non-medical reasons,&amp;rdquo; Legault said at a news conference, in which he also announced an interim public health director to replace Dr.</description></item><item><title>Quebec to impose a tax on people who are unvaccinated from COVID-19 | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de608acc344cf0856937e3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 05:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de608acc344cf0856937e3/</guid><description>Premier François Legault said the tax is under consideration over the burden those who aren&amp;rsquo;t vaccinated are having on the health-care system.
Summary Send this page to someone via emailQuebec is announcing it will impose a health tax on Quebecers who refuse to be vaccinated against COVID-19. Quebec Premier François Legault made the announcement in Montreal on Tuesday afternoon, as the number of pandemic-related hospitalizations continues to climb. Read more: COVID-19: Quebec tops 12,000 deaths as hospitalizations increase2:13 Quebec to introduce health tax for the unvaccinated Quebec to introduce health tax for the unvaccinatedLegault said he felt the ire of the vaccinated towards the unvaccinated, whom he blamed for clogging up the province’s hospitals.</description></item></channel></rss>