<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>died on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/died/</link><description>Recent content in died on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 05:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/died/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cristiano Ronaldo: Manchester United star announces his baby son has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e46b83d732d3eb55fac00/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 05:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625e46b83d732d3eb55fac00/</guid><description>Ronaldo&amp;rsquo;s Manchester United teammates David de Gea and Alex Telles are among those sending messages of support and condolence after the death of his son.
Highlights Cristiano Ronaldo and partner Georgina Rodriguez announce death of their son. Portuguese star said they are &amp;ldquo;devastated&amp;rdquo; at the loss of their newborn son. Ronaldo already has a four-year-old daughter with Ms Rodriguez, as well as three other children. David de Gea and Alex Telles among those sending messages of support and condolence.</description></item><item><title>Polish state has ‘blood on its hands’ after death of woman refused an abortion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f218db1f743d954f249f19/</guid><description>Family says young mother’s health deteriorated rapidly after the twins she was carrying died a week apart in the womb
Summary The family of a Polish woman who died on Tuesday after doctors refused to perform an abortion when the foetus’s heart stopped beating have accused the government of having “blood on their hands”. Her death comes a year after Poland introduced one of the most restrictive abortion laws in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Legislator dies using medical suicide law he helped pass</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 21:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</guid><description>A former Vermont legislator and House majority leader has died with the help of a law he himself helped pass that allows the terminally ill to end their own lives, his wife said. Willem Jewett died Jan.
Summary The former Vermont lawmaker and House majority leader died on Wednesday, Jan. 12, 2022. Jewett, who had cancer, helped pass a Vermont&amp;rsquo;s aid-in-dying law that allows terminally ill patients to ask their doctors for a lethal dose of medication.</description></item><item><title>Son of North Carolina police officer shot by father has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</guid><description>The son of a Jacksonville police officer has died following an accidental shooting that occurred Dec. 27, involving his father.
Summary ONSLOW COUNTY, N.C. (WITN/Gray Media) - The 15-year-old son of a Jacksonville, North Carolina police officer has died after being shot last Monday at a home in Onslow County. Information released last week by authorities said the police officer accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head. Thursday afternoon, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said the teen has died.</description></item></channel></rss>