<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>died on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/died/</link><description>Recent content in died on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 21:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/died/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legislator dies using medical suicide law he helped pass</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 21:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9cd68727bc17ccc5f9df6/</guid><description>A former Vermont legislator and House majority leader has died with the help of a law he himself helped pass that allows the terminally ill to end their own lives, his wife said. Willem Jewett died Jan.
Summary The former Vermont lawmaker and House majority leader died on Wednesday, Jan. 12, 2022. Jewett, who had cancer, helped pass a Vermont&amp;rsquo;s aid-in-dying law that allows terminally ill patients to ask their doctors for a lethal dose of medication.</description></item><item><title>Son of North Carolina police officer shot by father has died</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79149953202bc5e1f8c8e/</guid><description>The son of a Jacksonville police officer has died following an accidental shooting that occurred Dec. 27, involving his father.
Summary ONSLOW COUNTY, N.C. (WITN/Gray Media) - The 15-year-old son of a Jacksonville, North Carolina police officer has died after being shot last Monday at a home in Onslow County. Information released last week by authorities said the police officer accidentally shot his 15-year-old son in the head. Thursday afternoon, the Onslow County Sheriff’s Office said the teen has died.</description></item></channel></rss>