<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fatal on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/fatal/</link><description>Recent content in fatal on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/fatal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protesters call for firing of officer in fatal Florida dirt bike traffic stop</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cd3ced4379b3f93d073956/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cd3ced4379b3f93d073956/</guid><description>Demonstrators outside the Boynton Beach, Florida police headquarters also demanded transparency about how Stanley David Jr. died.
Summary Demonstrators outside police headquarters in Boynton Beach, Florida, Tuesday night called for the firing of the officer involved in the death of a 13-year old boy on a dirt bike during an attempted traffic stop Sunday, CBS West Palm Beach affiliate WPEC-TV reports. Demonstrators outside Boynton Beach, Florida police headquarters on night of December 29, 2021 pressed for the firing of the officer in a fatal attempted dirt bike traffic stop two days before.</description></item><item><title>Colorado DA asking court to reduce 110-year sentence for trucker in fatal crash to 20-30 years</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ca9a69911fd7afd99c2904/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61ca9a69911fd7afd99c2904/</guid><description>A district court judge in Colorado has scheduled a hearing for January 13 to reconsider the 110-year sentence of Rogel Aguilera-Mederos, a truck driver who was convicted in an interstate wreck that killed four people.
Summary (CNN) A district court judge in Colorado has scheduled a hearing for January 13 to reconsider the 110-year sentence of Rogel Aguilera-Mederos, a truck driver who was convicted in an interstate wreck that killed four people.</description></item></channel></rss>