<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tough on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tough/</link><description>Recent content in tough on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 06:14:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tough/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Whoopi Goldberg Returns To ‘The View’ After Two-Week Suspension: “We’re Going To Keep Having Tough Conversations”</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211dc314fb9d5f74a9e6e88/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 06:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211dc314fb9d5f74a9e6e88/</guid><description>Whoopi Goldberg returned to The View on Monday after a two-week suspension, opening the show by telling viewers, &amp;quot;Yes, I am back.&amp;quot;
Highlights Whoopi Goldberg returned to The View on Monday after a two-week suspension over comments she made about the Holocaust. Goldberg had apologized, but ABC News president Kim Godwin called her comments “wrong and hurtful” The Anti Defamation League condemned the remarks, and she later issued a written apology.</description></item><item><title>Dozens more graves found at former residential school sites</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e1fa125bbfbde8467d546/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 10:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620e1fa125bbfbde8467d546/</guid><description>Indigenous-led investigations have discovered more than 1,100 unmarked graves in recent months.
Highlights Indigenous-led investigations have discovered more than 1,100 unmarked graves in recent months. Indigenous-lead investigations have found more than a million unmarked graves. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a very tough time,&amp;rdquo; says one of the people at the site of the unmarked graves, the man said. &amp;ldquo;We walk every day, drive every day,&amp;rdquo; says the man who led the investigation, who said it was a &amp;ldquo;very tough time&amp;rdquo; for his community to find the graves in the community.</description></item></channel></rss>