<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>unions on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unions/</link><description>Recent content in unions on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 02:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/unions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Feds: National Guard members on state duty can join unions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870142d921a0dada4896c9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62870142d921a0dada4896c9/</guid><description>HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — The Department of Justice has given the green light to National&amp;hellip;
Highlights A 1978 federal law makes it a criminal felony for members of the armed forces, including the National Guard, to join or attempt to form a labor organization. The department on Tuesday settled a federal lawsuit filed in Connecticut by labor unions. Some Texas National Guard members already have moved ahead with their plans, joining the Texas State Employees Union starting in February.</description></item><item><title>Spain’s leftist cabinet approves landmark labour law reform which aims to reduce the use of temporary contracts and boost job security.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd833b98a1415b195d51e4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd833b98a1415b195d51e4/</guid><description>Spain&amp;rsquo;s leftist cabinet approved Tuesday (28 December) a landmark labour law reform which aims to reduce the use of temporary contracts and boost job security.
Summary Spain’s leftist cabinet approved Tuesday (28 December) a landmark labour law reform which aims to reduce the use of temporary contracts and boost job security. Spain is currently the European Union nation where the use of temporary contracts is highest, but the reform tightens conditions for their use in the eurozone’s fourth-largest economy.</description></item></channel></rss>