<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>list on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/list/</link><description>Recent content in list on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Southern Baptist leaders say they will release list of alleged sex abusers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628dd6544d938ee2e0c43eab/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628dd6544d938ee2e0c43eab/</guid><description>Board members of the Southern Baptist Convention’s administrative arm Tuesday issued an apology to sex abuse survivors.
Highlights Southern Baptist Convention leaders say they will release names from a list of alleged abusers they kept secretly for years. They also say they owe abuse survivors an apology and that the denomination must fundamentally change its culture. The report released Sunday sent shock waves through the country’s largest Protestant denomination. It said leaders maintained a secret database of alleged sexual abusers and found that a top leader was credibly accused of assaulting a woman a month after leaving the presidency of the 13 million-member convention.</description></item><item><title>Southern Baptists face push for public list of sex abusers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c29f47a1d2081514be8c1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c29f47a1d2081514be8c1/</guid><description>A blistering report on the Southern Baptist Convention’s mishandling of sex abuse allegations is raising the prospect that the denomination, for the first time, will create a publicly accessible database of pastors and other church personnel known to be abusers.
Highlights A blistering report on the Southern Baptist Convention’s mishandling of sex abuse allegations, released on Sunday, May 23, 2022, is raising the prospect that the denomination, for the first time, will create a publicly accessible database of pastors and other church personnel known to be abusers.</description></item></channel></rss>