<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>abortion on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abortion/</link><description>Recent content in abortion on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abortion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police suspect arson in fire at Wyoming abortion clinic site</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291caab4cdc92f3f00e1212/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291caab4cdc92f3f00e1212/</guid><description>Police believe an overnight fire in Wyoming that damaged a building being renovated to house a new abortion clinic was deliberately set
Highlights Fire damaged building being renovated to house abortion clinic in Casper, Wyoming. Clinic was set to open in June as only the second place in the state to offer abortions. Clinic organizers had been receiving harassing emails and telephone messages. No injuries were reported; police are reviewing video footage from the area in hopes of identifying the suspect.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs the nation’s strictest abortion ban</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f89f3cd3741808d78f4c8/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628f89f3cd3741808d78f4c8/</guid><description>OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt on Wednesday signed into law the nation’s strictest abortion ban, making the state the first in the nation to effectively end availability of the procedure.
Highlights The law takes effect immediately upon Stitt’s signature and prohibits all abortions with few exceptions. The ban enforced by civil lawsuits rather than criminal prosecution, similar to a Texas law that was passed last year. The only exceptions in the Oklahoma law are to save the life of a pregnant woman or if the pregnancy is the result of rape or incest that has been reported to law enforcement.</description></item><item><title>Oklahoma governor signs Texas-style ban on most abortions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62720093b4de16de1e44862b/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 04:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62720093b4de16de1e44862b/</guid><description>Oklahoma’s Republican Gov. Kevin Stitt has signed a Texas-style abortion ban that prohibits abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy
Highlights Gov. Kevin Stitt signs a Texas-style abortion ban that prohibits abortions after about six weeks of pregnancy. A similar bill approved in Texas last year led to a dramatic reduction in the number of abortions performed in that state. Stitt&amp;rsquo;s signing of the bill comes on the heels of a leaked draft opinion from the nation&amp;rsquo;s high court that it is considering weakening or overturning the landmark Roe v.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court says leaked abortion draft is authentic; Roberts orders investigation into leak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271656c74189e2f9d880aa9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 17:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6271656c74189e2f9d880aa9/</guid><description>Roberts noted that the Supreme Court draft ruling, which would overturn decades-old abortion protections, does not represent the court&amp;rsquo;s final decision.
Highlights Chief Justice John Roberts confirms authenticity of leaked draft court opinion that would toss out longstanding abortion rights. The 98-page draft opinion was penned by Justice Samuel Alito, one of six conservatives on a court that has moved sharply to the right in the wake of the Trump administration.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court potential shock move on abortion sends protesters onto Washington streets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270e682e170eb5e76ac974c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 08:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6270e682e170eb5e76ac974c/</guid><description>Anti-abortion activists and pro-abortion rights supporters took to the streets of Washington on Tuesday after news that the U.S. Supreme Court may overturn the 1973 Roe v Wade ruling that legalized abortion.
Highlights A leaked initial draft majority opinion suggests the court has voted to overturn Roe v. Wade. The ruling would be the court&amp;rsquo;s most sweeping since former President Donald Trump succeeded in naming three justices to the court, cementing a 6-3 conservative majority.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis signs Florida's 15-week abortion ban into law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258c2e236048d621a24faa0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:57:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6258c2e236048d621a24faa0/</guid><description>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law on Thursday a Mississippi-style anti-abortion measure that bans the procedure after 15 weeks of pregnancy without exemptions for rape, incest or human trafficking.
Highlights Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law on Thursday banning abortion after 15 weeks of pregnancy. The bill, which goes into effect July 1, does allow exemptions in cases where a pregnancy is &amp;ldquo;serious risk&amp;rdquo; to the mother or a fatal fetal abnormality is detected.</description></item><item><title>DA moves to dismiss a murder charge against a Texas woman accused of a self-induced abortion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625348226b2f2c5c1dfc592f/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 21:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625348226b2f2c5c1dfc592f/</guid><description>Lizelle Herrera, 26, was released from custody Saturday night on $500,000 bond. Then, on Sunday, the DA said the Starr County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Department &amp;quot;did their duty in investigating the incident brought to their attention by the reporting hospital.&amp;quot; However, he said that this is not a criminal matter under Texas law.
Highlights Lizelle Herrera, 26, was arrested Thursday and held on $500,000 bond. She was released from custody Saturday night after an abortion rights advocacy fund posted bail on her behalf.</description></item><item><title>Spain bans harassment of women having abortions | Spain</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f0ea9e9edcf371e8c49c1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f0ea9e9edcf371e8c49c1/</guid><description>Activists could face up to a year in prison for trying to intimidate women into not having terminations
Highlights New law criminalises people who try to stop women having abortions in Spain. It also applies to those who attempt to intimidate doctors or hospital staff. The law was introduced in 1985 to allow abortion on demand in the first 14 weeks of pregnancy. The new law will come into effect after being approved by the Spanish Senate on Wednesday.</description></item></channel></rss>