<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>claim on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/claim/</link><description>Recent content in claim on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 20:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/claim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Burger King sued by customers who claim Whopper is smaller than advertised - CBS News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ca31eda55e7d8607e772f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 20:14:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ca31eda55e7d8607e772f/</guid><description>A class-action lawsuit alleges that ads inflate the Whopper&amp;rsquo;s size, making the burger appear 35% bigger than it actually is.
Highlights Four Burger King customers are suing the chain over its marketing practices. The lawsuit alleges that ads inflate the Whopper&amp;rsquo;s size, making it appear 35% bigger than it is in reality. The plaintiffs are seeking monetary damages for those who were &amp;ldquo;deceived&amp;rdquo; by the ads. A Burger King spokesperson says the chain doesn&amp;rsquo;t comment on the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Roman Abramovich and Ukrainian peace negotiators 'suffered symptoms of suspected chemical weapons poisoning' after talks in Kyiv</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242081602bfa921b1e53b4a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 19:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6242081602bfa921b1e53b4a/</guid><description>Symptoms included red eyes, constant and painful tearing and peeling skin on their hands and faces.
Highlights Three men including Mr Abramovich suffered symptoms including red eyes, constant and painful tearing and peeling skin on their hands and faces. U.S. official: &amp;lsquo;Intelligence &amp;lsquo;highly suggests&amp;rsquo; cause was environmental, &amp;rsquo;not poisoning&amp;rsquo; Ukrainian negotiator: &amp;lsquo;All members of the team are working normally, while Abramovich is fine and continues to work on the negotiations&amp;rsquo; The billionaire lost his sight for several hours and had to be treated in Turkey.</description></item></channel></rss>