<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>15 on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/15/</link><description>Recent content in 15 on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 19:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/15/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>North Korea reports 15 more suspected COVID-19 deaths</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281506ea32f14df61f9cc98/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281506ea32f14df61f9cc98/</guid><description>North Korea has confirmed 15 more deaths and high numbers of fevers as it mobilizes more than a million health and other workers to try to suppress the country&amp;rsquo;s first COVID-19 outbreak.
Highlights North Korea reports 15 more suspected COVID-19 deaths; another 296,180 people with fevers have been tallied. North Korea has said a fever has spread across the country &amp;ldquo;explosively&amp;rdquo; since late April. Experts say North Korea lacks diagnostic kits needed to test large number of suspected patients.</description></item><item><title>Target raises its minimum wage to as much as $24 an hour</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621efca21f2048a0356d87c0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 05:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621efca21f2048a0356d87c0/</guid><description>Worker shortages around the U.S. during the pandemic have forced retailers to boost their pay.
Highlights Target announced in 2017 it would increase hourly wages to $15 per hour by 2020. The Minneapolis-based discount retailer said Monday that it will adopt minimum wages that range from $15 to $24 an hour. Target&amp;rsquo;s CEO Brian Cornell: &amp;ldquo;We want to continue to have an industry-leading position&amp;rdquo; The new starting wage range is part of a company plan to spend an additional $300 million on its labor force this year that will also include broader, faster access to health care coverage for its hourly workers.</description></item><item><title>Gunman holds hostages at synagogue in Texas</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e37c59b3aaad26e9a234f3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e37c59b3aaad26e9a234f3/</guid><description>An FBI SWAT team was on the scene and law enforcement negotiated with the gunman.
Summary A rabbi and three others were taken hostage during a Shabbat service at the reform Beth Israel Synagogue in Colleyville, Texas, on Saturday. Another tweet two hours later updated that the hostage situation was still in progress. — Colleyville Police (@ColleyvillePD) January 15, 2022BREAKING: Gunman holding hostages at a synagogue in Colleyville, Texas — BNO News (@BNONews) January 15, 2022The area surrounding the synagogue was urgently evacuated, though local news claimed there did not seem to be a threat to the general public.</description></item></channel></rss>