<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2nd on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2nd/</link><description>Recent content in 2nd on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/2nd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>26 MPs of pro-Kurdish party charged with 'offending Turkish state' after calling for Armenian Genocide recognition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cba51c565c8ac983aa5aa7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 00:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cba51c565c8ac983aa5aa7/</guid><description>During the session of the&amp;hellip;
Summary Bill Gates reveals plan to save the planetKuwait forms new cabinetAttorney: Criminal prosecution against Artur Vanetsyan terminated, there was no preparation for Armenia PM&amp;rsquo;s murderArmenia army&amp;rsquo;s General Staff chief visits air force military unitArmenia opposition MP: Constitutional Court states that government should decide who will pay for employees' PCR testsBrawl takes place in Parliament of JordanArmenia Ombudsman meets with Russia Ambassador, return of Armenian captives being held in Azerbaijan discussedArmenia launches 42 cases regarding submission of declarations by officials in 2021Armenian man who was wanted arrives in Yerevan and voluntarily shows up at police stationArmenia MOD peacekeeping brigade soldiers participate in tactical military exercisesArmenia has new Ambassador to IsraelAzerbaijani opposition journalists protesting against repressive law on mediaArmenia President and his wife pay visit to Yerablur Military PantheonArmenia Competition Protection Commission to check pricing for COVID-19 tests at Zvartnots AirportAdvocate: Criminal prosecution against Armenian detachment commander Ashot Minasyan is overNEWS.</description></item><item><title>Police: 2nd person arrested after child says she was locked in closet for 25 days</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7beade982a21ad8b2876e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 01:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7beade982a21ad8b2876e/</guid><description>Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant.
Summary Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant. JACKSONVILLE, Fla. – Another person was arrested after a child said she was locked in a closet for nearly a month, according to an arrest warrant.</description></item></channel></rss>