<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>latin on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/latin/</link><description>Recent content in latin on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 10:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/latin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russia disinformation on Ukraine spreads on Spanish-speaking social media</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c166328b84db35b7d6b87/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 10:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c166328b84db35b7d6b87/</guid><description>Russia disinformation on Ukraine in Spanish is spreading widely, and Kremlin-controlled outlets are some of the top Spanish-language news sources about the war.
Highlights Russia is launching falsehoods into the feeds of Spanish-speaking social media users in Latin America. The aim is to gain support in those countries for the Kremlin’s war and stoke opposition against the U.S. The content thrives on Spanish-language websites, message boards and social media pages. Many of the claims have been discredited, but they’re spreading widely.</description></item><item><title>US will act ‘decisively’ if Russia deploys military to Cuba or Venezuela – White House</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e28d3ff7b48085346590e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 09:10:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e28d3ff7b48085346590e5/</guid><description>The American authorities would act “decisively” if Russia deployed its military to Latin America, the White House said on Thursday, following suggestions that Moscow could station some of its troops in Venezuela or Cuba.
Summary Moscow has refused to rule out sending military infrastructure to Venezuela or CubaThe American authorities would act “decisively” if Russia deployed its military to Latin America, the White House said on Thursday, following suggestions that Moscow could station some of its troops in Venezuela or Cuba.</description></item></channel></rss>