<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>real on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/real/</link><description>Recent content in real on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:40:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/real/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canada's Trudeau announces plan for national freeze on handguns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629563c4166e08fef4f508a9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629563c4166e08fef4f508a9/</guid><description>Canada&amp;rsquo;s government introduced legislation Monday to implement a &amp;quot;national freeze&amp;quot; on the sale and purchase of handguns as part of a gun control package that would also limit magazine capacities and ban some toys that look like guns.
Highlights Canada&amp;rsquo;s government introduces legislation to implement a &amp;ldquo;national freeze&amp;rdquo; on the sale and purchase of handguns as part of a gun control package. The new legislation would also limit magazine capacities and ban some toys that look like guns.</description></item><item><title>Two Illinois men get 14, 16 years in Minnesota mosque bombing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625694341db7fc2390744e2e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 09:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625694341db7fc2390744e2e/</guid><description>The men had pled guilty in the US attack and cooperated with prosecutors, testifying against the man who organised it.
Highlights Michael McWhorter, 33, and Joe Morris, 26, sentenced to just under 16 years in United States prison. Victims and prosecutors asked for leniency because the men cooperated and testified against the mastermind of the attack. The men had pleaded guilty in the US attack and cooperated with prosecutors, testifying against the man who organised it.</description></item><item><title>Havana syndrome has ‘dramatically hurt’ morale, US diplomats say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62066ea917969a1d41d8dffa/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 14:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62066ea917969a1d41d8dffa/</guid><description>American Foreign Service Association chief Eric Rubin says syndrome, whose cause has yet to be determined, has affected recruitment
Highlights The symptoms of the syndrome, which has not been identified, are still a mystery. The syndrome is thought to be a result of a lack of communication with the public. The symptoms are believed to be caused by the syndrome. In some cases, it is also the result of an illness that is believed to have been caused by a virus.</description></item><item><title>Birds are real, a US government agency wants you to assure you</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9fb7a03ad2604cf64f8af/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 21:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9fb7a03ad2604cf64f8af/</guid><description>And the US Consumer Product Safety Commission flew off on a meme tangent to prove it.
Summary Ohio Division of WildlifeA parody movement claims birds aren&amp;rsquo;t real. Now, a government agency, the US Consumer Product Safety Commission, is jumping in to defend its feathered friends. Background: Peter McIndoe, 23, created the &amp;ldquo;Birds Aren&amp;rsquo;t Real&amp;rdquo; movement in 2017 as a parody of conspiracy theories, according to The New York Times, His storyline claimed birds are drones created by the government to spy on its citizens, although McIndoe says he&amp;rsquo;s done with the joke now.</description></item></channel></rss>