<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shots on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shots/</link><description>Recent content in shots on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 22:10:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pfizer says 3 COVID shots protect children under 5</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c06400c1074f3a125a309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 22:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c06400c1074f3a125a309/</guid><description>Three doses of Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine offer strong protection for children younger than 5, the company announced Monday. It&amp;rsquo;s a step toward letting the littlest kids get vaccinated.
Highlights Three doses of Pfizer’s COVID-19 vaccine offer strong protection for children younger than 5, the company announced Monday, May 23, 2022. Pfizer plans to give the data to U.S. regulators later this week in a step toward letting the littlest kids get the shots.</description></item><item><title>US had 5 rabies deaths last year, highest total in a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</guid><description>Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade
Summary Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decadeNEW YORK &amp;ndash; Five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade — and health officials said Thursday that some of the people didn&amp;rsquo;t realize they had been infected or refused life-saving shots.</description></item><item><title>Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fire warning shots in the air to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</guid><description>The protest comes two days after the ministry issued travel curbs on women across Afghanistan, further curtailing their rights
Summary Witnesses say Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fired warning shots Tuesday to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country. The women marched through the streets of the Afghan capital toward the Ministry for the Promotion of Virtue and Prevention of Vice, which enforces Islamic law as interpreted by the Taliban.</description></item><item><title>CDC director says initial Covid shots 'may not be enough' as omicron rapidly sweeps the nation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c224461d573b547c66ea61/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c224461d573b547c66ea61/</guid><description>Description Dr. Rochelle Walensky said omicron has &amp;ldquo;over 50 mutations and because of those mutations, just being vaccinated with two doses may not be enough.&amp;rdquo;
Summary CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the omicron variant of the coronavirus has &amp;ldquo;over 50 mutations and because of those mutations, just being vaccinated with two doses may not be enough&amp;rdquo; ahead of the holidays. Even so, Walensky said that vaccines &amp;ldquo;may not prevent infection&amp;rdquo; according to data so far.</description></item></channel></rss>