<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>reveals on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reveals/</link><description>Recent content in reveals on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:12:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/reveals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu Resigns After FBI Reveals Anaheim Corruption Probe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c7745216ed39f72f0727e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c7745216ed39f72f0727e/</guid><description>Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu abruptly resigns following FBI corruption probe into city hall. Mayor&amp;rsquo;s lawyer Paul Meyer issued a statement defending the mayor’s actions while in office. An FBI affidavit alleges that Sidhu shared city information with the
Highlights Anaheim Mayor Harry Sidhu abruptly resigns Monday. The resignation comes after an FBI corruption probe into Anaheim City Hall was revealed. Sidhu&amp;rsquo;s lawyer Paul Meyer issued a statement defending the mayor’s actions while in office.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine rules out territorial concessions, as Russia steps up attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bb50b28d5e7b260085460/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628bb50b28d5e7b260085460/</guid><description>Kyiv revealed its worst military losses from a single attack of the Ukraine war on Monday, saying 87 people had been killed last week when Russian forces struck a barracks housing troops at a training base in the north.
Highlights Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s president says 87 people were killed when Russian forces struck barracks housing troops at a training base in the north last week. The disclosure that scores had been killed in the attack demonstrated Russia&amp;rsquo;s ability to inflict huge losses, even far from the front.</description></item><item><title>Wealthiest Americans pay just 3.4% of income in taxes, investigation reveals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627414acd9c07786891bd528/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 18:17:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627414acd9c07786891bd528/</guid><description>Tax records from 2014 to 2018, analysed by ProPublica, show 25 Americans collectively earned $401bn but paid just $13.6bn
Highlights The wealthiest Americans paid just 3.4% of their annual income in taxes between 2014 and 2018. The average tax rate for the 400 richest Americans was 22% from 2013 to 2018. Wealthier Americans get their income through investments, like stocks, which are taxed at a lower rate than ordinary income. Ten of the top 15 earners on the list are billionaires who made their money in tech, earning an average of $2.</description></item><item><title>‘They were all shot’: Russia accused of war crimes as Bucha reveals horror of invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a41bb1257dd0c87b4746b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624a41bb1257dd0c87b4746b/</guid><description>Ukrainian forces liberating the town of Bucha near Kyiv find streets littered with corpses of civilians and burned-out Russian tanks
Highlights At least 20 bodies, all in civilian clothing, found strewn across a single street in Bucha, a town north-west of the capital. At least 280 other bodies have been buried in mass graves in the town, local residents say. British foreign secretary Liz Truss said she was ‘appalled’ by atrocities in town of Bucha.</description></item></channel></rss>