<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>abuse on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abuse/</link><description>Recent content in abuse on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 06:15:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/abuse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ghislaine Maxwell juror to be questioned under oath by judge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621873e47f623c24f4c5c3f8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 06:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621873e47f623c24f4c5c3f8/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — A Ghislaine Maxwell trial juror who said on a written questionnaire that he&amp;rsquo;d never been a sexual abuse victim will be questioned by the trial judge
Highlights A juror who said he&amp;rsquo;d never been a sexual abuse victim will be questioned by the trial judge. The juror said during jury selection for Ghislaine Maxwell&amp;rsquo;s criminal trial only to reveal after the trial that he was a child sex abuse victim.</description></item><item><title>U.S. judge rejects Prince Andrew's bid to dismiss sex abuse accuser's lawsuit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df416ff7a3dc5a2429fa35/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 21:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df416ff7a3dc5a2429fa35/</guid><description>Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew failed to persuade a U.S. judge to dismiss Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit accusing the Duke of York of sexually abusing her when she was a teenager.
Summary Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew leaves St. Mary the Virgin church in Hillington, near royal Sandringham estate, in Norfolk, Britain January 19, 2020. REUTERS/Chris RadburnNEW YORK, Jan 12 (Reuters) - Britain&amp;rsquo;s Prince Andrew failed to persuade a U.S. judge to dismiss Virginia Giuffre&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit accusing the Duke of York of sexually abusing her when she was a teenager.</description></item><item><title>US farms made $200million via human smuggling and labor trafficking operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7e8df00c61d353cf0b258/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c7e8df00c61d353cf0b258/</guid><description>Two dozen conspirators forced workers to pay fees for travel and housing while forcing them to work for little to no pay
Summary Initially, the worker was told they would be working on a blueberry farm, but was sent to a corn-farming operation instead. “There was a lot of abuse for little pay,” the worker added. They were excluded from the National Labor Relations Act passed in 1935, and the Fair Labor Standards Act of 1938.</description></item></channel></rss>