<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>passed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/passed/</link><description>Recent content in passed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 12:26:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/passed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Tremors’ Star Fred Ward Has Passed Away at 79</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f9fdddea30f6364554f86/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 12:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f9fdddea30f6364554f86/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve learned the incredibly sad news this morning (via NPR) that actor Fred Ward has passed away at the age of 79, the actor of course beloved by horror
Highlights NPR reports that Fred Ward died on Sunday, May 8th. Ward played the lovable character Earl Bassett in the original Tremors back in 1990. He also appeared in Escape from Alcatraz, The Right Stuff, Miami Blues, The Player, Naked Gun 33 1/3, The Crow: Salvation, and Road Trip.</description></item><item><title>Citi's response to abortion bans: We'll pay for workers to travel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623299d241630a7aa830e455/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 02:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623299d241630a7aa830e455/</guid><description>After a number of US states passed laws severely restricting access to abortions, Citigroup this week said it is providing employees with travel benefits to facilitate access to abortion clinics.
Highlights Citigroup&amp;rsquo;s new policy covers employees&amp;rsquo; expenses when traveling to seek an abortion, according to a person with knowledge of the matter. The company declined to comment beyond what it published in its proxy statement. Several states have recently passed laws that make many abortions illegal.</description></item><item><title>Extreme heat in oceans ‘passed point of no return’ in 2014</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb3cf5463bd63d051ae416/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 02:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fb3cf5463bd63d051ae416/</guid><description>Formerly rare high temperatures now covering half of seas and devastating wildlife, study shows
Highlights Extreme heat in the world’s oceans passed the ‘point of no return’ in 2014 and has become the new normal. In some hotspots, extreme temperatures occur 90% of the time, severely affecting wildlife. Scientists analysed sea surface temperatures over the last 150 years, which have risen because of global heating. By 2019, the proportion of the global ocean suffering extreme heat was 57%, according to the study.</description></item></channel></rss>