<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>team on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/team/</link><description>Recent content in team on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:41:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Justice Dept. names 9 to aid in review of Uvalde shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a141aca88305a22c884acb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:41:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a141aca88305a22c884acb/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department has named a team of nine people, including an FBI official and former police chiefs, to aid in a review of the law enforcement response to the Uvalde, Texas, elementary school shooting that left 19 children and two teachers dead.
Highlights The critical incident review is being led by the Justice Department’s Office of Community Oriented Policing Services. The review will include an examination of police policies, training and communication, along with the deployment of officers and tactics.</description></item><item><title>11-foot hammerhead shark washes up on Florida beach</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d1e89536a2f1d2ec79352/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d1e89536a2f1d2ec79352/</guid><description>An 11-foot hammerhead shark washed up on a beach in southern Florida, much to beachgoers&amp;rsquo; surprise.
Highlights A female great hammerhead shark washed up on Pompano Beach, north of Fort Lauderdale, Florida. A team of scientists from the American Shark Conservancy took samples and identified the shark. The female was pregnant and weighed around 500 lbs, a conservation scientist says. A member of the team encountered the body with a hook in its mouth, which usually indicates someone was fishing for a large animal like a hammerhead, she says.</description></item><item><title>Anonymous team hacks database of Central Bank of Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c9975c0c447be38c729a4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c9975c0c447be38c729a4/</guid><description>A group of hackers Anonymous have hacked the database of the Central Bank of Russia and are going to make more than 35,000 files with secret agreements publicly available in the next 48 hours.
Highlights Anonymous team hacks database of Central Bank of Russia. More than 35,000 files will be released within 48 hours with secret agreements. Some 67% of Belarusians against shelling of Ukraine by Russian troops from territory of Belarus - study by Chatham House.</description></item><item><title>Pittsburgh Steelers hire Brian Flores after coach files racial discrimination suit against NFL</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621221f454dfa2ffb12d0f42/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 11:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621221f454dfa2ffb12d0f42/</guid><description>Former Miami Dolphins coach Brian Flores is returning to the National Football League as the senior defensive assistant and linebackers coach for the Pittsburgh
Highlights Brian Flores is returning to the National Football League as the senior defensive assistant and linebackers coach for the Pittsburgh Steelers. Flores filed a federal lawsuit alleging racial discrimination against the NFL, the New York Giants and other teams earlier this month. Flores, who is Black with Honduran roots, has over 14 years of coaching experience in the NFL.</description></item><item><title>Mt. Everest's highest glacier lost 2,000 years worth of ice since the 1990s</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62049e916292795fa96f27cf/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 05:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62049e916292795fa96f27cf/</guid><description>Even the world&amp;rsquo;s tallest mountain is not safe from climate change.
Highlights Scientists found that the South Col Glacier is losing ice 80 times faster than it took for ice to accumulate on the glacier&amp;rsquo;s surface. The glacier is currently losing several decades worth of ice accumulation every year. The melt could have serious impacts on the mountain, and those who live near it. Future research must focus on how widely these melting trends apply to other glaciers at the top of the world, the researchers concluded.</description></item><item><title>Betrayer of Anne Frank revealed; man named Arnold van den Bergh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5768daf6115b5dd1df873/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5768daf6115b5dd1df873/</guid><description>A retired FBI special agent and a team of investigators believe they&amp;rsquo;ve solved one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most well-known and tragic cold cases.
Summary Seventy-five years after its publication, &amp;ldquo;The Diary of Anne Frank&amp;rdquo; remains among the most widely-read books in the world. The area where Anne Frank lived is very normal. Jon Wertheim: This question of who betrayed Anne Frank, that had been investigated for years. I mean, the honor of the diary, the honor of Anne Frank, we had to treat this with utmost respect.</description></item><item><title>NASCAR rejects 'Let's Go Brandon' sponsorship, Brandonbilt Motorsports says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7f3c19f0269b84c42ecc1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7f3c19f0269b84c42ecc1/</guid><description>NASCAR has rejected Xfinity Series driver Brandon Brown&amp;rsquo;s sponsorship deal with cryptocurrency meme coin LGBcoin &amp;ndash; a reference to the controversial &amp;quot;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Brandon&amp;quot; phrase, his team acknowledged to CNN on Wednesday.
Summary (CNN) NASCAR has rejected Xfinity Series driver Brandon Brown&amp;rsquo;s sponsorship deal with cryptocurrency meme coin LGBcoin &amp;ndash; a reference to the controversial &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Brandon&amp;rdquo; phrase, his team acknowledged to CNN on Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;NASCAR did not speak with Brandonbilt Motorsports prior to making their decision to rescind the approval and multiple attempts to set-up a conversation to address this matter went unacknowledged,&amp;rdquo; Max Marcucci, Brandonbilt Motorsports spokesperson said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>