<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>team on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/team/</link><description>Recent content in team on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Betrayer of Anne Frank revealed; man named Arnold van den Bergh</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5768daf6115b5dd1df873/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5768daf6115b5dd1df873/</guid><description>A retired FBI special agent and a team of investigators believe they&amp;rsquo;ve solved one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most well-known and tragic cold cases.
Summary Seventy-five years after its publication, &amp;ldquo;The Diary of Anne Frank&amp;rdquo; remains among the most widely-read books in the world. The area where Anne Frank lived is very normal. Jon Wertheim: This question of who betrayed Anne Frank, that had been investigated for years. I mean, the honor of the diary, the honor of Anne Frank, we had to treat this with utmost respect.</description></item><item><title>NASCAR rejects 'Let's Go Brandon' sponsorship, Brandonbilt Motorsports says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7f3c19f0269b84c42ecc1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 08:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d7f3c19f0269b84c42ecc1/</guid><description>NASCAR has rejected Xfinity Series driver Brandon Brown&amp;rsquo;s sponsorship deal with cryptocurrency meme coin LGBcoin &amp;ndash; a reference to the controversial &amp;quot;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Brandon&amp;quot; phrase, his team acknowledged to CNN on Wednesday.
Summary (CNN) NASCAR has rejected Xfinity Series driver Brandon Brown&amp;rsquo;s sponsorship deal with cryptocurrency meme coin LGBcoin &amp;ndash; a reference to the controversial &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Brandon&amp;rdquo; phrase, his team acknowledged to CNN on Wednesday. &amp;ldquo;NASCAR did not speak with Brandonbilt Motorsports prior to making their decision to rescind the approval and multiple attempts to set-up a conversation to address this matter went unacknowledged,&amp;rdquo; Max Marcucci, Brandonbilt Motorsports spokesperson said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>