<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>epa on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/epa/</link><description>Recent content in epa on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/epa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EPA moves to give states, tribes more power to protect water</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299b37f48cdab34b624630f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299b37f48cdab34b624630f/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Thursday proposed undoing a Trump-era rule that limited the power of states and Native American tribes to block energy projects like natural gas pipelines based on their potential to pollute rivers and streams.
Highlights The Biden administration on Thursday, June 2, 2022, proposed undoing a Trump-era rule that limited the power of states and Native American tribes to block energy projects like natural gas pipelines based on their potential to pollute rivers and streams.</description></item><item><title>Fears for bees as US set to extend use of toxic pesticides that paralyse insects</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228b5e19ab8914eb54d9e8d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 14:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228b5e19ab8914eb54d9e8d/</guid><description>EPA to approve plan for four types of neonicotinoid chemical to be used on US farmland – despite being banned in Europe
Highlights Environmental Protection Agency poised to allow use of four of the most devastating chemicals to bees, butterflies and other insects to continue in America for the next 15 years. The chemicals assault receptors in an insect’s nerve synapse, causing uncontrollable shaking, paralysis and death. The use of neonicotinoids has contributed to the land becoming 48 times more toxic than it was a quarter of a century ago.</description></item></channel></rss>