<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>shooter on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooter/</link><description>Recent content in shooter on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/shooter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A dying Uvalde teacher was on the phone with her husband -- a school police officer whose boss decided not to enter her classroom, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629975d9766eab870f824e13/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629975d9766eab870f824e13/</guid><description>Eva Mireles spent some of her final monents on the phone with her police officer husband, The New York Times reported. But he couldn&amp;rsquo;t save his wife and 20 others massacred at Robb Elementary. And a negotiator&amp;rsquo;s attempts to reach the gunman were futile.
Highlights Texas State Sen. Roland Gutierrez questions whether 911 calls from inside Texas elementary school were relayed properly to responders at the scene of the shooting. Gutierrez promised to share that information with media once received.</description></item><item><title>Marcel Fontaine, falsely accused of being the Parkland shooter by Alex Jones, dies in apartment fire. He sued Jones and Infowars, paving the way for lawsuits by Sandy Hook parents.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286a42f7ad83437bea01c80/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 20:11:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286a42f7ad83437bea01c80/</guid><description>Former Norwalk resident Marcel Fontaine, who filed one of the first defamation lawsuits&amp;hellip;
Highlights Marcel Fontaine, 29, was among four people killed in a fire early Saturday in Worcester, Mass., authorities say. Fontaine filed a defamation lawsuit against Alex Jones for falsely identifying him as the shooter at Stoneman Douglas High School in Florida. The lawsuit, which is considered one of the first filed against Jones, is scheduled to go to trial in about a month.</description></item><item><title>As many as 8 dead in mass shooting at upstate New York supermarket: Law enforcement source - ABC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628029c58f94ee832d1c0140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 22:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628029c58f94ee832d1c0140/</guid><description>Reported mass shooting in upstate New York TOPS Friendly Markets
Highlights At least 10 people are dead and another 3 wounded after a mass shooting at a supermarket in Buffalo, New York, police say. The 18-year-old male suspect entered the supermarket shortly after 2:30 p.m. and fired a rifle, law enforcement officials say. One of the victims was a retired Buffalo police officer working security at the store, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>Sacramento church shooting leaves 5 dead, including 3 children</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621df1df3d31af810ed93f26/</guid><description>Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office confirmed.
Highlights Authorities say a man shot and killed his three children, one other person and then turned the gun on himself at a church in Sacramento. The victims included three girls ages 9, 10 and 13, officials said. The shooter, who is unidentified, had a restraining order against him, an official said.</description></item></channel></rss>