<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>nbc on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nbc/</link><description>Recent content in nbc on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 12:13:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/nbc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protesters' anguished shouts fail to dampen gun enthusiasm at NRA convention in Houston</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629211e3201cff31f1c8dce6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 12:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629211e3201cff31f1c8dce6/</guid><description>Less than 72 hours after a gunman killed 19 children and two teachers in Uvalde, Texas, thousands of gun owners gathered at an NRA meeting in Houston.
Highlights Gun owners gathered in Houston to defend and celebrate the types of laws that made it possible for a teenager to purchase a pair of AR-15-style semiautomatic rifles days after his 18th birthday. Gun control activists and gun owners were separated by a four-lane road, metal barricades and horse-mounted police.</description></item><item><title>'Good night': Uvalde school shooting survivors describe gunman's words before opening fire</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291e692abc53a8be0a4e245/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 09:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291e692abc53a8be0a4e245/</guid><description>Survivors of the Robb Elementary School shooting are recounting the gunman&amp;rsquo;s eerie final words of &amp;quot;Good night&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;You&amp;rsquo;re all gonna die&amp;quot; before opening fire.
Highlights 11-year-old Miah Cerrillo, 11, said the gunman looked at one of her teachers in the eye and said, “Good night” before shooting her. Samuel Salinas, 10, was a student in teacher Irma Garcia’s class on Tuesday when the shooting unfolded. Samuel said he survived by playing dead after he got hit in the leg with shrapnel that hit a chair between him and the shooter.</description></item><item><title>Connecticut boy, 6, severely burned in bullying attack, his family says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269b1f2f040ac8f3519c2c5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 21:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6269b1f2f040ac8f3519c2c5/</guid><description>A 6-year-old boy in Connecticut has been hospitalized with second- and third-degree burns after his family said a bully covered a tennis ball with gasoline, lit it on fire and threw it at his face.
Highlights Dominick Krankall was playing in the backyard of his family’s Bridgeport home with other children who live near them. An 8-year-old neighbor entered a shed on the property and got ahold of gasoline and lighters and called Dominick over, his sister says.</description></item></channel></rss>