<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stores on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stores/</link><description>Recent content in stores on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 07:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stores/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Potent protest: Bars drop Russian vodka, promote Ukraine’s</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c75e9878706c929ffd3de/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 07:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621c75e9878706c929ffd3de/</guid><description>By PAUL WISEMAN AP Business Writer Some bars and liquor stores think they&amp;rsquo;ve found a potent way to punish Russia for invading Ukraine: They&amp;rsquo;re pulling Russ
Highlights Some bars and liquor stores think they&amp;rsquo;ve found a potent way to punish Russia for invading Ukraine. Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine directed the state’s Commerce Department to cease the purchase and sale of Russian Standard, the only Russian vodka sold in Ohio (under the brand names Green Mark and Russian Standard) New Hampshire Gov.</description></item><item><title>Shoplifting is surging across America with dangerous and costly consequences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9b5397ad14d7c9fb8b9ae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9b5397ad14d7c9fb8b9ae/</guid><description>Summary This is not a one-time opportunistic or need-based robbery,&amp;quot; said Cory Lowe, an expert on retail crime and research scientist at the Loss Prevention Research Council, an industry coalition that researches retail crime, its impact and solutions to address it. But even then, it was more street robberies and not like retail theft as brazen as this.&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve talked to retailers across America who say shoplifting is now 2% to 3% of their total sales.</description></item><item><title>Quebec’s cannabis, liquor stores to require coronavirus vaccination proof</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d928a18bee74921efa930e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 06:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d928a18bee74921efa930e/</guid><description>As Quebec&amp;rsquo;s covid hospitalizations rise, Health Minister Christian Dubé said holdouts should know: “If they can’t get vaccinated, then they should stay home.”
Summary About a fifth of Quebec’s 8.5 million people are not vaccinated. But they account for about half of the patients in intensive care, Dubé said. “We’re going to make sure they understand very well that if they can’t get vaccinated, then they should stay home.” READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>