<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bus on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bus/</link><description>Recent content in bus on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/bus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reward grows to $22,500 for arrest of escaped inmate serving life for murder</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280f0e03ac5ff8dc8bd0c21/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 12:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6280f0e03ac5ff8dc8bd0c21/</guid><description>A Texas inmate serving life for murder managed to break free from his shackles, overpower a bus driver and escape from custody, officials said.
Highlights Gonzalo Lopez, 46, was on a transport bus en route from Gatesville to Huntsville for a medical appointment when he escaped. Lopez cut out the bottom of a door that separates inmates and the driver, Texas Department of Criminal Justice says. Lopez is serving a life sentence for a capital murder in Hidalgo County and an attempted capital murder.</description></item><item><title>Del. State Univ. president ‘incensed’ over Georgia police drug search of lacrosse team bus</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a48c984198c22fc472903/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 11:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a48c984198c22fc472903/</guid><description>The women’s team was on its way home from playing games in Florida and Georgia when the bus was stopped. Officers ransacked their luggage but found nothing illegal.
Highlights Delaware State University&amp;rsquo;s women&amp;rsquo;s lacrosse coach was surprised when the driver suddenly pulled off Interstate 95 in Liberty County, Georgia. A sheriff’s deputy told the driver that the left lane was prohibited for buses and asked him to step outside. Two deputies entered and announced they were going to search their luggage in the cargo bay below the bus.</description></item><item><title>Las Vegas woman who pushed elderly man off bus, leading to his death, gets prison sentence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211334a682d8ea3a435733d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 18:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211334a682d8ea3a435733d/</guid><description>A Las Vegas woman who admitted to pushing an elderly man off a public transit bus in 2019 was sentenced to prison Friday as part of a plea bargain.
Highlights Cadesha Bishop, 25, received a sentence of eight to 20 years for abuse of an older person resulting in death. On March 21, 2019, Bishop was captured on bus surveillance video arguing with Serge Fournier, 74. Bishop was seen pushing him, causing him to fall onto the sidewalk below.</description></item></channel></rss>