<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deposition on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deposition/</link><description>Recent content in deposition on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:14:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deposition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alex Jones avoids jail, faces escalating $25K daily fine until he complies with Sandy Hook testimony order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244e418430dee843ab53bd3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244e418430dee843ab53bd3/</guid><description>The fine, which could accumulate into six figures in as quickly as four days, was imposed&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones faces escalating daily fine of $25,000 for &amp;ldquo;intentionally failing to comply with the orders of the court” Judge Barbara Bellis also held him in contempt of court. The fine, which could accumulate into six figures in as quickly as four days, was imposed Wednesday. Bellis could have issued an order for Jones’ arrest to compel him to testify.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families seek Alex Jones arrest after 2nd no-show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e6309148241c2ccd593bb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:49:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e6309148241c2ccd593bb/</guid><description>Relatives of some victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting are asking a Connecticut judge to order the arrest of Infowars host Alex Jones for missing a court-ordered deposition this week
Highlights Relatives of some victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting are asking a Connecticut judge to order the arrest of Infowars host Alex Jones for missing a court-ordered deposition this week. Jones missed both days of a scheduled deposition Wednesday and Thursday in Austin, Texas.</description></item></channel></rss>