<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>baby on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/baby/</link><description>Recent content in baby on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/baby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A father says he put 1,000 miles on his car to find specialty formula for premature infant daughter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a5242bb66ba91358270f6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a5242bb66ba91358270f6/</guid><description>Mac Jaehnert said he put 1,000 miles on his car in the last week looking for a specialty nutritional formula for daughter MacKenzie and other premature babies in his southeastern Washington state community.
Highlights Mac Jaehnert described empty store shelves in his search for Similac NeoSure in Richland, Washington state. &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been a frustrating, heartbreaking, unnecessary challenge for a kid who has already overcome so much,&amp;rdquo; he said. The Biden administration has ordered the use of military aircraft to expedite the delivery of baby formula to the U.</description></item><item><title>FDA comes to agreement with baby formula factory to resume production</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62838336f45acb4232acb38b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 11:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62838336f45acb4232acb38b/</guid><description>Abbott Nutrition said it would still take months to get the product back on store shelves.
Highlights Abbott Nutrition agrees to fix safety issues at a Michigan factory that has been shuttered for more than three months. The agreement represents a first step toward resolving a problem that has sent parents scrambling from store to store to find sustenance for their infants. The company has previously said that once the FDA has signed off on the fixes, it will take six to eight weeks to get the product back on shelves.</description></item></channel></rss>