<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rights on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rights/</link><description>Recent content in rights on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 17:15:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High court limits suing officials over rights violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a22a9dce9fa7326ee77759/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 17:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a22a9dce9fa7326ee77759/</guid><description>It’s the latest in a line of cases narrowing the public’s ability to sue federal officials for rights violations.
Highlights The owner of the Smuggler’s Inn in Blaine, Washington, can’t sue a Border Patrol agent over a confrontation at his inn. Robert Boule says the agent shoved him and then retaliated against him when he complained that the man had used excessive force. It&amp;rsquo;s the latest in a line of cases narrowing the public&amp;rsquo;s ability to sue federal officials for rights violations.</description></item><item><title>Yelp, other companies take stance on abortion rights with travel benefit</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277c44928d516adc649175a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277c44928d516adc649175a/</guid><description>Yelp, Amazon, and Citigroup are among a small but growing number of companies rolling out policies to cover costs for American employees who need to travel out of state for an abortion.
Highlights Yelp, Amazon.com, Citigroup, Levi Strauss &amp;amp; Co and Amazon have all pledged to pay for employees&amp;rsquo; travel to obtain abortions. The issue has gained urgency now that 31 states have introduced abortion bans this year, according to policy analysis by research group Guttmacher Institute.</description></item><item><title>L.A. bans official travel to Florida and Texas over parents' rights bill, LGBTQ+ policies</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fd3388a2df1d47de220b6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 06:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624fd3388a2df1d47de220b6/</guid><description>TheLos Angeles County Board of Supervisors voted unanimously on Tuesday to suspend all official travel to both Florida and Texas. The travel ban was proposed and passed in response to legislationenacted in Florida and Texas. Critics, including the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors, claim those bills target LGBTQ+ youth and families. The board reportedly voted in support of the ban in order to support &amp;quot;affirming care and inclusion for LGBTQ+ youth and their families.</description></item><item><title>Russian mercenaries and Mali army accused of killing 300 civilians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d4c3a8940161e34f54ad7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:16:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d4c3a8940161e34f54ad7/</guid><description>Human Rights Watch says deaths during anti-jihadist operation in Moura ‘the worst atrocity in Mali in a decade’
Highlights Human Rights Watch says 300 civilian men were allegedly executed over five days in March. HRW says it is the worst single atrocity reported in Mali’s decade-long armed conflict. Mali&amp;rsquo;s army has long been accused of rights abuses during counter-insurgency operations. It has forged closer links with Russia after its relations soured with the west – its former ally France – which has committed to scaling down its forces in the Sahel region.</description></item><item><title>Colorado now guarantees the right to abortion in state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b5f2d7987f31f92c4ddf3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b5f2d7987f31f92c4ddf3/</guid><description>Abortion access is now guaranteed in Colorado law after Gov. Jared Polis signed a bill enshrining that right Monday.
Highlights The bill passed out of the Colorado legislature last month on a party-line vote. It would ban local and state governments from interfering in that care. It also would prevent a fertilized egg, embryo or fetus from having independent rights under state law. 15 other states and the District of Columbia have codified abortion into law with the “Reproductive Health Equity Act’s” The bill signed by Jared Polis, a Democrat of Pueblo, was passed by the House of Representatives last week.</description></item><item><title>Russian TV Editor Who Disrupted News Show With Anti-War Poster Missing, Her Lawyers Claim</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62310fe021594345dc4df9f6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 22:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62310fe021594345dc4df9f6/</guid><description>The incident, a highly unusual breach of security at Channel One, took place during its flagship news show called &amp;lsquo;Time&amp;rsquo;.
Highlights Marina Ovsyannikova was taken to a police station after the breach. Human rights group OVD-Info has claimed she is missing. She is believed to be being held in a secret location. Incident took place during Channel One&amp;rsquo;s flagship 9:00pm news show called &amp;lsquo;Time&amp;rsquo; It is watched by millions around the country, particularly by older Russians.</description></item><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court takes up clash between religion and LGBT rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217139e487cdb5d686aa9e0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217139e487cdb5d686aa9e0/</guid><description>The top court agreed to hear an evangelical Christian web designer&amp;rsquo;s free speech claim that she cannot be forced under a Colorado anti-discrimination law to produce websites for same-sex marriages.
Highlights The U.S. Supreme Court takes up a major new legal fight pitting religious beliefs against LGBT rights. Christian web designer Lorie Smith says she cannot be forced under a Colorado anti-discrimination law to produce websites for same-sex marriages. Colorado law bars anyone from refusing &amp;ldquo;goods, services, facilities, privileges, advantages or accommodations&amp;rdquo; based on sexual orientation, age, race, gender and religion.</description></item><item><title>LGBTQ Afghans face surge of rape, torture after Taliban takeover, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1d28bfa156b28b62252e2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1d28bfa156b28b62252e2/</guid><description>LGBTQ Afghans have increasingly been threatened, beaten and raped since the Taliban took control of the country in August, a new report found.
Summary LGBTQ Afghans have increasingly been threatened, beaten and raped since the Taliban took control of the country in August, a new report found. And while LGBTQ Afghans have long lived in peril, the groups concluded that the situation has “dramatically worsened” following the Taliban’s takeover. A few weeks after Taliban forces overtook Afghanistan’s capital, Kabul, in August, a 20-year-old gay man reported that Taliban members had detained him at a checkpoint.</description></item><item><title>Athletes warned against speaking up on human rights at Beijing Games</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e819869ee7d36089540e2d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 14:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e819869ee7d36089540e2d/</guid><description>Athletes travelling to next month&amp;rsquo;s Beijing Olympics were warned on Tuesday about speaking up on human rights issues while in China for their own safety by speakers at a seminar hosted by Human Rights Watch.
Summary REUTERS/Pawel Kopczynski/File PhotoJan 18 (Reuters) - Athletes travelling to next month&amp;rsquo;s Beijing Olympics were warned on Tuesday about speaking up on human rights issues while in China for their own safety by speakers at a seminar hosted by Human Rights Watch.</description></item><item><title>Florida gay rights activist found dead in landfill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4332d76fddecb2b237f78/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 15:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4332d76fddecb2b237f78/</guid><description>Jorge Diaz-Johnston, who was integral in passing marriage equality in Miami, was found dead in a landfill in what is being investigated as a homicide.
Summary A gay rights advocate who was integral in legalizing same-sex marriage in Florida was found dead in a landfill in what authorities are investigating as a homicide, the Tallahassee Police Department said Wednesday. While he had a high-profile brother, Diaz-Johnston made a name for himself.</description></item><item><title>Murphy signs bill enshrining abortion into NJ state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e19e4d69dd4e34eac0ed3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 16:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e19e4d69dd4e34eac0ed3d/</guid><description>TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — New Jersey Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy, anticipating possible changes to the Roe v. Wade ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court, signed a bill Thursday enshrining the right to an abortion into state law.
Summary Phil Murphy, anticipating possible changes to the Roe v. Wade ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court, signed a bill Thursday enshrining the right to an abortion into state law. ADVERTISEMENTIn addition to abortion rights, the bill also specifically outlines a right to access contraception, as well as to carry a pregnancy to term.</description></item><item><title>Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fire warning shots in the air to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</guid><description>The protest comes two days after the ministry issued travel curbs on women across Afghanistan, further curtailing their rights
Summary Witnesses say Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fired warning shots Tuesday to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country. The women marched through the streets of the Afghan capital toward the Ministry for the Promotion of Virtue and Prevention of Vice, which enforces Islamic law as interpreted by the Taliban.</description></item><item><title>Taliban Reportedly Opens Fire On Women Protesting Against Restrictions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</guid><description>Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women.
Summary Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women. Taliban officials did not immediately respond to requests from RFE/RL for comment.</description></item></channel></rss>