<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rights on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/rights/</link><description>Recent content in rights on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fire warning shots in the air to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</guid><description>The protest comes two days after the ministry issued travel curbs on women across Afghanistan, further curtailing their rights
Summary Witnesses say Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fired warning shots Tuesday to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country. The women marched through the streets of the Afghan capital toward the Ministry for the Promotion of Virtue and Prevention of Vice, which enforces Islamic law as interpreted by the Taliban.</description></item><item><title>Taliban Reportedly Opens Fire On Women Protesting Against Restrictions</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</guid><description>Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women.
Summary Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women. Taliban officials did not immediately respond to requests from RFE/RL for comment.</description></item></channel></rss>