<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rights on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rights/</link><description>Recent content in rights on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:12:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. Supreme Court takes up clash between religion and LGBT rights</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217139e487cdb5d686aa9e0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6217139e487cdb5d686aa9e0/</guid><description>The top court agreed to hear an evangelical Christian web designer&amp;rsquo;s free speech claim that she cannot be forced under a Colorado anti-discrimination law to produce websites for same-sex marriages.
Highlights The U.S. Supreme Court takes up a major new legal fight pitting religious beliefs against LGBT rights. Christian web designer Lorie Smith says she cannot be forced under a Colorado anti-discrimination law to produce websites for same-sex marriages. Colorado law bars anyone from refusing &amp;ldquo;goods, services, facilities, privileges, advantages or accommodations&amp;rdquo; based on sexual orientation, age, race, gender and religion.</description></item><item><title>LGBTQ Afghans face surge of rape, torture after Taliban takeover, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1d28bfa156b28b62252e2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 23:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1d28bfa156b28b62252e2/</guid><description>LGBTQ Afghans have increasingly been threatened, beaten and raped since the Taliban took control of the country in August, a new report found.
Summary LGBTQ Afghans have increasingly been threatened, beaten and raped since the Taliban took control of the country in August, a new report found. And while LGBTQ Afghans have long lived in peril, the groups concluded that the situation has “dramatically worsened” following the Taliban’s takeover. A few weeks after Taliban forces overtook Afghanistan’s capital, Kabul, in August, a 20-year-old gay man reported that Taliban members had detained him at a checkpoint.</description></item><item><title>Athletes warned against speaking up on human rights at Beijing Games</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e819869ee7d36089540e2d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 14:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e819869ee7d36089540e2d/</guid><description>Athletes travelling to next month&amp;rsquo;s Beijing Olympics were warned on Tuesday about speaking up on human rights issues while in China for their own safety by speakers at a seminar hosted by Human Rights Watch.
Summary REUTERS/Pawel Kopczynski/File PhotoJan 18 (Reuters) - Athletes travelling to next month&amp;rsquo;s Beijing Olympics were warned on Tuesday about speaking up on human rights issues while in China for their own safety by speakers at a seminar hosted by Human Rights Watch.</description></item><item><title>Florida gay rights activist found dead in landfill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4332d76fddecb2b237f78/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 15:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e4332d76fddecb2b237f78/</guid><description>Jorge Diaz-Johnston, who was integral in passing marriage equality in Miami, was found dead in a landfill in what is being investigated as a homicide.
Summary A gay rights advocate who was integral in legalizing same-sex marriage in Florida was found dead in a landfill in what authorities are investigating as a homicide, the Tallahassee Police Department said Wednesday. While he had a high-profile brother, Diaz-Johnston made a name for himself.</description></item><item><title>Murphy signs bill enshrining abortion into NJ state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e19e4d69dd4e34eac0ed3d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 16:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e19e4d69dd4e34eac0ed3d/</guid><description>TRENTON, N.J. (AP) — New Jersey Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy, anticipating possible changes to the Roe v. Wade ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court, signed a bill Thursday enshrining the right to an abortion into state law.
Summary Phil Murphy, anticipating possible changes to the Roe v. Wade ruling from the U.S. Supreme Court, signed a bill Thursday enshrining the right to an abortion into state law. ADVERTISEMENTIn addition to abortion rights, the bill also specifically outlines a right to access contraception, as well as to carry a pregnancy to term.</description></item><item><title>Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fire warning shots in the air to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 02:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cbc13cdbcbba3f9d60b180/</guid><description>The protest comes two days after the ministry issued travel curbs on women across Afghanistan, further curtailing their rights
Summary Witnesses say Taliban security forces in Afghanistan fired warning shots Tuesday to disperse a group of female activists in Kabul protesting restrictions placed on women in the country. The women marched through the streets of the Afghan capital toward the Ministry for the Promotion of Virtue and Prevention of Vice, which enforces Islamic law as interpreted by the Taliban.</description></item><item><title>Taliban Reportedly Opens Fire On Women Protesting Against Restrictions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb34b57d802f2a3073048a/</guid><description>Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women.
Summary Taliban militants have reportedly opened fire on a group of women protesting in the streets of Kabul against the government&amp;rsquo;s discriminatory policies two days after officials announced new travel restrictions on women. Taliban officials did not immediately respond to requests from RFE/RL for comment.</description></item></channel></rss>