<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>city on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/city/</link><description>Recent content in city on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 05:17:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/city/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde school district police chief won't be sworn in Tuesday as city council meeting is postponed for funerals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295a4d71f33fbe27fc809f3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 05:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6295a4d71f33fbe27fc809f3/</guid><description>With funerals for victims of last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting now taking place in Uvalde, Texas, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor has postponed a city council meeting at which new members &amp;ndash; including school district police chief Pedro &amp;quot;Pete&amp;quot; Arredondo &amp;ndash; were to be sworn in.
Highlights With funerals for victims of last week&amp;rsquo;s school shooting now taking place in Uvalde, Texas, the city&amp;rsquo;s mayor postpones a city council meeting. Mayor Don McLaughlin: &amp;ldquo;Our focus on Tuesday is on our families who lost loved ones&amp;rdquo; 19 school children and two teachers were killed in two adjoining classrooms at Robb Elementary by an 18-year-old gunman.</description></item><item><title>City employee fired gun over 20 times after Iowa juvenile refused to perform sex act</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c196c30b87d6889aeab51/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627c196c30b87d6889aeab51/</guid><description>Police say he shot more than 20 rounds toward the Raccoon River.
Highlights Michael Teeples allegedly asked one of the girls to perform a sex act in exchange for money. When she refused, he showed a handgun and threatened to shoot out their tires if they left. He then tried to grab the victims in the vehicle they were driving. He later fired the weapon in the victims’ direction. Police say he shot more than 20 rounds toward the Raccoon River.</description></item><item><title>New York subway shooting suspect indicted on terrorism charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277b5c61855fe506386caa8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 12:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6277b5c61855fe506386caa8/</guid><description>If convicted on the terrorism charge, James could be sentenced to life in prison.
Highlights Grand jury indicts Frank James, 62, for terrorism and other charges stemming from April 12 attack. James, a Bronx native, is accused of setting off smoke bombs and opening fire inside a New York City subway car in Brooklyn. If convicted on the terrorism charge, James could be sentenced to life in prison. The motive of the attack has not been determined but the suspect has been linked to several violent incidents in New York&amp;rsquo;s public transportation system in the past.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine accuses Russian forces of seizing 2,000 artworks in Mariupol</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ce19263899f92fa512651/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 07:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ce19263899f92fa512651/</guid><description>City council is reportedly preparing materials to initiate criminal proceedings over mass cultural looting
Highlights Russian forces have accused Russian forces of seizing “over 2,000 artworks” from museums in the occupied city of Mariupol and moving the pieces to areas of the Russian-controlled Donbas region. The haul includes several original works by the 19th-century. Russian President Vladimir Putin has ‘lost’ the art of Russian landscape in which he rejected Ukraine’s independent identity, language and traditions,” the city council said in a statement posted on its Telegram channel on Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Post-Floyd probe finds discrimination by Minneapolis police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a31eb977fe2b8190c7b9e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 06:20:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626a31eb977fe2b8190c7b9e/</guid><description>ST. PAUL, Minn. (AP) — The Minneapolis Police Department has engaged in a pattern of race discrimination for at least a decade, including stopping and arresting Black people at a higher rate than white people, using force more often on people of color and maintaining a culture where racist language is tolerated, a state investigation launched after George Floyd’s killing found.
Highlights Minnesota Department of Human Rights released report Wednesday. Report: Minneapolis Police Department engaged in a pattern of race discrimination for at least a decade.</description></item><item><title>Cañon City wild horse facility quarantined due to 'unknown yet highly contagious' disease outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626917bed64324c6d7ccd539/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 10:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626917bed64324c6d7ccd539/</guid><description>The Bureau of Land Management&amp;rsquo;s Cañon City Wild Horse and Burro Facility is under a voluntary quarantine due to an &amp;quot;unknown yet highly contagious&amp;quot; disease outbreak, the bureau announced Monday.
Highlights The Bureau of Land Management&amp;rsquo;s Cañon City Wild Horse and Burro Facility is under a voluntary quarantine. 57 horses have died so far since the outbreak began on April 23. Officials are working to determine the exact cause of death.</description></item><item><title>Detroit illegally overtaxed homeowners $600M resulting in 100,000 people losing their homes to foreclosure.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625be88e26fc10bd671f4fbc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 10:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625be88e26fc10bd671f4fbc/</guid><description>An estimated 100,000 Detoiters lost their home to foreclosures because of over-assessments
Highlights An estimated 100,000 Detroiters, most of them Black, lost their homes to foreclosure. Michigan Constitution prohibits property from being assessed at more than 50% of its market value. To this day, residents have not been compensated for losing their homes or paying more than they owed in property taxes. Coalition for Property Tax Justice surveyed more than 200 overtaxed residents to determine how they want to be compensated.</description></item><item><title>Philadelphia becomes first major US city to reinstate indoor mask mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255356262381e5d718436ec/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 08:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255356262381e5d718436ec/</guid><description>Covid-19 cases have risen more than 50% in 10 days, the threshold at which city’s guidelines call for masking indoors
Highlights Philadelphia is first major US city to reinstate its indoor mask mandate after sharp increase in coronavirus infections. Health inspectors will begin enforcing the mask mandate at city businesses on 18 April. Health officials believe the recent wave is being driven by the highly transmissible BA.2 sub-variant of Omicron, which has spread rapidly throughout Europe and Asia.</description></item><item><title>Miami Beach city leaders announce ban on alcohol sales after 6 PM starting Thursday; attempt to curtail spring break violence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cd14628c1f72d2ecf6bea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 20:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623cd14628c1f72d2ecf6bea/</guid><description>Alcohol sales will be prohibited in curfew areas after 6 p.m. starting Thursday. The alcohol sales ban does not include patrons buying drinks at restaurants or bars. The established curfew zone is from the area of 23rd Street and Dade
Highlights Alcohol sales will be prohibited in curfew areas after 6 p.m. starting Thursday. The alcohol sales ban does not include patrons buying drinks at restaurants or bars. The established curfew zone is from the area of 23rd Street and Dade Boulevard to the north to Government Cut to the south.</description></item><item><title>‘We don’t know how to survive here’: a cancer ward for Ukrainian children under siege</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f0b93114cd717580e51da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 06:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f0b93114cd717580e51da/</guid><description>Chernihiv children’s hospital is running out of morphine and mines cover all roads in and out
Highlights Children&amp;rsquo;s hospital in Chernihiv children&amp;rsquo;s hospital is under siege by Russian forces. Children aged 2-15 are battling cancer and running out of painkillers. Hospitals in Poland and Slovakia have agreed to continue treatment, waiving fees. The only way out would be on a helicopter, but the city is effectively under siege. The hospital wasn’t properly prepared for war, with a shelter in such a terrible condition that people were getting sick from sleeping there.</description></item><item><title>Despite over 100 people pleading for help at city hall, Tampa City Council shoots down rent control</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62189da62179b49dab557492/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 09:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62189da62179b49dab557492/</guid><description>Council cited legal reasons and will discuss an alternative ordinance on April 21.
Highlights Tampa City Council held a &amp;ldquo;rent stabilization workshop&amp;rdquo; today to discuss rent control in general. Many of the activists want council to declare a housing state of emergency in order to enact rent control. Council didn&amp;rsquo;t declare an emergency or move toward rent control, arguing that it couldn&amp;rsquo;t work legally. Council members proposed an ordinance that would require landlords to give six months notice before increasing rent.</description></item><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item><item><title>Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying 'sovereign stuff is not valid'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</guid><description>Detroit police break up peaceful and permitted Native sugarbush ceremony in River Rouge Park
Highlights Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying&amp;rsquo;sovereign stuff is not valid&amp;rsquo; Police officers shut down Indigenous sugarbush festival in River Rouge Park. Ceremony was held to kick off the third annual tapping season as part of the Detroit Sugarbush Project. Organizers say they had valid fire permits and approval from the city of Detroit. A video posted to Instagram shows officers standing side-by-side along the edge of the clearing as smoke from the recently extinguished fire billowed between them and attendees and attendees.</description></item><item><title>‘Extremely disappointed’: New 40-ton arches collapse onto bridge in downtown Hickory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211a15047c8a8529e01adfc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 02:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211a15047c8a8529e01adfc/</guid><description>Neighbors said it sounded like an earthquake when the arches came crashing down overnight. The arches were part of the city’s multimillion-dollar City Walk Project project. They weighed 40-ton and cost $750,
Highlights Arches fell onto the pedestrian walkway and onto Main Avenue Northeast over Highway 127, near downtown Hickory. Neighbors said it sounded like an earthquake when the arches came crashing down. The arches were part of the city’s multimillion-dollar City Walk Project project, whose contract was signed in June 2019.</description></item><item><title>New York City will begin removing homeless people from subways at night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 09:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</guid><description>Mayor says public fear of subways is driving riders from the system and announces more mental health support to homeless
Highlights New York leaders released a plan to strictly enforce rules on the New York City subway as part of an aggressive effort to remove homeless people from the city’s sprawling transit system. The plan comes in light of an uptick in felony assaults in the subway which, while rare, were up 25% in 2021 compared with 2019.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Springs to pay nearly $3 mln to family of Black man shot dead by police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</guid><description>A Colorado city has agreed to pay $2.9 million to settle a civil rights lawsuit filed by the family of a 19-year-old Black man who was fatally shot in the back by police in 2019, both sides in the litigation said on Tuesday.
Highlights De&amp;rsquo;Von Bailey was shot four times after he bolted from two Colorado Springs policemen who were questioning him about an armed robbery in August 2019. Police said they retrieved a handgun from Bailey after he was shot.</description></item><item><title>Removing trucks could be almost 'impossible,' say heavy towing experts | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201ee35b056c6045f7e942e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201ee35b056c6045f7e942e/</guid><description>Heavy-duty towing experts say it will be difficult or impossible to remove the hundreds of heavy trucks entrenched in Ottawa&amp;rsquo;s downtown — unless the drivers allow it.
Highlights CBC counted 40 trucks on Kent Street and 109 on Wellington Street Friday, with dozens more on other streets spread around the downtown core. The City of Ottawa has declared a state of emergency amid the protests. Sources say companies contracted by the city are refusing to tow trucks involved with the demonstration.</description></item><item><title>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</guid><description>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds
Summary Hamtramck judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weedsHamtramck Judge Alexis Krot has apologized to an elderly cancer patient she berated and threatened with jail time over some unkempt weeds outside his home. &amp;ldquo;I made a mistake,&amp;rdquo; Krot said in a statement shared with the Free Press by the court Thursday. Related: Michigan lawmaker to file complaint against Hamtramck judge who berated elderly manKrot has drawn widespread condemnation and media attention over her comments made during an online court hearing last week that was captured on a Zoom video that circulated on social media.</description></item><item><title>Girl under 10 is youngest person to die of COVID-19 in Houston, city health officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</guid><description>A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday.
Summary The nations COVID-19 death toll stands at around 800,000 as the anniversary of the U.S. vaccine rollout arrives. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke, File)HOUSTON – A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday. Privacy laws prevent the health department from providing any other identifiable information.</description></item><item><title>New York will allow non-citizens to vote under controversial law | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</guid><description>A watershed moment for the most populous US city as opponents vow to challenge the law
Summary More than 800,000 non-citizens and “Dreamers” could vote in New York City municipal elections as early as next year, after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to become law on Sunday. Opponents have vowed to challenge the law, which the city council approved a month ago. Unless a judge halts its implementation, New York is the first major US city to grant widespread municipal voting rights to non-citizens.</description></item><item><title>Russian Jets Knock Out Water Supply In Syria's Idlib: "Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water..."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</guid><description>Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.
Summary Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.</description></item><item><title>1 in 50 Manhattan Residents Infected With COVID in the Last Week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</guid><description>The omicron variant outbreak of COVID-19 in New York City is growing so quickly, 2% of all Manhattan residents were infected in just the last week.
Summary As the omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread out of control in New York City, transmission rates are soaring, with 2% of all Manhattan residents infected in the last week and nearing that level in the other boroughs. About 2,012 of every 100,000 Manhattan residents tested positive in the last seven days, according to the latest transmission data posted by the city.</description></item></channel></rss>