<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>city on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/city/</link><description>Recent content in city on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/city/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian Jets Knock Out Water Supply In Syria's Idlib: "Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water..."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</guid><description>Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.
Summary Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.</description></item><item><title>1 in 50 Manhattan Residents Infected With COVID in the Last Week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</guid><description>The omicron variant outbreak of COVID-19 in New York City is growing so quickly, 2% of all Manhattan residents were infected in just the last week.
Summary As the omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread out of control in New York City, transmission rates are soaring, with 2% of all Manhattan residents infected in the last week and nearing that level in the other boroughs. About 2,012 of every 100,000 Manhattan residents tested positive in the last seven days, according to the latest transmission data posted by the city.</description></item></channel></rss>