<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>city on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/city/</link><description>Recent content in city on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 06:16:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/city/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘We don’t know how to survive here’: a cancer ward for Ukrainian children under siege</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f0b93114cd717580e51da/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 06:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f0b93114cd717580e51da/</guid><description>Chernihiv children’s hospital is running out of morphine and mines cover all roads in and out
Highlights Children&amp;rsquo;s hospital in Chernihiv children&amp;rsquo;s hospital is under siege by Russian forces. Children aged 2-15 are battling cancer and running out of painkillers. Hospitals in Poland and Slovakia have agreed to continue treatment, waiving fees. The only way out would be on a helicopter, but the city is effectively under siege. The hospital wasn’t properly prepared for war, with a shelter in such a terrible condition that people were getting sick from sleeping there.</description></item><item><title>Despite over 100 people pleading for help at city hall, Tampa City Council shoots down rent control</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62189da62179b49dab557492/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 09:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62189da62179b49dab557492/</guid><description>Council cited legal reasons and will discuss an alternative ordinance on April 21.
Highlights Tampa City Council held a &amp;ldquo;rent stabilization workshop&amp;rdquo; today to discuss rent control in general. Many of the activists want council to declare a housing state of emergency in order to enact rent control. Council didn&amp;rsquo;t declare an emergency or move toward rent control, arguing that it couldn&amp;rsquo;t work legally. Council members proposed an ordinance that would require landlords to give six months notice before increasing rent.</description></item><item><title>Gunman charged with killing protester in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216b15ceddda3b0075e6c42/</guid><description>PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, told them to leave and then drew a pistol and opened fire, killing a woman and wounding four other people, a prosecutor said Tuesday.
Highlights A 43-year-old man confronted protesters against police violence in a Portland, Oregon, park, then drew a pistol and opened fire, a prosecutor said Tuesday. Brandy “June” Knightly, 60, was shot in the head at close range and died on the scene, Mota said.</description></item><item><title>Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying 'sovereign stuff is not valid'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 01:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212f1e3ef8b6740de3358c8/</guid><description>Detroit police break up peaceful and permitted Native sugarbush ceremony in River Rouge Park
Highlights Detroit police break up Native sugarbush ceremony, saying&amp;rsquo;sovereign stuff is not valid&amp;rsquo; Police officers shut down Indigenous sugarbush festival in River Rouge Park. Ceremony was held to kick off the third annual tapping season as part of the Detroit Sugarbush Project. Organizers say they had valid fire permits and approval from the city of Detroit.</description></item><item><title>‘Extremely disappointed’: New 40-ton arches collapse onto bridge in downtown Hickory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211a15047c8a8529e01adfc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 02:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211a15047c8a8529e01adfc/</guid><description>Neighbors said it sounded like an earthquake when the arches came crashing down overnight. The arches were part of the city’s multimillion-dollar City Walk Project project. They weighed 40-ton and cost $750,
Highlights Arches fell onto the pedestrian walkway and onto Main Avenue Northeast over Highway 127, near downtown Hickory. Neighbors said it sounded like an earthquake when the arches came crashing down. The arches were part of the city’s multimillion-dollar City Walk Project project, whose contract was signed in June 2019.</description></item><item><title>New York City will begin removing homeless people from subways at night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 09:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6210b49559b1433f4dc92816/</guid><description>Mayor says public fear of subways is driving riders from the system and announces more mental health support to homeless
Highlights New York leaders released a plan to strictly enforce rules on the New York City subway as part of an aggressive effort to remove homeless people from the city’s sprawling transit system. The plan comes in light of an uptick in felony assaults in the subway which, while rare, were up 25% in 2021 compared with 2019.</description></item><item><title>Colorado Springs to pay nearly $3 mln to family of Black man shot dead by police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 17:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203f6de20a72684b2fbef37/</guid><description>A Colorado city has agreed to pay $2.9 million to settle a civil rights lawsuit filed by the family of a 19-year-old Black man who was fatally shot in the back by police in 2019, both sides in the litigation said on Tuesday.
Highlights De&amp;rsquo;Von Bailey was shot four times after he bolted from two Colorado Springs policemen who were questioning him about an armed robbery in August 2019. Police said they retrieved a handgun from Bailey after he was shot.</description></item><item><title>Removing trucks could be almost 'impossible,' say heavy towing experts | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201ee35b056c6045f7e942e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 04:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201ee35b056c6045f7e942e/</guid><description>Heavy-duty towing experts say it will be difficult or impossible to remove the hundreds of heavy trucks entrenched in Ottawa&amp;rsquo;s downtown — unless the drivers allow it.
Highlights CBC counted 40 trucks on Kent Street and 109 on Wellington Street Friday, with dozens more on other streets spread around the downtown core. The City of Ottawa has declared a state of emergency amid the protests. Sources say companies contracted by the city are refusing to tow trucks involved with the demonstration.</description></item><item><title>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 07:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea5a1580c2efec7f115832/</guid><description>Michigan judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weeds
Summary Hamtramck judge apologizes for berating elderly cancer patient over weedsHamtramck Judge Alexis Krot has apologized to an elderly cancer patient she berated and threatened with jail time over some unkempt weeds outside his home. &amp;ldquo;I made a mistake,&amp;rdquo; Krot said in a statement shared with the Free Press by the court Thursday. Related: Michigan lawmaker to file complaint against Hamtramck judge who berated elderly manKrot has drawn widespread condemnation and media attention over her comments made during an online court hearing last week that was captured on a Zoom video that circulated on social media.</description></item><item><title>Girl under 10 is youngest person to die of COVID-19 in Houston, city health officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0228a2b91295e680927d7/</guid><description>A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday.
Summary The nations COVID-19 death toll stands at around 800,000 as the anniversary of the U.S. vaccine rollout arrives. (AP Photo/Matt Rourke, File)HOUSTON – A girl under the age of 10 is the city’s youngest confirmed pediatric COVID-19 death, the Houston Health Department announced Wednesday. Privacy laws prevent the health department from providing any other identifiable information.</description></item><item><title>New York will allow non-citizens to vote under controversial law | New York</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbaf648c8788f61dd3f7c3/</guid><description>A watershed moment for the most populous US city as opponents vow to challenge the law
Summary More than 800,000 non-citizens and “Dreamers” could vote in New York City municipal elections as early as next year, after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to become law on Sunday. Opponents have vowed to challenge the law, which the city council approved a month ago. Unless a judge halts its implementation, New York is the first major US city to grant widespread municipal voting rights to non-citizens.</description></item><item><title>Russian Jets Knock Out Water Supply In Syria's Idlib: "Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water..."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d40cacd1f8bf96d85e2579/</guid><description>Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.
Summary Russian warplanes have bombed a pumping station that provides water to rebel-controlled Idlib city in northwestern Syria, potentially depriving hundreds of thousands of people in the overcrowded city of water, according to witnesses and a monitoring group.</description></item><item><title>1 in 50 Manhattan Residents Infected With COVID in the Last Week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 09:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cc23ab8e1203a6f17935ee/</guid><description>The omicron variant outbreak of COVID-19 in New York City is growing so quickly, 2% of all Manhattan residents were infected in just the last week.
Summary As the omicron variant of COVID-19 continues to spread out of control in New York City, transmission rates are soaring, with 2% of all Manhattan residents infected in the last week and nearing that level in the other boroughs. About 2,012 of every 100,000 Manhattan residents tested positive in the last seven days, according to the latest transmission data posted by the city.</description></item></channel></rss>