<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>schools on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/schools/</link><description>Recent content in schools on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 09:10:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/schools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Virginia Governor Youngkin to Lift School Mask Mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 09:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</guid><description>New Virginia governor Glenn Youngkin says he’s against school mask and vaccine mandates, plus will change COVID-19 policies after his 2022 inauguration.
Summary What to Know Virginia&amp;rsquo;s incoming governor, Glenn Youngkin, said he will rescind the statewide K-12 mask mandate. The removal of the school mask mandate may disproportionately affect low-income residents and communities of color, a political science professor said. Glenn Youngkin said after he was sworn in that he signed an executive order lifting the statewide school mask mandate.</description></item><item><title>‘The economy cannot stay open’: Omicron’s effects ricochet across US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e05ab95a38c94edbdeee3f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e05ab95a38c94edbdeee3f/</guid><description>Biden has vowed to keep businesses and schools open but some experts wonder if that’s possible given nature of Covid variant
Summary Joe Biden has vowed to keep businesses and schools open, but some experts wonder if that’s possible given the nature of Omicron and the lack of adequate measures to combat it. “The economy cannot stay open and schools cannot stay open when so many people are getting sick,” said Margaret Thornton, an educational researcher at Princeton School of Public and International Affairs.</description></item></channel></rss>