<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>schools on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/schools/</link><description>Recent content in schools on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 21:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/schools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Massachusetts High School junior prom ends early due to students yelling racial slur while song was playing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62783231117069ae5523752b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 21:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62783231117069ae5523752b/</guid><description>Hamilton-Wenham Regional High School&amp;rsquo;s junior prom ended early on April 28. Students heard yelling the racial slur during a song, school officials said. Police have also been called into the investigation.
Highlights Students heard yelling the N-word at a junior prom. The song was playing at the time of the incident. Police have been called to the school. The incident occurred at a high school in the middle of the night.</description></item><item><title>Pennsylvania high school on lockdown after shooting, district says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c945614e63c644e1d6e44/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 19:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c945614e63c644e1d6e44/</guid><description>A student at Erie High School in Pennsylvania was injured during a shooting Monday morning, and a person of interest fled, according to officials.
Highlights Multiple shots were fired at Erie High School shortly after 9:20 a.m., Erie’s Public Schools said in a statement. One student was injured but stable, the district said in the afternoon. Police are searching for a person of interest who fled the campus. The school will be closed leading up to spring break, which begins next week, according to district.</description></item><item><title>Minneapolis school teachers call a strike; classes canceled</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62287dcd67fc0059580cec29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62287dcd67fc0059580cec29/</guid><description>Minneapolis public school teachers called a strike on Monday, their first for more than 50 years, leading the school district to cancel classes for 30,000 students beginning Tuesday until the work stoppage is resolved.
Highlights Some 4,500 teachers and support staff plan to form picket lines at school buildings on Tuesday morning and hold a rally and march in the afternoon. Teachers are demanding better wages, mental health support and limits on class sizes.</description></item><item><title>The Oconto County Sheriff’s office is investigating allegations that Suring Public Schools officials stripped students down to their underwear while searching for vaping devices.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ab79adceec35b7221dc34/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 20:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ab79adceec35b7221dc34/</guid><description>SURING, Wis. (WLUK) – The Oconto County Sheriff’s office is investigating allegations that Suring Public Schools officials, including at least one administrator, stripped students down to their underwear while searching for vaping devices. Sheriff Todd Skarban tells FOX 11 an investigator has been conducting interviews and gathering information and he expects the findings will be sent to the Oconto County District Attorney on Monday or Tuesday.
Highlights Oconto County Sheriff’s office is investigating allegations that Suring Public Schools officials stripped students down to their underwear while searching for vaping devices.</description></item><item><title>Conservative group trying to ban 16 books from Polk Schools, calling them pornographic</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fef6ec6c15d692ed4120d8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 22:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fef6ec6c15d692ed4120d8/</guid><description>A conservative political group in Florida complained that 16 books in public schools&amp;rsquo; libraries contain pornographic material harmful to children.
Highlights Conservative group trying to ban 16 books from Polk Schools, calling them pornographic. Polk County Public Schools Regional Assistant Superintendent John Hill and several of his colleagues gathered 16 books out of media centers Tuesday morning. County Citizens Defending Freedom, a conservative political group, complained to Superintendent Frederick Heid that the novels, graphic novels, autobiographies, and sex education books contain pornographic material harmful to children.</description></item><item><title>LGBTQ book ban proponent faces felony child molestation charge in Missouri</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcb554924c163f6425c201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 05:11:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcb554924c163f6425c201/</guid><description>The LGBTQ book banning advocate tried to have the award-winning graphic memoir “Fun Home,” removed from school libraries in Kansas City.
Highlights Ryan Utterback, a 29-year-old parent from a suburb of Kansas City, is now facing a felony charge of second-degree child molestation. He also faces a misdemeanor charge of fourth-degree domestic assault and furnishing or attempting to furnish pornographic material to a minor. He spoke at a school board meeting in November to advocate for the removal of books in North Kansas City Schools libraries that depicted sexual acts.</description></item><item><title>Video appears to confirm Lorain school worker forced student to eat from trash</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e9b1498e005d043e1f2786/</guid><description>Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can.
Summary LORAIN, Ohio (WOIO) - Security camera footage appears to confirm a Lorain elementary student’s claims that a school employee made her eat unwanted food after she threw it in a garbage can. “The video is shocking, it’s disheartening, it’s disturbing, and it’s what this child has been saying since the beginning,” said Jared Klebanow, the attorney representing the girl’s family.</description></item><item><title>New Virginia Governor Youngkin to Lift School Mask Mandate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 09:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e5303cb25594c5afcbaf84/</guid><description>New Virginia governor Glenn Youngkin says he’s against school mask and vaccine mandates, plus will change COVID-19 policies after his 2022 inauguration.
Summary What to Know Virginia&amp;rsquo;s incoming governor, Glenn Youngkin, said he will rescind the statewide K-12 mask mandate. The removal of the school mask mandate may disproportionately affect low-income residents and communities of color, a political science professor said. Glenn Youngkin said after he was sworn in that he signed an executive order lifting the statewide school mask mandate.</description></item><item><title>‘The economy cannot stay open’: Omicron’s effects ricochet across US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e05ab95a38c94edbdeee3f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 17:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e05ab95a38c94edbdeee3f/</guid><description>Biden has vowed to keep businesses and schools open but some experts wonder if that’s possible given nature of Covid variant
Summary Joe Biden has vowed to keep businesses and schools open, but some experts wonder if that’s possible given the nature of Omicron and the lack of adequate measures to combat it. “The economy cannot stay open and schools cannot stay open when so many people are getting sick,” said Margaret Thornton, an educational researcher at Princeton School of Public and International Affairs.</description></item></channel></rss>