<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>professional on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/professional/</link><description>Recent content in professional on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/professional/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas woman sought in fatal shooting of professional cyclist, US Marshals say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289fda745038516341b41ad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289fda745038516341b41ad/</guid><description>A manhunt is underway for a Texas woman wanted in connection with the fatal shooting of a professional cyclist.
Highlights Kaitlin Marie Armstrong, 35, is wanted in the killing of 25-year-old Anna Moriah Wilson. Wilson was found bleeding and unconscious with multiple gunshot wounds at a friend&amp;rsquo;s home the night of May 11. Authorities say she was once romantically linked to the suspect&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend. Armstrong&amp;rsquo;s Jeep was captured on surveillance footage from a neighboring residence stopping outside the residence the evening of the shooting, police say.</description></item><item><title>LAUSD lengthens 2022-23 school year to make up for lost instructional time during COVID</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fe6fc1f17cf4e0af9210e/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 14:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fe6fc1f17cf4e0af9210e/</guid><description>The district will add four optional instructional days to give students more time in the classroom in order to make up for the time they lost during the pandemic.
Highlights Los Angeles Unified School District announces it will slightly lengthen the 2022-23 academic year. The district will add four optional instructional days to give students more time in the classroom in order to make up for the time they lost during the pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>