<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>spared on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spared/</link><description>Recent content in spared on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 11:12:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spared/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>No Sri Lankan, rich or poor, spared as economic crisis worsens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252bb8797dda73995d854d5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 11:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6252bb8797dda73995d854d5/</guid><description>Savings evaporate, businesses face closure and the Sri Lankan poor struggle to eat as value of the rupee plummets.
Highlights The value of the Sri Lankan rupee has plummeted by 30 per cent against the U.S. dollar this year, making it the worst-performing currency in the world. Food prices have doubled in less than a year, with onions, dhal and rice costing double what they used to. In middle-class neighbourhoods, owners of cafés, bakeries and salons have had to let go of staff and are facing the prospect of closing shop altogether.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: No Russia regime change plans, says Blinken</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62408debffa723f107fcddc3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 16:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62408debffa723f107fcddc3/</guid><description>The US secretary of state spoke after President Biden said Vladimir Putin should not remain in power.
Highlights Lviv was one of several targets in the west to be struck despite Russia saying it would focus on the east. In Ukraine itself, the western city of Lviv came under heavy rocket fire on Saturday. The western city had been spared the worst of the fighting, but was hit by heavy fire.</description></item></channel></rss>