<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>violation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/violation/</link><description>Recent content in violation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 14:12:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/violation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Missouri ends effort to prosecute journalist who 'viewed source' in a web browser</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623dcdb0bf024e86cc55f24e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 14:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623dcdb0bf024e86cc55f24e/</guid><description>Missouri reporter Josh Renaud faced potential hacking charges for viewing website source code in browser. Renaud found Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Department of Elementary and Secondary Education&amp;rsquo;s website exposed the Social Security details of educators. Cole County Prosecutor Locke Thompson announced no charges would
Highlights Missouri reporter Josh Renaud faced potential hacking charges for viewing website source code in his browser. Renaud found that Missouri&amp;rsquo;s Department of Elementary and Secondary Education&amp;rsquo;s website exposed the Social Security details of educators.</description></item><item><title>South Korea fires multiple missiles in response to North Korea's rocket launch, its military says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c707b01668d1955c642b0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 13:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c707b01668d1955c642b0/</guid><description>The South Korean military said that it was ready and capable of precision strikes against the location where North Korea launched its missile.
Highlights Launch thought to be North Korea&amp;rsquo;s biggest ICBM test ever, militaries in South Korea and Japan say. Launch comes after country had announced moratorium on ICBM testing following two summits between North Korea and US president Donald Trump. Launch is believed to be the first full-capability launch of the nuclear-armed state&amp;rsquo;s largest missiles since 2017.</description></item><item><title>Gov. Newsom signs executive order outlawing price gouging of COVID-19 at-home test kits in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc4a1070867ba32c1e3bbe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc4a1070867ba32c1e3bbe/</guid><description>Gov. Gavin Newsom signed an executive order aimed at preventing price gouging of at-home COVID-19 test kits.
Summary EMBED &amp;gt;More News Videos COVID-19 testing continued at many Los Angeles Unified School District campuses on Sunday, Jan. 9, 2022, as students, teachers and staff prepared to return from winter break. SACRAMENTO, Calif. (KABC) &amp;ndash; Gov. Gavin Newsom has signed an executive order aimed at preventing price gouging of at-home COVID-19 test kits.</description></item></channel></rss>