<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>graduate on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/graduate/</link><description>Recent content in graduate on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 19:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/graduate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4 Air Force cadets may not graduate due to vaccine refusal</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ffef2302eef9713711edf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 19:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627ffef2302eef9713711edf/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Four cadets at the Air Force Academy may not graduate or be commissioned as military officers this month because they have refused the COVID-19 vaccine, and they may be required to pay back thousands of dollars in tuition costs, according to Air Force officials.
Highlights Four cadets at the Air Force Academy may not graduate or be commissioned as military officers in May 2022. They may be required to pay back thousands of dollars in tuition costs.</description></item><item><title>19-year-old could become the youngest African American law school graduate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62760ed4074b07ecd97af0ad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 06:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62760ed4074b07ecd97af0ad/</guid><description>Haley Taylor Schlitz was accepted to nine different law schools when she was only 16.
Highlights Haley Taylor Schlitz is set to graduate May 13 at Southern Methodist University&amp;rsquo;s Dedman School of Law. At 19 years old, she is the youngest African American to graduate law school. Her path to law school wasn&amp;rsquo;t conventional when she was just 13 years old. She hopes to work on education policy issues for an elected official or nonprofit organization.</description></item></channel></rss>