<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>using on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/using/</link><description>Recent content in using on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/using/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New York Supreme Court ruling reinstates law banning police officers from using chokeholds during arrests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628786636aa1ae9d6d363aba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 12:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628786636aa1ae9d6d363aba/</guid><description>A law banning New York law enforcement from using either a chokehold or a move that compresses someone&amp;rsquo;s diaphragm during an arrest has been reinstated after a state Supreme Court appeals court ruling on Thursday.
Highlights The law bans police from using a move that compresses someone&amp;rsquo;s diaphragm during an arrest. The law was passed by the city council in the aftermath of the death of Eric Garner. A state Supreme Court ruling reversed a June 2021 decision by the court that deemed the law &amp;ldquo;unnecessarily vague&amp;rdquo; and the ban in its entirety.</description></item><item><title>US Army using lessons from Ukraine war to aid own training</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b66326cba3c1fc94668b3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b66326cba3c1fc94668b3/</guid><description>FORT IRWIN, Calif. (AP) — In the dusty California desert, U.S. Army trainers are already using lessons learned from Russia&amp;rsquo;s war against Ukraine as they prepare soldiers for future fights against a major adversary such as Russia or China.
Highlights U.S. Army trainers are already using lessons learned from Russia’s war against Ukraine as they prepare soldiers for future fights against a major adversary such as Russia or China. The lessons, she said, range from equipment and logistics troubles to communications and use of the internet.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after colleague in bulldozer accidentally runs over port-a-potty he was using, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 05:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6228374b2eb47a65a5793737/</guid><description>A Florida landfill worker died Friday after a colleague in a bulldozer accidentally ran over the port-a-potty he was using, authorities said.
Highlights Aaron Henderson, 40, worked for CertiTemp, a company contracted by Polk County, Florida. He was pronounced dead on the scene. Investigators determined that a fellow bulldozer employee was putting the bulldozer away for the day when he drove up an embankment, with the front blade of his bulldozer “elevated 3-4 feet off the ground,” according to the sheriff’s office.</description></item><item><title>Swiss army bans WhatsApp, Telegram and Signal due to privacy concerns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db22c6d3ae192757fa6692/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61db22c6d3ae192757fa6692/</guid><description>Switzerland&amp;rsquo;s army has banned the use of WhatsApp whilst on duty, a spokesman confirmed Thursday, in favour of a Swiss messaging service deemed more secure in terms of data protection.
Summary The ban also applies to using other messaging apps like Signal and Telegram on soldiers’ private phones during service operations. READ MORE: Swiss army launches fitness app for future recruitsThe recommendation applies “to everyone”, including conscripts doing their military service and those returning for refresher courses, army spokesman Daniel Reist told AFP.</description></item><item><title>Teen honored after using his Make-A-Wish to feed homeless in Jackson</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da33b687ed3f55535f8f10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 01:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da33b687ed3f55535f8f10/</guid><description>A Jackson teen is being honored for giving back to his community and helping the homeless.
Summary Teen honored after using his Make-A-Wish to feed homeless in JacksonTeen honored after using his Make-A-Wish to feed homeless in JacksonPEARL, Miss. (WLBT) - A Jackson teen is being honored for giving back to his community and helping the homeless. We introduced you to 13-year-old Abraham last year after he used his Make-A-Wish to feed the homeless in Jackson.</description></item></channel></rss>