<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>searched on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/searched/</link><description>Recent content in searched on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 18:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/searched/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FBI: Gubernatorial candidate Ryan Kelley arrested, home searched</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a237981b0a2cc2be3c0654/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 18:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a237981b0a2cc2be3c0654/</guid><description>The FBI said that Kelley was arrested on charges relating to the Jan. 6 riot.
Highlights Ryan Kelley was arrested and a search was executed at his home Thursday morning. Kelley, 40, was among the Republican candidates looking to run in the 2022 August gubernatorial primary. He was seen at the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol, though he has said he didn&amp;rsquo;t go inside the building. An anonymous tipster pointed them toward pictures of Kelley in the crowd.</description></item><item><title>Teenage girl traumatised after police strip-search, says mum</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c849dc18a28627fe2e717/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 07:09:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c849dc18a28627fe2e717/</guid><description>A 14-year-old girl who was strip-searched by police was traumatised by the incident, her mum says.
Highlights Olivia was strip-searched by police after an argument with two boys. She was searched by police at the scene and nothing was discovered. The 14-year-old was traumatised by the incident, her mother said. She said Olivia had been out with friends when they had an argument. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>