<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>death on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/death/</link><description>Recent content in death on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:10:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/death/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tony Timpa Case: Supreme Court says wrongful death lawsuit against Dallas officers can go forward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6297e3abe3868d5995ba6f93/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6297e3abe3868d5995ba6f93/</guid><description>The Supreme Court upheld a federal appeals court&amp;rsquo;s ruling that will allow Tony Timpa&amp;rsquo;s wrongful death lawsuit to proceed against the city of Dallas and four police officers.
Highlights Tony Timpa called police for help as he had a drug and mental health crisis. The city of Dallas argued the officers are legally protected from lawsuits. The Supreme Court upheld a federal appeals court’s ruling that will allow the case to proceed.</description></item><item><title>9-Year-Old Girl Found Dead in NYC Home After Restaurant Below Calls Cops About Odor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283305f578af1aa023b4f5b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 05:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283305f578af1aa023b4f5b/</guid><description>Shalom Guifarro was found dead with body trauma off Lincoln Place.
Highlights Shalom Guifarro, 9, was found dead in her home in Crown Heights, Brooklyn. The medical examiner ruled the death a homicide. Police have not announced any arrests. The Administration for Children&amp;rsquo;s Protective Services says it is investigating. The girl was found unresponsive and had &amp;ldquo;trauma to her body,&amp;rdquo; a preliminary report from police said. Neighbors said they smelled a foul odor from the home before police arrived Sunday afternoon, and police questioned the girl&amp;rsquo;s mother, who was taken to the precinct for questioning after officers visited the home Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>Church linked to San Jose kidnapping also tied to apparent exorcism death of 3-year-old girl</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2fc63cee467d12289735/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 10:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e2fc63cee467d12289735/</guid><description>Disturbing details have come to light regarding a San Jose church where an alleged exorcism claimed the life of a 3-year-old girl.
Highlights Police were called to the South Bay church in September for a separate incident that involved the death of a 3-year-old girl. The death occurred at the Iglesia Evangelicas Apostoles y Profetas as family members were trying to rid the girl of an evil spirit. The medical examiner said ultimately the child died of asphyxia due to suffocation.</description></item><item><title>FDA chief explains why misinformation is leading cause of death in US</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62776d95b35e022b05e65963/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 07:13:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62776d95b35e022b05e65963/</guid><description>In an exclusive interview with CNN&amp;rsquo;s Pamela Brown, FDA chief Dr. Robert Califf explains why he says the leading cause of death in the US is misinformation.
Highlights FDA chief Dr. Robert Califf says the leading cause of death in the US is misinformation. Califf tells CNN&amp;rsquo;s Pamela Brown why he says the top cause of US death is death. The FDA chief says misinformation is leading to the death toll in the U.</description></item><item><title>World true pandemic death toll nearly 15 million, says WHO</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62745a696a0bf7f0b74bf6e2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62745a696a0bf7f0b74bf6e2/</guid><description>These include deaths from Covid and from the indirect effects of the pandemic over two years worldwide.
Highlights These calculations also take into account deaths which were not directly because of Covid but instead caused by its knock-on effects. It also accounts for poor record-keeping in some regions, and sparse testing at the start of the crisis. These include deaths from Covid and from the indirect effects of the pandemic over two years worldwide.</description></item><item><title>45-year-old Yan Zhiwen shot to death delivering food on scooter in Forest Hills, Queens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fde149f30552eec529f34/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 13:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fde149f30552eec529f34/</guid><description>It happened hours after Mayor Adams met with NYPD officials to address surging crime.
Highlights Yan Zhiwen, a food delivery worker, was shot and killed while on his scooter Saturday night in Queens. It happened near 108th Street and 67th Drive in Forest Hills at around 9:30 p.m. His final moments were captured on video before he was gunned down point blank in the middle of a residential street. Police are asking for help finding the shooter, who they say drove off in a light gray or tan Lexus.</description></item><item><title>3 California police officers who restrained a man who died in their custody will not face criminal charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254b63c139fa4c840d39694/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 23:14:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6254b63c139fa4c840d39694/</guid><description>The Alameda County district attorney will not file criminal charges against three police officers who restrained a Northern California man who died in their custody last year.
Highlights Mario Gonzalez Arenales, 26, died on April 19, 2021, following an encounter with three Alameda police officers. The county coroner&amp;rsquo;s office had classified the death as a homicide and pointed to the toxic effects of methamphetamine as the leading cause. Two wrongful death suits have been filed against the City of Alameda alleging the officers detained Gonzalez without reasonable suspicion and caused him to die of asphyxia.</description></item><item><title>Firing-squad executions get the greenlight in South Carolina</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62356611622f555e6036ad94/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 05:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62356611622f555e6036ad94/</guid><description>South Carolina has given the greenlight to firing-squad executions
Highlights South Carolina has given the greenlight to firing-squad executions, a method codified into state law last year. The state Corrections Department said Friday that renovations have been completed on the death chamber in Columbia. The three shooters, all volunteers, will have rifles loaded with live ammunition, with their weapons trained on the inmate&amp;rsquo;s heart. South Carolina is one of eight states to still use the electric chair and one of four to allow a firing squad.</description></item><item><title>Black man's death in Indiana ruled a lynching nearly 100 years later</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ff695d86a10484277cc20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 02:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ff695d86a10484277cc20/</guid><description>The death of a young Black man who was found hanging from a tree in Indiana nearly 100 years ago has finally been ruled a lynching, officials said.
Highlights George Tompkins&amp;rsquo; hands had been bound behind his back, but his death was ruled a suicide in 1922. Marion County Deputy Chief Coroner Alfie McGinty: &amp;ldquo;We will bring justice to something that was unconscionable to me&amp;rdquo; The U.S. Senate only last week gave final passage to a bill to make lynching a federal crime.</description></item><item><title>AP News: High court reimposes Boston Marathon bomber's death sentence</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622264466f6d31bf66694658/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 19:11:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622264466f6d31bf66694658/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court has reinstated the death sentence for Boston Marathon bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev. The justices, by a 6-3 vote Friday, agreed with the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s arguments that a federal appeals court was wrong to throw out the sentence of death a jury imposed on Tsarnaev for his role in the bombing that killed three people near the finish line of the marathon in 2013.
Highlights The Supreme Court reinstated the death sentence for Boston Marathon bomber Dzhokhar Tsarnaev.</description></item><item><title>Top Russian general killed in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221846ff9366cd0c39fb82d/</guid><description>Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky, the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division, was killed in fighting in Ukraine earlier this week.
Highlights Maj. Gen. Andrei Sukhovetsky was the commanding general of the Russian 7th Airborne Division. His death was confirmed by a local officers’ organization in the Krasnodar region in southern Russia. The circumstances of his death were not immediately clear. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Sinead O'Connor hospitalized, days after teenage son's death</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2a973fa37b5ca858db927/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 11:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e2a973fa37b5ca858db927/</guid><description>Sinéad O&amp;rsquo;Connor has been admitted to the hospital, one week after her 17-year-old son was found dead.
Summary (CNN) Sinéad O&amp;rsquo;Connor has been admitted to the hospital, one week after her 17-year-old son was found dead. The &amp;ldquo;Nothing Compares 2 U&amp;rdquo; singer told fans on Thursday night that she was heading to hospital to receive help after sharing in a series of disturbing Twitter posts that she planned to take her own life.</description></item><item><title>Betty White died of a stroke she suffered six days earlier</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd39455dd6101e65a7614e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 08:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dd39455dd6101e65a7614e/</guid><description>The beloved actor died on December 31.
Summary Betty White died from a stroke she had six days before her December 31 death at age 99, according to her death certificate. She was cremated and her remains were given Friday to Glenn Kaplan, the man in charge of White&amp;rsquo;s advanced health care directive. She took the last name of her husband Allen Ludden, to whom she was married from 1963 until his death in 1981.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan completely abolishes death penalty</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cccc6a55ef7819f582dcdf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 21:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cccc6a55ef7819f582dcdf/</guid><description>Kazakh President Kassym-Jomart Tokayev has signed amendments on the abolition of the death penalty in the country, the presidents press service said on Wednesday
Summary Kazakhstan ratified the protocol with one provision - the right to exercise the death penalty at a time of war for serious military crimes. The law amends the criminal, criminal procedural and penal codes, in addition to other laws. The article concerning the death penalty as an exceptional measure of punishment is completely excluded from the criminal code.</description></item><item><title>Autopsy: Death of Black Kansas teen in custody was homicide</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb42b96bd7dae261c96a96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 17:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb42b96bd7dae261c96a96/</guid><description>An autopsy report says that a Black youth’s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicide
Summary An autopsy report says that a Black youth’s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicideTOPEKA, Kan. &amp;ndash; A Black youth&amp;rsquo;s death following a physical struggle with staff at a Kansas juvenile center was a homicide, according to an autopsy report released Monday that contradicts an earlier, preliminary finding that the teenager hadn&amp;rsquo;t suffered life-threatening injuries.</description></item><item><title>Kim Potter, ex-Minnesota officer, found guilty of manslaughter in death of Daunte Wright</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c4ff89b7464a3fe2b86751/</guid><description>A Minneapolis jury reached an &amp;quot;outcome&amp;quot; in the trial of Kim Potter, a former police officer charged with fatally shooting Daunte Wright, a Black motorist.
Summary A Minneapolis jury on Thursday convicted former police officer Kim Potter on all charges she faced for fatally shooting Black motorist Daunte Wright — with a gun and not her Taser — earlier this year. Potter, 49, faces a maximum of 15 years in prison and is set to be sentenced Feb.</description></item></channel></rss>