<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deputy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deputy/</link><description>Recent content in deputy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 06:16:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deputy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deputy Sergeant dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 06:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</guid><description>A deputy sergeant has reportedly died as she worked to help those in the Eastland community evacuate the recent catastrophic wildfires happening in West Texas.
Highlights Deputy Sergeant Barbara Fenley dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents. Fenley was last heard from as she was headed to check on an elderly individual while massive flames continued to move across the area. She leaves behind her husband and three children.</description></item><item><title>Deputy U.N. chief left near tears by rape accounts in Ethiopia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</guid><description>Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed said on Friday she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women, which she described as &amp;quot;your worst nightmare.”
Highlights Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed says she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women. Mohammed spoke to reporters in New York a day after returning from Ethiopia. She called for accountability for atrocities committed against women and recounted sights of famine in the crisis-torn country.</description></item></channel></rss>