<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>deputy on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deputy/</link><description>Recent content in deputy on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/deputy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ex-deputy gets 18 years after detainees drown in locked van</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287bde024ee89e50b7aecc7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6287bde024ee89e50b7aecc7/</guid><description>A deputy in South Carolina whose police van was swept away by floodwaters in the aftermath of Hurricane Florence, drowning two women seeking mental health treatment trapped in a cage in the back has been sentenced to 18 years in prison
Highlights Former Horry County deputy Stephen Flood was found guilty of involuntary manslaughter and reckless homicide. Wendy Newton, 45, and Nicolette Green, 43, drowned in a police van after Hurricane Florence.</description></item><item><title>LA jail guards routinely punch incarcerated people in the head, monitors find | Los Angeles sheriff’s department accused of hours-long group strip-search as court report adds to string of scandals</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251249317adc028ae6f48a6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 06:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6251249317adc028ae6f48a6/</guid><description>Los Angeles sheriff’s department accused of hours-long group strip-search as court report adds to string of scandals
Highlights Los Angeles sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department appears to be routinely violating use-of-force policies, court-appointed monitors say. Guards have punched incarcerated people in the head and subjected them to a “humiliating” group strip-search where they were forced to wait undressed for hours. Guards who used force in violation of policy were at times sent to “remedial training” but that “actual discipline is seldom imposed” The report raises further concerns about the department’s use of the “Wrap” device, which functions like a full-body restraining jacket and is used to ‘immobilize’ people.</description></item><item><title>Deputy Sergeant dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 06:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6236c68e8c8951ed0e3e748d/</guid><description>A deputy sergeant has reportedly died as she worked to help those in the Eastland community evacuate the recent catastrophic wildfires happening in West Texas.
Highlights Deputy Sergeant Barbara Fenley dies in Eastland wildfires after trying to evacuate residents. Fenley was last heard from as she was headed to check on an elderly individual while massive flames continued to move across the area. She leaves behind her husband and three children.</description></item><item><title>Deputy U.N. chief left near tears by rape accounts in Ethiopia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 12:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208f69d684022b8210447a9/</guid><description>Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed said on Friday she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women, which she described as &amp;quot;your worst nightmare.”
Highlights Deputy U.N. Secretary-General Amina Mohammed says she was deeply shaken by accounts of rape from Ethiopian women. Mohammed spoke to reporters in New York a day after returning from Ethiopia. She called for accountability for atrocities committed against women and recounted sights of famine in the crisis-torn country.</description></item></channel></rss>