<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>won on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/won/</link><description>Recent content in won on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 05:14:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/won/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Smith, Chris Rock confrontation shocks Oscar audience</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62414400daa329aafadad8fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 05:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62414400daa329aafadad8fc/</guid><description>It was a big night for “CODA” at the 94th Academy Awards, which picked up three major wins at Sunday&amp;rsquo;s show. But most were talking about another Oscars moment. Here&amp;rsquo;s a rundown of what happened at Sunday&amp;rsquo;s show.
Highlights Will Smith slapped presenter Chris Rock on stage after he joked about a sequel to &amp;ldquo;G.I. Jane&amp;rdquo; Smith later apologized to the academy and his fellow nominees. Apple TV+ scored its first best picture Academy Award on Sunday, less than three years after launching the service.</description></item><item><title>Transgender swimmer Lia Thomas finishes 5th in NCAA women's 200-yard freestyle final</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62359e798e5a96ebf19631cb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62359e798e5a96ebf19631cb/</guid><description>University of Pennsylvania swimmer Lia Thomas finished tied for fifth Friday in the women&amp;rsquo;s 200-yard freestyle final at the NCAA swimming and diving championships at Atlanta.
Highlights Taylor Ruck of Stanford won the race in 1:41.12. Thomas touched the wall in 1.43.40, as did Riley Gaines of Florida. Thomas became the first transgender athlete to win an NCAA Division I title on Thursday. One person yelled &amp;ldquo;cheater&amp;rdquo; as Thomas gave her interview after the 500-yard freestyle race.</description></item><item><title>Jackson 1st Black woman to win speedskating</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209bcfe4bb564a9a11d3c19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 02:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209bcfe4bb564a9a11d3c19/</guid><description>BEIJING (AP) — The Latest on the Beijing Winter Olympics : ___ The United States has clinched the top seed in the Olympic men’s hockey tournament.
Highlights The U.S. has clinched the top seed in the Olympic men’s hockey tournament. The U.S. is the only team to win all three of its group stage games in regulation. The United States is the youngest team in the tournament with an average age of 25 and eight players under 21.</description></item></channel></rss>