<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>man on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/man/</link><description>Recent content in man on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:45:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/man/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hong Kong police make multiple arrests as Tiananmen gatherings banned</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bfc71ebc360e81f004434/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:45:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bfc71ebc360e81f004434/</guid><description>Hong Kong authorities on Saturday detained multiple people as they pounced on any attempt at public commemoration of the 33rd anniversary of the Tiananmen crackdown, as China vies to remove all reminders…
Highlights Hong Kong authorities pounced on any attempt at public commemoration of the 33rd anniversary of the Tiananmen crackdown. Discussion of June 4, 1989, when China set troops and tanks on peaceful protestors, is all but forbidden on the mainland.</description></item><item><title>Police: Man in Texas smashes ancient museum artifacts worth millions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299a62a58af4cc2164fc159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299a62a58af4cc2164fc159/</guid><description>According to police, the man used a metal chair to break into the museum.
Highlights Brian Hernandez, 21, is charged with criminal mischief of more than or equal to $300,000. He was booked Thursday into the Dallas County jail with bond set at $100,000. Jail records list no attorney for Hernandez. Police say he used a metal chair to break into the museum, smashed three ancient Greek artifacts before he was arrested.</description></item><item><title>Mona Lisa attacked with cake by man 'dressed as old lady in wheelchair'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294d093838e0dd5ce9877d1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 14:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6294d093838e0dd5ce9877d1/</guid><description>Footage captured at the Louvre in Paris shows a person apparently wearing lipstick and a wig asking people to &amp;quot;think of the planet&amp;quot; after attacking the world&amp;rsquo;s most famous portrait.
Highlights A person dressed as an old woman in a wheelchair staged an attack on the Mona Lisa in Paris. Footage shows the person apparently wearing lipstick and a wig asking people to &amp;ldquo;think of the planet&amp;rdquo; The painting, considered an archetypal masterpiece of the Italian Renaissance, was not damaged.</description></item><item><title>DC Man Pleads Guilty to Assaulting Asian Family</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930e7dbc13a9e8c2ef267d/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 06:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62930e7dbc13a9e8c2ef267d/</guid><description>A D.C. man pleaded guilty Thursday to assaulting three adults of Chinese descent who were walking down a street in the Glover Park area of Washington, D.C., the&amp;hellip;
Highlights Patrick Trebat, 39, pleaded guilty to three counts of simple assault, including one with a hate-bias enhancement. Trebat attacked a man, a woman and their adult son because they appeared to be from another country and spoke a language Trebat didn&amp;rsquo;t understand.</description></item><item><title>Illinois man convicted of giving son rifle he used to kill 4</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286c009e3eab34dff2e5e63/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 22:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286c009e3eab34dff2e5e63/</guid><description>An Illinois man faces up to three years in prison after being convicted of illegally giving his son an assault-style rifle he later used to shoot and kill four people in 2018 at a Waffle House in Tennessee
Highlights Jeffrey Reinking convicted of illegal delivery of a firearm to a person who had been treated for mental illness within the past five years. Prosecutors said Reinking knew his son, Travis Reinking, had undergone mental health treatment in 2016.</description></item><item><title>Russian soldier pleads guilty at Ukraine war crimes trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62860965105208870f83676f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 09:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62860965105208870f83676f/</guid><description>A 21-year-old Russian soldier facing the first war crimes trial since Moscow invaded Ukraine has pleaded guilty to killing an unarmed civilian
Highlights Sgt. Vadim Shishimarin could get life in prison for allegedly shooting a 62-year-old Ukrainian man in the head. Shishhimarin was a captured member of a Russian tank unit. He was prosecuted under a section of the Ukrainian criminal code that addresses the laws and customs of war. Investigators are investigating allegations that Russian troops violated Ukrainian and international law by killing, torturing and abusing possibly thousands of Ukrainian civilians.</description></item><item><title>Calling a man bald counts as sexual harassment, UK judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f3cf888623cdc9d5ea1d5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 05:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f3cf888623cdc9d5ea1d5/</guid><description>Calling a man &amp;quot;bald&amp;quot; is now classed as sexual harassment, a judge in a U.K. employment tribunal has ruled.
Highlights U.K. employment tribunal ruled that the use of the word &amp;ldquo;bald&amp;rdquo; as an insult related to a &amp;ldquo;protected characteristic of sex&amp;rdquo; The tribunal compared calling a man bald to commenting on the size of woman&amp;rsquo;s breasts. The ruling was made on a case where the insult was alleged to have been used against Tony Finn, an electrician for the British Bung Manufacturing Company.</description></item><item><title>Arrest Made in Balloon Littering Investigation at Coconut Grove Marina</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d9501153c50bbffbde2a5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 23:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627d9501153c50bbffbde2a5/</guid><description>Several boaters were caught on camera popping balloons and letting the trash fall into the water near a Coconut Grove marina in Miami-Dade County.
Highlights Cellphone video shows boaters popping balloons and letting the trash fall into the water near a Coconut Grove marina in Miami-Dade County. The man was identified as 29-year-old David Torres-Bocanegra. Balloon releases have been illegal in Florida since 1989. Balloons can be mistaken for food by sea turtles and other marine animals, and if eaten, can lead to internal injury, starvation, and death.</description></item><item><title>Man with cane shot, killed after being harassed by group of teens in north Houston: HPD</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b2b1cc7c9cda9ebc0b466/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 03:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b2b1cc7c9cda9ebc0b466/</guid><description>A man is dead after police said he was shot following harassment from teens in north Houston Monday.
Highlights A 49-year-old man was shot in the chest in north Houston Monday night. Police say he was approached and harassed by a group of teenagers. Four teenage girls ages 14-16 and two teenage boys that are believed to be 16-18 years old. Police said they aren’t sure if the teens got away on foot or in a vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky man, 22, shoots mom after dispute over Xbox controller on Mother’s Day, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a9fe136294392194c0e03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 17:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a9fe136294392194c0e03/</guid><description>A Kentucky man has been arrested after shooting his mother on Mother’s Day following a dispute over an Xbox controller he gave her as a gift, officials say.
Highlights Jacob R. Small, of Monticello, Kentucky, was charged with attempted murder, first-degree assault and second-degree criminal mischief. Small told authorities he got into a verbal dispute with his mother over an Xbox controller he gave her as a Mother’s Day gift. The mother was treated at the Wayne County Hospital and transferred to the University of Kentucky Hospital for further treatment.</description></item><item><title>Man who received landmark pig heart transplant died of pig virus, surgeon says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275ffbf4227b5eef2a839fe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 05:13:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275ffbf4227b5eef2a839fe/</guid><description>David Bennett died two months after groundbreaking surgery in which a genetically modified pig’s heart was transplanted into him
Highlights David Bennett, 57, died in March after undergoing a pig heart transplant. Surgeon says the pig&amp;rsquo;s heart was infected with porcine cytomegalovirus, which may have contributed to Bennett’s death. Experts believe that the experiment may have been derailed as a result of an ‘unforced error’ Experts say the specific type of virus in the donor heart is not capable of infecting human cells.</description></item><item><title>One of Ahmaud Arbery's killers had 16 phone calls with DA before arrest, court filings say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275da44488a5a806f788401/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:33:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6275da44488a5a806f788401/</guid><description>In the weeks following the fatal shooting of Ahmaud Arbery, Greg McMichael, one of the men later convicted in Arbery&amp;rsquo;s death, participated in 16 phone calls with the former Brunswick Judicial Circuit District Attorney Jackie Johnson, according to court documents filed in the Superior Court of Glynn County on Wednesday.
Highlights The three men were found guilty in February of trying to run away from each other. The three were sentenced to life in prison.</description></item><item><title>Man arrested for allegedly threatening Merriam-Webster over definition of female</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62648816f9039dbaefa37d3a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 23:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62648816f9039dbaefa37d3a/</guid><description>A California man was arrested after making online threats against the dictionary publisher over their entries that defined women, investigators said.
Highlights Jeremy David Hanson, 34, of Rossmoor, California, was charged on April 20 with one count of interstate communication of threats to commit violence. He allegedly sent the company several threatening messages through its &amp;ldquo;Contact us&amp;rdquo; section on its website and in the comments section. The threats were serious enough to force Merriam-Webster to close its Springfield and New York offices out of an abundance of caution.</description></item><item><title>Sarasota man pleads guilty to threatening to kill U.S. Rep. Ilhan Omar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262e43c40378adcdd7c2f34/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 17:22:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6262e43c40378adcdd7c2f34/</guid><description>The email, in part, asked Omar if she was prepared “to die for Islam.”
Highlights David Hannon, 67, of Sarasota, entered the plea Tuesday to a charge of threatening a federal official. Hannon sent an email to Omar on July 16, 2019, after a televised news conference held by Omar and three other members of Congress. The email, in part, asked Omar if she was prepared “to die for Islam” and said Hannon was going to shoot her in the head, Justice Department says.</description></item><item><title>Hate crimes in New York City are up 76% this year compared to the same period in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c06160027fdf4c7e549d9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 12:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c06160027fdf4c7e549d9/</guid><description>Hate crimes in New York City have increased 76% so far this year compared to the same period last year, according to data from the New York Police Department Hate Crimes Task Force (HCTF) released this week.
Highlights New York City has seen a rise in hate crimes compared to last year. Hate crimes have increased 76% since January 1 to April 10, data shows. The data was released as part of the New York Police Department&amp;rsquo;s plan to combat hate crimes.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pepper-Sprayed Man Taking Photos of His Own Children in Arlington: Police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625acec4c676a0d4b268a865/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 14:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625acec4c676a0d4b268a865/</guid><description>Police are looking for a woman who pepper-sprayed a man who was taking photos of his own children in Arlington, Virginia, police said.
Highlights Police are looking for a woman who pepper-sprayed a man who was taking photos of his own children in Arlington, Virginia. The woman reported the man to a security officer Tuesday afternoon in the 1100 block of S. Hayes Street, which is the block where Pentagon City Mall is located.</description></item><item><title>SoCal man says car computer on his new Tesla froze, causing vehicle to be stuck at 83 mph on freeway</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625872214d15145552062de9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 19:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625872214d15145552062de9/</guid><description>The owner of a new Tesla Model 3 was left in shock after the car&amp;rsquo;s main features allegedly froze while he was driving on the freeway.
Highlights Javier Rodriguez of Irvine said it happened last Thursday while he was driving on the 10 Freeway through Cabazon. He said the car was stuck going 83 mph and the main screen was frozen. All of the buttons and switches - including turn signals and hazard lights - were not working.</description></item><item><title>Former Picayune police officer receives maximum sentence for child porn charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62514e0dbffd455e23bb3dc8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62514e0dbffd455e23bb3dc8/</guid><description>A Picayune man will spend the next 30 years in prison after pleading guilty to producing a video of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct.
Highlights Joshua Christopher Stockstill enticed a child to engage in sexually explicit conduct so he could capture it on his cellphone camera. The video circulated for nearly two years before the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children became aware of it in July 2021.</description></item><item><title>Police corner black man, twice, for 'wearing a coat'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62449e66fc5d72893b232ea5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 18:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62449e66fc5d72893b232ea5/</guid><description>Eric Taylor, 20, has video evidence showing him being ‘cornered’ by three law enforcement vehicles on Monday, March 28th, at 10:15pm when he was travelling to work from a restaurant. He was
Highlights Eric Taylor, 20, was recently stopped and searched by police officers for being &amp;rsquo;not dressed for the climate&amp;rsquo; He has video evidence showing him being ‘cornered’ by three law enforcement vehicles on Monday, March 28th, at 10:15pm when he was travelling to work from a restaurant.</description></item><item><title>Police seize over 60 guns linked to man accused of making untraceable firearms in Salem</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235f2fe435ad0ddd64485d2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 15:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235f2fe435ad0ddd64485d2/</guid><description>SALEM, Ore. — A Salem man was indicted for distributing counterfeit prescription pills containing fentanyl and running the state’s largest homemade firearm or &amp;quot;ghost gun&amp;quot; workshop out of his basement. Tyler Ray Harnden, 29, was indicted on multiple felony charges, including drug possession and illegally possessing a gun as a convicted felon. Investigators served a search warrant at Harnden’s south Salem home on February 16 and found a large firearm manufacturing operation.</description></item><item><title>Man used COVID loan to buy Pokémon card, sentenced to prison.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622739c4be3299fe68de2766/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 11:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622739c4be3299fe68de2766/</guid><description>A Georgia man has been sentenced to three years in prison after he used a COVID-19 relief loan to buy a rare Pokémon card, according to the Department of Justice.
Highlights Vinath Oudomsine, 31, was awarded an Economic Injury Disaster Loan (EIDL) for $85,000 after claiming to own a small business that supported 10 employees. He used $57,789 of the loan to buy a first-edition, shadowless and holographic Charizard card with a 9.</description></item><item><title>Ahmaud Arbery: White trio guilty of hate crimes in killing of black man while he was out running</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215848c68b57b186495b716/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215848c68b57b186495b716/</guid><description>Greg and Travis McMichael, and their neighbour William &amp;quot;Roddie&amp;quot; Bryan have already been convicted of the murder of Mr Arbery and sentenced to life in prison.
Highlights Ahmaud Arbery, 25, was chased and shot by Travis McMichael, 35; his father and former police officer Greg, 66, and their neighbour William &amp;ldquo;Roddie&amp;rdquo; Bryan, 52, on 23 February 2020 in Satilla Shores just outside the city of Brunswick, Georgia. The trio had denied federal hate crime charges but were convicted of violating Mr Arbery&amp;rsquo;s civil rights and targeting him because he was black.</description></item><item><title>Pennsylvania man charged in killing of Uber driver who begged for her life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211c076d3569ae4f6d0f37e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:16:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211c076d3569ae4f6d0f37e/</guid><description>A Pennsylvania man is accused of killing an Uber driver who vanished last week in what authorities described Friday as a fatal robbery.
Highlights Christina Spicuzza, 38, disappeared Feb. 10 after driving for Uber in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. She was found dead from a single gunshot wound, police say. A dash cam inside her car captured Crew allegedly pointing a gun at her neck as she drove. Crew allegedly tried to transfer money to his girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s phone, a criminal complaint says.</description></item><item><title>Man accused of blasphemy stoned to death by mob in Pakistan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209c889b0c489fcc9d6551d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209c889b0c489fcc9d6551d/</guid><description>Police say an enraged mob has stoned to death a middle-aged man for allegedly desecrating the Quran in a remote village in eastern Pakistan
Highlights Police say mob stoned to death a middle-aged man for allegedly desecrating the Quran. Mosque custodian said he saw the man burning the Muslim holy book inside the mosque. Violence took place in a village in the district of Khanewal in Punjab province. Police say the victim was identified as Mushtaq Ahmed, 41, of a nearby village.</description></item><item><title>DA clears deputy who shot and killed homeless Black man in San Clemente</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209576aad8df3fdf4c17013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 19:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209576aad8df3fdf4c17013/</guid><description>DA says Deputy Eduardo Duran was justified in shooting and killing Kurt Andreas Reinhold. Reinhold, 42, was shot and killed in San Clemente, Orange County, in September 2020. DA: Deputies had no reason to
Highlights DA’s Office says Deputy Eduardo Duran was justified in shooting and killing Kurt Andreas Reinhold. Reinhold, 42, was stopped by deputies on suspicion of jaywalking in San Clemente, Orange County. He was struck twice in his upper torso in the Sept.</description></item><item><title>Protesters for Amir Locke, a Black man killed by Minneapolis police, demand police chief's resignation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 07:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620217ba65b08321cbb78a05/</guid><description>A caravan of vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke, the 22-year old Black man who was fatally shot by Minneapolis police as officers served a no-knock search warrant.
Highlights A caravan of about 50 vehicles drove through Minneapolis demanding justice in the death of Amir Locke. The caravan was organized by the Racial Justice Network and other police accountability groups. Some in the caravan then gathered in a neighborhood outside what’s believed to be the home of interim Police Chief Amelia Huffman.</description></item><item><title>Amir Locke shooting: hundreds protest in Minneapolis after police killing of Black man</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200399b222e57fce50c1459/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 21:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200399b222e57fce50c1459/</guid><description>Demonstrators demand unconditional ban on ‘no-knock’ warrants after Locke, 22, was killed during a raid on an apartment this week
Highlights Police killed Amir Locke, 22, during &amp;rsquo;no-knock&amp;rsquo; raid on apartment earlier this week. Video showed Locke holding a gun as he twisted beneath blanket on sofa moments before he was shot. Police have said the officers were exercising a ‘no’knock” search warrant, which authorizes police to enter private property without first alerting occupants or announcing their presence.</description></item><item><title>Body camera video shows Minneapolis officers shooting Black man during no-knock warrant. Attorneys say he wasn't the target</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd41fac083c07eb133b322/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd41fac083c07eb133b322/</guid><description>In the early morning hours Wednesday, Minneapolis police officers gently placed a key in a city apartment door before bursting through the doorway yelling &amp;quot;Police! Search warrant!,&amp;quot; according to body camera footage released by city officials Thursday night.
Highlights Minneapolis police officers placed a key in a door before bursting through the doorway yelling &amp;ldquo;Police! Search warrant!&amp;rdquo; The man was shot and killed in the early morning hours Wednesday morning. He was not named in any search warrants before the entry, police say.</description></item><item><title>Connecticut Man Arrested After Racist Tirade Over Smoothie, Cops Say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edec720ff1e559f57c5e50/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61edec720ff1e559f57c5e50/</guid><description>A Connecticut man, James Iannazzo, was arrested on bias intimidation and trespassing charges after a racist tirade at a smoothie shop, cops say - and Merrill&amp;hellip;
Summary Roughly 30 minutes later, police say he called 911 from his home for a child having an allergic reaction. When employees couldn&amp;rsquo;t answer, cops say Iannazzo became irate, yelling vulgarly, throwing a drink at one employee and questioning her immigration status. Cops say he was asked to leave and refused, even attempting to open a locked &amp;ldquo;Employees Only&amp;rdquo; door to get behind the store&amp;rsquo;s counter.</description></item><item><title>Man found alive in Scotland after faking his death to evade U.S. sex assault charges, official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</guid><description>A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities
Summary A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities said Thursday. Utah County Attorney David O. Leavitt admitted that had Rossi not contracted Covid and needed medical care, he would still probably be living &amp;ldquo;off the grid&amp;rdquo; successfully.</description></item><item><title>Bob Saget is dead at 65</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dba14f0e3f78f96fee79ed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 03:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dba14f0e3f78f96fee79ed/</guid><description>Bob Saget has died. TMZ first reported the comedian and actor&amp;rsquo;s death, suggesting he died Sunday at the Ritz-Carlton in Orlando. First responders were called to his hotel room Sunday afternoon, but the actor was pronounced dead at the scene. He was 65. No cause of death has been reported.Saget has [&amp;hellip;]
Summary First responders were called to his hotel room Sunday afternoon, but the actor was pronounced dead at the scene.</description></item><item><title>US had 5 rabies deaths last year, highest total in a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</guid><description>Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade
Summary Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decadeNEW YORK &amp;ndash; Five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade — and health officials said Thursday that some of the people didn&amp;rsquo;t realize they had been infected or refused life-saving shots.</description></item><item><title>‘The governor is an enemy of the people,’ well-known activist says as he’s handcuffed ahead of DeSantis news conference</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4dfa5dd187fb13ff9f722/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4dfa5dd187fb13ff9f722/</guid><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis had a scheduled COVID-19 news conference Tuesday morning at the Florida Department of Health – Duval County in Jacksonville, but it was a well-known activist who showed up at the news conference ahead of the governor who stole the show.
Summary A well-known activist was placed into handcuffs Tuesday after he refused to leave the Department of Health building in Jacksonville ahead of Gov. Ron DeSantis’ scheduled press conference.</description></item><item><title>Mom: Daughter mistaken for intruder by father, fatally shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce724e6aaed51be37d241e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce724e6aaed51be37d241e/</guid><description>Police say a man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family’s Ohio home after he mistook her for an intruder
Summary Police say a man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family’s Ohio home after he mistook her for an intruderCOLUMBUS, Ohio &amp;ndash; A man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family&amp;rsquo;s Columbus home after he mistook her for an intruder, according to what the girl&amp;rsquo;s mother told police.</description></item></channel></rss>