<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>man on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/man/</link><description>Recent content in man on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/man/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US had 5 rabies deaths last year, highest total in a decade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d80fd81212f63092b0bbb0/</guid><description>Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade
Summary Health officials say five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decadeNEW YORK &amp;ndash; Five Americans died of rabies last year — the largest number in a decade — and health officials said Thursday that some of the people didn&amp;rsquo;t realize they had been infected or refused life-saving shots.</description></item><item><title>‘The governor is an enemy of the people,’ well-known activist says as he’s handcuffed ahead of DeSantis news conference</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4dfa5dd187fb13ff9f722/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4dfa5dd187fb13ff9f722/</guid><description>Gov. Ron DeSantis had a scheduled COVID-19 news conference Tuesday morning at the Florida Department of Health – Duval County in Jacksonville, but it was a well-known activist who showed up at the news conference ahead of the governor who stole the show.
Summary A well-known activist was placed into handcuffs Tuesday after he refused to leave the Department of Health building in Jacksonville ahead of Gov. Ron DeSantis’ scheduled press conference.</description></item><item><title>Mom: Daughter mistaken for intruder by father, fatally shot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce724e6aaed51be37d241e/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 03:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce724e6aaed51be37d241e/</guid><description>Police say a man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family’s Ohio home after he mistook her for an intruder
Summary Police say a man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family’s Ohio home after he mistook her for an intruderCOLUMBUS, Ohio &amp;ndash; A man fatally shot his 16-year-old daughter in the family&amp;rsquo;s Columbus home after he mistook her for an intruder, according to what the girl&amp;rsquo;s mother told police.</description></item></channel></rss>