<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>finland on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/finland/</link><description>Recent content in finland on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/finland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US: Turkey's NATO issues with Sweden, Finland will be fixed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629272f6d7aabfc0ae2ece69/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 19:08:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629272f6d7aabfc0ae2ece69/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken said Friday he’s confident Turkey’s objections to Finland and Sweden joining NATO can be overcome swiftly, possibly in time for a summit of alliance leaders at the end of next month.
Highlights U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken says Turkey’s objections to Finland and Sweden joining NATO can be overcome swiftly. Turkey has cited alleged support for Kurdish militants whom Turkey considers terrorists and restrictions on weapons sales to Turkey.</description></item><item><title>Sweden's ruling party backs joining NATO, paving way for bid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62815f419889176b513ea0b5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62815f419889176b513ea0b5/</guid><description>Sweden&amp;rsquo;s ruling Social Democrats said on Sunday they backed the country joining NATO, abandoning decades of opposition in the wake of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine and creating a large parliament majority in favour of membership.
Highlights Sweden&amp;rsquo;s ruling Social Democrats said on Sunday they backed the country joining NATO. With neighboring Finland already set to hand in its application, Prime Minister Magdalena Andersson is now all but certain to launch a formal application within days.</description></item><item><title>Finland and Sweden set to join NATO as soon as summer, report says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62541d77696e01bb58d98fc4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62541d77696e01bb58d98fc4/</guid><description>Russia has made a &amp;quot;massive strategic blunder&amp;quot; as Finland and Sweden look poised to join NATO as early as the summer, The Times reported Monday, citing unidentified officials.
Highlights Finland and Sweden look poised to join NATO as early as summer, report says. NATO membership for both Nordic countries was “a topic of conversation and multiple sessions” during talks between the alliance’s foreign ministers last week attended by Sweden and Finland.</description></item><item><title>Sweden and Finland to further strengthen security cooperation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223b5c9bb3e58e7c05ad246/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 19:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223b5c9bb3e58e7c05ad246/</guid><description>Sweden and Finland will further strengthen their security cooperation in light of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine, the prime ministers of both countries said on Saturday, but they were non-committal on joining NATO.
Highlights Sweden and Finland will further strengthen their security cooperation in light of Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine, the prime ministers of both countries said on Saturday. Finnish Prime Minister Sanna Marin said it was &amp;ldquo;understandable&amp;rdquo; that more people in both countries now want to join NATO.</description></item></channel></rss>