<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>born on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/born/</link><description>Recent content in born on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/born/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Americans seeking to renounce their citizenship are stuck with it for now</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2a6d6c5e9a68ea4682554/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 14:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2a6d6c5e9a68ea4682554/</guid><description>As many as 30,000 citizens living abroad have been unable to secure a ‘loss of nationality’ interview during the pandemic
Highlights He discovered that along with thousands of other US citizens living abroad, he was caught in a Kafkaesque trap. Grant, 30, feels ready to acquire German citizenship, but under German law he must let go of his US passport. “The US appears intent on preventing its citizens from exercising their natural and fundamental right to voluntarily renounce their citizenship,” it says.</description></item><item><title>California twins, born 15 minutes apart, arrive in different years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d48b3dd97f23d2c8457317/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d48b3dd97f23d2c8457317/</guid><description>Alfredo Antonio Trujillo was born at 11:45 p.m. on Dec. 31, 2021. He was followed by his twin sister, Aylin Yolanda Trujillo, who arrived at 12 a.m. on Jan. 1, 2022, making her the first baby to be born this year at Natividad Medical Center and in Monterey County, according to a statement from the hospital.
Summary Twins in California might have been born just 15 minutes apart, but they were born in different years.</description></item><item><title>World's oldest person celebrates 119th birthday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2207f869bf4c9b1a8f411/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 22:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d2207f869bf4c9b1a8f411/</guid><description>Kane Tanaka at 119 has lived during the Meiji, Taisho, Showa, Heisei and current Reiwa eras
Summary Japan’s Kane Tanaka, who was born a year before the Russo-Japanese War began and is the world’s oldest person, celebrated her 119th birthday in Fukuoka Prefecture on Sunday. Notable people born in 1903 include British novelist George Orwell, film director Yasujiro Ozu and Japanese poet Misuzu Kaneko. Tanaka was recognized by Guinness World Records in March 2019 as the world’s oldest living person at 116 years old and also achieved an all-time Japanese age record when she became 117 years and 261 days old.</description></item></channel></rss>