<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>identified on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/identified/</link><description>Recent content in identified on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 18:10:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/identified/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Human remains found 50 years ago in Florida are finally identified through DNA testing</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b9ff2b9f9beac33473f43/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 18:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b9ff2b9f9beac33473f43/</guid><description>The Palm Beach County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office has identified human remains that were found nearly 50 years ago with the help of genealogy testing.
Highlights The remains belong to 15-year-old Susan Gale Poole, who went missing in Broward County just before Christmas in 1972. Poole&amp;rsquo;s remains were identified following genealogy testing by Othram Labs, a private forensic laboratory that utilizes genome sequencing to build DNA profiles, Detective Bill Springer said. The remains were found in June of 1974 belong to Poole who was 15 years old when she was last seen in June 1972, Springer said Thursday at a news conference in Palm Beach County, Florida, police said in a press conference.</description></item><item><title>Uvalde school police chief identified as commander who decided not to breach classroom</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62918b67c7239b3eba9f1372/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62918b67c7239b3eba9f1372/</guid><description>At a news conference Friday, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Col. Steven McCraw said the person who made the decision not to breach the Uvalde elementary school classroom where a gunman was shooting children and teachers was the school district police chief, calling it the “wrong decision” to not engage the gunman sooner.
Highlights Pedro “Pete” Arredondo is identified on the Uvalde School District website as the police chief. At a news conference Friday, Texas Department of Public Safety Director Col.</description></item><item><title>Equine virus identified in deaths of wild captive horses in Colorado</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f62792a8eb5fe62c6ec66/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 04:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f62792a8eb5fe62c6ec66/</guid><description>Laboratory tests have pinpointed the equine virus suspected of triggering an outbreak of a respiratory illness that has killed at least 95 captive wild horses in less than a week at a federal corral in Colorado, U.S. government officials said on Thursday.
Highlights Outbreak emerged April 23 at the BLM&amp;rsquo;s Wild Horse and Burro Corrals in Canon City, Colorado. Virus strain, an equine influenza designated &amp;ldquo;subtype H3N8,&amp;rdquo; is not uncommon in both wild and domestic horses.</description></item><item><title>Alleged killer in Portland’s Normandale Park protest shooting identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215b4d93a6de5fd52c009c9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215b4d93a6de5fd52c009c9/</guid><description>Benjamin Jeffrey Smith, 43, is suspected of shooting and killing a racial justice demonstrator Saturday night in Portland, Oregon. Police confirmed Tuesday morning that Smith remains hospitalized in serious condition. Smith&amp;rsquo;s roommate and neighbors said he had grown increasingly angry
Highlights Benjamin Jeffrey Smith, 43, is suspected of shooting and killing a racial justice demonstrator Saturday night. Police confirmed Tuesday morning that Smith remains hospitalized in serious condition. Smith&amp;rsquo;s roommate and neighbors said he had grown increasingly angry with protests in the neighborhood and across the city.</description></item><item><title>Mississippi soldier, missing in action in 1942, finally identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201995e34d5a3c843435b88/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 22:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6201995e34d5a3c843435b88/</guid><description>A south Mississippi family has finally found answers to an eight-decade mystery.
Highlights Private Andrew Ladner disappeared during World War II, during the Battle of Buna-Gona. His remains were discovered in April 1943 and buried at a temporary U.S. cemetery in the nearby village of Soputa. The still-unidentified remains were later moved to the Philippines and buried in another cemetery in 1949. A review of unknown casualty records prompted the exhumation of Ladner’s body in November 2016.</description></item></channel></rss>