<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>teacher on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teacher/</link><description>Recent content in teacher on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 17:12:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teacher/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde teacher who officials mistakenly said left door open is traumatized and heartbroken, attorney says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a40e402048bbc42543666/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 17:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629a40e402048bbc42543666/</guid><description>A Robb Elementary teacher has been traumatized and heartbroken since officials incorrectly said she left a door open prior to the shooting, her lawyer tells ABC News.
Highlights Lawyer Don Flanary: &amp;ldquo;She&amp;rsquo;s heartbroken&amp;rdquo; after Texas officials incorrectly said she left a door open prior to the shooting. Officials have determined that she did close the door, but it failed to lock. Flanary says she saw the gunman crash a gray Ford pickup truck and head her way, toward the school, armed with a gun.</description></item><item><title>Indonesian court sentences teacher to death for raping 13 students</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bdece0338368267d6701e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624bdece0338368267d6701e/</guid><description>An Indonesian court handed down a death sentence on Monday to a teacher for raping 13 girls at an Islamic school, upholding an appeal by prosecutors for the death penalty after he had initially received a sentence of life in prison.
Highlights Indonesian court sentences Herry Wirawan to death for raping 13 girls at Islamic boarding school. Prosecutors had called for the death penalty after he was sentenced to life in jail in February.</description></item><item><title>An Indiana teacher granted early retirement after hitting a student in the face is charged with battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223e0464af0841f6b89842e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 22:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223e0464af0841f6b89842e/</guid><description>A now-retired Indiana high school teacher who was arrested after video showed him hitting a student during a confrontation over wearing a hooded sweatshirt on school grounds was charged Friday with battery, according to court documents.
Highlights Michael Hosinski, 61, was arrested after video showed him hitting a student during a confrontation over wearing a hooded sweatshirt on school grounds. The incident occurred February 25 at Jimtown High School in Elkhart, Indiana.</description></item><item><title>Indiana state senator apologizes for saying educators need to be impartial when teaching about racism and Nazism</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de1a3f8eee9986ea4169eb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de1a3f8eee9986ea4169eb/</guid><description>An Indiana lawmaker is apologizing for saying teachers should exercise impartiality when teaching about Nazism or fascism.
Summary (CNN) An Indiana lawmaker is apologizing for saying teachers should exercise impartiality when teaching about Nazism or fascism. His remarks came after a concerned history teacher said he was teaching Nazism in his history class, and that when teaching the subject he does not remain neutral. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re learning about the rise of fascism and the rise of Nazism right now and I&amp;rsquo;m just not neutral on the political ideology of fascism.</description></item></channel></rss>