<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>prorussia on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prorussia/</link><description>Recent content in prorussia on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 10:13:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/prorussia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thousands of pro-Russia Serbs march in Belgrade</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224891bf52dde79888106e9/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 10:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6224891bf52dde79888106e9/</guid><description>Flags and flares are paraded through the Serbian capital, as marchers show support for Moscow.
Highlights Up to 4,000 people take part in pro-Russia demonstration in Serbian capital. It was a show of support for Moscow after its invasion of Ukraine. Serbia has religious, ethnic and political ties with Russia that have existed for centuries. The Serbian capital is Serbia&amp;rsquo;s capital of Beljevevevlija, which borders Russia and Ukraine, has long been friendly with Russia.</description></item><item><title>Putin to Recognize Ukraine Separatist Territories as Independent – Kremlin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214434651520b64d0fdc07b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214434651520b64d0fdc07b/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin has signed a decree recognizing the independence of eastern Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s separatist republics.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin signs decree recognizing independence of eastern Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s separatist republics. Putin calls for Russia&amp;rsquo;s upper house of parliament to &amp;ldquo;support this decision&amp;rdquo; State television shows Putin signing mutual aid agreements with rebel leaders in Donetsk and Luhansk. The move comes despite warnings from the West that it could trigger sweeping sanctions on Russia and the West.</description></item></channel></rss>