<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rioter on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rioter/</link><description>Recent content in rioter on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:17:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rioter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jan. 6 rioter who said he wanted Trump's 'approval' found guilty by jury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 08:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625929fc5bfddf4f8682c992/</guid><description>A Donald Trump supporter who told jurors that he was &amp;quot;following presidential orders&amp;quot; when he stormed the Capitol was found guilty.
Highlights Dustin Thompson, 38, of Ohio, admitted he stole a coat rack and a bottle of liquor from the Capitol. He testified that he was seeking former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s “respect’ and “approval” on Jan. 6, 2021. Thompson&amp;rsquo;s attorney argued that “Donald Trump encouraged people like Dustin Thompson to storm the Capitol’s Capitol&amp;quot; District Judge Reggie Walton ordered Thompson detained until his sentencing, even though the government didn’t ask him to.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioter from Idaho gets 4 years for attacking police with pipe</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62240471aa5e446be35bc120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62240471aa5e446be35bc120/</guid><description>An Idaho man who hit a police officer with a pipe as part of the mob that stormed the U.S.
Highlights Idaho man sentenced to more than four years in federal prison. Duke Edward Wilson, 68, hit a police officer with a pipe as part of the mob that stormed the U.S. Capitol. Prosecutors said he attacked at least three officers in a tunnel in the Capitol Building on Jan. 6, 2021.</description></item><item><title>Capitol rioter ordered back to jail after DWI arrest, AR-15 rifle discovered in car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8d048cb6990eaabe4cbcc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 03:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8d048cb6990eaabe4cbcc/</guid><description>An accused Capitol rioter has been ordered to be returned to federal custody after he tried to flee an arrest for suspected drunk driving last month and police discovered an AR-15 rifle in his car.
Summary James Tate Grant, who is accused of attacking a Capitol Police officer in the Jan. 6, 2021, riot. As he was being arrested, Grant tried to flee, the filing said. In Grant’s car, police recovered an AR-15 assault rifle, 60 rounds of ammunition, weapon accessories and combat fatigues, court documents said.</description></item></channel></rss>