<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>downtown on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/downtown/</link><description>Recent content in downtown on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 02:52:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/downtown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>'Multiple victims' shot, critically hurt near downtown Chattanooga bar, say police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629d6ba34d44427d20a6f759/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 02:52:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629d6ba34d44427d20a6f759/</guid><description>2:30 PM UPDATE:Chattanooga Police Department is beginning to re-open portions of McCallie Avenue. We have a crew at the scene:1 PM UPDATE:Chattanooga Mayor Tim Kelly and Chief Murphy held a press conference following the shooting this morning. Mayor Kelly is asking for Congress to take action to address the issue of gun violence in the country. &amp;quot;Our city will put a stop to this,” says Mayor Kelly.
Highlights Police Department is beginning to re-open portions of McCallie Avenue.</description></item><item><title>6 people shot in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, on Saturday night</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629433fb1e04b2a48468459b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629433fb1e04b2a48468459b/</guid><description>Six people were shot, and two of them suffered life-threatening injuries, following an altercation between two groups of people in downtown Chattanooga, Tennessee, on Saturday night, police said.
Highlights Police: &amp;ldquo;Multiple parties exchanging gunfire and numerous people fleeing the area&amp;rdquo; Four are expected to survive while two have life-threatening injuries, police say. Most of those shot were teenagers or in their early 20s, police Sgt. Jeremy Eames says. Investigators believe the shooting was not gang-related, police chief Celeste Murphy says.</description></item><item><title>Attacks by Boston youth ‘terrorizing unsuspecting citizens’ continue downtown; police can’t make arrests because many suspects ‘too young’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62701ffa2bb077417f6e68b8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 18:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62701ffa2bb077417f6e68b8/</guid><description>At least five violent attacks involving juveniles &amp;quot;terrorizing unsuspecting citizens&amp;quot; that have occurred across Boston. The most recent attack happened on Wednesday night when Boston police were dispatched to Boston Common shortly after 6:30 p.m. Two women claimed
Highlights At least five violent attacks involving juveniles have occurred across Boston. The apparent ringleader of the group — a slim 5-foot-3-inch girl is “well known to Officers as she has been terrorizing unsuspecting citizens of Downtown Boston,” authorities said.</description></item><item><title>Tacoma woman sentenced for burning 5 police cars during 2020 Seattle protests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221f3b8bac6367231fee1d1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 11:11:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6221f3b8bac6367231fee1d1/</guid><description>Margaret Aislinn Channon was arrested on June 11, 2020, after an investigation by the FBI, ATF and the Seattle Police Department. Channon admitted to smashing windows at a Verizon store, entering a sandwich shop and destroying a
Highlights Margaret Aislinn Channon was arrested on June 11, 2020, after an investigation by the FBI, ATF and the Seattle Police Department. Channon is shown using fire and aerosol cans as a blowtorch to light five Seattle police cars on fire.</description></item><item><title>‘Freedom Convoy’ protesters shut down third border crossing as Ottawa police warn of arrests ‘without a warrant’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620653efcdee5ffe18c39374/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 12:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620653efcdee5ffe18c39374/</guid><description>Raucous protests against vaccine mandates and coronavirus restrictions blocked a third border crossing with the United States.
Highlights The mayor of Windsor, Ontario, says the city and auto groups are seeking an injunction to end a blockade by protesters. The self-styled “Freedom Convoy,” now heading into its third weekend, has paralyzed the Canadian capital. The White House says it is “monitoring” the situation at the border “very closely” and that Cabinet officials are “engaged around the clock’ to bring this to a swift end” The protests started in opposition to U.</description></item><item><title>Ottawa police might need military aid to end downtown occupation, chief says | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbd57b3c826e358b4a975f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 13:16:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fbd57b3c826e358b4a975f/</guid><description>People who live in downtown Ottawa are bracing as the nearly week-long protest looks poised to continue, with the police chief concerned that policing alone may not end the &amp;quot;intolerable&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;unprecedented&amp;quot; demonstration.
Highlights A nearly week-long protest against COVID-19 public health mandates looks poised to continue in Ottawa. The police chief is concerned policing alone may not end the &amp;ldquo;intolerable&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;unprecedented&amp;rdquo; demonstration. Mayor Jim Watson asks Saskatchewan politicians to apologize for supporting the &amp;ldquo;illegal action&amp;rdquo; that&amp;rsquo;s caused hardship to Ottawans.</description></item></channel></rss>