<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tornado on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tornado/</link><description>Recent content in tornado on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 17:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/tornado/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tornado hits Gaylord, extensive damage reported</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62891d9deba5fa4f6a005c29/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 17:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62891d9deba5fa4f6a005c29/</guid><description>OTSEGO COUNTY, Mich. (WPBN/WGTU) &amp;ndash; The Gaylord community is assessing the damage after a powerful tornado hit. The National Weather Service confirmed a large and “extremely dangerous” tornado was located over Gaylord, moving northeast at 50 mph Friday around 3:45 p. m. Extensive damage was reported in Gaylord with buildings destroyed. Several roads are closed in the area due to downed power lines.
Highlights A large and &amp;ldquo;extremely dangerous&amp;rdquo; tornado was located over Gaylord, moving northeast at 50 mph.</description></item><item><title>March breaks record for most tornados in a single month</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62537c727be68abbd107b567/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62537c727be68abbd107b567/</guid><description>It was a chaotic meteorological transition into spring as March saw the highest number of tornadoes in a single month in U.S. history.
Highlights At least 218 tornadoes occurred in March, with many of the tornadoes happening toward the end of the month. More tornadoes and severe weather are expected in the coming days. More severe weather that could conjure up more tornadoes is expected over the next several days. On Sunday and Monday, tornadoes could pop up in eastern Oklahoma, northeast Texas, southern Missouri and much of Arkansas.</description></item></channel></rss>