<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>case on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/case/</link><description>Recent content in case on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 21:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Former Deputy Accused Of Raping 14-Year-Old Avoids Jail Time And Sex Offender Registry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223d2017fafb61c1417dae1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223d2017fafb61c1417dae1/</guid><description>Brian Beck, 47, was accused of raping a 14-year-old girl over a 20-month period of time. The former Shelby County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputy pleaded guilty to aggravated assault. He faced 30 years in prison for each
Highlights Brian Beck, 47, was accused of raping a 14-year-old girl over a 20-month period of time. The former Shelby County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputy pleaded guilty to a lesser charge of aggravated assault. The judge suspended a four-year prison term in favor of probation.</description></item><item><title>What should you do in case of a nuclear explosion? U.S. government updates guidance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62214b6c64ad147693db931d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 23:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62214b6c64ad147693db931d/</guid><description>Friday, the official Ready.gov website updated its guidance about what to do in the case of a nuclear blast. It was not immediately clear if the update was tied to anything specific with the Russia-Ukraine conflict or just coincidental.
Highlights The official Ready.gov website updated its guidance about what to do in the case of a nuclear blast Friday. It was not immediately clear if the update was tied to anything specific or just coincidental.</description></item><item><title>Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 22:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</guid><description>The 44-year-old woman who was filmed in a TikTok video, had been sold at least three times, Chinese officials said.
Highlights Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say. Chinese authorities say she had been sold at least three times, first when she was 20 years old. She was discovered after being filmed in a TikTok video. A man claiming to be her husband said she was mentally ill.</description></item><item><title>Lawsuit aiming to break up Facebook group Meta can go ahead, US court rules | Meta</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfea45e2a3897f563787aa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfea45e2a3897f563787aa/</guid><description>The Federal Trade Commission wants to force sale of Instagram and WhatsApp
Summary The US competition watchdog can proceed with a breakup lawsuit against Facebook’s owner, a federal judge has ruled. Mark Zuckerberg’s Meta, the parent of Facebook, Instagram and WhatsApp, had asked a court to dismiss an antitrust complaint brought by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) for the second time. However, Judge James Boasberg said on Tuesday that the FTC’s revised lawsuit should be allowed to proceed.</description></item></channel></rss>