<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>case on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/case/</link><description>Recent content in case on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 06:12:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Governor saw deadly arrest video months before prosecutors</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291bd2b9981fdbc4f19f1ed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 06:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291bd2b9981fdbc4f19f1ed/</guid><description>BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — With racial tensions still simmering over the killing of George Floyd, Louisiana Gov. John Bel Edwards and his top lawyers gathered in a state police conference room in October 2020 to prepare for the fallout from a troubling case closer to home: troopers’ deadly arrest of Ronald Greene.
Highlights Governor saw deadly arrest video months before prosecutors had video, AP finds. Video showed a bruised and bloody Ronald Greene going limp and drawing his final breaths.</description></item><item><title>Utah hunting guide faces felony charge for Donald Trump Jr.’s big-game hunt</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289af7a326f453252954bcc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 03:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289af7a326f453252954bcc/</guid><description>Prosecutors have indicated there was no evidence showing Trump Jr. would have known about alleged baiting that went on during the hunt.
Highlights Utah hunting guide Wade Lemon faces five years in state prison for the death of a bear killed during a guided hunt on May 18, 2018. Donald Trump Jr. was in Utah to help launch Hunter Nation, a hunting advocacy group. The group would later launch its own super PAC, Hunter Nation Action, which spent $96,997 in ads against Democrats in the 2020 election.</description></item><item><title>Family of Abducted Girl Claims Inaction of Dallas Police &amp;amp; Mavs in Sex Trafficking Case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e75d75ff24d07ddad92a1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627e75d75ff24d07ddad92a1/</guid><description>“The American Airlines Center (and the Dallas Mavericks) are grateful that the teenager has been found.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; - A statement from the Mavs.
Highlights 15-year-old girl from North Richland Hills is now home after being abducted by a man at an April 8 Dallas Mavericks game at American Airlines Center. Family still seeks answers, and is pressing the Mavs, AAC and Dallas Police for not acting swiftly enough regarding the crime. The girl&amp;rsquo;s father informed police at the game when he realized she was missing, but was told to report the allegations to his hometown North Richlands Hills Police.</description></item><item><title>Celebrity chef Mario Batali found not guilty of indecent assault, battery</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b8cb9af72e9ed3331e533/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 10:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627b8cb9af72e9ed3331e533/</guid><description>Celebrity chef Mario Batali was being tried for a 2017 incident in Boston.
Highlights Mario Batali has been found not guilty of indecent assault and battery for a 2017 incident in Boston. Natalie Tene, 32, said Batali forcibly kissed her and grabbed her breasts, buttocks and groin after meeting him in a Boston bar in March 2017. Four women accused Batali of inappropriate touching in December 2017, which prompted him to leave the ABC daytime cooking show &amp;ldquo;The Chew&amp;rdquo; and remove himself from his restaurant business.</description></item><item><title>Tesla stockholders ask judge to silence Musk in fraud case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d02621548d4d67b4cc1fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 06:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625d02621548d4d67b4cc1fa/</guid><description>DETROIT (AP) — A group of Tesla shareholders suing CEO Elon Musk over some 2018 tweets about taking the company private is asking a federal judge to order Musk to stop commenting on the case. Lawyers for stockholders of the Austin, Texas-based company also say in court documents that the judge in the case has ruled that Musk&amp;rsquo;s tweets about having “funding secured” to take Tesla private were false, and that his comments also violate a 2018 court settlement with U.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Proud Boys chairman Tarrio ordered detained pending trial in Capitol riot case</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231807d650ab0795eef6523/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 06:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231807d650ab0795eef6523/</guid><description>A U.S. judge ordered former Proud Boys chairman Enrique Tarrio be detained while he awaits trial on charges stemming from the U.S. Capitol riots, a Justice Department spokesperson confirmed.
Highlights Former Proud Boys chairman Enrique Tarrio ordered to be detained while he awaits trial on charges stemming from the riots at the U.S. Capitol. Tarrio, 38, is among the most high-profile of more than 775 people criminally charged for their roles in the assault on the Capitol by supporters of then-President Donald Trump in an effort to keep Congress from certifying Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s election victory.</description></item><item><title>Exxon Mobil loses appeal to stop climate change probes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231645207d13f324cfb5f4f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 04:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231645207d13f324cfb5f4f/</guid><description>A U.S. federal appeals court on Tuesday rejected Exxon Mobil Corp&amp;rsquo;s effort to stop Massachusetts and New York from probing whether the oil company lied to investors and the public regarding what it knew about climate change.
Highlights The 2nd U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in Manhattan said Exxon could not sue in federal court because it was pursuing the same case in Massachusetts state courts. It also said Exxon&amp;rsquo;s federal case against New York Attorney General Letitia James was moot after she decided not to appeal a state judge&amp;rsquo;s dismissal of her lawsuit against the company.</description></item><item><title>Homeless men targeted in deadly NYC street attacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ef9a25801095e62696544/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 08:16:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622ef9a25801095e62696544/</guid><description>The NYPD was searching for a gunman who was targeting homeless people sleeping in on the streets of Manhattan.
Highlights The NYPD was searching for a gunman who was targeting homeless people sleeping in on the streets of Manhattan. They were looking into whether the same man was responsible for killing a homeless man on Sunday evening and two previous attacks. The case could also be linked to violence against homeless men in Washington, D.</description></item><item><title>Former Deputy Accused Of Raping 14-Year-Old Avoids Jail Time And Sex Offender Registry</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223d2017fafb61c1417dae1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6223d2017fafb61c1417dae1/</guid><description>Brian Beck, 47, was accused of raping a 14-year-old girl over a 20-month period of time. The former Shelby County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputy pleaded guilty to aggravated assault. He faced 30 years in prison for each
Highlights Brian Beck, 47, was accused of raping a 14-year-old girl over a 20-month period of time. The former Shelby County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office deputy pleaded guilty to a lesser charge of aggravated assault. The judge suspended a four-year prison term in favor of probation.</description></item><item><title>What should you do in case of a nuclear explosion? U.S. government updates guidance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62214b6c64ad147693db931d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 23:13:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62214b6c64ad147693db931d/</guid><description>Friday, the official Ready.gov website updated its guidance about what to do in the case of a nuclear blast. It was not immediately clear if the update was tied to anything specific with the Russia-Ukraine conflict or just coincidental.
Highlights The official Ready.gov website updated its guidance about what to do in the case of a nuclear blast Friday. It was not immediately clear if the update was tied to anything specific or just coincidental.</description></item><item><title>Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 22:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62195460ecc136a40e6e8dbf/</guid><description>The 44-year-old woman who was filmed in a TikTok video, had been sold at least three times, Chinese officials said.
Highlights Woman found chained in Chinese village is victim of trafficking, authorities say. Chinese authorities say she had been sold at least three times, first when she was 20 years old. She was discovered after being filmed in a TikTok video. A man claiming to be her husband said she was mentally ill.</description></item><item><title>Lawsuit aiming to break up Facebook group Meta can go ahead, US court rules | Meta</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfea45e2a3897f563787aa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 09:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dfea45e2a3897f563787aa/</guid><description>The Federal Trade Commission wants to force sale of Instagram and WhatsApp
Summary The US competition watchdog can proceed with a breakup lawsuit against Facebook’s owner, a federal judge has ruled. Mark Zuckerberg’s Meta, the parent of Facebook, Instagram and WhatsApp, had asked a court to dismiss an antitrust complaint brought by the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) for the second time. However, Judge James Boasberg said on Tuesday that the FTC’s revised lawsuit should be allowed to proceed.</description></item></channel></rss>