<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cancel on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cancel/</link><description>Recent content in cancel on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/cancel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CDC's suggestion to cancel football, band in nearly every US school called 'unrealistic'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e69dcd61f0da782771a1fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e69dcd61f0da782771a1fd/</guid><description>If the scientists at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had their way, to curb the spread of Covid-19 right now, nearly every US school would cancel football, wrestling, band and loads of other mainstay school activities.
Summary (CNN) If the scientists at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had their way, to curb the spread of Covid-19 right now, nearly every US school would cancel football, wrestling, band and loads of other mainstay school activities.</description></item><item><title>United Airlines preemptively cancels 112 Christmas Eve flights due to COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5701796cb667903e95aaf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 07:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c5701796cb667903e95aaf/</guid><description>United and Delta Airlines have preemptively canceled almost 200 Christmas Eve flights, the airlines announced Thursday.
Summary United and Delta Airlines have preemptively canceled almost 200 Christmas Eve flights, the airlines announced Thursday. In a statement, United Airlines blamed the cancellations on staffing shortages due to COVID-19. Eleven of the flights were United, while no Delta flights were canceled today. One of the delayed flights is United, while no Delta flights have been delayed at this time.</description></item></channel></rss>