<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ended on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ended/</link><description>Recent content in ended on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 12:22:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/ended/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rare, record-breaking snow falls in Portland, Oregon</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62556ee522d3309d48081897/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 12:22:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62556ee522d3309d48081897/</guid><description>The residents of Portland, Oregon, woke up to a rare April sight on Monday: a blanket of fresh, white snow.
Highlights Snowfall was the city’s first measurable snow in April since record keeping began more than 80 years ago. One to three inches of snow fell around Portland, Oregon, on Monday. The snow and gusty winds brought down trees and power lines across the greater Portland area. Last April was the driest on record for the city, followed by an unprecedented, multi-day heat wave in June.</description></item><item><title>Sources: Judge Peter Cahill Signed ‘No-Knock’ Warrant That Ended In Police Shooting Of Amir Locke</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62000188a8d2567622720151/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 17:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62000188a8d2567622720151/</guid><description>Two sources confirm to WCCO-TV that Judge Peter Cahill, who presided over the Derek Chauvin trial, signed off on the “no-knock” search warrant that ended in the fatal police shooting of Amir Locke on Wednesday morning.
Highlights Sources confirm to WCCO-TV that Judge Peter Cahill signed off on the “no-knock” warrant that ended in the fatal police shooting of Amir Locke. The original search warrants remain under seal as they are part of an active homicide investigation.</description></item></channel></rss>