<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wounded on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wounded/</link><description>Recent content in wounded on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 21:08:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/wounded/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Families of kids wounded in Uvalde school shooting sue suspected gunman’s estate</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a10fb8699c26c11939e684/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 21:08:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a10fb8699c26c11939e684/</guid><description>The families of four students injured in the Uvalde school shooting filed a lawsuit against the suspected gunman&amp;rsquo;s estate.
Highlights The families of four students injured in the Uvalde, Texas, school shooting are suing the suspected gunman&amp;rsquo;s estate. Salvador Ramos, 18, allegedly killed 19 children and two teachers at Robb Elementary School on May 24. The plaintiffs suffered severe injuries to the face, leg, back and other parts of the body, resulting in having them undergo multiple surgeries, according to the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Gunman in California church attack subdued by parishioners</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282ccb264f9e59da030c066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 22:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282ccb264f9e59da030c066/</guid><description>LAGUNA WOODS, Calif. (AP) — A gunman in a deadly attack at a Southern California church was a Chinese immigrant motivated by hate for Taiwanese people, authorities said. The shooter killed Dr.
Highlights Suspect identified as David Chou, 68, of Las Vegas. Shooter killed Dr. John Cheng, 52, and wounded five others during a lunch held by Irvine Taiwanese Presbyterian Church, which worships at Geneva Presbyterian Church in Laguna Woods, California.</description></item></channel></rss>