<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>planning on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/planning/</link><description>Recent content in planning on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 04:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/planning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CIA Director: US “sees no practical evidence” that Russia is planning nuclear strikes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627744c8e19655f5e9112b8b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 04:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627744c8e19655f5e9112b8b/</guid><description>The CIA director said the United States does not see Russia preparing for a nuclear strike
Highlights CIA director William Burns said the U.S. does not see Russia preparing for a nuclear strike. The preparations for such a strike are monitored from satellites, Burns said. Burns said Putin is in such a mindset that he cannot allow himself to be defeated. The second phase of the Russian invasion of Ukraine may be &amp;ldquo;even riskier&amp;rdquo; than the first phase, Burns noted.</description></item><item><title>UK Says Russia Is Planning To Overthrow Ukraine’s Government - Buzzfeed News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed89b7507b1de48c8fe763/</guid><description>“The information being released today shines a light on the extent of Russian activity designed to subvert Ukraine, and is an insight into Kremlin thinking,” Foreign Secretary Liz Truss said in a statement shared with BuzzFeed News.
Summary BAKHMUT, Ukraine — Russia has drawn up plans to install a pro-Kremlin former member of parliament to lead Ukraine as it considers a new invasion of the country and the overthrow of its central government, according to a British assessment shared with BuzzFeed News.</description></item></channel></rss>