<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mcdonalds on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mcdonalds/</link><description>Recent content in mcdonalds on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 23:10:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mcdonalds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starbucks exits Russia, shutting 130 coffee shops</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c14419acf93c60a516322/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 23:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628c14419acf93c60a516322/</guid><description>The coffee chain joins McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in taking its brand out of the country. Starbucks had temporarily paused operations in March.
Highlights Starbucks says it is leaving Russia after 15 years in business. The coffee chain had temporarily shut down its stores in March over Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine. Starbucks joins McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in taking its brand out of the country. The company says it will continue paying its nearly 2,000 employees in Russia for six months and help them find new jobs.</description></item><item><title>'She created a McMess': Polk County woman arrested for calling 911 over McDonald's order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a0bf429f664b833325895/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 10:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a0bf429f664b833325895/</guid><description>The Polk County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office arrested a woman they say called 911 and assaulted restaurant workers because her McDonald&amp;rsquo;s order was wrong.
Highlights Polk County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office arrested a woman they say called 911 and assaulted restaurant workers because her McDonald&amp;rsquo;s order was wrong. Tianis Jones, 22, was arrested Friday evening. She was arrested on burglary with assault, criminal mischief, disorderly conduct and misuse of 911 charges. Surveillance video shows Jones becoming increasingly displeased with the service, despite workers offering to fix the issues as well as return her money.</description></item><item><title>Ice Cream Machine Hackers Sue McDonald's for $900 Million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62204e4e8d171ce6d3400fdb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 05:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62204e4e8d171ce6d3400fdb/</guid><description>Kytch alleges that the Golden Arches crushed its business—and left soft serve customers out in the cold.
Highlights Kytch filed a long-expected legal complaint against McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Tuesday night. Kytch&amp;rsquo;s cofounders are asking for no less than $900 million in damages. Since 2019, Kytch has sold a phone-sized gadget designed to be installed inside McDonald&amp;rsquo;s ice cream machines. Those Kytch devices would intercept the machines&amp;rsquo; internal communications and send them out to a web or smartphone interface to help owners remotely monitor and troubleshoot the machines.</description></item></channel></rss>