<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>grow on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/grow/</link><description>Recent content in grow on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/grow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Protests grow across Canada as police struggle to reopen key bridge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62092e9df129c204bad68b5a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62092e9df129c204bad68b5a/</guid><description>Police had early success in clearing Ambassador Bridge, but demonstrators still choke vital trade route
Highlights Police arrest first protester on Ambassador Bridge in Windsor, Ontario, Canada. Anti-vaccine protesters have been blocking access to a US-Canadian border bridge for a sixth day. Canadian police say they are awaiting more officers before ending what they described as an illegal occupation. Canadian prime minister Justin Trudeau emphasised that border crossings could not and would not remain closed, with all options remaining on the table.</description></item><item><title>Thailand gives green light to growing cannabis at home</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0f195c9d19063d5ee4288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 07:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0f195c9d19063d5ee4288/</guid><description>Thailand&amp;rsquo;s narcotics board on Tuesday said it would remove cannabis from its drugs list, paving the way for households to grow the plant.
Summary Thailand became the first Southeast Asian country to legalise marijuana in 2018 for medical use and research. Under the new rule, people can grow cannabis plants at home after notifying their local government, but the cannabis cannot be used for commercial purposes without further licenses, Health Minister Anutin Charnvirakul told reporters.</description></item><item><title>The United States records an average of 700,000 new cases per day; Fauci says the nation could grow to 1 million</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 12:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc1fe6a0563c0965964f02/</guid><description>Summary The country reported about 4.91 million cases in the week ending Saturday. “I would not be surprised at all if we go over a million cases per day,” Dr. Anthony Fauci, the president’s chief medical adviser, told News 4 New York in an interview Saturday. But Fauci told the TV station the dismal numbers could start to decline by month’s end. 📈Today’s numbers: The U.S. has recorded more than 60 million confirmed COVID-19 cases and more than 837,000 deaths, according to Johns Hopkins University data.</description></item><item><title>Tony Blair blasts unvaccinated 'idiots' as fears grow over spread of Omicron - "Frankly, if you're not vaccinated at the moment and you're eligible, and you've got no health reasons for not being unvaccinated, you're not just irresponsible. You're an idiot."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c66d2cb17fc1ddd51ae3b4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c66d2cb17fc1ddd51ae3b4/</guid><description>The former Labour Prime Minister said those who are not vaccinated are putting strain on the NHS due to the transmissibility of the new strain.
Summary Tony Blair has slammed people who are still refusing to get the coronavirus vaccine as &amp;ldquo;idiots&amp;rdquo; with concerns growing over the spread of the Omicron variant. His comments come after First Minister Nicola Sturgeon announced new restrictions to halt the spread of Omicron which is now the dominant variant in Scotland.</description></item></channel></rss>