<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>political on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/political/</link><description>Recent content in political on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 09:14:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/political/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conservative Disney employees fear retaliation for “Don’t be gay” bill.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d87be4203066f34294097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d87be4203066f34294097/</guid><description>A new petition asks Disney to be more politically neutral on issues like the “Don’t Say Gay’s” bill. The bill would ban discussion of sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade. The
Highlights An open letter to Disney employees asks them to remain neutral on issues like the &amp;lsquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rsquo; bill. The bill would ban discussion about sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade.</description></item><item><title>MI5 has warned Chinese government 'agent' has been 'active' in UK parliament, MPs told</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0a102673bfa47de8734e0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0a102673bfa47de8734e0/</guid><description>Christine Lee has made large donations to Labour MP Barry Gardiner&amp;rsquo;s office, but he said MI5 has reassured him they were all above board. Her son resigned from his office today.
Summary MI5 has warned that a Chinese government agent has been working in parliament &amp;ldquo;to subvert the processes&amp;rdquo;, MPs have been told. Christine Lee &amp;lsquo;involved in political interference in UK&amp;rsquo;MI5 said Ms Lee, a lawyer, has been involved with MPs and hopeful MPs as well as members of the now-disbanded all-party parliamentary group, Chinese in Britain.</description></item></channel></rss>