<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>political on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/political/</link><description>Recent content in political on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:24:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/political/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hezbollah's coalition loses parliamentary majority in Lebanon's first vote after uprising, financial collapse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283da1347a4cd7c3a951c63/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 17:24:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283da1347a4cd7c3a951c63/</guid><description>Iran-backed Hezbollah has lost its parliamentary coalition majority in a Lebanese election that delivered significant gains to its rivals as well as to a protest movement that swept the country in a 2019 uprising.
Highlights Hezbollah has lost its parliamentary coalition majority in a Lebanese election. Reformist political groups that sprung out of nationwide demonstrations have won around 10% of the country&amp;rsquo;s parliamentary seats, according to a CNN tally. The group&amp;rsquo;s main Christian rival &amp;ndash; the Saudi-allied Lebanese Forces &amp;ndash; gained new seats.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court sides with Ted Cruz, striking down cap on use of campaign funds to repay personal campaign loans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282956286f0c83e21eb00c8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282956286f0c83e21eb00c8/</guid><description>The Supreme Court on Monday ruled in favor of Republican Sen. Ted Cruz of Texas in a case involving the use of campaign funds to repay personal campaign loans, dealing the latest blow to campaign finance regulations.
Highlights The Supreme Court rules in favor of Ted Cruz in a case involving the use of campaign funds to repay personal campaign loans. Chief Justice John Roberts wrote the 6-3 decision; Justice Elena Kagan wrote the dissent for her liberal colleagues, Justice Stephen Breyer and Justice Sonia Sotomayor.</description></item><item><title>Conservative Disney employees fear retaliation for “Don’t be gay” bill.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d87be4203066f34294097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 09:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623d87be4203066f34294097/</guid><description>A new petition asks Disney to be more politically neutral on issues like the “Don’t Say Gay’s” bill. The bill would ban discussion of sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade. The
Highlights An open letter to Disney employees asks them to remain neutral on issues like the &amp;lsquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay&amp;rsquo; bill. The bill would ban discussion about sexual orientation and gender identity in kindergarten through third grade.</description></item><item><title>MI5 has warned Chinese government 'agent' has been 'active' in UK parliament, MPs told</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0a102673bfa47de8734e0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e0a102673bfa47de8734e0/</guid><description>Christine Lee has made large donations to Labour MP Barry Gardiner&amp;rsquo;s office, but he said MI5 has reassured him they were all above board. Her son resigned from his office today.
Summary MI5 has warned that a Chinese government agent has been working in parliament &amp;ldquo;to subvert the processes&amp;rdquo;, MPs have been told. Christine Lee &amp;lsquo;involved in political interference in UK&amp;rsquo;MI5 said Ms Lee, a lawyer, has been involved with MPs and hopeful MPs as well as members of the now-disbanded all-party parliamentary group, Chinese in Britain.</description></item></channel></rss>