<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>misinformation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/misinformation/</link><description>Recent content in misinformation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/misinformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disinformation Governance Board to tackle spread of misinformation in U.S., focusing on Russia and U.S.-Mexico border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d1962dbb68bb45dd6e9e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d1962dbb68bb45dd6e9e5/</guid><description>The immediate focus will be on misinformation from human smugglers, who spread falsehoods about border policy to migrants to help drum up business.
Highlights The Department of Homeland Security is setting up a Disinformation Governance Board to try to counter the spread of false information. The board will focus on misinformation coming from Russia as well as misleading messages about the U.S.-Mexico border. The immediate focus will be on misinformation from human smugglers, who spread false claims about border policy to migrants to help drum up business.</description></item><item><title>Neil Young Wants His Music Off Spotify Over Joe Rogan Vaccine Misinformation</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 07:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efa0125cc854c8eb002b96/</guid><description>Neil Young demanded that Spotify remove his music, citing its spread of vaccine misinformation via &amp;quot;The Joe Rogan Experience&amp;quot; podcast.
Summary Neil Young wants his music pulled from Spotify, citing the spread of vaccine misinformation on the popular Joe Rogan Experience podcast as the cause. “They can have Rogan or Young. Not both,” Young wrote in an open letter to his management team and record label posted to his Neil Young Archives website, according to Rolling Stone.</description></item><item><title>YouTube is major conduit of fake news, factcheckers say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df25579f65b2978b9e70d3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df25579f65b2978b9e70d3/</guid><description>Platform is not doing enough to tackle spread of falsehoods, claims letter signed by 80 groups
Summary YouTube is a major conduit of online disinformation and misinformation worldwide and is not doing enough to tackle the spread of falsehoods on its platform, according to a global coalition of factchecking organisations. “YouTube is allowing its platform to be weaponised by unscrupulous actors to manipulate and exploit others, and to organise and fundraise themselves.</description></item></channel></rss>