<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crime on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crime/</link><description>Recent content in crime on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Shoplifting is surging across America with dangerous and costly consequences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9b5397ad14d7c9fb8b9ae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9b5397ad14d7c9fb8b9ae/</guid><description>Summary This is not a one-time opportunistic or need-based robbery,&amp;quot; said Cory Lowe, an expert on retail crime and research scientist at the Loss Prevention Research Council, an industry coalition that researches retail crime, its impact and solutions to address it. But even then, it was more street robberies and not like retail theft as brazen as this.&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve talked to retailers across America who say shoplifting is now 2% to 3% of their total sales.</description></item><item><title>Ahmaud Arbery's family says they rejected a plea deal for federal hate crime charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8fe4e74331aeeab779bbb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8fe4e74331aeeab779bbb/</guid><description>Travis McMichael, his father Gregory McMichael and William &amp;quot;Roddie&amp;quot; Bryan were convicted in state murder charges in November.​
Summary The family of Ahmaud Arbery rejected a plea deal in the federal civil rights case of two of the men convicted of shooting and killing Arbery while he was jogging in a Brunswick, Georgia, neighborhood in February 2020, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney said. Cooper-Jones told &amp;ldquo;CBS Mornings&amp;rdquo; she rejected the deal because she wants the men to stand trial in court for those charges.</description></item></channel></rss>