<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crime on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crime/</link><description>Recent content in crime on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:40:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Phoenix cops find 1,200 catalytic converters as thefts soar</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292c0ce9c917c756d459b5e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6292c0ce9c917c756d459b5e/</guid><description>An Arizona man is facing multiple theft charges after detectives found a huge stash of stolen catalytic converters packed into a storage unit in Phoenix
Highlights An Arizona man is facing multiple theft charges after detectives found a huge stash of stolen catalytic converters packed into a storage unit in Phoenix. The bust came amid a national surge in thefts of the pricy auto parts that play a critical in reducing vehicle emissions and has led lawmakers in 36 states and in Washington D.</description></item><item><title>Tory MP arrested on suspicion of rape and banned from Commons – reports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284e5d3247053e9feca08f9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 12:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284e5d3247053e9feca08f9/</guid><description>MP arrested on suspicion of indecent assault, sexual assault, rape, abuse of position of trust and misconduct
Highlights MP arrested on suspicion of indecent assault, sexual assault, rape, abuse of position of trust and misconduct in public office. Metropolitan Police said offences are alleged to have taken place between 2002 and 2009. MP&amp;rsquo;s arrest followed a two-year investigation and remains in custody. Whips’ Office has asked MP not to come to parliament while investigation is ongoing.</description></item><item><title>Southern California woman who accused Black teen of stealing phone, pleads guilty to hate crime charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255ddb34392a0bec8121f93/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255ddb34392a0bec8121f93/</guid><description>Miya Ponsetto, 23, pleads guilty to unlawful imprisonment in the second degree as a hate crime. She falsely accused Keyon Harrold Jr. of stealing her cell phone and then attacking him in a New York
Highlights Miya Ponsetto pleads guilty to unlawful imprisonment in the second degree as a hate crime. She falsely accused Keyon Harrold Jr. of stealing her cell phone and then attacking him in a New York hotel lobby.</description></item><item><title>Biden signs bill making lynching a federal hate crime</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 19:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244ab96461e97cf533e5c21/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Presidents typically say a few words before they turn legislation into law. But Joe Biden flipped the script Tuesday when it came time to put his signature on the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act.
Highlights Biden signs the Emmett Till Anti-Lynching Act in the White House Rose Garden. Biden said it&amp;rsquo;s “a little unusual to do the bill signing, not say anything and then speak” Biden: “Racial hate isn’t an old problem — it’s a persistent problem.</description></item><item><title>FBI: Americans Lost $1 Billion to Romance Scams in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bd563650f6c85d32cc422/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bd563650f6c85d32cc422/</guid><description>Organized Crime and Corruption Reporting Project
Highlights Romance scams have been on the rise since the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic and cost Americans more than US$1 billion in 2021 alone. Perpetrators mainly target women over 40 who are widowed, divorced, elderly or disabled. “The victim just wants connection and companionship. The bad guy generally wants cold hard cash,” the FBI warned. Phishing attacks and social engineering, like romance scams, remain two of the most common crimes on the web.</description></item><item><title>City of Little Rock declares violent crime a public health emergency amid surge in shootings</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd33bb2d83b4bf15f467ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 14:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd33bb2d83b4bf15f467ee/</guid><description>The City of Little Rock, Arkansas, has declared violent crime a public emergency amid a surge in shootings in recent weeks.
Highlights The resolution includes provisions to fund community partners via grants and other funding. At least 10 people were shot in Little Rock over the weekend, police said. &amp;ldquo;The loss of life is just astounding, and I look at it as basically a whole generation is being genocided,&amp;rdquo; city director Doris Wright said.</description></item><item><title>Shoplifting is surging across America with dangerous and costly consequences</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9b5397ad14d7c9fb8b9ae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d9b5397ad14d7c9fb8b9ae/</guid><description>Summary This is not a one-time opportunistic or need-based robbery,&amp;quot; said Cory Lowe, an expert on retail crime and research scientist at the Loss Prevention Research Council, an industry coalition that researches retail crime, its impact and solutions to address it. But even then, it was more street robberies and not like retail theft as brazen as this.&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve talked to retailers across America who say shoplifting is now 2% to 3% of their total sales.</description></item><item><title>Ahmaud Arbery's family says they rejected a plea deal for federal hate crime charges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8fe4e74331aeeab779bbb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d8fe4e74331aeeab779bbb/</guid><description>Travis McMichael, his father Gregory McMichael and William &amp;quot;Roddie&amp;quot; Bryan were convicted in state murder charges in November.​
Summary The family of Ahmaud Arbery rejected a plea deal in the federal civil rights case of two of the men convicted of shooting and killing Arbery while he was jogging in a Brunswick, Georgia, neighborhood in February 2020, the family&amp;rsquo;s attorney said. Cooper-Jones told &amp;ldquo;CBS Mornings&amp;rdquo; she rejected the deal because she wants the men to stand trial in court for those charges.</description></item></channel></rss>