<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>flu on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/flu/</link><description>Recent content in flu on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 02:39:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/flu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>U.S. detects highly lethal bird flu in Tyson Foods chickens</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620db52c676483c088fd4d29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 02:39:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620db52c676483c088fd4d29/</guid><description>A flock of about 240,000 chickens owned by Tyson Foods Inc in Kentucky tested positive for a highly lethal form of bird flu, government officials and the company said on Monday, widening an outbreak that threatens the U.S. poultry industry.
Highlights A flock of about 240,000 chickens owned by Tyson Foods Inc in Kentucky tested positive for a highly lethal form of bird flu. It is Kentucky&amp;rsquo;s first outbreak of the highly lethal bird flu, which killed more than 50 million U.</description></item><item><title>One million chickens culled after H5N1 Bird Flu virus found spreading among several UK farms</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79f59c1c0128349f0b525/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 02:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d79f59c1c0128349f0b525/</guid><description>Lincolnshire is a bird flu hot-spot during the largest outbreak of infections England has known.
Summary Professor Ian Brown, of the Animal and Plant Health Agency, said: &amp;ldquo;There is a high density of poultry farms in Lincolnshire and the virus has found its way in because it has been able to breach the biosecurity barrier of the farms.&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Israel reports first case of ‘flurona’ – rare double infection of Covid and influenza</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d185d9143166e250c1b4a7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d185d9143166e250c1b4a7/</guid><description>Flurona case reported in Israel
Summary Israel has recorded the first case of a rare mixture of two diseases, influenza and coronavirus, dubbed “flurona”. Local reports said that the patient was a young pregnant woman, who was in hospital, although her symptoms were mild. “The disease is the same disease: they’re viral and cause difficulty breathing since both attack the upper respiratory tract,” Prof Vizhnitser added. It is definitely a great challenge dealing with a woman who comes in with a fever at childbirth,” said Prof Vizhnitser.</description></item></channel></rss>