<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stop on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stop/</link><description>Recent content in stop on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:12:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The NFL said it did not attempt to stop Eminem from taking a knee during the Super Bowl LVI halftime show Sunday night in Inglewood, California.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8d6ae9a093e919438c5f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8d6ae9a093e919438c5f/</guid><description>The NFL says it watched &amp;quot;all elements&amp;quot; of Eminem&amp;rsquo;s show in rehearsals and was aware he was going to kneel.
Highlights Eminem took a knee during the Super Bowl LVI halftime show. The NFL says it watched &amp;ldquo;all elements&amp;rdquo; of the show in rehearsals. The Rams won Sunday&amp;rsquo;s game against the Bengals, 23-20, in Los Angeles. Eminem performed with hip-hop heavyweights Dr. Dre, Snoop Dogg, Mary J. Blige and Kendrick Lamar during the well-received halftime show at SoFi Stadium.</description></item><item><title>SpaceX loses 40 satellites to geomagnetic storm a day after launch</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203d9c9b2a3e13296d24fc4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203d9c9b2a3e13296d24fc4/</guid><description>A powerful magnetic storm takes out most of a batch of Starlink satellites the day after launch.
Highlights A powerful magnetic storm takes out most of a batch of Starlink satellites the day after launch. The drag was strong enough to stop the satellites ever getting out of that &amp;ldquo;safe mode&amp;rdquo; and back into orbit they needed to reach to be stable. Instead, &amp;ldquo;up to 40&amp;rdquo; will fall back into the Earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere and burn up.</description></item><item><title>Russia told the US and West to stop supplying arms to Ukraine, saying it's threatening Russia..</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</guid><description>Russia is amassing troops on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border. The US and Ukraine warn of an imminent Russian invasion.
Summary The US and Ukraine have repeatedly warned that Russia appeared to be preparing to invade. The US has also given Ukraine military assistance, including arms and training. The US, Ukraine, and other allies have repeatedly warned that Russia appears to be preparing to invade Ukraine. And Ukraine warned that Russia was almost done gathering enough troops along its border for a possible offensive.</description></item></channel></rss>