<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>stop on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stop/</link><description>Recent content in stop on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 03:04:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/stop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ferdinand Marcos Jr urged to stop pretending he has an Oxford degree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628310a576d1b4d894c00a06/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628310a576d1b4d894c00a06/</guid><description>University has said Philippines leader was awarded ‘special diploma in social studies’ in 1978, not a BA
Highlights Ferdinand Marcos Jr is facing calls to stop misrepresenting the circumstances of his studies at Oxford University. The university has confirmed that he did not complete his BA in Philosophy, Politics and Economics after enrolling in 1975. Marcos Jr has claimed in interviews that Oxford issued him with a bachelor’s degree, while his official spokesperson has said that the politician and his team “stand by the degree confirmation which was issued by the University of Oxford” Marcos failed two of his three preliminary exams at Oxford in the summer of 1976, later doing only enough to pass one of two resits – failing politics for a second time.</description></item><item><title>A 15-year-old boy died by suicide after relentless cyberbullying, and his parents say the Latin School could have done more to stop it</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c3863494177b7445150f7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 19:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626c3863494177b7445150f7/</guid><description>A 15-year-old boy named Nate Bronstein was enrolled at one of the most prestigious private schools in Chicago and had a promising future — that is, until his parents say he became a victim of relentless cyberbullying by his classmates.
Highlights Nate Bronstein, 15, took his own life at the Latin School of Chicago. His parents say he was bullied by classmates at the prestigious private school. They say they were never told about the extent of the bullying.</description></item><item><title>Postal workers hope new law will 'stop the bleeding' at U.S. Postal Service</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eb95f2dc254370c322023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 10:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624eb95f2dc254370c322023/</guid><description>Postal workers in Wisconsin are optimistic that a new law overhauling the U.S. Postal Service and injecting more than $100 billion into the service will help put an end to years of instability in the service.
Highlights Postal Service Reform Act will save money by reducing USPS’s health care costs and eliminating a burdensome federal requirement that the service pre-fund retirees&amp;rsquo; expenses. The bill also makes six-day delivery a matter of law, after some cost-cutting plans could have ended Saturday service.</description></item><item><title>Burger King sued by customers who claim Whopper is smaller than advertised - CBS News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ca31eda55e7d8607e772f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 20:14:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ca31eda55e7d8607e772f/</guid><description>A class-action lawsuit alleges that ads inflate the Whopper&amp;rsquo;s size, making the burger appear 35% bigger than it actually is.
Highlights Four Burger King customers are suing the chain over its marketing practices. The lawsuit alleges that ads inflate the Whopper&amp;rsquo;s size, making it appear 35% bigger than it is in reality. The plaintiffs are seeking monetary damages for those who were &amp;ldquo;deceived&amp;rdquo; by the ads. A Burger King spokesperson says the chain doesn&amp;rsquo;t comment on the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>FTC sues Intuit to stop ‘bait-and-switch’ TurboTax ads</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243c1134440f91d00deb1c4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243c1134440f91d00deb1c4/</guid><description>The Federal Trade Commission is suing TurboTax maker Intuit, saying its ads for “free” tax filing misled consumers. Intuit says it will fight the suit. The consumer protection agency said Tuesday that millions of consumers cannot actually use the free tax-prep software option — two-thirds of tax filers in 2020.
Highlights The consumer protection agency said millions of consumers cannot actually use the free tax-prep software option because they are ineligible for it.</description></item><item><title>UFC Fighter Kevin Holland Helps Stop Gunman In Houston Restaurant Shooting</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231d62b4737427c172c88b0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:21:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6231d62b4737427c172c88b0/</guid><description>The 29-year-old and two other men reportedly stopped a dangerous situation late Monday night.
Highlights UFC fighter Kevin Holland, 29, and two other men reportedly stopped a dangerous situation at a Houston-area restaurant late Monday night. The incident took place around 11:30 p.m. local time when a panic alarm went off at Ra Sushi in Highland Village, Texas. Police say 40-50 people were inside the restaurant when the suspect pulled out a gun and fired one time into the air.</description></item><item><title>CNN to stop broadcasting in Russia after new law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222e3d7db18f478c954d5c2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222e3d7db18f478c954d5c2/</guid><description>CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia, the news channel said on Friday after the introduction of a new law there that could jail anyone intentionally spreading &amp;quot;fake&amp;quot; news.
Highlights Russia has introduced a new law that could jail anyone for spreading &amp;ldquo;fake&amp;rdquo; news. The law was passed by Russian lawmakers in the wake of the Ukraine crisis. CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia while the law is in place. The U.</description></item><item><title>The NFL said it did not attempt to stop Eminem from taking a knee during the Super Bowl LVI halftime show Sunday night in Inglewood, California.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8d6ae9a093e919438c5f/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a8d6ae9a093e919438c5f/</guid><description>The NFL says it watched &amp;quot;all elements&amp;quot; of Eminem&amp;rsquo;s show in rehearsals and was aware he was going to kneel.
Highlights Eminem took a knee during the Super Bowl LVI halftime show. The NFL says it watched &amp;ldquo;all elements&amp;rdquo; of the show in rehearsals. The Rams won Sunday&amp;rsquo;s game against the Bengals, 23-20, in Los Angeles. Eminem performed with hip-hop heavyweights Dr. Dre, Snoop Dogg, Mary J. Blige and Kendrick Lamar during the well-received halftime show at SoFi Stadium.</description></item><item><title>SpaceX loses 40 satellites to geomagnetic storm a day after launch</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203d9c9b2a3e13296d24fc4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6203d9c9b2a3e13296d24fc4/</guid><description>A powerful magnetic storm takes out most of a batch of Starlink satellites the day after launch.
Highlights A powerful magnetic storm takes out most of a batch of Starlink satellites the day after launch. The drag was strong enough to stop the satellites ever getting out of that &amp;ldquo;safe mode&amp;rdquo; and back into orbit they needed to reach to be stable. Instead, &amp;ldquo;up to 40&amp;rdquo; will fall back into the Earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere and burn up.</description></item><item><title>Russia told the US and West to stop supplying arms to Ukraine, saying it's threatening Russia..</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 23:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e8980a5c260071bb4b4a67/</guid><description>Russia is amassing troops on Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s border. The US and Ukraine warn of an imminent Russian invasion.
Summary The US and Ukraine have repeatedly warned that Russia appeared to be preparing to invade. The US has also given Ukraine military assistance, including arms and training. The US, Ukraine, and other allies have repeatedly warned that Russia appears to be preparing to invade Ukraine. And Ukraine warned that Russia was almost done gathering enough troops along its border for a possible offensive.</description></item></channel></rss>