<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>troops on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/troops/</link><description>Recent content in troops on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/troops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kremlin media: Ukraine preparing to attack, not Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2df1ba28cb0e739d8aa32/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 18:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2df1ba28cb0e739d8aa32/</guid><description>The threat of a Russian invasion is &amp;quot;imaginary&amp;quot;, and Ukraine is a failing state, says Russian TV.
Highlights As for the 100,000 Russian troops reportedly massed on the border with Ukraine, they get much less attention. When they do, the message is that Moscow is free to do whatever it likes with its own troops on its own territory. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Ukraine urges calm, saying Russian invasion not imminent</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 21:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f064f918cacd0e7ccdc868/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s leaders sought Tuesday to reassure the nation that an invasion from neighboring Russia was not imminent, even as they acknowledged the threat is real and received a shipment of U.S.
Summary British Prime Minister Boris Johnson also said he is prepared to send troops to protect NATO allies in Europe. Fighting between Ukrainian forces and Russia-backed rebels has killed over 14,000 people, and efforts to reach a settlement have stalled.</description></item><item><title>UK sends 30 elite troops and 2,000 anti-tank weapons to Ukraine amid fears of Russian invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 04:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ea2fdb086631cde065c9cb/</guid><description>British surveillance aircraft have also been spotted as part of a quiet but notable build-up of support to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s military by the UK.
Summary A group of around 30 elite British troops has arrived in Ukraine to help train the Ukrainian armed forces on new anti-tank weapons gifted by the UK amid fears of an imminent, new Russian invasion, Sky News understands. Open source flight-tracking software has plotted Royal Air Force C-17 transport aircraft flying back and forth between the UK and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Kazakhstan president tells troops to 'shoot to kill without warning' as he vows to 'completely eliminate' protesters and gives 'special thanks' to Putin for his help</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da09976841fb5aefc2beaa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da09976841fb5aefc2beaa/</guid><description>Security forces appeared to be in control of the streets of Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s main city Almaty on Friday morning and the president claimed constitutional order had mostly been restored.
Summary Fresh gunshots could be heard in the morning near the city&amp;rsquo;s central square, where troops and protesters had battled through much of the previous day. Kazakh service members stand guard in a square following the protests triggered by fuel price increase in central Almaty, Kazakhstan January 7, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Over 10,000 Russian troops removed from Ukrainian border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cac43934eb8adaee54e55a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cac43934eb8adaee54e55a/</guid><description>The removal of 10,000 Russian troops from the Ukrainian border comes weeks after talks between the White House, NATO and Moscow. Initially, U.S. intelligence reports said Moscow could be ready to invade Ukraine just after the new year. Christina Ruffini has the story.
Summary Over 10,000 Russian troops removed from Ukrainian border The removal of 10,000 Russian troops from the Ukrainian border comes weeks after talks between the White House, NATO and Moscow.</description></item></channel></rss>