<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>troops on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/troops/</link><description>Recent content in troops on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/troops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kazakhstan president tells troops to 'shoot to kill without warning' as he vows to 'completely eliminate' protesters and gives 'special thanks' to Putin for his help</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da09976841fb5aefc2beaa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61da09976841fb5aefc2beaa/</guid><description>Security forces appeared to be in control of the streets of Kazakhstan&amp;rsquo;s main city Almaty on Friday morning and the president claimed constitutional order had mostly been restored.
Summary Fresh gunshots could be heard in the morning near the city&amp;rsquo;s central square, where troops and protesters had battled through much of the previous day. Kazakh service members stand guard in a square following the protests triggered by fuel price increase in central Almaty, Kazakhstan January 7, 2022.</description></item><item><title>Over 10,000 Russian troops removed from Ukrainian border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cac43934eb8adaee54e55a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 08:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cac43934eb8adaee54e55a/</guid><description>The removal of 10,000 Russian troops from the Ukrainian border comes weeks after talks between the White House, NATO and Moscow. Initially, U.S. intelligence reports said Moscow could be ready to invade Ukraine just after the new year. Christina Ruffini has the story.
Summary Over 10,000 Russian troops removed from Ukrainian border The removal of 10,000 Russian troops from the Ukrainian border comes weeks after talks between the White House, NATO and Moscow.</description></item></channel></rss>