<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>die on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/die/</link><description>Recent content in die on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 05:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/die/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bird flu makes jump to mammals: three baby foxes die in Michigan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281dee89b5ad7acaa7c391c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 05:20:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6281dee89b5ad7acaa7c391c/</guid><description>Three red fox kits died from highly pathogenic avian influenza in Michigan, which is the state&amp;rsquo;s first confirmation of the virus in wild mammals. The fox kits came from three separate dens in Lapeer, Macomb and St. Clair counties.
Highlights Three red fox kits died from highly pathogenic avian influenza in Michigan. This is the state&amp;rsquo;s first confirmation of the virus in wild mammals. The kits were observed circling, tremoring and seizing.</description></item><item><title>FOX 11 Los Angeles: 2 maintenance workers die after fentanyl exposure at downtown LA apartment complex.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fc758b7d9f8ec1d8d5e42/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fc758b7d9f8ec1d8d5e42/</guid><description>Two maintenance workers are dead after police believe they may have been exposed to fentanyl at a downtown Los Angeles apartment complex.
Highlights Los Angeles Police Department responded to a hazmat call in the 800 block of South Olive Street a little before 11 a.m. Thursday. When officers arrived at the apartment complex, they found two unconscious men unconscious. Luis Garcia and John Black, who were maintenance workers at the building, were pronounced dead at the scene.</description></item><item><title>Georgia man accused of leaving grandmother in freezer to die</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c20412ef6526eb4670e0b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 14:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625c20412ef6526eb4670e0b/</guid><description>Police say a northwest Georgia man killed his grandmother by stuffing her in a freezer while she was still alive.
Highlights Police say a northwest Georgia man killed his grandmother by stuffing her in a freezer while she was still alive. The body of Doris Cumming, 82, was found late Thursday in the Armuchee home she shared with her grandson, 29-year-old Robert Keith Tincher III. Police say they believe she was injured in a fall in December and that instead of getting her medical attention, he dragged her through home.</description></item><item><title>Pregnant woman, baby die after Russia bombed maternity ward</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f22e291316eae80f265a0/</guid><description>MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned. Images of the woman being rushed to an ambulance on a stretcher had circled the world, epitomizing the horror of an attack on humanity’s most innocent.
Highlights A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned.</description></item></channel></rss>