<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lake on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lake/</link><description>Recent content in lake on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 09:15:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/lake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Archaeological sites once thought lost under Lake Powell reappear</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284b9169849449075f90aed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 09:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6284b9169849449075f90aed/</guid><description>When Lake Powell on the Colorado River first began to fill in the 1960s, it flooded archaeological sites and places with cultural and spiritual significance to Indigenous peoples. Now some of those sites have reemerged as drought shrinks the reservoir. KNAU’s Melissa Sevigny reports, the future of the area is unclear.
Highlights Archaeologists removed what they could before Glen Canyon disappeared beneath Lake Powell. At least a quarter of the sites documented in the Glen Canyon Project still exist and are on dry land again.</description></item><item><title>AZ water future uncertain as leaders deal with severe shortages on Colorado River</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278e9c10afa37d2a7a8e4e3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278e9c10afa37d2a7a8e4e3/</guid><description>Arizona will have to learn to live with less water from the Colorado River.
Highlights A twenty-two-year drought across the West, compounded by climate change has caused historic shortages on the river and the lakes that store it. The river accounts for 40% of Arizona&amp;rsquo;s water supply. Lake Powell sits on the Arizona-Utah border and is the second-largest reservoir on river. But its water level has fallen within 30 feet of dead pool elevation.</description></item><item><title>South Lake Tahoe police say calls about massive bear Hank the Tank are disrupting operations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218652706e83fbe08484056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6218652706e83fbe08484056/</guid><description>South Lake Tahoe police have had it with people calling about the 500-pound bear nicknamed &amp;quot;Hank the Tank.&amp;quot;
Highlights Bear nicknamed Hank the Tank is known in the area for breaking into homes and eating people&amp;rsquo;s food. The 500-pound bear is being blamed for dozens of break-ins since last July. South Lake Tahoe police say they&amp;rsquo;re getting so many calls, it&amp;rsquo;s affecting their ability to take real emergency calls. The department says they have no say in what happens to Hank.</description></item></channel></rss>