<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>past on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/past/</link><description>Recent content in past on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 08:12:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/past/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mark Cuban aims to lower prescription drug prices with online pharmacy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f081e01d3d7035de3a82c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 08:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629f081e01d3d7035de3a82c/</guid><description>People searching for cheaper alternatives to high priced prescription drugs have a new and perhaps unexpected option. It&amp;rsquo;s an online pharmacy founded by Mark Cuban, a billionaire businessman, Shark Tank star and owner of the Dallas Mavericks. His new direct-to-consumer company, Cost Plus Drugs, offers more than 100 generic medications at discounted prices. He joins Geoff Bennett to discuss.
Highlights Mark Cuban&amp;rsquo;s new direct-to-consumer company, Cost Plus Drugs, offers more than 100 generic medications at discounted prices.</description></item><item><title>Zelenskyy 'survives three assassination attempts in past week'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62222cb07315ad90267b81ed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 15:14:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62222cb07315ad90267b81ed/</guid><description>The mercenaries reportedly track Zelenskyy&amp;rsquo;s every movement via his cell phone.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskyy has reportedly survived three assassination attempts in the last week. The Kremlin-backed Wagner Group and Chechen special forces have both attempted to kill the Ukrainian president. The mercenaries are said to have been in Ukraine since January and are tracking Zelenkyy&amp;rsquo;s every movement via his cell phone. Zelenkey has refused to leave Kyiv even when offered help to get out of the country by the US.</description></item></channel></rss>