<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>teen on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teen/</link><description>Recent content in teen on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 09:12:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man died parachuting from San Diego high-rise as teen daughter watched, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ed8e818450e06414b662a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 09:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ed8e818450e06414b662a/</guid><description>A man was killed after attempting to parachute from the top of a high-rise apartment building in San Diego as his 16-year-old daughter watched, police said.
Highlights The 48-year-old man was attempting to parachute from the 23-story Palisade UTC luxury apartment complex. 911 caller heard a ‘loud pop’ similar to a gunshot, looked over balcony and saw the man bleeding on the ground. Police believe that his daughter was up on the rooftop with him, and was able to view what happened.</description></item><item><title>Man ‘playing with gun’ kills pregnant teen, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</guid><description>Deputies allege the suspect was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back.
Highlights Chad Blackard faces several charges, including negligent homicide, third-degree feticide and illegal use of weapons. 17-year-old Karrington Smith was 25 weeks pregnant at the time, and her unborn child also died. Deputies say Blackard was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back. Blackard told deputies when he tried to reposition the gun, it “went off.</description></item><item><title>Parents of teen charged in school shooting to stand trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621849448fcfdc1d906600e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621849448fcfdc1d906600e5/</guid><description>A judge on Thursday ordered the parents of a 15-year-old boy charged with killing four students at his Michigan high school to stand trial on involuntary manslaughter charges.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley is charged as an adult with first-degree murder, assault with intent to murder, terrorism and gun charges in the Nov. 30 shooting at Oxford High School. The 15-year-old is accused of killing four students and a teacher at the Michigan school.</description></item></channel></rss>