<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>teen on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teen/</link><description>Recent content in teen on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:12:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/teen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>State trooper who shot, killed New Haven teen in 2020 arrested</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62605af434eec5f93f8564ad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 19:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62605af434eec5f93f8564ad/</guid><description>It was unclear Tuesday evening what exactly the trooper was charged with. He turned&amp;hellip;
Highlights Brian North turned himself in to the inspector general at Troop I in Bethany around 7:30 p.m. Tuesday. He was released on a $50,000 bond and scheduled to appear in Superior Court in Milford on May 3. Mubarak Soulemane, 19, was shot and killed on Jan. 15, 2020, after he allegedly showed a knife at an AT&amp;amp;T store in Norwalk and carjacked a ride share driver.</description></item><item><title>Southern California woman who accused Black teen of stealing phone, pleads guilty to hate crime charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255ddb34392a0bec8121f93/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6255ddb34392a0bec8121f93/</guid><description>Miya Ponsetto, 23, pleads guilty to unlawful imprisonment in the second degree as a hate crime. She falsely accused Keyon Harrold Jr. of stealing her cell phone and then attacking him in a New York
Highlights Miya Ponsetto pleads guilty to unlawful imprisonment in the second degree as a hate crime. She falsely accused Keyon Harrold Jr. of stealing her cell phone and then attacking him in a New York hotel lobby.</description></item><item><title>Non-verbal teen lost in L.A. area woods found after clinking rocks together, alerting rescuers</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d14026dac76a05bbb067f/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 04:16:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624d14026dac76a05bbb067f/</guid><description>A non-verbal teen who was lost in a heavily wooded area near Los Angeles was after rescuers followed the sound made by his favorite objects — rocks.
Highlights The 16-year-old was found in a canyon near Los Angeles after he ran off into trees. Rescuers heard him clinking rocks as he threw them together. He was treated by paramedics and released to his family, authorities said. The sheriff&amp;rsquo;s department said it was &amp;ldquo;thrilled this incident had a happy ending,&amp;rdquo; adding: &amp;ldquo;Our Department was thrilled this incident has a good ending&amp;rdquo; The boy, 16, was found &amp;ldquo;sitting under an oak tree,&amp;rdquo; a sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputy said at a news conference in Los Angeles County, California, said he was &amp;ldquo;lucky&amp;rdquo; to find him after six hours of searching for him.</description></item><item><title>Teen is arrested after posting on social media with drugs, money, guns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62497366e3b2cc0b8df68d95/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 10:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62497366e3b2cc0b8df68d95/</guid><description>SAN ANTONIO (WOAI) — Deputies arrested a teen after he posted images on social media with drugs, money and guns. Teen is arrested after posting on social media with drugs, money, and guns (Photo Courtesy of Bexar County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office) The incident happened Tuesday, March 29, when David Anakin Guerra, 17 posted on social media that he had THC cartridges, weapons and cash.
Highlights Deputies arrested a teen after he posted images on social media with drugs, money and guns.</description></item><item><title>Man died parachuting from San Diego high-rise as teen daughter watched, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ed8e818450e06414b662a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 09:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ed8e818450e06414b662a/</guid><description>A man was killed after attempting to parachute from the top of a high-rise apartment building in San Diego as his 16-year-old daughter watched, police said.
Highlights The 48-year-old man was attempting to parachute from the 23-story Palisade UTC luxury apartment complex. 911 caller heard a ‘loud pop’ similar to a gunshot, looked over balcony and saw the man bleeding on the ground. Police believe that his daughter was up on the rooftop with him, and was able to view what happened.</description></item><item><title>Man ‘playing with gun’ kills pregnant teen, deputies say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 18:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622f866cfb272f2cf6566700/</guid><description>Deputies allege the suspect was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back.
Highlights Chad Blackard faces several charges, including negligent homicide, third-degree feticide and illegal use of weapons. 17-year-old Karrington Smith was 25 weeks pregnant at the time, and her unborn child also died. Deputies say Blackard was “playing with the handgun” when it discharged, hitting the victim in the back. Blackard told deputies when he tried to reposition the gun, it “went off.</description></item><item><title>Parents of teen charged in school shooting to stand trial</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621849448fcfdc1d906600e5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621849448fcfdc1d906600e5/</guid><description>A judge on Thursday ordered the parents of a 15-year-old boy charged with killing four students at his Michigan high school to stand trial on involuntary manslaughter charges.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley is charged as an adult with first-degree murder, assault with intent to murder, terrorism and gun charges in the Nov. 30 shooting at Oxford High School. The 15-year-old is accused of killing four students and a teacher at the Michigan school.</description></item></channel></rss>