<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>french on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/french/</link><description>Recent content in french on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 21:12:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/french/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>France: Four neo-Nazis arrested for planning 'Jew hunt' during soccer match</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bca879668686dd7523827/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 21:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629bca879668686dd7523827/</guid><description>The men, aged between 45-53, were affiliated with far-right neo-Nazi groups and had intended on &amp;quot;hunting Jews&amp;quot; during a soccer match in Strasbourg.
Highlights Four neo-Nazi men in France&amp;rsquo;s Alsace region were indicted for possessing and trafficking an &amp;ldquo;impressive&amp;rdquo; amount of weapons that were intended for use against Jews, prosecutor Edwige Roux-Morizot said on Friday. The men, aged between 45-53, had intended on &amp;ldquo;hunting Jews&amp;rdquo; during a soccer match in Strasbourg, she said.</description></item><item><title>French President Emmanuel Macron said he “really wants to piss off” the unvaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d517e13adecc797b78cc9c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 04:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d517e13adecc797b78cc9c/</guid><description>French President Emmanuel Macron raised eyebrows and provoked a fair amount of shock on Tuesday when he warned people in France not yet vaccinated against Covid-19 that he would annoy them by limiting access to key aspects of life in the country.
Summary “I don’t want to piss the French people off… But as for the non-vaccinated, I really want to piss them off (emmerder). You will no longer be able to go for a coffee, you will no longer be able to go to the theatre.</description></item><item><title>Covid-19: French MPs get death threats over support for vaccine pass that would bar the unvaccinated from much of public life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 15:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d4610f7a7699d1fdbb04b1/</guid><description>They report the threats as they consider tougher restrictions on unvaccinated people in France.
Summary In an interview with BFM TV, she said she had reported the threats to the police and would not be deterred from supporting the vaccine pass. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>That’s a wrap: French plastic packaging ban for fruit and veg begins</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf99a95a79d35167885f01/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf99a95a79d35167885f01/</guid><description>Law bans sale of carrots, bananas and other items in plastic as environment groups urge other countries to follow
Summary Spain will introduce a ban on plastic packaging of fruit and vegetables from 2023. For years, international campaigners have said unnecessary plastic packaging is causing environmental damage and pollution at sea. From New Year’s Day, France will ban supermarkets and other shops from selling cucumbers wrapped in plastic, and peppers, courgettes, aubergines and leeks in plastic packaging.</description></item></channel></rss>