<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jones on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jones/</link><description>Recent content in jones on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:32:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/jones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandy Hook families defamed by Alex Jones want him to pay their legal fees fighting his ‘sham’ bankruptcy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1f640b048304815a9edad/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 13:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a1f640b048304815a9edad/</guid><description>Families of victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting say they want to be reimbursed for fighting Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; &amp;quot;sham&amp;quot; bankruptcy.
Highlights Sandy Hook families won three defamation cases against Alex Jones in Connecticut, Texas. They say Jones&amp;rsquo; bankruptcy filing was a &amp;ldquo;calculated stunt&amp;rdquo; to avoid jury trials. The families want state judges to make Jones pay their legal costs for the 45 days they had to fight his &amp;ldquo;sham&amp;rdquo; filing in federal court.</description></item><item><title>The top elected official in Texas’ smallest county has been charged with cattle theft</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289b82c48c13617ffcd2c32/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 04:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6289b82c48c13617ffcd2c32/</guid><description>Loving County Judge Skeet Jones, the scion of a powerful ranching family, was arrested after a yearlong investigation that is ongoing, authorities said.
Highlights Judge Skeet Jones, 71, is facing three felony counts of livestock theft and one count of engaging in criminal activity. He is accused of gathering up and selling stray cattle in Loving County, Texas. The county has no school, no church, no grocery store and no bank, population 57 as of the last U.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones back on the hook for damages after bankruptcy judge sends Sandy Hook cases to Texas court</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62886660069aa21ece71281f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 04:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62886660069aa21ece71281f/</guid><description>The bankruptcy judge’s ruling means the Texas trial to determine what Alex Jones owes&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones&amp;rsquo; defamation cases are sent back to state court in Texas, where the parents of two boys slain in the Sandy Hook massacre await jury trials to see how much Jones owes them. Jones&amp;rsquo; bankruptcy filing put on hold the two trials in Texas and the third in Connecticut, since federal court trumps state proceedings.</description></item><item><title>Marcel Fontaine, falsely accused of being the Parkland shooter by Alex Jones, dies in apartment fire. He sued Jones and Infowars, paving the way for lawsuits by Sandy Hook parents.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286a42f7ad83437bea01c80/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 20:11:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6286a42f7ad83437bea01c80/</guid><description>Former Norwalk resident Marcel Fontaine, who filed one of the first defamation lawsuits&amp;hellip;
Highlights Marcel Fontaine, 29, was among four people killed in a fire early Saturday in Worcester, Mass., authorities say. Fontaine filed a defamation lawsuit against Alex Jones for falsely identifying him as the shooter at Stoneman Douglas High School in Florida. The lawsuit, which is considered one of the first filed against Jones, is scheduled to go to trial in about a month.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families can resume defamation lawsuits vs InfoWars owner, attorneys say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fe4567c322dfc0e69381c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 17:18:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627fe4567c322dfc0e69381c/</guid><description>Families of the victims of the 2012 Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre will be dismissed from the InfoWars bankruptcy case, allowing them to resume their defamation lawsuits against the website&amp;rsquo;s owner, conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, attorneys said in court on Friday.
Highlights Families of the victims of the 2012 Sandy Hook Elementary School massacre will be dismissed from the InfoWars bankruptcy case. They will be able to resume their defamation lawsuits against the website&amp;rsquo;s owner, conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, attorneys said in court on Friday.</description></item><item><title>1 dead, several injured in shooting at Mississippi Mudbug Festival, sheriff says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f067a09b1d93aa6366652/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 22:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626f067a09b1d93aa6366652/</guid><description>One person has died and five others have been injured at the Mississippi Mudbug Festival, Hinds County Sheriff Tyree Jones said on Twitter late Saturday.
Highlights One person died and five others were injured at the Mississippi Mudbug Festival in Jackson, authorities say. The person who died is suspected to have been one of the shooters, officials say. Two juveniles have been detained, but no charges have been filed in the incident.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones’ attorney Norm Pattis defends using racial slur in comedy act caught on video</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62676140a4fd7c5c9d1463d1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 03:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62676140a4fd7c5c9d1463d1/</guid><description>The attorney known for defending high-profile clients like Alex Jones and Fotis Dulos is&amp;hellip;
Highlights Norm Pattis defended his use of racist and homophobic slurs during a stand-up show at a restaurant last month. Pattis was caught on camera insulting Black Lives Matter activists, interracial couples, gay people and transgender individuals. In a blog post on Wednesday, Pattis wrote that the comments were directed at the “new high priests and priestesses of identity politics” whom he called a social cancer on the body politic.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones after CT deposition in Sandy Hook defamation case: ‘I could have done a better job’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f622a41d64e74d5897f29/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 22:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624f622a41d64e74d5897f29/</guid><description>Alex Jones sat for depositions on Tuesday and Wednesday in the Sandy Hook case, ending&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones sat for a second day of questioning under oath in the Sandy Hook defamation case on Wednesday. Jones said in a video that he was being demonized for falsely reporting that the worst crime in modern Connecticut history never happened. Jones flew to Connecticut this week from the Texas headquarters of his “Infowars” internet program.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones avoids jail, faces escalating $25K daily fine until he complies with Sandy Hook testimony order</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244e418430dee843ab53bd3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 23:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6244e418430dee843ab53bd3/</guid><description>The fine, which could accumulate into six figures in as quickly as four days, was imposed&amp;hellip;
Highlights Alex Jones faces escalating daily fine of $25,000 for &amp;ldquo;intentionally failing to comply with the orders of the court” Judge Barbara Bellis also held him in contempt of court. The fine, which could accumulate into six figures in as quickly as four days, was imposed Wednesday. Bellis could have issued an order for Jones’ arrest to compel him to testify.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families reject Alex Jones settlement offer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243d971dd15a452375a2b70/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 04:16:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6243d971dd15a452375a2b70/</guid><description>HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — Infowars host Alex Jones offered to pay $120,000 per plaintiff to resolve a lawsuit by relatives of Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting victims who said he defamed them by asserting the massacre never happened, according to court filings Tuesday.
Highlights Infowars host Alex Jones offered to pay $120,000 per plaintiff to resolve lawsuit by relatives of Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting victims. Relatives said he defamed them by asserting the massacre never happened, according to court filings.</description></item><item><title>Sandy Hook families seek Alex Jones arrest after 2nd no-show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e6309148241c2ccd593bb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:49:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623e6309148241c2ccd593bb/</guid><description>Relatives of some victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting are asking a Connecticut judge to order the arrest of Infowars host Alex Jones for missing a court-ordered deposition this week
Highlights Relatives of some victims of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting are asking a Connecticut judge to order the arrest of Infowars host Alex Jones for missing a court-ordered deposition this week. Jones missed both days of a scheduled deposition Wednesday and Thursday in Austin, Texas.</description></item><item><title>Alex Jones met with 1/6 committee and says he pleaded the Fifth ‘almost 100 times’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0b94e81066c404de9d405/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 03:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0b94e81066c404de9d405/</guid><description>Summary By Annie Grayer and Oliver Darcy, CNNRight-wing conspiracy theorist Alex Jones met virtually on Monday with the House select committee investigating the January 6 insurrection, he announced on his broadcast. “I just had a very intense experience being interrogated by the January 6 committee,” Jones said on his broadcast on Monday. Jones also relayed on Monday that the committee had asked him whether he had heard of any plans for violence on January 6.</description></item></channel></rss>