<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>study on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/study/</link><description>Recent content in study on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Study finds Western megadrought is the worst in 1,200 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ae1ac91656a521e5d6581/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ae1ac91656a521e5d6581/</guid><description>In tree ring records dating back to AD 800, the only multidecade drought that came close to today&amp;rsquo;s was in the 1500s. Researchers say climate change is a factor and the U.S. must plan for less water.
Highlights Study finds Western megadrought is the worst in 1,200 years, according to new study. Western U.S. and northern Mexico are experiencing their driest period in at least 1,000 years. Federal water managers declared the first-ever water shortage along the Colorado River last year.</description></item><item><title>Multiple sclerosis caused by Epstein-Barr-Virus — study: Researchers say Epstein-Barr-Virus is a main cause of MS, which affects 2.8 million people worldwide. New treatments and prevention may now be possible</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e166079eb8286c8eccaa6f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e166079eb8286c8eccaa6f/</guid><description>Researchers say Epstein-Barr-Virus is a main cause of MS, which affects 2.8 million people worldwide. New treatments and prevention may now be possible.
Summary Multiple sclerosis (MS) is an unpredictable condition — an autoimmune disease that attacks the central nervous system, the brain and spinal cord. The link between Epstein-Barr-Virus and MSIn a study conducted in the United States, researchers say they found that the Epstein-Barr-Virus (EBV) was definitely associated with all but one of 801 cases of multiple sclerosis.</description></item></channel></rss>