<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>study on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/study/</link><description>Recent content in study on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 08:16:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Researchers Pinpoint Reason Infants Die From SIDS</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cc251a8ff8a6061c42d90/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 08:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627cc251a8ff8a6061c42d90/</guid><description>Researchers from The Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital Westmead in Sydney, Australia released a study that confirmed not only how infants die from sudden infant death syndrome, but why.
Highlights Sudden infant death syndrome accounts for 37% of sudden unexpected infant deaths a year in the U.S. Researchers from The Children&amp;rsquo;s Hospital Westmead in Sydney, Australia released a study that confirmed not only how infants die from SIDS, but why. The study found activity of the enzyme butyryrylcholinesterase (BChE) was significantly lower in babies who died of SIDS compared to living infants and other non-SIDS infant deaths.</description></item><item><title>There are only 10 of the world's smallest marine mammal left in the world</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627907e2c58c99ef614806fb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627907e2c58c99ef614806fb/</guid><description>The world&amp;rsquo;s smallest marine mammal is so critically endangered that there are only about 10 left in its sole habitat of Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Gulf of California. But that may not yet spell doom for the vaquita porpoise, according to new research.
Highlights The world&amp;rsquo;s smallest marine mammal is so critically endangered that there are only about 10 remaining in its habitat in Mexico&amp;rsquo;s Gulf of California. The vaquitas have been pushed to the brink of going extinct due to illegal gillnetting, which is used to capture shrimp and totoaba fish that share the same habitat as the porpoises.</description></item><item><title>Microplastics found deep in lungs of living people for first time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dae51ba412bfae4ac2197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624dae51ba412bfae4ac2197/</guid><description>Particles discovered in tissue of 11 out of 13 patients undergoing surgery, with polypropylene and PET most common
Highlights Microplastic pollution found in almost all lung tissue taken from 13 patients undergoing surgery. Polyethylene, used in plastic bags, was one of the most common particles. Microplastics were detected in human blood for the first time in March, showing the particles can travel around the body and may lodge in organs. The impact on human health is as yet unknown, but researchers are concerned as microplastics cause damage to human cells in the laboratory and air pollution particles are already known to enter the body.</description></item><item><title>Even mild Covid is linked to brain damage months after illness, scans show</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622674fee966cacf67496df6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622674fee966cacf67496df6/</guid><description>How Covid infection affects the brain: Even mild cases of Covid-19 are associated with subtle tissue damage and accelerated losses in brain volume, study shows.
Highlights Covid-19 is associated with subtle tissue damage and accelerated losses in brain regions tied to the sense of smell, a new study finds. Having mild Covid is also associated with a cognitive function deficit. The research was published Monday in Nature. It is the first study of the disease’s potential impact on the brain that is based on brain scans taken both before and after participants contracted the coronavirus.</description></item><item><title>Scientists propose Tyrannosaurus had three species, not just 'rex'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e381194cfbdff93ca18b1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e381194cfbdff93ca18b1/</guid><description>A group of researchers is proposing that Tyrannosaurus, the most famous of all dinosaurs and the ultimate apex predator, actually includes three species and not just the single T. rex, based on thighbone and tooth variations among dozens of its fossils.
Highlights Researchers propose that Tyrannosaurus, the most famous of all dinosaurs, actually includes three species. T. rex, meaning &amp;ldquo;tyrant lizard king,&amp;rdquo; has been the sole species of the genus Tyrannosaurus recognized since the dinosaur was first described in 1905.</description></item><item><title>Study finds Western megadrought is the worst in 1,200 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ae1ac91656a521e5d6581/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 23:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620ae1ac91656a521e5d6581/</guid><description>In tree ring records dating back to AD 800, the only multidecade drought that came close to today&amp;rsquo;s was in the 1500s. Researchers say climate change is a factor and the U.S. must plan for less water.
Highlights Study finds Western megadrought is the worst in 1,200 years, according to new study. Western U.S. and northern Mexico are experiencing their driest period in at least 1,000 years. Federal water managers declared the first-ever water shortage along the Colorado River last year.</description></item><item><title>Multiple sclerosis caused by Epstein-Barr-Virus — study: Researchers say Epstein-Barr-Virus is a main cause of MS, which affects 2.8 million people worldwide. New treatments and prevention may now be possible</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e166079eb8286c8eccaa6f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e166079eb8286c8eccaa6f/</guid><description>Researchers say Epstein-Barr-Virus is a main cause of MS, which affects 2.8 million people worldwide. New treatments and prevention may now be possible.
Summary Multiple sclerosis (MS) is an unpredictable condition — an autoimmune disease that attacks the central nervous system, the brain and spinal cord. The link between Epstein-Barr-Virus and MSIn a study conducted in the United States, researchers say they found that the Epstein-Barr-Virus (EBV) was definitely associated with all but one of 801 cases of multiple sclerosis.</description></item></channel></rss>