<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trans on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trans/</link><description>Recent content in trans on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:35:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/trans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alabama ban on gender-affirming care for transgender youth takes effect</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62791893fb2f9e68b3b85713/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62791893fb2f9e68b3b85713/</guid><description>An Alabama law that makes it a felony to provide gender-affirming medical treatment to transgender youth went into effect on Sunday while a federal judge weighs whether to grant a motion to put a temporary hold on it.
Highlights Alabama law that makes it a felony to provide gender-affirming medical treatment to transgender youth went into effect on Sunday. A federal judge weighs whether to grant a motion to put a temporary hold on it.</description></item><item><title>Trans people can be excluded from single-sex services if ‘justifiable’, says EHRC</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b6d55ca5efb9b6221a543/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 22:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b6d55ca5efb9b6221a543/</guid><description>UK government’s equalities watchdog says justifications could include reasons of privacy or health and safety
Highlights Equality and Human Rights Commission issues guidance on single-sex services. Transgender people can be legitimately excluded from services if the reasons are ‘justifiable and proportionate’ The guidance, published on Monday, is intended to help organisations such as hospitals, retailers, hospitality and sports clubs implement policies that are both legal and balance the needs of different groups.</description></item></channel></rss>