<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>companies on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/companies/</link><description>Recent content in companies on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:11:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/companies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tesla removed from S&amp;amp;P 500 ESG Index, prompting Musk fury</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628617a4ddfd2c410d9c0440/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 10:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628617a4ddfd2c410d9c0440/</guid><description>An S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones Indices executive said it had removed Tesla from the S&amp;amp;P 500 ESG Index because of issues including claims of racial discrimination and crashes linked to its autopilot vehicles.
Highlights S&amp;amp;P Dow Jones Indices says it has removed electric carmaker Tesla from the widely followed index. Tesla CEO Elon Musk responded with harsh tweets including that &amp;ldquo;ESG is a scam&amp;rdquo; The back-and-forth over the index changes reflects a wider debate about the metrics used to judge corporate performance on environmental, social and governance (ESG) issues.</description></item><item><title>Revealed: top US corporations raising prices on Americans even as profits surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62697beba7247058163f5aee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 17:23:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62697beba7247058163f5aee/</guid><description>A Guardian analysis uncovers how companies enriched themselves and their investors while boasting about jacking up prices
Highlights Analysis of 100 US corporations finds profits up by 49% and 111,000%. All but ten executed massive stock buyback programs or bumped dividends to enrich investors. Hershey’s net profits spiked 62% between the fourth quarters in 2019 and 2021, its operating margin widened. Inflation, meanwhile, rose to 8.5% year over year in March; inflation hit a new peak in March, eating into most Americans’ wages and further imperiling the financially vulnerable.</description></item><item><title>$10 toothpaste? U.S. household goods makers face blowback on price hikes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f34f8c5f64b2ee7524bf7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 09:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f34f8c5f64b2ee7524bf7/</guid><description>Get ready for the $10 tube of toothpaste.
Highlights Colgate-Palmolive CEO Noel Wallace said Colgate&amp;rsquo;s new Optic White Pro Series toothpaste is the type of premium product &amp;ldquo;vital&amp;rdquo; to its ability to raise prices. Some lawmakers and consumer advocates argue that companies are excessively raising prices in order to fuel profits and return money to shareholders. Target said on Tuesday in an earnings call that bumping up pricing is the last lever it pulls when faced with increased costs.</description></item><item><title>Alberta towing companies reject requests to supply trucks to RCMP</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcd17f97a599df106bd952/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 07:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fcd17f97a599df106bd952/</guid><description>“A lot of these smaller companies don’t want to ruin their reputation in the communities they serve so they don’t want to get involved.” Recommended for you Plans underway for farm-tractor convoy from Alexandria to Ottawa Trump responds to Biden attacks in Jan. 6 speech – here’s what he said 7-Year-Old Injured By Tornado Which […]
Highlights A number of towing companies in southern Alberta have been approached to help remove trucks from the Coutts border blockade.</description></item><item><title>Two-thirds of anti-vax propaganda online created by just 12 influencers, research finds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eebf090fd36e18585676cb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 15:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61eebf090fd36e18585676cb/</guid><description>Jokes on Instagram and Tik Tok continue to affect young people, experts say - while warning over the dangers of labelling as anti-vaxxers those who are vaccine hesitant.
Summary Two-thirds of anti-vaccination propaganda posted online is created by just 12 so-called influencers, research has found. Please use Chrome browser for a more accessible video player 2:49 Boris Johnson has previously spoken out against anti-vaxxersAfter social media companies were made aware of the prevalence of the material some was removed, but many videos and articles remain online today.</description></item><item><title>Chinese companies vanish from world's top 10 by market cap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c24067198006ba3442e83c/</guid><description>Description TOKYO &amp;ndash; Tencent Holdings and Alibaba Group Holding have dropped out of the global top 10 companies in market capitalization, new data shows, leaving
Summary Alibaba Group Holding founder Jack Ma, then executive chairman, celebrates at the New York Stock Exchange on Sept. 19, 2014, the day that the company held its initial public offering and began trading there. © Getty ImagesMANAMI OGAWA, Nikkei staff writer READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>