<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>life on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/life/</link><description>Recent content in life on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:16:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pennsylvania man charged in killing of Uber driver who begged for her life</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211c076d3569ae4f6d0f37e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:16:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6211c076d3569ae4f6d0f37e/</guid><description>A Pennsylvania man is accused of killing an Uber driver who vanished last week in what authorities described Friday as a fatal robbery.
Highlights Christina Spicuzza, 38, disappeared Feb. 10 after driving for Uber in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. She was found dead from a single gunshot wound, police say. A dash cam inside her car captured Crew allegedly pointing a gun at her neck as she drove. Crew allegedly tried to transfer money to his girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s phone, a criminal complaint says.</description></item><item><title>SoCal man gets life for killing 2 women with meat cleaver as wife, son waited in car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffbc230f72e3b3986275c5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffbc230f72e3b3986275c5/</guid><description>Christopher Ken Ireland killed two women with a meat cleaver after a New Year’s Eve party in 2017 while his wife and son waited in a car outside. He was sentenced Friday to life in prison without the possibility of parole.
Highlights Christopher Ken Ireland killed two women with a meat cleaver after a New Year’s Eve party in 2017 while his wife and 11-year-old son waited in a car outside.</description></item><item><title>Mexican journalist who told president she feared for her life shot dead</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efd85c1236c67fb3adec2e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 11:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61efd85c1236c67fb3adec2e/</guid><description>Journalist Lourdes Maldonado López was killed in the Mexican border city of Tijuana on Sunday, days after news photographer Margarito Martínez was gunned down at his home there.
Summary Journalist Lourdes Maldonado López was killed in the Mexican border city of Tijuana on Sunday, days after news photographer Margarito Martínez was gunned down at his home there. According to local news reports, Maldonado was found dead of one gunshot inside a car outside her home.</description></item><item><title>E.O. Wilson, naturalist dubbed a modern-day Darwin, dies at 92</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca8ca75c77cef8ec2c31af/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca8ca75c77cef8ec2c31af/</guid><description>E.O. Wilson, an American naturalist dubbed the modern day Darwin whose interest in ants led him to conclusions about human nature being directed by genetics rather than culture, died on Sunday at the age of 92, his foundation said.
Summary Wilson, an American naturalist dubbed the modern day Darwin whose interest in ants led him to conclusions about human nature being directed by genetics rather than culture, died on Sunday at the age of 92, his foundation said.</description></item></channel></rss>