<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>set on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/set/</link><description>Recent content in set on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:10:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/set/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Police suspect arson in fire at Wyoming abortion clinic site</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291caab4cdc92f3f00e1212/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6291caab4cdc92f3f00e1212/</guid><description>Police believe an overnight fire in Wyoming that damaged a building being renovated to house a new abortion clinic was deliberately set
Highlights Fire damaged building being renovated to house abortion clinic in Casper, Wyoming. Clinic was set to open in June as only the second place in the state to offer abortions. Clinic organizers had been receiving harassing emails and telephone messages. No injuries were reported; police are reviewing video footage from the area in hopes of identifying the suspect.</description></item><item><title>Twitter set to accept ‘best and final offer’ of Elon Musk</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266acba63a9d45c947a6449/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6266acba63a9d45c947a6449/</guid><description>Twitter Inc is poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, the price the chief executive of Tesla Inc has called his &amp;quot;best and final&amp;quot; offer for the social media company, people familiar with the matter said.
Highlights Twitter poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, people familiar with the matter said. Twitter may announce the $54.20-per-share deal later on Monday once its board has met to recommend the transaction to Twitter shareholders.</description></item><item><title>Unseen JRR Tolkien paintings, photographs and video clips released</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aca3f5e420779fe720d02/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 00:48:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621aca3f5e420779fe720d02/</guid><description>Estate of Lord of the Rings author also publishes unseen draft manuscripts and letters on its website
Highlights Estate of JRR Tolkien, author of Lord of the Rings fantasy books, relaunched website. Unseen photographs and paintings of Tolkien have been released by the writer’s estate. It also publishes unseen draft manuscripts and letters on its website. Audio recordings and video clips of Tolkien and his son Christopher are among the new material.</description></item><item><title>Melbourne man sets himself on fire while screaming about Dan Andrews' Covid vaccine mandates</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</guid><description>A man has lit himself on fire in front of horrified diners in Richmond on Saturday while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates.
Summary A man has set himself and his car on fire in front of horrified diners while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates. The man emerged from a silver MG3 hatchback engulfed in flames near Church St in Richmond about 8pm on Saturday. A man has set himself and his MG3 hatch on fire in Richmond while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 mandates on Saturday (pictured)The bystanders helped restrain the man before police officers pinned him to the ground.</description></item><item><title>Alaska reached temperatures warmer than Southern California in December</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf8b966c5aaf2a4bddbdb6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf8b966c5aaf2a4bddbdb6/</guid><description>Kodiak Island in southern Alaska set a record for the warmest December day at 67 degrees. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bill Weir has more on the unusual warm temperatures many Americans are experiencing this holiday season.
Summary Kodiak Island in southern Alaska set a record for the warmest December day at 67 degrees. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bill Weir has more on the unusual warm temperatures many Americans are experiencing this holiday season. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>