<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>set on Reddit News</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/set/</link><description>Recent content in set on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/categories/set/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Melbourne man sets himself on fire while screaming about Dan Andrews' Covid vaccine mandates</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 23:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61d0dd1ba0cb361233349814/</guid><description>A man has lit himself on fire in front of horrified diners in Richmond on Saturday while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates.
Summary A man has set himself and his car on fire in front of horrified diners while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 vaccine mandates. The man emerged from a silver MG3 hatchback engulfed in flames near Church St in Richmond about 8pm on Saturday. A man has set himself and his MG3 hatch on fire in Richmond while screaming about Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 mandates on Saturday (pictured)The bystanders helped restrain the man before police officers pinned him to the ground.</description></item><item><title>Alaska reached temperatures warmer than Southern California in December</title><link>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cf8b966c5aaf2a4bddbdb6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gabrielepicco.github.io/reddit-news/p/61cf8b966c5aaf2a4bddbdb6/</guid><description>Kodiak Island in southern Alaska set a record for the warmest December day at 67 degrees. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bill Weir has more on the unusual warm temperatures many Americans are experiencing this holiday season.
Summary Kodiak Island in southern Alaska set a record for the warmest December day at 67 degrees. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bill Weir has more on the unusual warm temperatures many Americans are experiencing this holiday season. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>