<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mothers on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mothers/</link><description>Recent content in mothers on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mothers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vermont man accused of killing mom, grandfather in attempt to get millions in inheritance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bac21884a163cd02193aa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:29:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bac21884a163cd02193aa/</guid><description>A 28-year-old Vermont man is accused of killing his grandfather to obtain trust fund money and later killing his mother while they were at sea for a purported
Highlights Nathan Carman, 28, is accused of killing his grandfather to obtain trust fund money. His mother, Linda, disappeared during a 2016 fishing trip on her son&amp;rsquo;s boat, prosecutors say. He is expected to be arraigned Wednesday in U.S. District Court in Rutland, Vermont.</description></item><item><title>Kentucky man, 22, shoots mom after dispute over Xbox controller on Mother’s Day, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a9fe136294392194c0e03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 17:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a9fe136294392194c0e03/</guid><description>A Kentucky man has been arrested after shooting his mother on Mother’s Day following a dispute over an Xbox controller he gave her as a gift, officials say.
Highlights Jacob R. Small, of Monticello, Kentucky, was charged with attempted murder, first-degree assault and second-degree criminal mischief. Small told authorities he got into a verbal dispute with his mother over an Xbox controller he gave her as a Mother’s Day gift. The mother was treated at the Wayne County Hospital and transferred to the University of Kentucky Hospital for further treatment.</description></item><item><title>Toddler Shoots Mother, Infant Sibling at Granbury, Texas Walmart</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d73cfc46f7dda712559f72/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d73cfc46f7dda712559f72/</guid><description>A toddler accidentally shot his mother and infant sibling outside a Granbury, Texas Walmart Wednesday, police said.
Summary A woman and her infant child are injured after a toddler accidentally fired a gun in a car parked outside a Granbury Walmart on Wednesday morning. Police said a 1-year-old child and a 3-month-old child were inside a vehicle at the time of the incident. The mother of the children, a 23-year-old woman, was standing outside next to the driver’s door while their father, a 26-year-old man, was standing at the rear of the truck.</description></item></channel></rss>