<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>leave on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/leave/</link><description>Recent content in leave on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:19:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/leave/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lithuania expels Russian ambassador, downgrades diplomatic ties</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b1a7747e04a77047dc816/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:19:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b1a7747e04a77047dc816/</guid><description>On Monday, Lithuania downgraded its diplomatic ties with Russia and ordered the ambassador to leave the country.
Highlights Lithuania downgrades diplomatic ties with Russia and orders ambassador to leave country. Russian consulate in Klaipėda ordered to close, while Lithuania’s current ambassador to Moscow will also return to the country. Foreign Minister Gabrielius Landsbergis said: &amp;ldquo;The brutality of the Russian occupation forces has gone beyond any norms of the civilised world&amp;rdquo; Lithuania also ordered the Lithuanian ambassador to Ukraine to return to Kyiv, while the ambassador to Russia is returning to Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>New York City to try installing subway barriers after attacks leave riders on edge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621802e703db442705631c6e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 22:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621802e703db442705631c6e/</guid><description>New York City will experiment with installing barriers or doors on a few subway platforms, the city&amp;rsquo;s transit chief said on Wednesday, with residents on edge over a rise in violence against riders.
Highlights New York City will experiment with installing barriers or doors on a few subway platforms, transit chief says. Move comes five weeks after a 40-year-old woman, Michelle Go, was struck and killed by a train at the Times Square subway station.</description></item><item><title>Russia evacuating diplomatic staff from Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208e70ecb4bcf5d9af06d49/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 11:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6208e70ecb4bcf5d9af06d49/</guid><description>Move follows US warning that a Russian invasion is imminent
Highlights Russian diplomats and consular officers in Ukraine have begun to leave for Russia, state-owned Ria Novosti news agency reports. Russia has said it has no plans to invade Ukraine and has not officially announced the withdrawal of its diplomatic staff there. State Department officials told Associated Press that US embassy staff would be asked to leave Kiev on Saturday, but the decision was not officially confirmed.</description></item><item><title>US State Department issues 'do not travel' warning for Ukraine as embassy staff is told to leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee326a11fc5601404430b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 05:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee326a11fc5601404430b2/</guid><description>The U.S. State Department has ordered the evacuation of American citizens in Ukraine amid the threat of Russian military action.
Summary The U.S. State Department has ordered the evacuation of American citizens in Ukraine amid the threat of Russian military action. &amp;ldquo;U.S. citizens in Ukraine should be aware that Russian military action anywhere in Ukraine would severely impact the U.S. Embassy’s ability to provide consular services, including assistance to U.S. citizens in departing Ukraine,&amp;rdquo; the State Department said in a travel advisory.</description></item><item><title>Schools must allow children leave during religion class, says Atheist Ireland</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcd6b8e0abe38feacbc466/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 01:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dcd6b8e0abe38feacbc466/</guid><description>‘We are now a pluralist country with Catholic laws that we are gradually dismantling’
Summary Sign up for alerts from The Irish Times Not Now I am interestedJust click on “Allow Notifications” on the message appearing on your browser to activate them. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Intel tells unvaccinated employees they face unpaid leave</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2bef470c67f2d4569d498/</guid><description>Description Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April
Summary Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don’t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in AprilPORTLAND, Ore. &amp;ndash; Intel has told workers that unvaccinated people who don&amp;rsquo;t get an exemption for religious or medical reasons will be on unpaid leave beginning in April.</description></item></channel></rss>