<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>burger on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/burger/</link><description>Recent content in burger on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 13:38:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/burger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>McDonald's to exit Russia after 30 years</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628253b8c0286768a3ad7324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 13:38:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628253b8c0286768a3ad7324/</guid><description>McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Corp on Monday became one of the biggest global names to exit Russia, laying out plans to sell all its restaurants after operating for more than 30 years in the country following its invasion of Ukraine.
Highlights McDonald&amp;rsquo;s plans to sell all its restaurants in Russia after operating for more than 30 years in the country following its invasion of Ukraine. The world&amp;rsquo;s largest burger chain will take a related non-cash charge of up to $1.</description></item><item><title>Burger King sued by customers who claim Whopper is smaller than advertised - CBS News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ca31eda55e7d8607e772f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 20:14:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ca31eda55e7d8607e772f/</guid><description>A class-action lawsuit alleges that ads inflate the Whopper&amp;rsquo;s size, making the burger appear 35% bigger than it actually is.
Highlights Four Burger King customers are suing the chain over its marketing practices. The lawsuit alleges that ads inflate the Whopper&amp;rsquo;s size, making it appear 35% bigger than it is in reality. The plaintiffs are seeking monetary damages for those who were &amp;ldquo;deceived&amp;rdquo; by the ads. A Burger King spokesperson says the chain doesn&amp;rsquo;t comment on the lawsuit.</description></item><item><title>Burger King franchise 'refuses' to close 800 Russian restaurants</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234be1618f3c7014b0e55ee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 17:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234be1618f3c7014b0e55ee/</guid><description>Burger King is trying to suspend its operations in Russia, but that&amp;rsquo;s proving difficult. A business partner controlling 800 restaurants has &amp;quot;refused&amp;quot; to close them, the company said.
Highlights Burger King is trying to suspend its operations in Russia, but that&amp;rsquo;s proving difficult. A business partner controlling 800 restaurants has &amp;ldquo;refused&amp;rdquo; to close them, the company said. Burger King can&amp;rsquo;t just snap its fingers and close up shop. The burger chain, owned by, has a joint venture partnership with businessman Alexander Kolobov in Russia.</description></item></channel></rss>