<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>warned on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/warned/</link><description>Recent content in warned on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 22:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/warned/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Turkey defuses mine after Russia warns of strays from Ukraine ports</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f8fc509f15f9d5ca3e169/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 22:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623f8fc509f15f9d5ca3e169/</guid><description>Turkey&amp;rsquo;s military deactivated a mine on Saturday that had drifted in from the Black Sea, setting off a loud explosion north of Istanbul, days after Russia warned several of them had washed away from Ukrainian ports.
Highlights Turkey&amp;rsquo;s military deactivated a mine that had drifted in from the Black Sea, setting off a loud explosion north of Istanbul. The mine was first discovered by fishermen in the upper Bosphorus strait. Russia warned several of them had washed away from Ukrainian ports earlier this month.</description></item><item><title>Five people killed in Russian hit on Kyiv TV tower – video | World news</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f7b32a27f2a44bc06a5d9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 14:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f7b32a27f2a44bc06a5d9/</guid><description>Five people have been killed and several wounded in a Russian attack on a TV tower in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s capital, Kyiv, according to reports
Highlights Two explosions heard in Borshchahivka and Dorohozhychi areas, reports say. Several channels were knocked off air, knocking several channels off air. The incident was first reported on social media by the Ukrainian interior ministry adviser, Anton Herashchenko, moments after Russia warned Kyiv residents to evacuate military and intelligence infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>