<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rise on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rise/</link><description>Recent content in rise on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/rise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coastal Panel Staff Advises Against Huntington Beach Desalination Plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fcd74951274a79e6720e9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:24:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626fcd74951274a79e6720e9/</guid><description>A proposed California desalination plant that would produce 50 million gallons of drinking water per day failed a crucial regulatory hurdle on Monday, possibly dooming a project that had been promoted as a partial solution for sustained drought.
Highlights Staff of the California Coastal Commission recommended denying approval of the Huntington Beach plant proposed by Poseidon Water. The plant is expected to produce 50 million gallons of drinking water per day, enough for 16% of the homes in the Orange County Water District, where 2.</description></item><item><title>Sea levels rising twice as fast as thought in New Zealand</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ef82be37e79a1dec8850b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 21:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626ef82be37e79a1dec8850b/</guid><description>Major new projections show infrastructure and homes in Auckland and Wellington - as well as many other places - risk inundation decades earlier than expected.
Highlights New data shows the sea level is rising twice as fast as previously thought in some parts of Aotearoa. In just 18 years parts of Wellington will see 30cm of sea level rise, causing once-in-a-century flood damage every year. Previously, councils and other authorities had not expected to reach this threshold until 2060 - halving the time to plan for mitigation or retreat.</description></item><item><title>The Satanic Temple sues elementary school as after-school club rejected</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62678e4abae8fd0668296396/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62678e4abae8fd0668296396/</guid><description>The Satanic Temple intends to prove the Pennsylvania school&amp;rsquo;s board discriminated against the organization by barring the creation of the &amp;quot;After School Satan&amp;quot; club.
Highlights The Satanic Temple has filed a lawsuit against a Pennsylvania elementary school after the school board voted to deny the establishment of the &amp;ldquo;After School Satan&amp;rdquo; club. Northern Elementary School in York, Pa., is being sued on the grounds of constitutional violation. The temple intends to prove the board discriminated against the organization by barring the creation of the club, despite other organizations being allowed to operate their own programs.</description></item></channel></rss>