<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>child on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/child/</link><description>Recent content in child on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 07:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/child/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nearly half of families with kids can no longer afford enough food 5 months after child tax credit ended</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b052da9b95990b0708483/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 07:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629b052da9b95990b0708483/</guid><description>Nearly half of parents who got expanded child tax credit checks now say they can&amp;rsquo;t afford enough food to feed their families, according to a May survey.
Highlights Child tax credit was expanded in 2021 through President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s American Rescue Plan. The legislation boosted the credit to $3,000 from $2,000, with a $600 bonus for kids under the age of 6 for the 2021 tax year. Nearly half of parents who used to get the checks now say they can&amp;rsquo;t afford enough food to feed their families, according to a May survey.</description></item><item><title>North Dakota lawmaker quits after child porn suspect texts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62680c5e20c0a0a2ae59d0d2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62680c5e20c0a0a2ae59d0d2/</guid><description>BISMARCK, N.D. (AP) — North Dakota’s longest-serving state senator announced Monday that he would resign following a report that he had traded scores of text messages with a man jailed on child pornography charges.
Highlights Republican Ray Holmberg, who rose to become one of the state’s most powerful lawmakers in a career that spanned 46 years, said he would resign effective June 1. His term was scheduled to end on Nov.</description></item><item><title>Former Picayune police officer receives maximum sentence for child porn charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62514e0dbffd455e23bb3dc8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 09:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62514e0dbffd455e23bb3dc8/</guid><description>A Picayune man will spend the next 30 years in prison after pleading guilty to producing a video of a minor engaging in sexually explicit conduct.
Highlights Joshua Christopher Stockstill enticed a child to engage in sexually explicit conduct so he could capture it on his cellphone camera. The video circulated for nearly two years before the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children became aware of it in July 2021.</description></item><item><title>Toronto Police Arrest Man And Woman On Hundreds Of Sexual Abuse Crimes Spanning 15 Years, 41 Victims Identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 17:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</guid><description>Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. Police have a number of unidentified victims and are seeking the public&amp;rsquo;s assistance in identifying them.
Highlights Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. It is alleged that a man and a woman committed multiple sexual and physical assaults against men, women and children. Martin “Mark” Wettlaufer, 37, and Kathleen Wardlaw, 42, of Toronto, have been arrested and charged with hundreds of offences relating to the allegations listed above.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated New Brunswick dad loses custody of at-risk child</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fddd6474a012ed43774f97/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 02:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fddd6474a012ed43774f97/</guid><description>A New Brunswick father who is refusing to be vaccinated against COVID-19 has lost his right to see his immunocompromised child in person.
Highlights A New Brunswick father has lost his right to see his immunocompromised child and his two other children in person. He refused to be vaccinated against the deadly virus COVID-19 vaccine. The parents and the children are not named in the 26-page court ruling. The decision is the first written ruling of its kind in the province and will serve as a precedent for other cases.</description></item><item><title>Mother shoots her 4-year-old child twice while attempting to clean gun, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</guid><description>A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said.
Summary A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said. The mother initially told officers someone opened fire outside an apartment after unsuccessfully trying to snatch her purse, hitting the child twice.</description></item></channel></rss>