<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>child on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/child/</link><description>Recent content in child on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 17:15:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/child/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Toronto Police Arrest Man And Woman On Hundreds Of Sexual Abuse Crimes Spanning 15 Years, 41 Victims Identified</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 17:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621e5474f708338e3738b1fa/</guid><description>Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. Police have a number of unidentified victims and are seeking the public&amp;rsquo;s assistance in identifying them.
Highlights Toronto Police Arrest a Man and Woman in a Child Sexual Abuse Investigation,Hundreds of Charges Laid. It is alleged that a man and a woman committed multiple sexual and physical assaults against men, women and children. Martin “Mark” Wettlaufer, 37, and Kathleen Wardlaw, 42, of Toronto, have been arrested and charged with hundreds of offences relating to the allegations listed above.</description></item><item><title>Unvaccinated New Brunswick dad loses custody of at-risk child</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fddd6474a012ed43774f97/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 02:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fddd6474a012ed43774f97/</guid><description>A New Brunswick father who is refusing to be vaccinated against COVID-19 has lost his right to see his immunocompromised child in person.
Highlights A New Brunswick father has lost his right to see his immunocompromised child and his two other children in person. He refused to be vaccinated against the deadly virus COVID-19 vaccine. The parents and the children are not named in the 26-page court ruling. The decision is the first written ruling of its kind in the province and will serve as a precedent for other cases.</description></item><item><title>Mother shoots her 4-year-old child twice while attempting to clean gun, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 02:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dce4d476807db792fe25c7/</guid><description>A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said.
Summary A Detroit woman who claimed a robber shot her 4-year-old child later confessed that she accidentally pulled the trigger while cleaning her gun, authorities said. The mother initially told officers someone opened fire outside an apartment after unsuccessfully trying to snatch her purse, hitting the child twice.</description></item></channel></rss>