<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>street on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/street/</link><description>Recent content in street on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 19:16:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/street/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buffalo shooting suspect planned to continue rampage down street, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282a1f5f0021dc365650e78/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 19:16:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6282a1f5f0021dc365650e78/</guid><description>The 18-year-old suspected shooter accused of storming a Buffalo supermarket Saturday and killing 10 and injuring three others, planned to continue his bloody rampage.
Highlights Payton Gendron, 18, is accused of storming a Buffalo, New York, supermarket Saturday and killing 10 and injuring three others. Police say he planned to continue his bloody rampage down the street before he was stopped, police said. Police Commissioner Joseph Gramaglia said the supermarket attack was a hate crime as 11 of 13 people who were shot were Black.</description></item><item><title>7 people injured in shooting in Winston-Salem</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62822494a3b8e0c540099a75/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 10:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62822494a3b8e0c540099a75/</guid><description>Police received a shots fired notification after 7:30 p.m.
Highlights Winston-Salem police received a shots fired notification after 7:30 p.m. Sunday. Police say the shootings are connected and all victims have non-life threatening injuries. Police found over 50 spent shell casings from different caliber weapons in the road and in the park. Evidence suggests there was a large exchange of gunfire at 925 Bethlehem Lane and shortly more shots were fired in the 2000 block of East 25th street resulting in five victims being shot on 25th Street and two victims on Highway 52 North.</description></item><item><title>False trampling death rumours a sign of misinformation campaign, say police | CBC News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212317433487e095ed1496c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6212317433487e095ed1496c/</guid><description>Officers on horseback rode down Rideau Street in Ottawa late Friday afternoon, leading to two people being knocked over — and a persistent yet false social media rumour that one woman had been trampled.
Highlights Mounted officers on horseback rode down Rideau Street in Ottawa late Friday afternoon. Two people were knocked over during the operation, leading to a persistent yet false rumour that one woman had been trampled. Fox News contributor with 1.</description></item></channel></rss>