<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pinkett on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pinkett/</link><description>Recent content in pinkett on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 23:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pinkett/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Academy condemns Will Smith's actions, launches review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624241029131b5dbacbf29d3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 23:13:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624241029131b5dbacbf29d3/</guid><description>LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences on Monday condemned the actions of Will Smith during Sunday night’s Oscars and launched an inquiry into his slapping of presenter Chris Rock .
Highlights The Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences condemns the actions of Will Smith during Sunday night’s Oscars. The film academy has launched an inquiry into his slapping of presenter Chris Rock. Smith stunned the Dolby Theatre crowd and viewers at home when he took the stage during Rock&amp;rsquo;s remarks after the comedian made a joke about Jada Pinkett Smith, Smith&amp;rsquo;s wife.</description></item><item><title>Chris Rock isn't pressing charges against Will Smith for Oscars slap</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241b6a992a96833ba48a433/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 13:23:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6241b6a992a96833ba48a433/</guid><description>Chris Rock will not be pressing charges against Will Smith following their onstage altercation at this year&amp;rsquo;s Oscars, the Los Angeles Police Department has said.
Highlights Chris Rock will not be pressing charges against Will Smith, the Los Angeles Police Department says. Smith appeared to strike Rock at Sunday night&amp;rsquo;s ceremony after the comedian made a joke about his wife&amp;rsquo;s shaved head. Rock quipped: &amp;ldquo;Jada I love you, &amp;lsquo;G.I. Jane 2,&amp;rsquo; can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see it,&amp;rdquo; the camera cut to Jada Pinkett Smith, who rolled her eyes.</description></item></channel></rss>