<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fox on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fox/</link><description>Recent content in fox on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:57:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Aggressive Fox’ Reported Near US Capitol, bites congressman</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ce54073720655e10e1ba6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ce54073720655e10e1ba6/</guid><description>U.S. Capitol Police have received “several reports of aggressive fox encounters on or near the grounds of the U.S. Capitol,” the department said Tuesday.
Highlights A fox bit a member of Congress and a woman near the U.S. Capitol. Authorities captured one of the animals and warned the public about &amp;ldquo;aggressive fox encounters&amp;rdquo; Rep. Ami Bera (D-Calif.) described the moment the fox &amp;ldquo;nipped&amp;rdquo; his leg on Monday to NBC News. Animal control officers captured one fox — a little guy seen peering up from inside a cage — at 3:35 p.</description></item><item><title>Russian foreign minister praises Fox News coverage of war in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623527b9f4ca64ee362fcd4d/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 00:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623527b9f4ca64ee362fcd4d/</guid><description>Sergei Lavrov says only Fox is presenting an ‘alternative point of view’ rather than ‘information terrorism’
Highlights Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister praises Fox News for its coverage of Ukraine. Sergei Lavrov says only Fox is presenting an ‘alternative point of view’ rather than ‘information terrorism’ in the US. Comments came as six western nations accused Moscow of using UN security council to launder disinformation and spread propaganda. Russian diplomats again raised allegations that the US was involved in biological weapons, which have been repeatedly denied by both Washington and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Man convicted of threatening to kill Sen. Manchin and Fox News hosts</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a5f733c642574e6752c8e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 17:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a5f733c642574e6752c8e/</guid><description>A man who posted videos threatening to kill Sen. Joe Manchin and Fox News hosts Laura Ingraham and Greg Gutfeld was convicted Thursday of threatening a federal official and making interstate threats.
Highlights Rickey Johnson was convicted by a jury after a weeklong trial in Manhattan federal court. Prosecutors allege Johnson said Manchin was “dead” and would be “executed,” that he was going to kill Ingraham with his “bare hands” Johnson could face up to 20 years in prison and is expected to be sentenced May 25.</description></item><item><title>Fox's Neil Cavuto said a second case of Covid-19 nearly killed him</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214e28aa60336e59135c446/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 13:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214e28aa60336e59135c446/</guid><description>Neil Cavuto, an immunocompromised Fox anchor who has dissented from the loudest voices at the right-wing network and spoken out in favor of Covid-19 vaccines, revealed on Monday that he had been hospitalized for weeks with a serious case of coronavirus and nearly died.
Highlights Fox Business anchor Neil Cavuto, an immunocompromised Fox anchor who has dissented from the loudest voices at the right-wing network and spoken out in favor of Covid-19 vaccines, revealed on Monday that he had been hospitalized for weeks with a serious case of coronavirus and nearly died.</description></item><item><title>SoCal man gets life for killing 2 women with meat cleaver as wife, son waited in car</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffbc230f72e3b3986275c5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ffbc230f72e3b3986275c5/</guid><description>Christopher Ken Ireland killed two women with a meat cleaver after a New Year’s Eve party in 2017 while his wife and son waited in a car outside. He was sentenced Friday to life in prison without the possibility of parole.
Highlights Christopher Ken Ireland killed two women with a meat cleaver after a New Year’s Eve party in 2017 while his wife and 11-year-old son waited in a car outside.</description></item><item><title>OC Deputy DA, vocal critic of vaccine mandates, dies of COVID-19</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d55e2fe9b4c05c90c6e4cb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 09:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d55e2fe9b4c05c90c6e4cb/</guid><description>Orange County Deputy District Attorney Kelly Ernby has died of COVID-19. Ernby was an outspoken critic of COVID vaccine mandates on a number of occasions.
Summary Orange County Deputy District Attorney Kelly Ernby has died of COVID-19, according to Ben Chapman, Chairman of the Greater Costa Mesa Republicans. Ernby was an outspoken critic of COVID-19 vaccine mandates on a number of occasions. &amp;ldquo;The Orange County District Attorney’s Office is utterly heartbroken by the sudden and unexpected passing of Deputy District Attorney Kelly Ernby,&amp;rdquo; District Attorney Todd Spitzer said in a statement Monday.</description></item><item><title>Outlets hurt by dwindling public interest in news in 2021</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca61aa085cc54e084f7f8a/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 01:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ca61aa085cc54e084f7f8a/</guid><description>NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. To a large degree, 2021 represented the inevitable hangover.
Summary (AP Photo)NEW YORK (AP) — The presidential election, pandemic and racial reckoning were stories that drove intense interest and engagement to news outlets in 2020. The Trump era saw explosive subscriber growth for some digital news sites like The New York Times and Washington Post.</description></item><item><title>Fox cancels ‘New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022’ telecast due to omicron surge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c456c95106b7bcbd5c15e2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 11:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c456c95106b7bcbd5c15e2/</guid><description>Fox has cancelled its &amp;quot;New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022&amp;quot; production in New York due to the recent surge in Covid-19 cases as the omicron variant spreads.
Summary Fox has decided against moving forward with its “New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022” production in New York due to the ongoing surge of Covid-19 and its omicron variant. “While we are confident in the health and safety protocols for ‘Fox’s New Year’s Eve Toast &amp;amp; Roast 2022,’ the recent velocity of the spread of Omicron cases has made it impossible to produce a live special in Times Square that meets our standards,” Fox Entertainment said in a statement.</description></item></channel></rss>