<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mail on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mail/</link><description>Recent content in mail on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:18:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tennessee Gov. Bill Lee signs law adding criminal penalties to abortion pill distribution via mail</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278ce21021783408abd9f42/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6278ce21021783408abd9f42/</guid><description>The bill adds criminal penalties to abortion bill dispensation through telehealth or mail distribution means.
Highlights Tennessee Gov. Bill Lee signs law adding criminal penalties to abortion pill distribution via mail. The bill prohibits any distribution of abortion medication except when prescribing is done in person by a physician. The legislation also makes it a Class E felony punishable by a fine of up to $50,000 if that procedure is not followed.</description></item><item><title>Robberies of mail carriers rise dramatically in U.S. with no signs of abating</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62645e36bfba38a4d925ad94/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 20:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62645e36bfba38a4d925ad94/</guid><description>Criminals across the country are increasingly targeting mail carriers.
Highlights Criminals across the country are increasingly targeting mail carriers. Between 2018 and 2021, robberies of mail carriers more than tripled. Robberies involving a gun more than quadrupled, according to U.S. Postal Inspection Service data. USPS says surge in letter carrier robberies fueled by economic impact of Covid crisis, growth in USPS parcel volume amid the rise of e-commerce, e-mailing of government checks related to pandemic aid programs.</description></item><item><title>Black female WWII unit recognized with congressional honor</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dd62e05407eb0b7a77687/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 08:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621dd62e05407eb0b7a77687/</guid><description>BOSTON (AP) — The House voted Monday to award the only all-female, Black unit to serve in Europe during World War II with the Congressional Gold Medal. The 422-0 vote follows a long-running campaign to recognize the 6888th Central Postal Directory Battalion.
Highlights The 6888th Central Central. Central. Center for the New York Democratic Rep. Brian Higgins, who sponsored the. post office bill, was given the “Indiana. Hunt-Martin” after veteran Indiana.</description></item><item><title>High numbers of mail ballots are being rejected in Texas under a new state law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c6bda24612d02cb48af8e/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 03:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620c6bda24612d02cb48af8e/</guid><description>In Harris County — home to Houston — election officials so far have sent back to voters nearly 38% of mail-in ballots, citing issues with new state ID requirements.
Highlights Local election officials in Texas are sending mail-in ballots back to voters with incorrect IDs. The state&amp;rsquo;s controversial new voting law includes new restrictions on vote-by-mail ballots. The law requires that the ID voters use when they vote by mail matches what&amp;rsquo;s on their voter registration record.</description></item></channel></rss>