<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>replace on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/replace/</link><description>Recent content in replace on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:12:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/replace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fire season drives demand for July 4 drone shows to replace fireworks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279677c714e6cdb05bab85d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6279677c714e6cdb05bab85d/</guid><description>When the Caldor Fire raced toward the southern shore of Lake Tahoe last year, its 100-foot (30-meter) flames spread across the tree canopy. Miles away, towns on the north shore took notice.
Highlights Three communities on the California-Nevada border are switching from the traditional fireworks show for the U.S. Independence Day holiday this July 4 to a drone light show. With Western states enduring a historic drought, some towns are rejecting fireworks as a wildfire risk.</description></item><item><title>Russian fast-food chain backed by parliament to replace McDonald’s reveals near-identical branding</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62337aaa05c32bdfaa5b6bfb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 18:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62337aaa05c32bdfaa5b6bfb/</guid><description>Moscow has invested in domestic fast-food chains after McDonald’s shut its restaurants in Russia
Highlights A trademark registration for the Uncle Vanya franchise has been filed with Russian authorities. Social media users were quick to point out its similarity to McDonald’s branding. McDonald&amp;rsquo;s last week said it would temporarily close all 847 of its 847 restaurants in Russia. The city council was said to have awarded 500m rubles (£3.6m) to domestic fast food chains.</description></item></channel></rss>