<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>spread on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spread/</link><description>Recent content in spread on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 12:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/spread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>‘Extremely active’ jumping worms that can leap a foot raise alarm in California</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a291375db4663c34924e3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 12:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628a291375db4663c34924e3/</guid><description>Earthworm native to east Asia and known for its big appetite poses threat to forest ecosystems, scientists say
Highlights The Amynthas agrestis, also known as the Asian jumping worm, Alabama jumper or crazy snake worm, has been spotted in California in recent months. The earthworm is native to east Asia, particularly to Japan and the Korean peninsula. In recent years the worms made their way to North America via various landscape plants that have been imported from the region.</description></item><item><title>UK officials: 4 men infected with "rare" monkeypox in London | AP News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283bbe561941fe64158a0f1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 15:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6283bbe561941fe64158a0f1/</guid><description>LONDON (AP) — British health authorities say they have identified four “rare and unusual” cases of the disease monkeypox among men who appear to have been infected in London and had no history of travel to the African countries where the smallpox-like disease is endemic.
Highlights Three of the men identified as gay, bisexual or men who have sex with men. All had no history of travel to African countries where the smallpox-like disease is endemic.</description></item><item><title>Disinformation Governance Board to tackle spread of misinformation in U.S., focusing on Russia and U.S.-Mexico border</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d1962dbb68bb45dd6e9e5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626d1962dbb68bb45dd6e9e5/</guid><description>The immediate focus will be on misinformation from human smugglers, who spread falsehoods about border policy to migrants to help drum up business.
Highlights The Department of Homeland Security is setting up a Disinformation Governance Board to try to counter the spread of false information. The board will focus on misinformation coming from Russia as well as misleading messages about the U.S.-Mexico border. The immediate focus will be on misinformation from human smugglers, who spread false claims about border policy to migrants to help drum up business.</description></item><item><title>Facebook fails to label 80% of posts promoting bioweapons conspiracy theory</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245ab8f36c6bcab5d73fcd7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 13:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6245ab8f36c6bcab5d73fcd7/</guid><description>A study found that external articles shared on the bioweapons myth were not labeled as ‘false information’ or ‘missing context’
Highlights Facebook failed to label 80% of posts promoting a conspiracy theory that the US is funding the use of bioweapons in Ukraine. Center for Countering Digital Hate (CCDH) studied a sample of posts from between 24 February and 14 March. The White House has condemned the myth, saying it may have been manufactured by Moscow to justify a possible use of chemical weapons against Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>CNN to stop broadcasting in Russia after new law</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222e3d7db18f478c954d5c2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222e3d7db18f478c954d5c2/</guid><description>CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia, the news channel said on Friday after the introduction of a new law there that could jail anyone intentionally spreading &amp;quot;fake&amp;quot; news.
Highlights Russia has introduced a new law that could jail anyone for spreading &amp;ldquo;fake&amp;rdquo; news. The law was passed by Russian lawmakers in the wake of the Ukraine crisis. CNN will stop broadcasting in Russia while the law is in place. The U.</description></item><item><title>Michigan woman won’t be charged for outing anti-mask nurses on Twitter</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd914e20fa07a434457363/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd914e20fa07a434457363/</guid><description>A conservative sheriff in Michigan who wanted charges to be filed against a Howell woman for calling out anti-maskers on Twitter won’t get his way&amp;hellip;.
Summary click to enlarge ShutterstockIn a series of tweets earlier this month, Kasey Helton took aim at anti-mask nurses who spread misinformation about COVID-19. This evening I was notified by my attorney that the Livingston County prosecutor’s office WILL NOT seek felony charges for a dubious criminal complaint brought against me by the @LCSOMI related to my tweets exposing nurses for publicly spreading COVID #misinfo at gov’t meetings.</description></item><item><title>Tony Blair blasts unvaccinated 'idiots' as fears grow over spread of Omicron - "Frankly, if you're not vaccinated at the moment and you're eligible, and you've got no health reasons for not being unvaccinated, you're not just irresponsible. You're an idiot."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c66d2cb17fc1ddd51ae3b4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 01:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c66d2cb17fc1ddd51ae3b4/</guid><description>The former Labour Prime Minister said those who are not vaccinated are putting strain on the NHS due to the transmissibility of the new strain.
Summary Tony Blair has slammed people who are still refusing to get the coronavirus vaccine as &amp;ldquo;idiots&amp;rdquo; with concerns growing over the spread of the Omicron variant. His comments come after First Minister Nicola Sturgeon announced new restrictions to halt the spread of Omicron which is now the dominant variant in Scotland.</description></item></channel></rss>