<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>washington on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/washington/</link><description>Recent content in washington on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:13:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/washington/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>9-year-old girl survives rare cougar attack in Washington</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62963e6987821c594dfb490f/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62963e6987821c594dfb490f/</guid><description>The girl fought back while her friends ran for their lives.
Highlights Witnesses say a 9-year-old girl survived a cougar attack after wandering up a trail with two friends. The girl fought back while her friends ran for their lives. Adults rushed to help and found the girl covered in blood. She was soon airlifted to a hospital, where she’s recovering after surgery for multiple wounds to her head and upper body.</description></item><item><title>Man dies after setting himself on fire in front of the Supreme Court, police say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626479f4fadd7c8bdeffb56e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 22:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626479f4fadd7c8bdeffb56e/</guid><description>The court said there were no other injuries, and there does not appear to be a public safety concern.
Highlights Police identify the man as 50-year-old Wynn Bruce, of Boulder, Colorado. The court said there were no other injuries, and there does not appear to be a public safety concern. Police have identified a person of interest in the case, but have not named or apprehended a suspect. The incident comes amid a chaotic day in Washington D.</description></item><item><title>COVID cases continue steep decline in U.S.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222040052acfee18920c8ba/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 12:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6222040052acfee18920c8ba/</guid><description>COVID case rates continued a steep decline over the last few weeks with the seven-day rolling average dropping to roughly 59,000 cases a day.
Highlights COVID case rates continued a steep decline over the last two weeks with the seven-day rolling average dropping to roughly 59,000 cases a day. The lowest case rates were seen in Nebraska with six cases per 100,000 people, followed by Delaware and Maryland. Montana and Alaska had the highest rates at 49 cases per cent and 47 in Alaska.</description></item><item><title>Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch again doesn't wear mask on bench, Sotomayor and Breyer log in remotely</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de7ca8993b9a45497b3e57/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 07:10:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de7ca8993b9a45497b3e57/</guid><description>Two justices, Sonia Sotomayor and Stephen Breyer, appeared remotely due to apparent concerns about Covid-19 as Neil Gorsuch did not wear a mask.
Summary Associate Justice Neil Gorsuch poses during a group photo of the Justices at the Supreme Court in Washington, April 23, 2021. Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch did not wear a mask for a hearing Tuesday, even as all the other justices in attendance did so, while two colleagues appeared remotely due to apparent concerns about Covid-19 infection.</description></item><item><title>11-week Kellogg’s strike to end after multi-year agreement reached</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 18:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c2163b7a1ba2cb195170e5/</guid><description>Description Summary The 11-week strike at Kellogg’s has come to an end after workers approved a contract with the company. Read more trending newsUnionized workers had been on strike since Oct. 5 in Michigan, Nebraska, Pennsylvania and Tennessee, The Washington Post reported.
The Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers’ International Union president Anthony Shelton said the contract makes gains for the 1,400 union workers and has no concessions. The five-year agreement has wage increases and cost-of-living adjustments the first year, in addition to the expansion of health care and retirement, the Post reported.</description></item></channel></rss>