<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>authorities on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/authorities/</link><description>Recent content in authorities on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 02:27:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/authorities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vancouver health authorities warn staff to shelter and hide medical credentials during anti-vaxx convoy</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200838b5cb0a71ae8cc8c7a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 02:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6200838b5cb0a71ae8cc8c7a/</guid><description>Vancouver’s two health authorities are urging health-care workers to take defensive measures to avoid clashes with a convoy of anti-vaccination and anti-restriction demonstrators heading toward the city on Saturday.
Highlights A convoy of anti-vaccination and anti-restriction demonstrators are heading to Vancouver on Saturday. The convoy is expected to pass Mount Saint Joseph and St. Paul’s hospitals in the city. A health-care memo sent to staff at both hospitals tells them not to engage in the convoy.</description></item><item><title>Argentinians urged to throw out cocaine after tainted batches kill at least 23</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5dff7e2224bc1a12c9d6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fd5dff7e2224bc1a12c9d6/</guid><description>Officials fear death toll from adulterated cocaine could increase, with 84 people currently in intensive care
Highlights At least 23 people have died after ingesting tainted cocaine in Buenos Aires area. Officials fear death toll could rise as more victims are found to have died at home. Police are warning the public not to consume any of the drugs they may have purchased in the last two days. The victims are believed to have been victims of a turf war between rival drug gangs who may have been involved in the drug trade.</description></item><item><title>Uyghur woman sentenced for 14 years for teaching Islam, hiding Qurans</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbbd6e8cd39bc4dc4118c6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbbd6e8cd39bc4dc4118c6/</guid><description>Hasiyet Ehmet has not been heard from since her abduction four years ago.
Summary A Manas county court official confirmed that Hasiyet Ehmet had been sentenced to 14 years. “It was because of teaching kids the Quran and hiding two copies of Quran when authorities were confiscating them, and later getting caught,” the official said. Hasiyet had stopped teaching children two years before her arrest because of health problems. Authorities did not try Hasiyet on the charges in court, but instead sent a court verdict letter to her family, the person said.</description></item></channel></rss>