<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>isolation on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/isolation/</link><description>Recent content in isolation on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 22:10:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/isolation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Michigan says it won't follow CDC's more relaxed COVID-19 quarantine recommendations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce2bfb7e28cc2bb7b6ae30/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 22:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce2bfb7e28cc2bb7b6ae30/</guid><description>Michigan health officials say they won&amp;rsquo;t adopt shorter federal COVID-19 isolation/quarantine guidelines until the review
Summary Michigan says it won&amp;rsquo;t follow CDC&amp;rsquo;s more relaxed COVID-19 quarantine recommendationsShow Caption Hide Caption CDC shortens COVID-19 isolation and quarantine guidelines CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the changes were made based on &amp;ldquo;two years of science&amp;rdquo; about the virus. Rather, Michigan health leaders say they will continue to recommend previous, longer quarantine and isolation guidelines, including those for K-12 schools and congregate care settings.</description></item><item><title>CDC shortens recommended Covid-19 isolation and quarantine time</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 15:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb26a4028200197939a7fd/</guid><description>The CDC shortened the recommended times that people should isolate when they&amp;rsquo;ve tested positive for Covid-19 from 10 days to five days if they don&amp;rsquo;t have symptoms &amp;ndash; and if they wear a mask around others for at least five more days.
Summary The CDC also shortened the recommended time for people to quarantine if they are exposed to the virus to a similar five days if they are vaccinated. People who are fully vaccinated and boosted may not need to quarantine at all, the CDC said.</description></item></channel></rss>