<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>aid on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/aid/</link><description>Recent content in aid on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 22:11:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/aid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Landlords finding ways to evict after getting rental aid</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083067608dae9638d05bd8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 22:11:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62083067608dae9638d05bd8/</guid><description>A day before she was due to be evicted in November from her Atlanta home, Shanelle King heard that she had been awarded about $15,000 in rental assistance. She could breathe again. But then the 43-year-old hairdresser got a letter last month from her landlord saying the company was canceling her lease in March —- seven months early — without any explanation.
Highlights $46.5 billion Emergency Rental Assistance Program has paid out tens of billions of dollars to help avert an eviction crisis.</description></item><item><title>16 top colleges sued for alleged violation of federal antitrust laws by colluding on their financial-aid practices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de4469dcb8e76e3289f4dc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 03:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61de4469dcb8e76e3289f4dc/</guid><description>Sixteen top US universities, including Duke, Vanderbilt and Northwestern, are being sued by five former students claiming those schools may be involved in antitrust violations in the way those institutions worked together in determining financial aid awards for students, according to the lawsuit filed in a US District Court in Illinois.
Summary &amp;ldquo;All Defendants, in turn, have conspired to reduce the amount of financial aid they provide to admitted students,&amp;rdquo; the complaint read.</description></item></channel></rss>