<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vaccinated on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vaccinated/</link><description>Recent content in vaccinated on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 06:10:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vaccinated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Florida Department of Health Medical Director has been put on leave for encouraging his own staff to get vaccinated.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7a8f9c4f184581f640580/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 06:10:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e7a8f9c4f184581f640580/</guid><description>Florida Department of Health confirms Dr. Raul Pino put on leave for encouraging Orange County Department of Health employees to get vaccinated
Summary The Florida Department of Health Medical Director that oversees areas of Orange County including Orlando has been put on leave for encouraging his own staff to get vaccinated. Orange County Medical Director Dr. Raul Pino wrote an email to staff on Jan. 4th encouraging them to get vaccinated and boosted for COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>The highly contagious Omicron variant will 'find just about everybody,' Fauci says, but vaccinated people will still fare better</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df4f9397214fa7f9c39295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df4f9397214fa7f9c39295/</guid><description>Covid-19 hospitalizations in the United States have reached a new record high, surpassing the previous peak from January 2021, according to data from the US Department of Health and Human Services.
Summary More than 62% of the country has been fully vaccinated, but only 23% are fully vaccinated and boosted, according to data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. While fully vaccinated people are accounting for a larger share of Covid-19 hospitalizations, multiple accounts suggest that those who are fully vaccinated and boosted account for a small share.</description></item><item><title>Quebec’s cannabis, liquor stores to require coronavirus vaccination proof</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d928a18bee74921efa930e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 06:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d928a18bee74921efa930e/</guid><description>As Quebec&amp;rsquo;s covid hospitalizations rise, Health Minister Christian Dubé said holdouts should know: “If they can’t get vaccinated, then they should stay home.”
Summary About a fifth of Quebec’s 8.5 million people are not vaccinated. But they account for about half of the patients in intensive care, Dubé said. “We’re going to make sure they understand very well that if they can’t get vaccinated, then they should stay home.” READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>CDC: 'Avoid cruise travel, regardless of vaccination status'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ced4bcbc79f23f80e7e9b0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 10:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ced4bcbc79f23f80e7e9b0/</guid><description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Thursday urged all travelers — vaccinated and unvaccinated — to avoid cruise ship travel due to the omicron variant
Summary The CDC said the coronavirus &amp;ldquo;spreads easily between people in close quarters on board ships, and the chance of getting COVID-19 on cruise ships is very high.&amp;rdquo; It said the travel health notice upgrade from level 3 to level 4 &amp;ldquo;reflects increases in cases onboard cruise ships since identification of the omicron variant.</description></item></channel></rss>