<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mansion on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mansion/</link><description>Recent content in mansion on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:15:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/mansion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BLM co-founder admits she held parties at mansion bought with donor funds</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bd2eef1dbe204e3793f09/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 15:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bd2eef1dbe204e3793f09/</guid><description>Black Lives Matter Co-Founder Patrisse Cullors admitted in an Associated Press interview she spent overnights and hosted multiple personal events at the group’s controversial Malibu mansion. Cullors’sstatements come after she claimed to have “never misappropriated funds” related to the Black Lives Matter Global Network Foundation’s (BLMGNF) purchase of a $6 million Malibu home with donor funds.
Highlights Patrisse Cullors admitted in an Associated Press interview she spent overnights and hosted multiple personal events at the group&amp;rsquo;s controversial Malibu mansion.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine: Squatters occupy Russian oligarch's London mansion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fa205053f8b3ad4f0e568/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 20:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fa205053f8b3ad4f0e568/</guid><description>Protesters want to give the property, believed to be owned by Oleg Deripaska, to Ukrainian refugees.
Highlights Protesters want to give the property believed to be owned by Oleg Deripaska to Ukrainian refugees. One man said: &amp;ldquo;A lot of civilians and women and children are dying every day for Putin and it&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable&amp;rdquo; Protesters want the property to be given to refugees in Ukraine. One said: &amp;lsquo;We need to protest in every way we can because this war is not right.</description></item><item><title>The mentor of Swedish princess Sofia brought young women to Jeffrey Epstein’s mansion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622272fd44d8ecaff8bc4fb8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 20:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622272fd44d8ecaff8bc4fb8/</guid><description>• Unique photos of the young Swedish women visit the billionaire convicted of sex crimes • How the Stockholm School of Economics tried to cover up the collaboration.
Highlights Swedish-American financial veteran Barbro Ehnbom founded the scholarship “Female economist of the year” in close collaboration with the Stockholm School of Economics. On at least three occasions scholarship recipients were invited to dinner and champagne parties at the home of Jeffrey Epstein, who at the time was a convicted sex offender.</description></item></channel></rss>