<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>closed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/closed/</link><description>Recent content in closed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/closed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Teacher Closed Propped-Open Door Before Uvalde School Shooting: Police</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296dc96ec3c53a05746ae29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6296dc96ec3c53a05746ae29/</guid><description>New details are emerging about the door the Uvalde gunman used to gain access to the elementary school.
Highlights A Texas elementary school teacher propped the door open with a rock, police say. She then closed the door shut when she realized there was a shooter on campus, an official says. Investigators are still trying to interview the police chief who was the commander of the school shooting scene. 19 students and two teachers were killed in a classroom in Uvalde, Texas, on May 24.</description></item><item><title>Lockheed Martin Plant Locked Down After Shooting Incident, ‘Suspicious Device' Found</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628797ef27d9bbb70d2f70bd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 13:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628797ef27d9bbb70d2f70bd/</guid><description>A Lockheed Martin in North Texas is locked down after a shooting incident that occurred on Thursday morning.
Highlights A man in his 60s fatally shot himself outside the main gate at Lockheed Martin in Fort Worth Thursday morning. No other people were injured during the shooting, police said. The main entry gate was reopened around 11 a.m. Thursday, followed by the roads nearby. Bomb techs from the Fort Worth Police Department were called in to get a closer look at a briefcase in the man&amp;rsquo;s vehicle.</description></item><item><title>Temple Mount closed to Jews 'until further notice,' says site admin.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265f14fe87068c7e5eadf39/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6265f14fe87068c7e5eadf39/</guid><description>Police made decision after ongoing clashes with Arab protesters at site
Highlights Police made decision after ongoing clashes with Arab protesters at site. Jewish prayers will be held at the gates of the Temple Mount and next to the Western, Southern, Eastern and Northern Walls. Clashes have broken out between Arabs and Israeli security forces at the site and al-Aqsa Mosque in recent days as Muslims celebrated Ramadan and Jews celebrated Passover.</description></item><item><title>French zoo closed temporarily after pack of nine wolves escape</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6c18b8a48eff90184401b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 07:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c6c18b8a48eff90184401b/</guid><description>No people were injured during the incident, but the wolf pack was killed due to safety concerns.
Summary &amp;ldquo;There were not many people in the zoo at the time and at no time was the public in immediate danger,&amp;rdquo; said Mr Chollet. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>