<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>supporters on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supporters/</link><description>Recent content in supporters on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 17:40:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/supporters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Annadale man who allegedly called for ‘extermination’ of Biden supporters gets 3 years on gun charge</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628680e11b0f18d6d51254ea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 17:40:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628680e11b0f18d6d51254ea/</guid><description>Brian Maiorana, 55, was arrested late last year after allegedly calling for the ‘extermination’ of Democrats and their families. Authorities at the time discovered at the house a semiautomatic Glock pistol, two magazines
Highlights Brian Maiorana, 55, pleaded guilty to being a felon in possession of a firearm in April 2021. Authorities at the time discovered at the house a semiautomatic Glock pistol, two magazines of.45-caliber ammunition, parts for a.22-caliber firearm and additional ammunition.</description></item><item><title>Alexei Navalny faces 15 more years in prison as new trial starts | Alexei Navalny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bed6c4e1ddc178fa90dc2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 18:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620bed6c4e1ddc178fa90dc2/</guid><description>Russian opposition leader in fresh trial at penal colony far from support base on charge of embezzlement
Highlights Alexei Navalny is accused of embezzling donations to his FBK anti-corruption organisation. He is serving a three-and-a-half-year sentence at the IK-2 penal colony in Vladimir. Navalny has denied the charges and calls them politically motivated. His family and supporters say the Kremlin is seeking an easy conviction by holding the trial in a prison colony far away from his support base in Moscow.</description></item></channel></rss>