<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>france on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/france/</link><description>Recent content in france on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anti-vax protesters in France tell Macron, ‘we’ll piss you off’: More than 100,000 people across France protested Saturday over what they say are government plans to further restrict the rights of the unvaccinated</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61daeaa2b40419db0d6bfddd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61daeaa2b40419db0d6bfddd/</guid><description>More than 100,000 people across France protested Saturday over what they say are government plans to further restrict the rights of the unvaccinated, days after French President Emmanuel Macron vowed…
Summary Macron said this week he wanted to &amp;lsquo;piss off&amp;rsquo; unvaccinated people by making their lives so complicated they would end up getting jabbed. Protesters in Paris retorted by chanting, with the same slang, &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll piss you off&amp;rdquo;. 01:54&amp;rsquo;No to vaccine passes&amp;rsquo;In Paris, protesters, many of them unmasked, braved the cold and rain brandishing placards emblazoned with the word &amp;ldquo;Truth&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;No to vaccine passes&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>France fines Google, Facebook for not allowing users to deny cookies as simply as accepting them.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d720514135940d89a9bd1a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d720514135940d89a9bd1a/</guid><description>The French government is fining the tech giants millions over data that tracks users' activity. They&amp;rsquo;ve given the companies three months to comply or face further fines.
Summary France&amp;rsquo;s National Commission for Information Technology and Freedom (CNIL) on Thursday hit Facebook and Google with €210 million ($237 million) in fines. Google, which also owns YouTube, was fined €150 million, breaking a record €100-million fine the company received in December 2020 over similar practices.</description></item><item><title>France introduces free birth control for all women under 25</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d12370227d4f1c2543b386/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d12370227d4f1c2543b386/</guid><description>Free birth control for all women under 25 will be available in France from Saturday, expanding a scheme targeting under-18s to ensure young women don&amp;rsquo;t stop taking contraception because they cannot a…
Summary Contraception including the pill, IUDs, contraceptive patches and other methods will be free for women aged 25 and under in France from January 1, 2021. Free birth control for all women under 25 will be available in France from Saturday, expanding a scheme targeting under-18s to ensure young women don&amp;rsquo;t stop taking contraception because they cannot afford it.</description></item><item><title>Wearing masks outdoors mandatory in Paris starting Friday</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8066c775ab3f79990e35/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 04:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ce8066c775ab3f79990e35/</guid><description>Wearing masks even outdoors will be mandatory in Paris starting on Friday, French authorities have announced, as the country struggles to come to grips with an Omicron surge. France is leading Europe…
Summary People wearing face masks walk on the Palais Royal grounds in Paris on January 16, 2021Wearing masks even outdoors will be mandatory in Paris starting on Friday, French authorities have announced, as the country struggles to come to grips with an Omicron surge.</description></item></channel></rss>