<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>following on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/following/</link><description>Recent content in following on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:14:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/following/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buddy, the cat mauled by two dogs in Frankford, heads to foster care</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249b9967a171534a1420b65/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 15:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6249b9967a171534a1420b65/</guid><description>Buddy, the cat who was mauled by two dogs in Frankford, was taken into foster care Friday morning by a veterinarian who tended to him at the BluePearl Pet Hospital in Philadelphia. The pet will be monitored at his foster home before the Pennsylvania SPCA possibly puts him up for adoption.
Highlights The Pennsylvania SPCA said it will monitor Buddy&amp;rsquo;s progress at his foster home before possibly putting him up for adoption.</description></item><item><title>Infant formula recall expanded following child's death, FDA says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ebf110fc0069c1457d86a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621ebf110fc0069c1457d86a/</guid><description>Abbott Laboratories recalled some Similac PM 60/40 cans and cases produced at a Michigan facility, after an infant who was exposed to the powdered baby formula died.
Highlights Abbott recalled some Similac PM 60/40 cans and cases produced at a Michigan facility. An infant who was exposed to the powdered baby formula died, the U.S. Food and Drug Administration said on Monday. A few days earlier, Abbott recalled certain baby formula made at the facility in Sturgis city following complaints about bacterial infections in infants who consumed the products.</description></item><item><title>Navy SEAL candidate dies and another hospitalized following 'Hell Week'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff4b6c1f0b1f227aa330a4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 04:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ff4b6c1f0b1f227aa330a4/</guid><description>A Navy SEAL candidate died Friday and another was hospitalized in San Diego after completing a training phase known as &amp;quot;Hell Week.&amp;quot;
Highlights The cause of the SEAL candidate&amp;rsquo;s death is under investigation. The injured candidate is in stable condition at the Naval Medical Center San Diego. They began suffering symptoms &amp;ldquo;several hours&amp;rdquo; after completing a training phase known as &amp;ldquo;Hell Week&amp;rdquo; They were not &amp;ldquo;actively&amp;rdquo; training when they started to suffer symptoms, officials said.</description></item><item><title>Nanaimo fisherman handed lifetime ban following midnight poaching of hundreds of crabs in Vancouver harbour</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 13:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c1cfe7c0e62451f2d5a60d/</guid><description>Description A B.C. Supreme Court judge has banned Nanaimo fisherman Scott Stanley Matthew Steer from fishing for life.
Summary The sentence was delivered on Nov. 12, 2021, and it is the first lifetime ban for a Pacific region fisherman in more than a decade. Along with the lifetime ban, Steer&amp;rsquo;s sentence includes:A prohibition from being aboard a fishing vessel. Steer was caught illegally fishing for crab in the Vancouver harbour after Vancouver SeaBus officials tipped off police.</description></item></channel></rss>