<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>homes on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/homes/</link><description>Recent content in homes on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 10:10:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/homes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Texas power use to break all-time high next week</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299de08d07c4d299e8f970b/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 10:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6299de08d07c4d299e8f970b/</guid><description>Power demand in Texas will break the all-time high next week as economic growth boosts overall usage and hot weather causes homes and businesses to crank up their air conditioners, the state&amp;rsquo;s power grid operator forecast on Thursday.
Highlights Power demand in Texas will break the all-time high next week as economic growth boosts overall usage and hot weather causes homes and businesses to crank up their air conditioners. High temperatures in Houston would remain in the low to mid 90s Fahrenheit (33.</description></item><item><title>New Jersey notifies 186,000 buildings, homes drinking water comes through lead pipes</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216a3312ed622f97b752e15/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 21:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6216a3312ed622f97b752e15/</guid><description>Water systems are required to notify residents of the lead pipes.
Highlights New Jersey announced Thursday it is notifying nearly 200,000 homes and businesses that they are receiving drinking water from service lines contaminated with lead. The 186,830 known lead service lines feed into buildings all over the state, officials said. Water systems are required to notify residents of the lead pipes. The state&amp;rsquo;s Lead Service Line Replacement law was enacted in July 2021, the law calls for the replacement of these lines by 2031.</description></item><item><title>Canada should temporarily ban foreign home buyers, rezone cities - housing minister</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c464def47fd04f449d4106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 12:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c464def47fd04f449d4106/</guid><description>Municipalities should rezone broadly to allow more density and Canada should temporarily ban foreign buyers to help alleviate the housing affordability crunch faced by residents, the country&amp;rsquo;s housing minister said on Tuesday.
Summary Canada&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Housing, Diversity, and Inclusion Ahmed Hussen speaks during Question Period in the House of Commons on Parliament Hill in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada November 30, 2021. REUTERS/Blair Gable/OTTAWA, Dec 21 (Reuters) - Municipalities should rezone broadly to allow more density and Canada should temporarily ban foreign buyers to help alleviate the housing affordability crunch faced by residents, the country&amp;rsquo;s housing minister said on Tuesday.</description></item></channel></rss>