<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vladimir on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vladimir/</link><description>Recent content in vladimir on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 03:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/vladimir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Russian oligarch's superyacht is stuck in Norway because no one will sell it fuel</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232a78c6ecb8dcdcd1bde27/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6232a78c6ecb8dcdcd1bde27/</guid><description>The Ragnar is owned by Russian oligarch Vladimir Strzhalkovsky, a former KGB agent with deep ties to Russian President Vladimir Putin. Onboard amenities include an amphibious ATV and an island.
Highlights The Ragnar is owned by Russian oligarch Vladimir Strzhalkovsky, a former KGB agent. The yacht is stuck in a port city in northern Norway because no one will sell it fuel. The Ragnar was custom-built on the hull of a former service ship capable of pushing its way through ice.</description></item><item><title>Putin to Recognize Ukraine Separatist Territories as Independent – Kremlin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214434651520b64d0fdc07b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 01:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214434651520b64d0fdc07b/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin has signed a decree recognizing the independence of eastern Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s separatist republics.
Highlights Russian President Vladimir Putin signs decree recognizing independence of eastern Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s separatist republics. Putin calls for Russia&amp;rsquo;s upper house of parliament to &amp;ldquo;support this decision&amp;rdquo; State television shows Putin signing mutual aid agreements with rebel leaders in Donetsk and Luhansk. The move comes despite warnings from the West that it could trigger sweeping sanctions on Russia and the West.</description></item></channel></rss>