<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>witnessed on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/witnessed/</link><description>Recent content in witnessed on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 13:21:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/witnessed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Uvalde gunman threatened rapes and school shootings on social media app Yubo in weeks leading up to the massacre, users say | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629221ca3d1645a02e9a7e47/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 13:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629221ca3d1645a02e9a7e47/</guid><description>Salvador Ramos told girls he would rape them, showed off a rifle he bought, and threatened to shoot up schools in livestreams on the social media app Yubo, according to several users who witnessed the threats in recent weeks.
Highlights Three users say they saw Ramos threaten to commit sexual violence or carry out school threats on Yubo. The social media app is used by tens of millions of young people around the world.</description></item><item><title>A teenager in Utah died after a tunnel he was digging in a sand dune collapsed</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62844325902f359e063568f1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 00:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62844325902f359e063568f1/</guid><description>A 13-year-old boy in Utah died from injuries sustained in a dune collapse last weekend, according to Utah State Parks.
Highlights Park rangers believe the teen had been digging a tunnel in the side of a sand dune at Coral Pink Sand Dunes State Park. The tunnel collapsed, trapping him underneath the sand, Utah State Parks says. A family member witnessed the collapse about 5:30 p.m., and he was located six-and-a-half feet beneath the sand.</description></item></channel></rss>