<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fighter on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fighter/</link><description>Recent content in fighter on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 22:13:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/fighter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Germany to buy dozens of US fighter jets in spending spree</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fbdf920e4a7f7bf4e31b2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 22:13:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622fbdf920e4a7f7bf4e31b2/</guid><description>Germany plans to buy up to 35 US-made F-35 fighter jets and 15 Eurofighter jets, a parliamentary source said Monday, as part of a major push to modernise the armed forces in response to Russia&amp;rsquo;s inva…
Highlights Germany plans to buy up to 35 F-35 fighter jets and 15 Eurofighter jets, a parliamentary source said Monday. The jets made by Lockheed Martin would replace Germany&amp;rsquo;s decades-old Tornado fleet, the source said.</description></item><item><title>US Navy Wants To Get Crashed Stealth Fighter Back From South China Sea, Before China Can</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1e0adc906535dea756a32/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f1e0adc906535dea756a32/</guid><description>The United States Navy is trying to retrieve its most advanced fighter jet from the depths of the South China Sea, an extremely complex operation that analysts say will be closely monitored by Beijing.
Summary The F-35C, a single-engine stealth fighter and the newest jet in the US Navy fleet, crash-landed on the aircraft carrier USS Carl Vinson during routine operations on Monday, the Navy said. Chinese naval and coast guard vessels maintain a constant presence in South China Sea waters.</description></item><item><title>Taiwan detects 39 Chinese warplanes, scrambles jets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee86c9e9f7489b0e0ad76d/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 11:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ee86c9e9f7489b0e0ad76d/</guid><description>Dozens of Chinese jets entered Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s air defense zone, the island&amp;rsquo;s officials said. Taiwan responded by scrambling its own fighter jets and activating missile defense systems.
Summary Taiwan reported on Sunday that 39 Chinese warplanes, including a bomber, were detected in the south-western Air Defense Identification Zone (ADIZ). The island&amp;rsquo;s ministry of defense said 34 fighter aircraft and an H-6 bomber were among the aircraft involved in the incursion. According to flight paths the ministry officials posted online, Chinese aircraft flew to the northeast of the Taiwan-controlled Pratas Island.</description></item></channel></rss>