<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pleaded on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pleaded/</link><description>Recent content in pleaded on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:10:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/pleaded/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>White supremacists are convicted of training for a civil war in Michigan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628552a6e5e231b8adcade10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628552a6e5e231b8adcade10/</guid><description>The Base is a pro-Hitler movement that advocates a race war against non-white people
Highlights The Base is a pro-Hitler movement that advocates a race war against non-white people. Justen Watkins, Thomas Denton, and Tristan Webb were charged in August 2021 with larceny in a building, gang membership, felony possession of a firearm, and conspiracy to train with firearms for a civil war. They were accused of breaking into a vacant Michigan Department of Corrections Camp Tuscola annex and stealing state-issued clothing from one of the jails in October 2020.</description></item><item><title>Ex-Virginia police officer and West Virginia lawmaker plead guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 08:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623590f631aa2ff3ae59a51e/</guid><description>Jacob Fracker, who has agreed to cooperate with federal prosecutors, was fired from his job as a police officer in Rocky Mount, Virginia while Derrick Evans resigned from the West Virginia state legislature before the session started.
Highlights Jacob Fracker pleads guilty to conspiring to obstruct an official proceeding, the joint session of Congress that convened on January 6, 2021, to certify President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s electoral victory. A former West Virginia state lawmaker pleaded guilty Friday to a civil disorder charge, punishable by up to five years in prison.</description></item><item><title>Senator pleads guilty to inappropriately touching nurse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62134a0f5f8f25a84285ef98/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 08:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62134a0f5f8f25a84285ef98/</guid><description>LANSING, Mich. (AP) — A state senator pleaded guilty Thursday to misdemeanor battery after a nurse practitioner said he inappropriately touched her during an exam. Sen. John Bizon, a Battle Creek Republican, faces up to 93 days in jail when he is sentenced at a later date.
Highlights Sen. John Bizon, a Battle Creek Republican, faces up to 93 days in jail when he is sentenced at a later date. Incident occurred Aug.</description></item><item><title>Mother of Michigan school shooting suspect pleaded to keep her job hours after the shooting, boss says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62033fb45fce6e0f7cd841b5/</guid><description>The text exchange was revealed in court Tuesday during a preliminary hearing for Jennifer and James Crumbley, who are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring clear warning signs that he was a threat to others.
Highlights Ethan Crumbley, 15, opened fire with a 9mm handgun at his Michigan high school, killing four students and injuring seven. His parents are accused of giving their son a firearm and ignoring warning signs that he was a threat to others.</description></item><item><title>In milestone deal, Proud Boy pleads guilty in Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61c3d840908ab4009e911071/</guid><description>A New York man pleaded guilty Wednesday to storming the U.S. Capitol with fellow members of the far-right Proud Boys, a milestone in the Justice Department&amp;rsquo;s prosecution of extremists who joined the Jan.
Summary At least four others linked to the Oath Keepers also have pleaded guilty to riot-related charges. Proud Boys members describe themselves as a politically incorrect men’s club for “Western chauvinists.” Its members frequently have engaged in street fights with antifascist activists at rallies and protests.</description></item></channel></rss>