<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>syria on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/syria/</link><description>Recent content in syria on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/syria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US official: Russia appoints new Ukraine war commander</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253f14366b76509ed863537/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 09:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253f14366b76509ed863537/</guid><description>WASHINGTON (AP) — Russia has tapped a new Ukraine war commander to take centralized control of the next phase of battle after its costly failures in the opening campaign and carnage for Ukrainian civilians.
Highlights Russia has appointed Gen. Alexander Dvornikov as commander of an armed campaign that Russian authorities still refer to as a “special military operation&amp;quot; U.S. officials don’t see one man making a difference in Moscow’s prospects. The White House national security adviser, Jake Sullivan, said “no appointment of any general can erase the fact that Russia has already faced a strategic failure in Ukraine” The decision to establish new battlefield leadership comes as Russia gears up for what is expected to be a large and more focused push to expand Russian control in Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s east and south, including the Donbas, and follows a failed opening bid in the north.</description></item><item><title>Arctic Seed Vault to Receive Rare Deposits</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a487c92e353c0dbaf25ae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 12:18:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/620a487c92e353c0dbaf25ae/</guid><description>A vault built on an Arctic mountainside to preserve the world&amp;rsquo;s crop seeds from catastrophes will receive new deposits, including one from the first organisation that made a withdrawal from the facility.
Highlights Svalbard facility is global back-up for seed banks designed to safeguard biodiversity of crops. Facility is on Spitsbergen island halfway between mainland Norway and the North Pole. On Monday, gene banks from Sudan, Uganda, New Zealand, Germany and Lebanon will deposit seeds.</description></item></channel></rss>