<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>council on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/council/</link><description>Recent content in council on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 09:14:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/council/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UN votes Russia out of human rights council citing Bucha killings - National | Globalnews.ca</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ffcd7a38f10728a169aa3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 09:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624ffcd7a38f10728a169aa3/</guid><description>An overwhelming majority of member countries in the United Nations General Assembly voted to suspend Russia from its human rights body following recent killings in Bucha.
Highlights The United Nations General Assembly voted to suspend Russia from its human rights body on Thursday over the war in Ukraine. Russia&amp;rsquo;s deputy UN Ambassador Gennady Kuzmin called the decision an “illegitimate and politically motivated step’ Russia has vehemently denied the allegations, despite the mounting evidence.</description></item><item><title>Anti-vaccination doctor Jonie Girouard can no longer practise in New Zealand</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbe7a8993d260601a318fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dbe7a8993d260601a318fa/</guid><description>A Kaiapoi doctor caught handing out fake vaccine exemptions is no longer registered to practise medicine in New Zealand.
Summary A Kaiapoi doctor caught handing out fake vaccine exemptions is no longer registered to practise medicine in New Zealand. Medical Council chairperson Curtis Walker said Dr Girouard​ was now unable to practise medicine in New Zealand, as she was no longer registered. &amp;ldquo;The Medical Council thanks the thousands of doctors who are contributing to New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s pandemic response.</description></item></channel></rss>