<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>dont on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dont/</link><description>Recent content in dont on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:09:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/dont/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>San Francisco Giants manager: 'I don't plan on coming out for the anthem going forward until I feel better about the direction of our country'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62929d8c4f33c669c86a6cce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:09:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62929d8c4f33c669c86a6cce/</guid><description>San Francisco Giants manager Gabe Kapler told reporters ahead of his team&amp;rsquo;s Friday game against the Cincinnati Reds that he intends to forgo the pregame US national anthem moving forward.
Highlights Kapler: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t plan on coming out for the anthem going forward until I feel better about the direction of our country&amp;rdquo; Kapler questioned whether the U.S. is truly &amp;ldquo;the land of the free and the home of the brave&amp;rdquo; Comments come after 19 children and two adults were killed at an elementary school in Uvalde, Texas, by a lone, 18-year-old gunman.</description></item><item><title>Disney heir comes out publicly as transgender, condemns anti-LGBTQ bills</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256390f88773962a92c94bf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 02:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6256390f88773962a92c94bf/</guid><description>Charlee Corra, a member of the Disney family, came out publicly as transgender and condemned anti-LGBTQ bills in a recent interview.
Highlights Charlee Corra, a member of the Disney family, came out publicly as transgender and condemned anti-LGBTQ bills in a recent interview. They announced that their family would match up to $250,000 in donations to the Human Rights Campaign, the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest LGBTQ advocacy group, during the organization&amp;rsquo;s annual gala in Los Angeles last month.</description></item><item><title>Alabama legislature passes 'Don't Say Gay,' trans care and bathroom ban bills</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625060280f64251b5da48776/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625060280f64251b5da48776/</guid><description>Two bills targeting the LGBTQ community passed on Thursday.
Highlights Two bills targeting the LGBTQ community passed on Thursday. SB 184, the Vulnerable Child Protection Act, would ban gender-affirming care to minors under 18. HB 322 would ban trans students from using bathrooms and locker rooms that align with their gender identity. The Trevor Project has condemned the passage of such bills as an attack on bodily autonomy for trans youth and their families.</description></item><item><title>Disney apologises for 'silence' on 'Don't Say Gay' bill</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622db560d5aeaf9e26187bda/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 09:12:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622db560d5aeaf9e26187bda/</guid><description>It comes after the BBC is shown a letter which also claims &amp;quot;gay affection&amp;quot; is cut from Pixar content.
Highlights Disney has cut &amp;ldquo;nearly every moment of overtly gay affection&amp;rdquo; from its content, a letter says. The letter also claims &amp;ldquo;gay affection&amp;rdquo; is cut from Pixar content. The company did not reply to BBC&amp;rsquo;s requests for comment. The BBC is shown a letter which also claims &amp;lsquo;gay affection&amp;rsquo; has been cut from Disney content.</description></item></channel></rss>