<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officials on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officials/</link><description>Recent content in officials on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 12:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boy, 8, on vacation in S. Carolina killed by man shooting at random cars, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298aa1586b0582da10c7b0b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 12:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6298aa1586b0582da10c7b0b/</guid><description>An 8-year-old boy vacationing in South Carolina was fatally shot when a man shooting randomly at passing cars struck his family’s vehicle, authorities said Tues
Highlights Quarius Naqua Dunham, a third grader from Portsmouth, New Hampshire, was fatally injured in the shooting Saturday near Florence, the Florence County Sheriff&amp;rsquo;s Office said. Quarius’ father, who was driving the car, was struck in the leg, the release said. Charles Montgomery Allen, 40, was arrested on suspicion of murder, attempted murder and other crimes, the sheriff&amp;rsquo;s office said.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo shooter's prior threat, hospital stay face scrutiny</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628287d793848ae566447b38/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 17:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/628287d793848ae566447b38/</guid><description>BUFFALO, N.Y. (AP) — The white gunman accused of a racist rampage at a Buffalo supermarket planned to keep killing if he had escaped the scene, the police commissioner said Monday, as authorities investigated the massacre of 10 Black people as a potential hate crime or act of domestic terrorism.
Highlights Police: Buffalo gunman aimed to keep killing if he got away. Payton Gendron, 18, had threatened to carry out a shooting at Susquehanna Valley High School in Conklin around graduation, a law enforcement official says.</description></item><item><title>SC man suffers heart attack, dies while burying body of murdered wife: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bf1c89b85fabeff9948e3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 17:27:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627bf1c89b85fabeff9948e3/</guid><description>A man from a small town in South Carolina died of a heart attack while burying the body of his wife he had strangled inside of their home, according to officials in Edgefield County. Augusta, Georgia-based ABC affiliate WJBF reportsthat the body of Joseph McKinnon, 60, was found in his Trenton yard Saturday morning. Officials responded to the scene and found a second body &amp;ndash; that of 65-year-old Patricia Dent &amp;ndash; in a freshly dug pit.</description></item><item><title>Lake Powell officials take unprecedented, emergency steps to delay water releases as level plummets</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272440efa0fbce065f9788c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 09:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6272440efa0fbce065f9788c/</guid><description>The federal government announced Tuesday it is taking unprecedented, emergency steps to help boost water levels at Lake Powell.
Highlights The US Bureau of Reclamation expects the dual actions will boost Lake Powell by nearly 1 million acre-feet of water. The measures are intended to buy the surrounding communities more time to plan for the very real possibility the reservoir will soon run out of water and the ability to produce hydropower amid the West&amp;rsquo;s climate change-driven megadrought.</description></item><item><title>Cañon City wild horse facility quarantined due to 'unknown yet highly contagious' disease outbreak</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626917bed64324c6d7ccd539/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 10:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626917bed64324c6d7ccd539/</guid><description>The Bureau of Land Management&amp;rsquo;s Cañon City Wild Horse and Burro Facility is under a voluntary quarantine due to an &amp;quot;unknown yet highly contagious&amp;quot; disease outbreak, the bureau announced Monday.
Highlights The Bureau of Land Management&amp;rsquo;s Cañon City Wild Horse and Burro Facility is under a voluntary quarantine. 57 horses have died so far since the outbreak began on April 23. Officials are working to determine the exact cause of death.</description></item><item><title>Shields Up: U.S. officials preparing for potential Russian cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625cf39939981094c84e5cdc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 05:14:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625cf39939981094c84e5cdc/</guid><description>Bill Whitaker reports on the proven capabilities of Russia&amp;rsquo;s hackers, who just a few years ago were able to infiltrate the computer network of a Kansas nuclear power plant.
Highlights U.S. cyber defenders say they&amp;rsquo;re bracing themselves with &amp;ldquo;Shields Up&amp;rdquo; initiative. The agency helps secure computer networks in 16 sectors deemed vital to national security, like energy, finance and communications. The Biden administration has been releasing sensitive intelligence and dire warnings that the Kremlin is preparing to launch a new generation of cyberattacks on American soil.</description></item><item><title>Florida education officials reject 54 math textbooks for ‘attempts to indoctrinate students’</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b7bd835918c1480a7c20e/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 02:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625b7bd835918c1480a7c20e/</guid><description>Dozens of math textbooks were rejected by the Florida Department of Education after officials said the publishers were attempting to indoctrinate students.
Highlights 54 textbooks submitted for the state of Florida&amp;rsquo;s approved list have been rejected by the Florida Department of Education. 41% of the submitted textbooks included references to critical race theory, common core and social emotional learning. Governor Ron DeSantis said in a statement, “It seems that some publishers attempted to slap a coat of paint on an old house built on the foundation of Common Core, and indoctrinate concepts like race essentialism, bizarrely for elementary students.</description></item><item><title>Evacuations ordered at Florida building deemed unsafe not far from site of Surfside collapse</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c33ad61157a0f9ede858c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 12:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624c33ad61157a0f9ede858c/</guid><description>Residents were ordered to evacuate an apartment building in North Miami Beach, Florida, after engineers found the five-story structure unsafe months after the
Highlights Engineers found excessive &amp;ldquo;deflection&amp;rdquo; — or sagging — in concrete slabs on the building&amp;rsquo;s second and third floors. Bayview 60 Homes&amp;rsquo; owners began examining the building in July, just after 98 people were killed when a Surfside, Florida, condo building collapsed. Tenants will be compensated for accommodations for the next three nights at up to $150 per night, and they will be refunded their April rent and security deposits.</description></item><item><title>Russia bombards areas where it pledged to scale back</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62459d1489baa3486838579d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 12:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62459d1489baa3486838579d/</guid><description>KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces bombarded areas around Kyiv and another city just hours after pledging to scale back operations in those zones to promote trust between the two sides, Ukrainian authorities said Wednesday.
Highlights Russian forces bombarded areas around Kyiv and another city just hours after pledging to scale back operations in those zones to promote trust between the two sides. Talks between Ukraine and Russia were set to resume Friday by video.</description></item><item><title>Korean marine deserts to serve as Ukrainian foreign legion saying 'I choose meaningful death than meaningless one'</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ac8a8484ae9a730d666e9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 07:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623ac8a8484ae9a730d666e9/</guid><description>(ATTN: CHANGES headline, lead; UPDATES with new info in paras 2-3, minor edits in paras 4-&amp;hellip;
Highlights Marine attempted to enter Ukraine from Poland but was denied entry at a border checkpoint, official says. Ukraine authorities are set to transfer his custody to South Korean officials in Poland. The Marine is set to be transferred to South Korea by Ukraine authorities in South Korea, official said. Marine&amp;rsquo;s custody will be transferred in Poland, the official said, adding the Ukraine authorities will transfer it to his South Korean counterparts.</description></item><item><title>FBI eyeing 6 suspects after bomb threats at Black colleges</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234e7f30c7769f643588f73/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 20:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6234e7f30c7769f643588f73/</guid><description>As the nation’s historically Black colleges remain on edge after receiving dozens of bomb threats in recent weeks, federal law enforcement officials said they have identified six suspects who they believe are responsible for most of the racially motivated crimes.
Highlights More than a third of America’s 101 historically Black colleges and universities have been targeted by calls or emails threatening to set off bombs on their campuses since early January.</description></item><item><title>Kidnapped Ukrainian mayor freed in 'special operation,' officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233a429752aecd02bb0c39f/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 21:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6233a429752aecd02bb0c39f/</guid><description>The mayor of Melitopol was allegedly abducted by Russian forces on March 11.
Highlights Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky calls for release of Melitopol&amp;rsquo;s mayor. Mayor Ivan Fedorov has been freed in a &amp;ldquo;special operation,&amp;rdquo; an adviser to Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s presidential office says. Russian forces allegedly abducted the mayor on March 11. The Russian-controlled separatists then announced they were bringing charges against him for &amp;ldquo;aiding terrorism&amp;rdquo; A pro-Russian lawmaker says a &amp;ldquo;committee of the chosen&amp;rdquo; is now taking over the running of the city, a lawmaker tells people not to allow pro-Ukrainian activists to &amp;ldquo;destabilize&amp;rdquo; the situation.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine war: Joe Biden, Hillary Clinton and senior White House officials banned from entering Russia</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230f3844097207c39ce6940/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 20:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6230f3844097207c39ce6940/</guid><description>Joining Joe Biden and Hillary Clinton on a Kremlin &amp;quot;stop list&amp;quot; are the president&amp;rsquo;s secretary of state Antony Blinken, CIA chief William Burns, the US defence secretary Lloyd Austin, and national security adviser Jake Sullivan.
Highlights Joe Biden has not visited Russia since 2011, when he was vice president to Barack Obama. Joining the 79-year-old on a Kremlin &amp;ldquo;stop list&amp;rdquo; are his secretary of state Antony Blinken, CIA chief William Burns, defence secretary Lloyd Austin, and national security adviser Jake Sullivan.</description></item><item><title>New intel suggests Russia is prepared to launch an attack before the Olympics end, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207f8c086885f39180adf30/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 18:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207f8c086885f39180adf30/</guid><description>The US and its allies have new intelligence that suggests Russia could launch an attack on Ukraine even before the end of the Olympics, multiple sources familiar with the matter tell CNN.
Highlights New intelligence suggests Russia could launch an attack on Ukraine even before the end of the Olympics. Ukraine is among the targets identified in the new intelligence, three sources say. President Obama is set to hold a meeting with NATO and European allies on Friday to discuss the intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Protesters enter southern Alberta school, demand end of mask rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</guid><description>School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday where the gathering called for an end to mask mandates.
Highlights School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday. The gathering called for an end to mask mandates. The protest was quickly de-escalated by school officials and protestors were peacefully escorted out of the building.</description></item><item><title>The next Covid variant will be more contagious than omicron, but the question is whether it will be more deadly, WHO says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</guid><description>A top WHO official warned against theories that the virus will continue to mutate into milder strains that make people less sick than earlier variants.
Summary RT: Maria Van Kerkhove, Head a.i. Emerging Diseases and Zoonosis at the World Health Organization (WHO), speaks during a news conference on the situation of the coronavirus at the United Nations in Geneva, Switzerland, January 29, 2020. The next Covid-19 variant that will rise to world attention will be more contagious than omicron, but the real question scientists need to answer is whether or not it will be more deadly, World Health Organization officials said Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Biden says it's possible U.S. would sanction Putin personally if he invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 02:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden,&amp;hellip;
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden, speaking to reporters in Washington, said there would be &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; for Putin if there is a Russian invasion. Earlier Tuesday, U.S. officials said Washington is prepared to impose sanctions and export controls on critical sectors of the Russian economy if Putin invades Ukraine, the Wall Street Journal reported.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pushed to Her Death in Front of Oncoming Train at Times Square Station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</guid><description>Police have taken a person of interest into custody with a history of prior arrests.
Summary An Asian woman was pushed to her death at a subway station in Times Square on Saturday morning in what city officials are calling an &amp;ldquo;unprovoked&amp;rdquo; attack. At an afternoon press conference held a host of city officials, police said there appeared to be no connection between the victim and her attacker. #BREAKING: @NYPDTransit says a woman was killed after being shoved onto the subway tracks and into the path of a southbound R train at Times Square this morning.</description></item><item><title>Man found alive in Scotland after faking his death to evade U.S. sex assault charges, official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</guid><description>A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities
Summary A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities said Thursday. Utah County Attorney David O. Leavitt admitted that had Rossi not contracted Covid and needed medical care, he would still probably be living &amp;ldquo;off the grid&amp;rdquo; successfully.</description></item><item><title>US hospitals letting infected staff members stay on the job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dda9e3ed20d35c62907d0b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dda9e3ed20d35c62907d0b/</guid><description>Health authorities around the U.S. are increasingly taking the extraordinary step of allowing nurses and other workers infected with the coronavirus to stay on the job if they have mild symptoms or none at all
Summary The move is a reaction to the severe hospital staffing shortages and crushing caseloads that the omicron variant is causing. California health authorities announced over the weekend that hospital staff members who test positive but are symptom-free can continue working.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>'We're done. This is the end of the 2020 election': Maricopa County officials rebut error-plagued review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</guid><description>Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election.
Summary (CNN) Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election . Presenting the rebuttal to the Maricopa County Board of Supervisors in a four-hour meeting Wednesday, county elections officials said that 76 of the 77 claims made in the Cyber Ninjas report were false or misleading.</description></item><item><title>Colorado wildfire: Marshall fire may have destroyed 1,000 homes in Boulder County, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</guid><description>The Marshall fire that tore through parts of Superior and Louisville may have destroyed up to 1,000 homes, Gov. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle said Friday.
Summary The winter wildfire, which exploded amid bone-dry conditions fueled by climate warming, quickly became the most destructive wildfire in Colorado history. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle estimated up to 1,000 homes in Superior and Louisville may have been destroyed as the roaring wildfire decimated entire subdivisions with shocking speed.</description></item><item><title>California man driving to White House to kill leaders on 'hit list' arrested in Iowa, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</guid><description>A heavily armed California man was arrested in Iowa after he told law enforcement officers that he would &amp;quot;do whatever it takes&amp;quot; to kill government leaders on
Summary The man, Kuachua Brillion Xiong, 25, has been held in the Pottawattamie County Jail in Council Bluffs since Thursday, according to sheriff&amp;rsquo;s records. Xiong had been driving from his home near Sacramento, California, since Dec. 18 &amp;ldquo;with the intention of driving straight to the White House &amp;hellip; to kill persons in power,&amp;rdquo; Larson wrote.</description></item></channel></rss>