<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>officials on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officials/</link><description>Recent content in officials on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 18:13:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/officials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New intel suggests Russia is prepared to launch an attack before the Olympics end, sources say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207f8c086885f39180adf30/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 18:13:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6207f8c086885f39180adf30/</guid><description>The US and its allies have new intelligence that suggests Russia could launch an attack on Ukraine even before the end of the Olympics, multiple sources familiar with the matter tell CNN.
Highlights New intelligence suggests Russia could launch an attack on Ukraine even before the end of the Olympics. Ukraine is among the targets identified in the new intelligence, three sources say. President Obama is set to hold a meeting with NATO and European allies on Friday to discuss the intelligence.</description></item><item><title>Protesters enter southern Alberta school, demand end of mask rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fdd4bc9874e7ceeff2bf62/</guid><description>School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday where the gathering called for an end to mask mandates.
Highlights School board officials as well as RCMP confirm a protest took place inside a school in Dunmore, Alta., Friday. The gathering called for an end to mask mandates. The protest was quickly de-escalated by school officials and protestors were peacefully escorted out of the building.</description></item><item><title>The next Covid variant will be more contagious than omicron, but the question is whether it will be more deadly, WHO says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 09:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f10db1e857a5450041eee3/</guid><description>A top WHO official warned against theories that the virus will continue to mutate into milder strains that make people less sick than earlier variants.
Summary RT: Maria Van Kerkhove, Head a.i. Emerging Diseases and Zoonosis at the World Health Organization (WHO), speaks during a news conference on the situation of the coronavirus at the United Nations in Geneva, Switzerland, January 29, 2020. The next Covid-19 variant that will rise to world attention will be more contagious than omicron, but the real question scientists need to answer is whether or not it will be more deadly, World Health Organization officials said Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Biden says it's possible U.S. would sanction Putin personally if he invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 02:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden,&amp;hellip;
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden, speaking to reporters in Washington, said there would be &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; for Putin if there is a Russian invasion. Earlier Tuesday, U.</description></item><item><title>Woman Pushed to Her Death in Front of Oncoming Train at Times Square Station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 22:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e344136bffa8589ef6f86b/</guid><description>Police have taken a person of interest into custody with a history of prior arrests.
Summary An Asian woman was pushed to her death at a subway station in Times Square on Saturday morning in what city officials are calling an &amp;ldquo;unprovoked&amp;rdquo; attack. At an afternoon press conference held a host of city officials, police said there appeared to be no connection between the victim and her attacker. #BREAKING: @NYPDTransit says a woman was killed after being shoved onto the subway tracks and into the path of a southbound R train at Times Square this morning.</description></item><item><title>Man found alive in Scotland after faking his death to evade U.S. sex assault charges, official says</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e149dd3b3bf48867eddbc6/</guid><description>A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities
Summary A Rhode Island man faked his death to evade sexual assault charges before he was found alive — suffering from Covid-19 — and arrested in Scotland, authorities said Thursday. Utah County Attorney David O. Leavitt admitted that had Rossi not contracted Covid and needed medical care, he would still probably be living &amp;ldquo;off the grid&amp;rdquo; successfully.</description></item><item><title>US hospitals letting infected staff members stay on the job</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dda9e3ed20d35c62907d0b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 16:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dda9e3ed20d35c62907d0b/</guid><description>Health authorities around the U.S. are increasingly taking the extraordinary step of allowing nurses and other workers infected with the coronavirus to stay on the job if they have mild symptoms or none at all
Summary The move is a reaction to the severe hospital staffing shortages and crushing caseloads that the omicron variant is causing. California health authorities announced over the weekend that hospital staff members who test positive but are symptom-free can continue working.</description></item><item><title>At least 19 dead, including 9 children, after dozens injured in NYC fire: Officials</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc11cd779b64aa92285732/</guid><description>At least 19 are dead, including nine children, after dozens were injured in a fire at a Bronx apartment in New York City.
Summary At least 19 people are dead, including nine children, following a massive fire in New York City on Sunday, officials said. More than 60 people were injured in the fire, according to the New York City Fire Department. Many of the injured victims were located on the upper floors and likely suffered from severe smoke inhalation, New York City Fire Department Commissioner Daniel Nigro said during a press conference Sunday afternoon.</description></item><item><title>'We're done. This is the end of the 2020 election': Maricopa County officials rebut error-plagued review</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d775330a2d91c55d5ae292/</guid><description>Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election.
Summary (CNN) Maricopa County officials on Wednesday undercut nearly every claim that cast doubt on the validity of ballots in an error-plagued report that Arizona Senate Republicans had commissioned of the 2020 election . Presenting the rebuttal to the Maricopa County Board of Supervisors in a four-hour meeting Wednesday, county elections officials said that 76 of the 77 claims made in the Cyber Ninjas report were false or misleading.</description></item><item><title>Colorado wildfire: Marshall fire may have destroyed 1,000 homes in Boulder County, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 14:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d05e7f674766a50297578f/</guid><description>The Marshall fire that tore through parts of Superior and Louisville may have destroyed up to 1,000 homes, Gov. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle said Friday.
Summary The winter wildfire, which exploded amid bone-dry conditions fueled by climate warming, quickly became the most destructive wildfire in Colorado history. Jared Polis and Boulder County Sheriff Joe Pelle estimated up to 1,000 homes in Superior and Louisville may have been destroyed as the roaring wildfire decimated entire subdivisions with shocking speed.</description></item><item><title>California man driving to White House to kill leaders on 'hit list' arrested in Iowa, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 07:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd590bac6172a072a31bef/</guid><description>A heavily armed California man was arrested in Iowa after he told law enforcement officers that he would &amp;quot;do whatever it takes&amp;quot; to kill government leaders on
Summary The man, Kuachua Brillion Xiong, 25, has been held in the Pottawattamie County Jail in Council Bluffs since Thursday, according to sheriff&amp;rsquo;s records. Xiong had been driving from his home near Sacramento, California, since Dec. 18 &amp;ldquo;with the intention of driving straight to the White House &amp;hellip; to kill persons in power,&amp;rdquo; Larson wrote.</description></item></channel></rss>