<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>work on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/work/</link><description>Recent content in work on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:24:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High schooler runs sub-4 minute mile, breaking record that had stood since 1965</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285c66385f44101ea3d81fa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6285c66385f44101ea3d81fa/</guid><description>Gary Martin accomplished the feat at the Pennsylvania Catholic League Championship
Highlights Gary Martin, a senior at Archbishop Wood High School Warminster, Penn., broke a record that had been set by Jim Ryun in 1965. Ryun became the first high schooler to run a mile in under four minutes in 1964, then broke his own record five times before graduating. Martin is now the 14th American high school athlete to break four minutes, and his time now ranks third all-time in outdoor runs.</description></item><item><title>‘Hate is alive and well’: Burnley fan arrested for apparent Nazi salute at Spurs</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62834b24cb7ae7e4d9bcca07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 07:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62834b24cb7ae7e4d9bcca07/</guid><description>Three Burnley supporters were arrested on suspicion of discriminatory behaviour after Sunday’s match at Tottenham, the Lancashire club has said
Highlights Three Burnley supporters arrested on suspicion of discriminatory behaviour after Sunday&amp;rsquo;s match at Tottenham Hotspur. Video appears to show a fan performing a Nazi salute at the game. Tottenham said they would support the police with their investigation. Two Brentford players said they had been racially abused at Everton on Sunday.</description></item><item><title>800 employees resign after company asks them to work from office</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f8ea528063013b5ee7d3b/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 11:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627f8ea528063013b5ee7d3b/</guid><description>Over 800 WhiteHat Jr employees have resigned from the kids online coding learning edtech start-up in the last two months after being asked to work from home. The company asked remote employees to return to office within a month’s
Highlights Over 800 WhiteHat Jr employees have resigned from the kids online coding learning edtech start-up in the last two months after being asked to work from home. This comes after the company asked its employees to return to office within a month’s time.</description></item><item><title>Couple found 1950s McDonald's bag with french fries inside wall during home renovations | CNN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e00d338fbd75617b9c23b/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 03:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/626e00d338fbd75617b9c23b/</guid><description>Cold french fries are bad enough. But cold, old french fries are even worse.
Highlights Rob and Gracie Jones were doing work on their 1959 Crystal Lake, Illinois, home. They found a decades-old McDonald&amp;rsquo;s bag behind one wall. Rob was in the bathroom replacing the old toilet paper fixture when he found the bag. &amp;ldquo;As he pulled the fixture out, he noticed a rolled up piece of cloth bunched up inside the wall,&amp;rdquo; Gracie said.</description></item><item><title>Netflix is finally going after password sharing. Here’s how it’s likely to work</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264f882b1aea6a4bc7ab5c0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 07:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6264f882b1aea6a4bc7ab5c0/</guid><description>Netflix doesn&amp;rsquo;t plan to shut down password sharers overnight. Rather, it intends to bill shared accounts an extra fee in a global rollout that may take a year.
Highlights Netflix plans to charge an extra fee for shared accounts being used by multiple people outside of the home. The company has already started a test of this feature in Peru, Costa Rica and Chile. Netflix didn&amp;rsquo;t say how much revenue it expects to generate from implementing its strategy worldwide, though it didn&amp;rsquo;t survey how many current account payers would be willing to pay more to share with others.</description></item><item><title>Taliban ban women in Afghanistan from flying without male chaperone</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62417c65fec179ca39729779/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62417c65fec179ca39729779/</guid><description>The move comes after the Taliban backtracked on their commitment to open high schools to girls.
Highlights The Taliban have told airlines in Afghanistan that women cannot board domestic or international flights without a male chaperone. The move comes after the Taliban backtracked on their previous commitment to open high schools to girls. Unaccompanied women who had already booked tickets would be allowed to travel on Sunday and Monday. The Taliban administration spokesman had previously said that women travelling abroad for study should be accompanied by a male relative.</description></item><item><title>Long Covid could create a generation affected by disability, expert warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c624d3113187a8076cab9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 12:22:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623c624d3113187a8076cab9/</guid><description>Prof Danny Altmann, immunologist at Imperial College London, says UK’s approach fails to take the impact of infections seriously
Highlights Long Covid could lead to a generation of people forced out of their homes and work, expert says. 1.5m people in the UK have long Covid - 2.4% of the population - with 45% reporting infection more than a year ago. Prof Danny Altmann says UK&amp;rsquo;s current approach to Covid fails to take the impact of infections sufficiently seriously.</description></item><item><title>Photos show first work in years at North Korea nuke site, analysts say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622757d473e1ee594f0a31ac/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 13:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/622757d473e1ee594f0a31ac/</guid><description>Recent photos taken from space show new buildings and other signs of work at North Korea’s Punggye-ri nuclear testing facility, analysts say.
Highlights Recent photos taken from space show new buildings and other signs of work at North Korea’s nuclear testing facility, analysts say. They call it a worrying sign that the country could be planning to resume testing atomic bombs after having claimed to have destroyed the site in 2018.</description></item><item><title>Woman attacked with hammer in New York subway station</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621a7b0f47e39d28abb79bad/</guid><description>A 57-year-old woman was hit in the head with a hammer several times and robbed in one of the latest violent crimes in a New York subway station, police said.
Highlights The woman&amp;rsquo;s family identified her as Nina Rothschild, a scientist for the New York City Department of Health. She was attacked about 11 p.m. Thursday by a 6-foot tall male wearing a dark jacket, bluejeans and holding a cane, police say.</description></item><item><title>Taliban forces have fired pepper spray at a group of women protesting in Afghanistan’s capital to demand rights to work and education. The Taliban authorities have blocked female public sector employees from returning to work, many secondary schools have still not reopened for girls.</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e54c5923213e546a33c184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e54c5923213e546a33c184/</guid><description>One woman reportedly taken to hospital after protest calling for right to work and education is stopped
Summary Taliban forces have fired pepper spray at a group of women protesting in Afghanistan’s capital to demand rights to work and education. Since seizing control of the country by force in August, the Taliban authorities have imposed creeping restrictions on Afghans, especially on women. About 20 women gathered in front of Kabul University on Sunday, chanting “equality and justice” and carrying banners that read “women’s rights, human rights”, an AFP correspondent reported.</description></item><item><title>'Like a slap in the face': Nurses told to use vacation and sick days to stay home if they test positive</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1036ffdaad0efa69433b8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e1036ffdaad0efa69433b8/</guid><description>Early in the pandemic, nurses were celebrated as heroes, with nightly symphonies of clapping or banging pots and pans.
Summary Now, many are being asked to go into work despite positive Covid tests — or they say they are being told they must use their vacation and sick days to stay home when they contract the coronavirus. In some instances, nurses who test positive have also been instructed to return to work if they are asymptomatic, according to another internal memo, also reviewed by NBC News.</description></item></channel></rss>