<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>season on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/season/</link><description>Recent content in season on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 19:12:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/season/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NFL says all 32 teams must have minority offensive coach this season</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624359e2288b1f939fdbdfd7/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 19:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624359e2288b1f939fdbdfd7/</guid><description>The NFL announced that teams must have a minority assistant on their offensive staffs for the 2022 season, a new requirement under the league’s Rooney Rule
Highlights The NFL announced on Monday that all 32 teams must have a minority assistant on their offensive staffs for the 2022 season, a new requirement under the league’s Rooney Rule. The pipeline for minorities on offense is lacking, as Steelers owner Art Rooney II reiterated on Monday.</description></item><item><title>Alaska reached temperatures warmer than Southern California in December</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf8b966c5aaf2a4bddbdb6/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 23:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cf8b966c5aaf2a4bddbdb6/</guid><description>Kodiak Island in southern Alaska set a record for the warmest December day at 67 degrees. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bill Weir has more on the unusual warm temperatures many Americans are experiencing this holiday season.
Summary Kodiak Island in southern Alaska set a record for the warmest December day at 67 degrees. CNN&amp;rsquo;s Bill Weir has more on the unusual warm temperatures many Americans are experiencing this holiday season. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item></channel></rss>