<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>putin on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/putin/</link><description>Recent content in putin on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 07:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/putin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Celebrated Russian conductor fired from Munich Philharmonic for supporting Putin’s invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f18cf7dfa09141e26bcf1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 07:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f18cf7dfa09141e26bcf1/</guid><description>Munich mayor Dieter Reiter said in a news release that the decision came after he issued an ultimatum to the 68-year-old Russian conductor to reject the invasion.
Highlights Russian conductor Valery Gergiev was fired from the Munich Philharmonic orchestra on Tuesday. Mayor Dieter Reiter said decision came after he issued an ultimatum to the 68-year-old Russian conductor to reject Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Reiter: “I had expected him to rethink and revise his very positive assessment of the Russian leader,” Reiter says.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine moves to impose state of emergency as U.S., allies pressure Russia with sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</guid><description>Russia had all of the necessary military capabilities Wednesday to launch a full-scale invasion into neighboring Ukraine, a senior U.S. defense official said.
Highlights At least five Ukrainian websites were hit by cyberattacks ahead of state of emergency vote. Russia evacuates its embassy in Kyiv, state news agency reports. U.S., Europe and other allies impose first salvo of sanctions on Moscow. Secretary of State Antony Blinken cancels a meeting with Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister.</description></item><item><title>Tanks seen in Donetsk after Putin recognises breakaway regions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214d55c6581bcad8420da43/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214d55c6581bcad8420da43/</guid><description>A Reuters witness saw columns of military vehicles including tanks early Tuesday on the outskirts of Donetsk, the capital of one of two breakaway regions of eastern Ukraine, after Russian President Vladimir Putin recognised them as independent states.
Highlights A Reuters witness saw columns of military vehicles including tanks early Tuesday on the outskirts of Donetsk, the capital of one of two breakaway regions of eastern Ukraine. The appearance of the tanks came hours after Putin signed friendship treaties with the two separatist regions and ordered Russian troops to deploy on what Moscow called a peacekeeping operation.</description></item><item><title>More than 130,000 Russian troops now staged outside Ukraine: U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 01:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</guid><description>Some airlines cancelled flights to the Ukrainian capital and troops there unloaded fresh shipments of weapons from NATO members Sunday, as its president sought to project confidence in the face of U.S. warnings of possible invasion within days by a growing number of Russian forces.
Highlights NEW: U.S. intelligence officials believe targeting the military exercise is just one of multiple options that Russia has weighed as a possibility for a false pretext for an invasion.</description></item><item><title>US holds firm on Ukraine’s right to join Nato in its response to Russian demands</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2c2e2367bed77f481b21b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2c2e2367bed77f481b21b/</guid><description>US officials also offer negotiate on European security with Moscow but won’t move on most contentious issue
Highlights The US has presented its written response to Russian demands on Ukraine, but made clear that it did not change Washington’s support for Ukraine’s right to pursue Nato membership, the most contentious issue in relations with Moscow. Blinken was speaking hours after his Russian counterpart, Sergei Lavrov, threatened “retaliatory measures” if the US response did not satisfy the Kremlin.</description></item><item><title>Biden says it's possible U.S. would sanction Putin personally if he invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 02:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden,&amp;hellip;
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden, speaking to reporters in Washington, said there would be &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; for Putin if there is a Russian invasion. Earlier Tuesday, U.</description></item><item><title>Russian ships, tanks and troops on the move to Ukraine as peace talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</guid><description>With negotiations deadlocked, Moscow is continuing to build up its military forces for a possible invasion
Summary The US president, Joe Biden, last week said that Putin himself may not know what he plans to do. The Russian foreign minister, Sergei Lavrov, called talks with US secretary of state Antony Blinken “frank and substantive”. The decision to fast-track arms to Ukraine reflects an understanding that Russia could launch an attack at any moment.</description></item><item><title>Russian dissident Alexei Navalny says he has 'no regrets': After spending a year behind bars, Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: "Don't be afraid of anything."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</guid><description>After spending a year behind bars, the prominent Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: &amp;quot;Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of anything.&amp;quot;
Summary His return and arrest led to protests and a monthslong crackdown on his political network. Navalny on Monday took to social media to share his sentiments on the anniversary of his arrest on charges he has maintained are politically motivated. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t regret it for a second,&amp;rdquo; Navalny said of his decision to return to Russia, only to be arrested.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item><item><title>‘Say no to Putin’: Ukrainians support protests in Kazakhstan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</guid><description>Demonstrators in Kyiv fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots.
Summary Demonstrators in Kyiv and Kharkov fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots. Kyiv, Ukraine – With their country’s fate being discussed at this week’s US-Russia talks, Ukrainians took to the streets over the weekend to defend their independence and champion an additional cause – that of Kazakhstan’s protests.</description></item><item><title>Finland says it could join NATO if it wants to, despite Russia's opposition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</guid><description>Finland’s President Sauli Niinistö on Saturday reiterated his country’s right to join Nato if it wants to, in a dismissal of Russian demands for no further expansion of the Western military alliance near its borders.
Summary Last month Russian President Vladimir Putin sought guarantees that Finland would not join Nato. In a statement released by the Kremlin, President Putin said Russian wants “international legal security guarantees” ruling out “Nato’s further movement eastward”.</description></item></channel></rss>