<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>putin on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/putin/</link><description>Recent content in putin on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 07:14:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/putin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Putin tries to justify Ukraine invasion; Russian forces continue to storm Mariupol steel plant</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1095e7461c917c05b323/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627a1095e7461c917c05b323/</guid><description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s Putin has attempted to justify his unprecedented invasion of Ukraine on &amp;quot;Victory Day&amp;quot; — a key event on the country&amp;rsquo;s calendar.
Highlights Putin said the West was &amp;ldquo;preparing for the invasion of our land, including Crimea,&amp;rdquo; Putin said. He added that NATO was creating threats at Russia&amp;rsquo;s borders. Russia had amassed some 190,000 troops on its borders with Ukraine in the weeks before its invasion. There was little evidence of military aggression from Ukraine toward Russia, and Moscow&amp;rsquo;s claims to the contrary were seen by many as a pretext for justifying the invasion.</description></item><item><title>Putin may soon officially declare war on Ukraine, US and Western officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627146df96c07c69892b0674/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/627146df96c07c69892b0674/</guid><description>Russian President Vladimir Putin could formally declare war on Ukraine as soon as May 9, a move that would enable the full mobilization of Russia&amp;rsquo;s reserve forces as invasion efforts continue to falter, US and Western officials believe.
Highlights Russia began evacuating its embassy in Kyiv, and Ukraine urged its citizens to leave Russia. Russian President Vladimir Putin ordered his forces not to storm the last remaining Ukrainian stronghold in the besieged city of Mariupol but to block it &amp;ldquo;so that not even a fly comes through&amp;rdquo; May 9, known as “Victory Day” inside of Russia, commemorates the country’s defeat of the Nazis in 1945.</description></item><item><title>Russia tests nuclear-capable ballistic missile that Putin says has no peer</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260ca2406bc58abffb7cc1c/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 03:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260ca2406bc58abffb7cc1c/</guid><description>In a show of strength two months into its assault on Ukraine, Russia test-launched a new nuclear-capable intercontinental ballistic missile which President Vladimir Putin said on Wednesday would make Moscow&amp;rsquo;s enemies stop and think.
Highlights Russia test-launched a new nuclear-capable intercontinental ballistic missile which President Vladimir Putin said on Wednesday would make Moscow&amp;rsquo;s enemies stop and think. Putin was shown on TV being told by the military that the long-awaited Sarmat missile had been test launched for the first time from Plesetsk in northwest Russia and hit targets in the Kamchatka peninsula, nearly 6,000 km (3,700 miles) away.</description></item><item><title>US defense secretary being regularly briefed on any potential Russian nuclear moves, officials say</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260238cfeeb91a52b763db3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6260238cfeeb91a52b763db3/</guid><description>The United States&amp;rsquo; military is keeping a constant watch on Russia&amp;rsquo;s nuclear arsenal as the war in Ukraine continues.
Highlights US officials are more concerned about the threat of Russia using nuclear weapons than at any time since the Cold War, sources say. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin is being briefed two or three times a week by the top US general who oversees US nuclear weapons and defenses. The US has not seen any indication Russia has made any moves to prepare nuclear weapons for use during the war.</description></item><item><title>More than 4.5 million have fled war in Ukraine: UN</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253106dea533b02023fdc6c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 17:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6253106dea533b02023fdc6c/</guid><description>Russia turns to Alexander Dvornikov, who has a record of brutality against civilians in Syria, say US officials.
Highlights The death toll from Friday’s railway station bombing in Kramatorsk has risen to 52. Russia denies responsibility, saying missiles responsible for the attack were used by the attack only. Russia turns to Alexander Dvornikov, who has a record of brutality against civilians in Syria, officials in Kyiv said. The U.N. has updated the number of refugees fleeing Ukraine since the war started, bringing the total to some 4.</description></item><item><title>UK joins US in imposing sanctions on Putin’s daughters | Vladimir Putin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625108f78579b18c26e3b182/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 04:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625108f78579b18c26e3b182/</guid><description>Maria Vorontsova and Katerina Tikhonova will be subject to asset freeze and travel ban
Highlights Katerina Tikhonova and Maria Vorontsova will be subject to asset freeze and travel ban. It is not clear whether they have ever visited the UK or if they own assets within reach of UK officials. The US imposed sanctions on the women on Wednesday, with a senior US official saying many of Putin’s assets were hidden with family members.</description></item><item><title>US seizes yacht owned by oligarch with close ties to Putin</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b0b54b6120a0e234e8111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/624b0b54b6120a0e234e8111/</guid><description>PALMA DE MALLORCA, Spain (AP) — The U.S. government seized a mega yacht in Spain owned by an oligarch with close ties to the Russian president on Monday, the first in the government’s sanctions initiative to “seize and freeze” giant boats and other pricey assets of Russian elites.
Highlights The yacht is among the assets linked to Viktor Vekselberg, a billionaire and close ally with Russia&amp;rsquo;s President Vladimir Putin, who heads the Moscow-based Renova Group.</description></item><item><title>Russian Media: "Vladimir Putin has assumed a historic responsibility for the final solution of the Ukrainian question"</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623760a5871577f2f340a45a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 17:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/623760a5871577f2f340a45a/</guid><description>A quickly deleted article referred to the independence of Belarus and Ukraine as a &amp;quot;terrible catastrophe.&amp;quot;
Highlights Opinion piece seemingly published by Russian news agency RIA Novosti before being quickly taken down. Petr Akopov wrote that Russia is &amp;ldquo;restoring its unity&amp;rdquo; and providing a &amp;ldquo;solution to the Ukrainian question&amp;rdquo; in its invasion of Ukraine. The article was recorded by the Internet Archive&amp;rsquo;s Wayback Machine before it was taken offline. It referred to the 1991 declarations of independence by Belarus and Ukraine as a &amp;ldquo;terrible catastrophe&amp;rdquo; and an &amp;ldquo;unnatural dislocation&amp;rdquo; Author theorized that Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s statehood would not be liquidated if Russia succeeds in its goals, but would instead be &amp;ldquo;reorganized, re-established and returned to its natural state&amp;rdquo; READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Kremlin vet says aides would kill Putin before sharing ‘bad news,’ now Putin orders house arrests</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235823fb21e3f2dd3e57fa6/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 07:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6235823fb21e3f2dd3e57fa6/</guid><description>Vladimir Putin has now put some of his own intelligence officials under house arrest, according to sources who spoke to The New York Times, as Russia suffers a high death toll in its Ukraine invasion. The report suggests Putin may be insulated from solid information, or worried that these aides might try to overthrow him, as former Russian Foreign Minister Andrei Kozyrev told MSNBC in a recent interview. In this segment, MSNBC’s Ari Melber reports on the intrigue at the Kremlin, with analysis from Council on Foreign Relations President Richard Haass, who says Putin may be &amp;quot;paranoid&amp;quot; about his aides trying to oust him, and NYU history professor, Ruth Ben-Ghiat.</description></item><item><title>U.S. estimates 2,000 to 4,000 Russian troops killed in Ukraine war</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62289b807562b419b4dd1c48/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62289b807562b419b4dd1c48/</guid><description>&amp;quot;I think Putin&amp;rsquo;s assumptions have turned out to be profoundly flawed.&amp;quot;
Highlights Between 2,000 and 4,000 Russian troops have been killed over the course of Putin&amp;rsquo;s 12-day war in Ukraine, U.S. intelligence officials say. Putin may turn to more brutal tactics in the coming days and weeks, intelligence officials testify. CIA Director Bill Burns says Putin is likely to &amp;ldquo;double down&amp;rdquo; and may escalate his assault on heavily populated civilian areas.</description></item><item><title>Celebrated Russian conductor fired from Munich Philharmonic for supporting Putin’s invasion</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f18cf7dfa09141e26bcf1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 07:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621f18cf7dfa09141e26bcf1/</guid><description>Munich mayor Dieter Reiter said in a news release that the decision came after he issued an ultimatum to the 68-year-old Russian conductor to reject the invasion.
Highlights Russian conductor Valery Gergiev was fired from the Munich Philharmonic orchestra on Tuesday. Mayor Dieter Reiter said decision came after he issued an ultimatum to the 68-year-old Russian conductor to reject Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Reiter: “I had expected him to rethink and revise his very positive assessment of the Russian leader,” Reiter says.</description></item><item><title>Ukraine moves to impose state of emergency as U.S., allies pressure Russia with sanctions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62169564004df7608ea12793/</guid><description>Russia had all of the necessary military capabilities Wednesday to launch a full-scale invasion into neighboring Ukraine, a senior U.S. defense official said.
Highlights At least five Ukrainian websites were hit by cyberattacks ahead of state of emergency vote. Russia evacuates its embassy in Kyiv, state news agency reports. U.S., Europe and other allies impose first salvo of sanctions on Moscow. Secretary of State Antony Blinken cancels a meeting with Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign minister.</description></item><item><title>Tanks seen in Donetsk after Putin recognises breakaway regions</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214d55c6581bcad8420da43/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6214d55c6581bcad8420da43/</guid><description>A Reuters witness saw columns of military vehicles including tanks early Tuesday on the outskirts of Donetsk, the capital of one of two breakaway regions of eastern Ukraine, after Russian President Vladimir Putin recognised them as independent states.
Highlights A Reuters witness saw columns of military vehicles including tanks early Tuesday on the outskirts of Donetsk, the capital of one of two breakaway regions of eastern Ukraine. The appearance of the tanks came hours after Putin signed friendship treaties with the two separatist regions and ordered Russian troops to deploy on what Moscow called a peacekeeping operation.</description></item><item><title>More than 130,000 Russian troops now staged outside Ukraine: U.S. official</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 01:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6209b618e4d665d43751e0fc/</guid><description>Some airlines cancelled flights to the Ukrainian capital and troops there unloaded fresh shipments of weapons from NATO members Sunday, as its president sought to project confidence in the face of U.S. warnings of possible invasion within days by a growing number of Russian forces.
Highlights NEW: U.S. intelligence officials believe targeting the military exercise is just one of multiple options that Russia has weighed as a possibility for a false pretext for an invasion.</description></item><item><title>US holds firm on Ukraine’s right to join Nato in its response to Russian demands</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2c2e2367bed77f481b21b/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f2c2e2367bed77f481b21b/</guid><description>US officials also offer negotiate on European security with Moscow but won’t move on most contentious issue
Highlights The US has presented its written response to Russian demands on Ukraine, but made clear that it did not change Washington’s support for Ukraine’s right to pursue Nato membership, the most contentious issue in relations with Moscow. Blinken was speaking hours after his Russian counterpart, Sergei Lavrov, threatened “retaliatory measures” if the US response did not satisfy the Kremlin.</description></item><item><title>Biden says it's possible U.S. would sanction Putin personally if he invades Ukraine</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 02:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61f0ab3e91167efeeee874d5/</guid><description>President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden,&amp;hellip;
Summary President Joe Biden on Tuesday said it&amp;rsquo;s possible the U.S. would sanction Russian President Vladimir Putin personally if the leader invades Ukraine. Biden, speaking to reporters in Washington, said there would be &amp;ldquo;enormous consequences worldwide&amp;rdquo; for Putin if there is a Russian invasion. Earlier Tuesday, U.S. officials said Washington is prepared to impose sanctions and export controls on critical sectors of the Russian economy if Putin invades Ukraine, the Wall Street Journal reported.</description></item><item><title>Russian ships, tanks and troops on the move to Ukraine as peace talks stall</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61ed97b3f15f65928c60d702/</guid><description>With negotiations deadlocked, Moscow is continuing to build up its military forces for a possible invasion
Summary The US president, Joe Biden, last week said that Putin himself may not know what he plans to do. The Russian foreign minister, Sergei Lavrov, called talks with US secretary of state Antony Blinken “frank and substantive”. The decision to fast-track arms to Ukraine reflects an understanding that Russia could launch an attack at any moment.</description></item><item><title>Russian dissident Alexei Navalny says he has 'no regrets': After spending a year behind bars, Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: "Don't be afraid of anything."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</guid><description>After spending a year behind bars, the prominent Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: &amp;quot;Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of anything.&amp;quot;
Summary His return and arrest led to protests and a monthslong crackdown on his political network. Navalny on Monday took to social media to share his sentiments on the anniversary of his arrest on charges he has maintained are politically motivated. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t regret it for a second,&amp;rdquo; Navalny said of his decision to return to Russia, only to be arrested.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item><item><title>‘Say no to Putin’: Ukrainians support protests in Kazakhstan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</guid><description>Demonstrators in Kyiv fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots.
Summary Demonstrators in Kyiv and Kharkov fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots. Kyiv, Ukraine – With their country’s fate being discussed at this week’s US-Russia talks, Ukrainians took to the streets over the weekend to defend their independence and champion an additional cause – that of Kazakhstan’s protests.</description></item><item><title>Finland says it could join NATO if it wants to, despite Russia's opposition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</guid><description>Finland’s President Sauli Niinistö on Saturday reiterated his country’s right to join Nato if it wants to, in a dismissal of Russian demands for no further expansion of the Western military alliance near its borders.
Summary Last month Russian President Vladimir Putin sought guarantees that Finland would not join Nato. In a statement released by the Kremlin, President Putin said Russian wants “international legal security guarantees” ruling out “Nato’s further movement eastward”.</description></item></channel></rss>