<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>putin on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/putin/</link><description>Recent content in putin on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/putin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Russian dissident Alexei Navalny says he has 'no regrets': After spending a year behind bars, Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: "Don't be afraid of anything."</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 14:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61e6c80bf5bee8e568fe398c/</guid><description>After spending a year behind bars, the prominent Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny posted a message on social media telling his followers: &amp;quot;Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of anything.&amp;quot;
Summary His return and arrest led to protests and a monthslong crackdown on his political network. Navalny on Monday took to social media to share his sentiments on the anniversary of his arrest on charges he has maintained are politically motivated. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t regret it for a second,&amp;rdquo; Navalny said of his decision to return to Russia, only to be arrested.</description></item><item><title>U.S., NATO reject Russia’s demand to exclude Ukraine from alliance</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61df33685b356693c986c378/</guid><description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken and NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg said Russia would have no say over who should be allowed to join the bloc.
Summary The former Soviet republic is unlikely to join the alliance in the foreseeable future, but NATO nations won’t rule it out. Story continues below advertisementBlinken and Stoltenberg spoke separately following an extraordinary virtual meeting of NATO foreign ministers. Canada’s foreign affairs minister, Melanie Joly, participated in the NATO meeting.</description></item><item><title>‘Say no to Putin’: Ukrainians support protests in Kazakhstan</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 19:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61dc825855331a706be13b5c/</guid><description>Demonstrators in Kyiv fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots.
Summary Demonstrators in Kyiv and Kharkov fly the blue and gold flag of Kazakhstan, where Russian troops have been sent to quell riots. Kyiv, Ukraine – With their country’s fate being discussed at this week’s US-Russia talks, Ukrainians took to the streets over the weekend to defend their independence and champion an additional cause – that of Kazakhstan’s protests.</description></item><item><title>Finland says it could join NATO if it wants to, despite Russia's opposition</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61d1cc32cfeececc13b78597/</guid><description>Finland’s President Sauli Niinistö on Saturday reiterated his country’s right to join Nato if it wants to, in a dismissal of Russian demands for no further expansion of the Western military alliance near its borders.
Summary Last month Russian President Vladimir Putin sought guarantees that Finland would not join Nato. In a statement released by the Kremlin, President Putin said Russian wants “international legal security guarantees” ruling out “Nato’s further movement eastward”.</description></item></channel></rss>