<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>high on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/high/</link><description>Recent content in high on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 17:15:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/high/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>High court limits suing officials over rights violations</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a22a9dce9fa7326ee77759/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 17:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/62a22a9dce9fa7326ee77759/</guid><description>It’s the latest in a line of cases narrowing the public’s ability to sue federal officials for rights violations.
Highlights The owner of the Smuggler’s Inn in Blaine, Washington, can’t sue a Border Patrol agent over a confrontation at his inn. Robert Boule says the agent shoved him and then retaliated against him when he complained that the man had used excessive force. It&amp;rsquo;s the latest in a line of cases narrowing the public&amp;rsquo;s ability to sue federal officials for rights violations.</description></item><item><title>3 high school graduations across the U.S. end with gunfire in less than 24 hours</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629199529bcc774208de3f22/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 03:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/629199529bcc774208de3f22/</guid><description>Three high school graduation ceremonies ended with shots fired in separate incidents in Louisiana, Michigan and Tennessee within the span of 24 hours this week.
Highlights Three high school graduation ceremonies ended with shots fired in separate incidents in Louisiana, Michigan and Tennessee within the span of 24 hours this week. At least one person was killed and seven others injured in collective shootings that resulted in the arrest of a 17-year-old gunman in Tennessee.</description></item><item><title>Tennessee woman accused of trading items for sexual encounters with 9 high school students</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215de457eb39a996791f944/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 07:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6215de457eb39a996791f944/</guid><description>Melissa A. Blair, of Englewood, Tennessee, is accused of having sexual encounters with nine high school boys for more than a year, authorities say.
Highlights Melissa A. Blair, 38, of Englewood, Tennessee, is accused of exchanging items for sexual encounters with nine high school boys she spoke with on social media. She was indicted on Feb. 15 on 23 charges, including 18 counts of aggravated statutory rape, four counts of human trafficking by patronizing prostitution and one count of solicitation of a minor.</description></item><item><title>BP profits hit eight-year high thanks to soaring gas and oil prices</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202c02c9a079d4f5c15a13b/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 19:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/6202c02c9a079d4f5c15a13b/</guid><description>Company swings to $12.8bn profit from loss of $5.7bn the year before as it cashes in on gas and oil price hikes
Highlights BP&amp;rsquo;s Bernard Looney dismissed calls for a windfall tax on fossil fuel companies. FTSE 100 oil giant swung to a profit of $12.8bn (£9.45bn) for last year, from a loss of $5.7bn the year before. BP&amp;rsquo;s profits for the final quarter of last year leapt 35-fold to $4.</description></item><item><title>Area more than six times the size of Manhattan destroyed in Brazilian Amazon in January</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc8bfe277d2eb22f97d9e4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 02:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61fc8bfe277d2eb22f97d9e4/</guid><description>Deforestation levels in the Brazilian Amazon hit a new record for January.
Highlights Deforestation levels in the Brazilian Amazon hit a new record for January just three weeks into the year. Nearly 360 square kilometres of forest cover – an area more than six times the size of Manhattan – were destroyed in the Amazon from 1 January to 21 January. Deforestation has surged since far-right President Jair Bolsonaro took office in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Alaska sets record high December temperature of 19.4C</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd12bcc2487fbf0b0cf8d7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 02:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cd12bcc2487fbf0b0cf8d7/</guid><description>The island community of Kodiak set the record on Sunday and scientists fear the population will be deluged with rain as climate warms
Summary An unusual winter warm spell in Alaska has brought daytime temperatures soaring past 15.5C (60F) and torrents of rain at a time of year normally associated with bitter cold and snow. At the island community of Kodiak, the air temperature at a tidal gauge hit 19.4C (67F) degrees on Sunday, the highest December reading ever recorded in Alaska, said scientist Rick Thoman of the Alaska Center for Climate Assessment and Policy.</description></item><item><title>'High risk' of armed conflict over Ukraine, Russian defense ministry warns</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb6cf7c10051328a2930df/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 20:10:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/61cb6cf7c10051328a2930df/</guid><description>The Biden administration has repeatedly called for diplomacy with Russia to deescalate tensions and end the war in Ukraine’s eastern provinces.
Summary Russia has said it has no plans to invade but demanded the U.S., NATO, and Ukraine take seriously its concerns. His Deputy Defense Minister Alexander Fomin blamed NATO again Monday for provoking conflict by sending warships and reconnaissance planes to back Ukraine. The estimated number of Russian troops near Ukraine have ranged from 60,000 to over 100,000, with one leaked U.</description></item></channel></rss>