<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>remove on Reddit News</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/categories/remove/</link><description>Recent content in remove on Reddit News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 18:17:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.redditnews.io/categories/remove/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Legal effort to remove Greene from Ga. ballot can proceed, judge rules</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625efc8e940e2e4e95b941bb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 18:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/625efc8e940e2e4e95b941bb/</guid><description>The judge cited Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene&amp;rsquo;s (R-Ga.) alleged role in the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol.
Highlights A group of Georgia voters filed a lawsuit to disqualify Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) from reelection because of her alleged role in the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol. A judge denied Greene’s request for a preliminary injunction and temporary restraining order in a 73-page ruling. READ THE ORIGINAL ARTICLE</description></item><item><title>Facebook, Twitter remove disinformation accounts targeting Ukrainians</title><link>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d571721856a605d0bcc99/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 23:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.redditnews.io/p/621d571721856a605d0bcc99/</guid><description>Facebook and Twitter removed two anti-Ukrainian “covert influence operations” over the weekend, one tied to Russia and another with connections to Belarus, the
Highlights Facebook and Twitter removed two anti-Ukrainian “covert influence operations” over the weekend. One of the operations was an offshoot of a known Russian disinformation operation. The other campaign used hacked accounts to push similar anti-Ukraine propaganda and was tied to a known Belarusian hacking group. Disinformation experts warned that Russia is expected to continue to try to manipulate narratives about Ukraine.</description></item></channel></rss>